1
00:00:29,496 --> 00:00:35,366
This story is a rewrite of a Nanyang tall tale

2
00:00:35,469 --> 00:00:39,371
It bears the moral that

3
00:00:39,473 --> 00:00:44,433
justice does prevail

4
00:00:44,545 --> 00:00:46,843
The film is extensively shot in Malaysia...

5
00:00:46,947 --> 00:00:52,180
and our story begins in a Coconut oil Garden...

6
00:01:48,842 --> 00:01:50,918
Where have you been? You never come see me

7
00:01:51,033 --> 00:01:52,207
Dad keeps mentioning you

8
00:01:53,713 --> 00:01:55,480
It's been very hectic at the law firm

9
00:01:56,113 --> 00:01:58,366
How are you? Feel better lately?

10
00:02:00,810 --> 00:02:03,799
Don't worry it'll get better soon...

11
00:02:03,907 --> 00:02:05,010
when you get a new job

12
00:02:06,307 --> 00:02:08,323
So, what brings you here this year?

13
00:02:09,091 --> 00:02:11,628
Mr. Hu told me bring the land ownership papers

14
00:02:11,734 --> 00:02:13,121
Mr. Chen needs to sign it

15
00:02:15,388 --> 00:02:16,324
Why?

16
00:02:16,953 --> 00:02:20,535
I heard it belongs to the Yang family now

17
00:02:20,919 --> 00:02:22,686
The lease is over

18
00:02:22,798 --> 00:02:24,779
They're going to take the property

19
00:02:26,799 --> 00:02:30,203
Little Yue...

20
00:02:30,313 --> 00:02:31,321
It's dad

21
00:02:31,635 --> 00:02:32,643
Daddy!

22
00:02:35,115 --> 00:02:38,554
Hey, Little Yue and Ah Yung!

23
00:02:38,907 --> 00:02:41,195
Mr. Hu is waiting for you two

24
00:02:41,308 --> 00:02:42,339
Let's go right now

25
00:02:42,456 --> 00:02:43,736
Shall we, Ah Yue?

26
00:02:44,126 --> 00:02:45,134
Let's go then

27
00:02:55,886 --> 00:02:56,953
Fu Sin Chen

28
00:02:57,068 --> 00:02:58,455
This is the loan agreement your father made...

29
00:02:58,564 --> 00:03:00,640
and signed before he died

30
00:03:00,756 --> 00:03:03,425
It's supposed to be paid in 5 years

31
00:03:03,539 --> 00:03:05,792
Otherwise, we can take over the property

32
00:03:05,905 --> 00:03:07,328
The Coconut oil Garden and the field are ours now

33
00:03:07,437 --> 00:03:09,690
We're here to re-gain possession

34
00:03:15,543 --> 00:03:17,167
This agreement was signed five years ago

35
00:03:17,282 --> 00:03:19,263
It's worth five times more than before

36
00:03:19,370 --> 00:03:21,208
I can't hand it over to you

37
00:03:21,840 --> 00:03:24,651
Mr. Hu. Please help me out?

38
00:03:27,615 --> 00:03:29,761
Mr. Yang. My client has rights

39
00:03:29,877 --> 00:03:32,202
He has a right to object

40
00:03:32,313 --> 00:03:35,337
You have to respect that

41
00:03:35,444 --> 00:03:36,511
Fu Sin Chen

42
00:03:36,626 --> 00:03:37,526
How dare you change the deal!

43
00:03:40,036 --> 00:03:42,324
Man, isn't your life dear to you?

44
00:03:45,395 --> 00:03:47,506
Speak, deal or no deal?

45
00:03:49,987 --> 00:03:50,887
Mr. Hu

46
00:03:51,761 --> 00:03:54,334
Mr. Yang. This is a law-abiding country

47
00:03:54,440 --> 00:03:56,029
We can discuss it

48
00:03:57,641 --> 00:03:58,921
There is no time to negotiate

49
00:03:59,032 --> 00:04:00,763
We'll kill you if you won't hand it over

50
00:04:01,502 --> 00:04:02,402
Fu Sin

51
00:04:19,524 --> 00:04:20,733
Push her over

52
00:04:21,299 --> 00:04:23,137
They are bullying your daughter. Hurry up!

53
00:04:24,048 --> 00:04:25,435
Call the police

54
00:04:32,676 --> 00:04:34,929
I've been working here for over 40 years

55
00:04:35,042 --> 00:04:37,023
No one has dared to make a scene

56
00:04:37,130 --> 00:04:38,374
Whoever tries to start something

57
00:04:38,486 --> 00:04:39,730
I'll kill them

58
00:05:05,241 --> 00:05:05,477
He is dead...

59
00:05:05,589 --> 00:05:07,427
Uncle Ah Ba, you have to go!

60
00:05:09,729 --> 00:05:10,903
Hurry up! Uncle Ah Ba, leave!

61
00:05:11,017 --> 00:05:12,606
Let's go, dad

62
00:05:29,770 --> 00:05:31,050
Over there...

63
00:05:36,415 --> 00:05:38,146
Don't move. Stop!

64
00:05:40,242 --> 00:05:41,309
Put the hand cuff on.

65
00:05:53,498 --> 00:05:55,265
Are you Mr. Sheng?

66
00:05:55,864 --> 00:05:57,179
I'm Shih Sin Lou

67
00:05:57,290 --> 00:05:59,092
He's my assistance Kou An Fu

68
00:06:03,308 --> 00:06:04,623
Mr. Lin. He...

69
00:06:07,936 --> 00:06:10,403
He'll be executed in half an hour

70
00:06:10,859 --> 00:06:13,599
I asked of him his last request

71
00:06:13,712 --> 00:06:15,788
He said that he wanted to see you alone

72
00:06:23,731 --> 00:06:25,260
Uncle Ah Ba

73
00:06:32,603 --> 00:06:34,026
Uncle Ah Ba

74
00:06:34,413 --> 00:06:38,647
Don't feel sorry for me, child

75
00:06:39,074 --> 00:06:43,142
I asked Mr. Hu to put me on the witness stand

76
00:06:43,771 --> 00:06:47,069
Chung Yue and I are your relatives

77
00:06:47,424 --> 00:06:48,668
so he said we can't be witnesses

78
00:06:49,199 --> 00:06:51,345
I argued with him for a long time

79
00:06:51,460 --> 00:06:52,704
But he wouldn't let me

80
00:06:54,140 --> 00:06:55,799
I know

81
00:06:57,271 --> 00:07:00,426
I watched you grow up

82
00:07:01,028 --> 00:07:03,697
I know you were trying to help me

83
00:07:06,803 --> 00:07:07,870
I...

84
00:07:10,353 --> 00:07:12,120
Look at me

85
00:07:14,145 --> 00:07:17,964
You can tell that I'm not afraid

86
00:07:18,076 --> 00:07:22,109
You have to be brave. OK?

87
00:07:29,244 --> 00:07:34,214
The only person I worry for now is Ah Yue

88
00:07:35,471 --> 00:07:42,671
You're the only one that she can count on

89
00:07:45,944 --> 00:07:48,481
Those two bastards from Yang family

90
00:07:48,589 --> 00:07:50,427
They will come back for more

91
00:07:52,764 --> 00:07:54,673
You've to protect little Yue

92
00:08:04,105 --> 00:08:09,252
You got polio when you were little

93
00:08:09,359 --> 00:08:11,505
As a result causing you to despise yourself

94
00:08:12,247 --> 00:08:15,757
I needed you to come see me today

95
00:08:15,865 --> 00:08:19,340
There is something important I need to tell you

96
00:08:30,443 --> 00:08:34,191
Look carefully!

97
00:08:36,288 --> 00:08:38,861
Hurry up! Look at it carefully

98
00:08:39,559 --> 00:08:40,803
What is this?

99
00:08:42,864 --> 00:08:45,046
It happened 20 years ago

100
00:08:45,647 --> 00:08:48,529
Your father was a shaman; sort of exorcist

101
00:08:48,638 --> 00:08:51,034
He got an incurable disease and so...

102
00:08:51,144 --> 00:08:54,204
he gave me the spell before he passed away

103
00:08:56,780 --> 00:08:58,618
He copied it down for me

104
00:08:58,903 --> 00:09:01,049
Hurry up! Write it down

105
00:09:02,034 --> 00:09:03,623
Hurry! Write it down quickly

106
00:09:13,620 --> 00:09:15,422
Your dad told me

107
00:09:15,533 --> 00:09:18,557
You learned Malay when you were little

108
00:09:19,013 --> 00:09:22,274
Can you understand it? My child

109
00:09:25,935 --> 00:09:27,844
Please you have to remember one thing

110
00:09:27,954 --> 00:09:30,871
This can only be used to protect the less fortunate

111
00:09:30,981 --> 00:09:33,898
You can't use it with a wrong intent...

112
00:09:34,008 --> 00:09:41,482
or you'll die

113
00:09:42,914 --> 00:09:48,370
in a very, very bad way...

114
00:09:57,143 --> 00:09:59,325
It's time to go! Mr. Lin. Let's go!

115
00:10:49,505 --> 00:10:51,414
Mr. Sheng, why are you so late?

116
00:10:51,523 --> 00:10:53,147
We need these documents this afternoon

117
00:10:54,203 --> 00:10:56,005
Has the document been typed out?

118
00:10:56,116 --> 00:10:57,396
Ms Liang is waiting

119
00:10:58,029 --> 00:10:59,831
I'll give it to you before I get off

120
00:10:59,943 --> 00:11:00,914
Don't take too long!

121
00:11:09,719 --> 00:11:11,557
What's wrong? Sheng Yung

122
00:11:14,659 --> 00:11:17,055
Your wife has...

123
00:11:23,496 --> 00:11:26,413
Please take care of yourself

124
00:11:27,150 --> 00:11:29,296
Do you want to take a day off?

125
00:11:29,412 --> 00:11:32,710
No, there is a case that I need to prepare for

126
00:11:33,169 --> 00:11:35,873
I haven't finished Mr. Wong's statement

127
00:11:36,161 --> 00:11:37,892
Don't worry! I got it ready

128
00:11:39,397 --> 00:11:40,262
Thank you

129
00:11:41,450 --> 00:11:42,908
Not at all. It's okay

130
00:11:43,606 --> 00:11:45,931
Mr. Hu. Please try your best

131
00:11:46,042 --> 00:11:48,188
No problem. I'll take care of it

132
00:11:48,304 --> 00:11:50,877
It should be just fine

133
00:11:52,827 --> 00:11:53,798
Please

134
00:11:55,575 --> 00:11:56,855
Xiao Ly, who is that lady?

135
00:11:57,245 --> 00:11:59,462
She is Yu Nian Lam, a dancer

136
00:11:59,576 --> 00:12:00,856
She was looking for Mr. Hu

137
00:12:01,037 --> 00:12:02,175
What kind of case is it?

138
00:12:02,289 --> 00:12:03,985
Rape

139
00:12:05,769 --> 00:12:06,943
Um... it's done

140
00:12:09,596 --> 00:12:10,805
Shouldn't be a problem

141
00:12:12,658 --> 00:12:14,567
I'll win this case

142
00:12:18,085 --> 00:12:20,587
Are we done with Wong Ta Chiang's statement?

143
00:12:20,694 --> 00:12:22,188
In a second I'll bring it to you

144
00:12:22,295 --> 00:12:24,347
What took you so long? Court is out

145
00:12:25,566 --> 00:12:27,404
Lin Yang Ba got executed today

146
00:12:27,514 --> 00:12:28,901
He asked me to take care of his affairs

147
00:12:29,010 --> 00:12:31,192
That's your own problem

148
00:12:31,306 --> 00:12:33,179
You were late

149
00:12:33,289 --> 00:12:34,356
Don't do it again

150
00:12:36,455 --> 00:12:39,159
I warned you twice. Be careful

151
00:12:39,273 --> 00:12:40,862
It will cost you your job next time, is that clear?

152
00:13:15,005 --> 00:13:16,843
Ah Yung, what about my father?

153
00:13:24,642 --> 00:13:26,195
Please go in!

154
00:13:36,158 --> 00:13:37,225
Have a seat

155
00:14:08,479 --> 00:14:12,061
Don't be sad! Uncle Ah Ba was very brave

156
00:14:12,550 --> 00:14:14,044
You have to be brave too

157
00:14:16,482 --> 00:14:20,408
I'm alone without him

158
00:14:20,517 --> 00:14:22,390
The Yang family won't leave me alone now

159
00:14:22,500 --> 00:14:24,267
Don't worry! You got me

160
00:14:24,414 --> 00:14:26,252
I promised your father

161
00:14:26,363 --> 00:14:27,916
I'd take care of you

162
00:14:48,560 --> 00:14:50,920
You've always been nice to me

163
00:14:51,030 --> 00:14:54,328
I know, I ought to be grateful

164
00:15:12,044 --> 00:15:14,890
Please stay over tonight

165
00:15:15,001 --> 00:15:15,937
Don't leave

166
00:15:17,332 --> 00:15:18,576
I don't think I should

167
00:15:19,037 --> 00:15:20,352
I can sleep on the floor

168
00:15:20,742 --> 00:15:21,750
No

169
00:15:22,238 --> 00:15:24,775
The Yang brothers might come looking for you

170
00:15:25,438 --> 00:15:28,320
I'm not afraid of them. I'll face them

171
00:15:29,788 --> 00:15:30,819
Little Yue

172
00:15:44,574 --> 00:15:47,598
I'm useless. I'm a loser

173
00:15:56,125 --> 00:15:59,730
Why am I crippled? Why?

174
00:16:39,649 --> 00:16:42,839
Dig a hole in the middle of the house?

175
00:16:44,972 --> 00:16:46,774
Dig a big hole?

176
00:17:59,740 --> 00:18:28,366
Please give me peace... and power...

177
00:19:56,918 --> 00:19:57,985
Damn it

178
00:20:04,851 --> 00:20:06,962
Brother, you first. I'll guard the place

179
00:20:07,077 --> 00:20:07,800
Alright

180
00:22:20,469 --> 00:22:24,110
Ghosts? Are you kidding?

181
00:22:24,227 --> 00:22:25,886
There is no such thing

182
00:22:26,801 --> 00:22:29,541
I mean it. It's true

183
00:22:29,654 --> 00:22:30,483
I saw it with my eyes

184
00:22:30,594 --> 00:22:33,298
My brother was killed by an oily monster

185
00:22:33,725 --> 00:22:36,322
You must've seen a ghost

186
00:22:36,439 --> 00:22:40,222
Ghost? A ghost...

187
00:22:40,336 --> 00:22:42,589
All right. Chief

188
00:22:42,702 --> 00:22:45,275
I think he is in shock. Talking nonsense

189
00:22:45,380 --> 00:22:47,977
He should be admitted to the mental hospital

190
00:22:48,476 --> 00:22:52,189
Chief, chief

191
00:22:52,304 --> 00:22:54,071
I haven't lied to you. There is a ghost

192
00:22:54,183 --> 00:23:00,090
There is a ghost. It's black and oily

193
00:23:00,236 --> 00:23:02,109
Tin Kin Yang was killed by the Oily Maniac

194
00:23:02,498 --> 00:23:04,442
The Oil-Maniac slays Tin Kin Yang

195
00:23:06,186 --> 00:23:08,723
Yu Nian Lam's rape case on trial today

196
00:23:09,804 --> 00:23:12,650
Shut up! Be quiet!

197
00:23:32,732 --> 00:23:34,641
The prosecution may continue

198
00:23:43,204 --> 00:23:44,307
Te Min Hong

199
00:23:44,422 --> 00:23:47,304
The evening of March 11th, 1965

200
00:23:47,414 --> 00:23:49,596
Why were you in Yu Nian Lam's home?

201
00:23:49,919 --> 00:23:52,136
I had a business dinner that night

202
00:23:52,249 --> 00:23:54,230
It was 3 a. M when I got home

203
00:24:05,992 --> 00:24:07,272
Ms. Lam, let me help you.

204
00:24:11,664 --> 00:24:14,060
You opened the door for her? Did you?

205
00:24:14,168 --> 00:24:14,997
Yes.

206
00:24:16,187 --> 00:24:19,662
Then? Did you go into her room?

207
00:24:25,372 --> 00:24:26,095
Bye

208
00:24:46,943 --> 00:24:47,808
You're lying

209
00:24:47,917 --> 00:24:50,028
Ms Lam didn't close the door. It was you

210
00:24:50,144 --> 00:24:52,290
I swear she closed the door

211
00:24:52,753 --> 00:24:54,211
The witness will please continue

212
00:24:55,188 --> 00:24:56,255
What happened next?

213
00:24:56,962 --> 00:24:59,108
I put her on the bed

214
00:25:12,654 --> 00:25:13,685
Then you had sex with her

215
00:25:13,802 --> 00:25:15,260
I mean, without being invited

216
00:25:15,367 --> 00:25:17,834
No. I was very calm

217
00:25:17,942 --> 00:25:19,365
My mind was very clear

218
00:25:19,473 --> 00:25:21,169
I wouldn't have done anything wrong

219
00:25:21,282 --> 00:25:23,084
I...

220
00:26:08,494 --> 00:26:09,632
Silence!

221
00:26:12,739 --> 00:26:15,312
The plaintiff will come on the witness stand

222
00:26:25,472 --> 00:26:27,274
Please swear, Everything you say will be truth

223
00:26:27,630 --> 00:26:30,026
Nothing but the truth, so help me God

224
00:26:34,101 --> 00:26:35,310
Ms Lam

225
00:26:35,423 --> 00:26:38,649
On the evening of March 11th, 1965

226
00:26:38,763 --> 00:26:40,565
How did you meet Te Min Hong?

227
00:26:41,303 --> 00:26:43,734
I went to a movie that night

228
00:26:43,843 --> 00:26:44,946
And got home before 12 o'clock

229
00:27:11,085 --> 00:27:12,614
The defendant went into your room

230
00:27:12,720 --> 00:27:14,487
Did he force you into the bed?

231
00:27:14,599 --> 00:27:15,358
Yes

232
00:27:20,444 --> 00:27:21,653
Help!

233
00:27:25,523 --> 00:27:27,147
Did he touch your breasts?

234
00:27:28,342 --> 00:27:29,242
He did

235
00:27:29,907 --> 00:27:31,603
Was it the right one?

236
00:27:31,716 --> 00:27:33,139
Or left?

237
00:27:34,464 --> 00:27:35,779
Both sides

238
00:27:39,787 --> 00:27:43,048
Did his hand move to other places?

239
00:27:45,911 --> 00:27:49,979
His hand was moving down past my belly

240
00:27:54,123 --> 00:27:56,625
His hand was on your genitals?

241
00:27:58,298 --> 00:28:00,551
Objection

242
00:28:00,662 --> 00:28:02,120
The prosecutor is misleading the jury

243
00:28:02,229 --> 00:28:03,925
It could well affect the verdict

244
00:28:06,299 --> 00:28:07,579
Your honor

245
00:28:07,691 --> 00:28:09,873
We are putting an innocent girl

246
00:28:09,987 --> 00:28:12,560
No, a victim of a serious crime...

247
00:28:12,666 --> 00:28:15,690
on the witness stand

248
00:28:16,876 --> 00:28:19,758
This poor girl was humiliated

249
00:28:19,868 --> 00:28:22,500
Insulted in front of so many people

250
00:28:22,617 --> 00:28:25,950
But she is willing to testify

251
00:28:26,305 --> 00:28:27,858
It's all because she doesn't wish to see.

252
00:28:27,974 --> 00:28:29,670
Another poor girl suffer

253
00:28:29,783 --> 00:28:32,843
To be a victim of another crime

254
00:28:36,394 --> 00:28:39,383
The defense's objection is denied, proceed

255
00:28:48,780 --> 00:28:50,689
Listen carefully! Ms Lam

256
00:28:51,007 --> 00:28:53,023
Tell the court

257
00:28:53,128 --> 00:28:54,824
Is this the person...

258
00:28:54,938 --> 00:28:56,776
who ripped your clothes off?

259
00:28:59,913 --> 00:29:01,193
Please answer

260
00:29:03,288 --> 00:29:04,532
Yes

261
00:29:04,645 --> 00:29:07,871
Then what did he do?

262
00:29:11,360 --> 00:29:12,463
Please speak up

263
00:29:14,700 --> 00:29:16,502
He...

264
00:29:19,328 --> 00:29:20,502
Your honor

265
00:29:20,614 --> 00:29:22,939
For the dignity of Ms Lam

266
00:29:23,050 --> 00:29:25,126
Would you please clear the room?

267
00:29:27,746 --> 00:29:28,990
All right

268
00:29:41,802 --> 00:29:42,905
You may continue

269
00:29:46,500 --> 00:29:47,994
Please

270
00:29:48,726 --> 00:29:52,367
He separated my legs

271
00:29:56,032 --> 00:29:57,003
Please go on

272
00:29:57,111 --> 00:30:01,215
He pushed his penis into my...

273
00:30:04,278 --> 00:30:04,621
Did it hurt?

274
00:30:04,730 --> 00:30:08,063
Yes. It was painful

275
00:30:08,174 --> 00:30:09,418
It was killing me

276
00:30:10,714 --> 00:30:13,145
Nonsense. She's lying

277
00:30:13,567 --> 00:30:14,741
Silence!

278
00:30:18,612 --> 00:30:20,201
No more questions

279
00:30:49,437 --> 00:30:52,010
I agree with the jury

280
00:30:52,116 --> 00:30:53,847
The defendant is guilty

281
00:30:53,961 --> 00:30:57,638
He will be suspended for 2 years

282
00:30:57,753 --> 00:31:02,438
and compensate Ms Lam

283
00:31:02,554 --> 00:31:04,285
A total of two hundred thousand dollars

284
00:31:15,914 --> 00:31:18,025
You're wonderful. Mr. Hu

285
00:31:18,141 --> 00:31:21,236
It looked so easy for you

286
00:31:21,690 --> 00:31:23,349
Without your cooperation

287
00:31:23,464 --> 00:31:25,337
I wouldn't win the case

288
00:31:25,447 --> 00:31:26,514
Yes

289
00:31:26,630 --> 00:31:28,776
I'll take 80 percent of the compensation

290
00:31:28,892 --> 00:31:31,145
What? I only get 20 percent

291
00:31:31,710 --> 00:31:34,342
You didn't put in any effort

292
00:31:34,459 --> 00:31:35,811
I planned the whole thing

293
00:31:36,685 --> 00:31:37,693
That's true!

294
00:31:49,140 --> 00:31:50,563
It's you. Ah Yung!

295
00:31:51,715 --> 00:31:53,588
This Durian? It's from Malaysia

296
00:31:53,698 --> 00:31:54,077
Thank you

297
00:31:54,186 --> 00:31:54,731
Try it

298
00:31:54,847 --> 00:31:55,855
Please sit down

299
00:31:56,725 --> 00:31:57,934
Are you eating with a friend?

300
00:31:58,638 --> 00:31:59,669
Come join us

301
00:31:59,996 --> 00:32:01,063
No, thanks

302
00:32:01,492 --> 00:32:03,888
I need to go after I've had a word with you

303
00:32:18,261 --> 00:32:19,684
What do you want to say?

304
00:32:21,879 --> 00:32:26,185
Please tell me the truth. Little Yue

305
00:32:27,098 --> 00:32:29,423
I... I抦 crippled

306
00:32:29,533 --> 00:32:30,956
Do you hate me because of it?

307
00:32:31,655 --> 00:32:34,845
We were good friends since we were little

308
00:32:41,502 --> 00:32:45,048
I hope you wouldn't refuse to marry me?

309
00:32:47,590 --> 00:32:48,977
Will you? Please tell me

310
00:32:49,678 --> 00:32:54,304
I'm sorry. I can't accept

311
00:32:54,409 --> 00:32:55,440
Why?

312
00:32:55,557 --> 00:33:00,313
Because... I promised someone else

313
00:33:01,473 --> 00:33:03,975
Who? Please tell me

314
00:33:12,014 --> 00:33:13,781
Am I late? Little Yue

315
00:33:18,520 --> 00:33:20,179
You're here. Mr. Sheng

316
00:33:20,295 --> 00:33:21,539
Will you eat with us?

317
00:33:22,312 --> 00:33:23,379
I'm not hungry

318
00:34:18,710 --> 00:34:22,149
Women... women!

319
00:36:11,366 --> 00:36:14,283
I need a shower, I'll be right back

320
00:36:14,393 --> 00:36:16,504
I can shower with you

321
00:36:17,524 --> 00:36:18,911
I'll get the water ready

322
00:36:30,466 --> 00:36:33,063
You can listen to some music first

323
00:37:38,971 --> 00:37:43,383
spare me... oh, please

324
00:37:54,280 --> 00:37:56,426
Hurry up! Get him in the car

325
00:37:56,541 --> 00:37:58,070
Hurry...

326
00:38:08,649 --> 00:38:09,823
Please move away

327
00:38:09,936 --> 00:38:11,489
We need some space

328
00:38:12,128 --> 00:38:14,274
Inspector Lou. Will you give us...

329
00:38:14,389 --> 00:38:16,298
some information on the oily maniac?

330
00:38:16,407 --> 00:38:19,182
Can you tell us anything?

331
00:38:19,713 --> 00:38:20,780
And...

332
00:38:20,895 --> 00:38:21,689
Please tell us

333
00:38:21,800 --> 00:38:23,531
What did Mr. Hong do?

334
00:38:23,644 --> 00:38:24,818
Why did you arrest him?

335
00:38:25,731 --> 00:38:28,363
I'm sure that he's the oily maniac

336
00:38:28,654 --> 00:38:29,519
What are you talking about?

337
00:38:29,628 --> 00:38:31,395
The oily maniac makes trouble everywhere

338
00:38:31,507 --> 00:38:33,488
He couldn't escape anymore

339
00:38:33,594 --> 00:38:36,927
No more trouble from now on

340
00:38:37,038 --> 00:38:38,176
Drive

341
00:38:55,930 --> 00:38:58,183
Sheng Yung, what's wrong?

342
00:38:59,201 --> 00:39:00,339
Didn't you sleep well last night?

343
00:39:01,080 --> 00:39:03,061
Have a cup of coffee! Come on!

344
00:39:03,168 --> 00:39:04,104
Thank you

345
00:39:09,882 --> 00:39:11,269
It is...

346
00:39:13,778 --> 00:39:15,889
Excuse me. My name is Julie Mo

347
00:39:16,006 --> 00:39:18,022
Mr. Hu told me to come

348
00:39:18,127 --> 00:39:19,823
Please. He is waiting in his office

349
00:39:19,937 --> 00:39:20,731
Thank you

350
00:39:27,661 --> 00:39:30,258
Her photos were in the newspaper

351
00:39:31,940 --> 00:39:35,095
Julie Mo is the lead singer of a group

352
00:39:45,405 --> 00:39:47,942
Ms Mo. You want to sue your doctor

353
00:39:48,049 --> 00:39:50,101
She messed up your plastic surgery

354
00:39:50,205 --> 00:39:51,449
I can't tell the difference

355
00:39:51,563 --> 00:39:53,092
Is there anything wrong with your face?

356
00:39:53,406 --> 00:39:54,935
Not my face

357
00:39:55,424 --> 00:39:56,882
Where?

358
00:39:58,938 --> 00:40:00,182
My breasts

359
00:40:02,939 --> 00:40:04,741
What happened to your breasts?

360
00:40:06,837 --> 00:40:10,027
I need to know the details. Ms Mo

361
00:40:10,141 --> 00:40:12,085
Otherwise I can't take this case

362
00:40:25,728 --> 00:40:27,981
She screwed it up totally

363
00:40:28,094 --> 00:40:30,205
I can't continue with show business

364
00:40:30,320 --> 00:40:32,466
She ruined it

365
00:40:32,582 --> 00:40:33,934
She's jeopardized my whole life

366
00:40:38,914 --> 00:40:39,459
All right!

367
00:40:39,576 --> 00:40:40,714
Please calm down

368
00:40:42,741 --> 00:40:43,772
What do you want?

369
00:40:45,107 --> 00:40:46,945
I want her to pay me 150,000

370
00:40:49,386 --> 00:40:52,018
I'm sorry I can't help you

371
00:40:52,692 --> 00:40:55,503
You have no chance

372
00:40:55,615 --> 00:40:57,975
Why? She has no license

373
00:40:58,085 --> 00:41:01,939
No, she is a registered doctor

374
00:41:02,050 --> 00:41:03,544
And there are three lawyers

375
00:41:03,651 --> 00:41:05,939
Who work as her attorneys

376
00:41:06,052 --> 00:41:08,589
And also before the surgery...

377
00:41:08,695 --> 00:41:10,639
you signed the consent form

378
00:41:10,748 --> 00:41:13,903
You can't sue her

379
00:41:14,854 --> 00:41:18,258
Mr. Hu, what should I do?

380
00:41:20,108 --> 00:41:22,160
The way I see it, only option is that...

381
00:41:22,264 --> 00:41:25,490
I'll negotiate with her

382
00:41:25,605 --> 00:41:27,443
and hopefully she will pay $10,000

383
00:41:28,005 --> 00:41:29,914
You can find another doctor

384
00:41:30,023 --> 00:41:31,754
And fix your breast

385
00:41:31,867 --> 00:41:32,875
$10,000?

386
00:41:32,980 --> 00:41:34,924
For all my loss

387
00:41:36,077 --> 00:41:38,365
I'm sorry I can't help you very much

388
00:41:38,791 --> 00:41:42,788
You're very famous. Ms Mo

389
00:41:42,896 --> 00:41:44,840
It'll be in the headlines...

390
00:41:44,949 --> 00:41:47,416
if this news leaks out

391
00:41:47,524 --> 00:41:49,741
It'll no longer be a secret

392
00:41:49,854 --> 00:41:51,692
Can you take the embarrassment?

393
00:41:52,394 --> 00:41:54,682
You'd better think it over

394
00:41:56,882 --> 00:41:58,269
What's your decision?

395
00:41:59,144 --> 00:42:02,061
All right. I'll take 10,000

396
00:42:03,284 --> 00:42:04,707
My charge is 50%

397
00:42:05,336 --> 00:42:06,995
I only get 5,000 dollars

398
00:42:07,912 --> 00:42:10,581
This is our rule. Will you take it?

399
00:42:12,712 --> 00:42:14,099
Yes. Alright

400
00:42:16,505 --> 00:42:19,600
Great! Please go home first

401
00:42:19,706 --> 00:42:20,880
I'll inform you as soon as possible

402
00:42:21,689 --> 00:42:22,933
Thank you

403
00:42:25,586 --> 00:42:26,653
Good bye

404
00:42:39,641 --> 00:42:40,885
Ms Liang

405
00:42:40,998 --> 00:42:42,765
Will you bring Ms Yoko in?

406
00:42:42,877 --> 00:42:43,885
OK

407
00:42:49,140 --> 00:42:50,314
Please come in

408
00:42:51,367 --> 00:42:52,611
Hello, Mr. Hu

409
00:42:53,837 --> 00:42:55,081
Have a seat

410
00:43:00,273 --> 00:43:01,447
My client asked me to press charges against you...

411
00:43:01,560 --> 00:43:04,300
because her surgery failed

412
00:43:04,936 --> 00:43:07,261
What are the conditions...

413
00:43:07,370 --> 00:43:08,828
if we settle outside court?

414
00:43:12,380 --> 00:43:14,811
You have to pay her $150,000

415
00:43:14,921 --> 00:43:16,617
And I'll help you settle

416
00:43:16,730 --> 00:43:17,974
$150,000?

417
00:43:19,513 --> 00:43:22,668
But she signed the consent form

418
00:43:22,784 --> 00:43:25,321
The results aren't my responsibility

419
00:43:27,758 --> 00:43:33,523
Don't forget you don't have license

420
00:43:34,265 --> 00:43:36,838
Surgery without registration

421
00:43:37,952 --> 00:43:40,454
You could be doing time for 5 years

422
00:43:40,979 --> 00:43:43,232
The matter can be resolved...

423
00:43:43,345 --> 00:43:45,076
If you pay 150,000

424
00:43:45,676 --> 00:43:48,178
You can continue with your work...

425
00:43:48,285 --> 00:43:51,309
and earn 2 million a year

426
00:43:52,739 --> 00:43:55,858
Think of it as a meager investment

427
00:43:55,974 --> 00:43:57,741
It's very cheap

428
00:43:59,454 --> 00:44:00,948
5 years in jail

429
00:44:01,054 --> 00:44:02,062
Or your freedom...

430
00:44:02,168 --> 00:44:04,421
with $150,000

431
00:44:05,159 --> 00:44:07,305
It's your choice

432
00:44:12,187 --> 00:44:13,574
I'll pay $150,000

433
00:44:13,683 --> 00:44:15,865
Do you guarantee no more problems?

434
00:44:16,710 --> 00:44:20,315
Of course! With my honor

435
00:44:20,746 --> 00:44:22,477
All right! I agree

436
00:44:36,994 --> 00:44:38,653
Congratulations! Ms Yoko

437
00:44:38,768 --> 00:44:41,543
There are no worries anymore

438
00:44:42,317 --> 00:44:42,826
Congratulations!

439
00:44:42,943 --> 00:44:43,772
Thank you

440
00:44:45,030 --> 00:44:46,239
Please

441
00:44:50,111 --> 00:44:51,842
- Good bye - Good bye

442
00:45:01,069 --> 00:45:03,357
That only took a couple of minutes

443
00:45:04,132 --> 00:45:06,208
And you got $150,000

444
00:45:06,324 --> 00:45:07,118
But we have to give Ms Mo $5,000

445
00:45:07,228 --> 00:45:09,445
She needs to fix her breast

446
00:45:09,559 --> 00:45:11,540
You're not that bad after all

447
00:45:13,073 --> 00:45:15,255
We're going to play Bridge with Senator Chen

448
00:45:15,369 --> 00:45:16,922
We're late! Let's go!

449
00:45:19,440 --> 00:45:21,171
Please deposit this check into my account

450
00:45:22,815 --> 00:45:25,555
Please sign the contracts, Mr. Hu

451
00:45:25,668 --> 00:45:27,364
Leave them on my desk. I have to go

452
00:45:27,477 --> 00:45:28,413
Let's go!

453
00:45:50,961 --> 00:45:52,763
She ruined my career

454
00:45:52,874 --> 00:45:54,427
And the rest of my life

455
00:46:06,200 --> 00:46:07,444
Please send her in!

456
00:46:12,045 --> 00:46:13,503
Come in! Miss

457
00:46:20,221 --> 00:46:21,750
Come here! Don't be afraid

458
00:46:23,908 --> 00:46:25,152
You can wait outside

459
00:46:25,475 --> 00:46:27,064
I have to talk to the doctor

460
00:46:29,788 --> 00:46:31,068
What can I do for you?

461
00:46:31,180 --> 00:46:33,540
Doctor, she hardly bled

462
00:46:33,651 --> 00:46:36,391
It didn't look like she was a virgin

463
00:46:36,503 --> 00:46:38,484
You have to pay more attention this time

464
00:46:38,591 --> 00:46:40,773
There are 4 more girls who will come to see you

465
00:46:40,887 --> 00:46:42,202
All right. You can leave!

466
00:46:53,099 --> 00:46:54,937
Should we fix this first? Doctor

467
00:46:55,048 --> 00:46:56,744
No need; just anesthetize her lower half

468
00:50:34,340 --> 00:50:37,601
It's oily everywhere. Inspector Lou

469
00:50:37,714 --> 00:50:39,445
Is it really the oily maniac?

470
00:50:40,254 --> 00:50:41,285
I deduce that the person...

471
00:50:41,402 --> 00:50:43,975
put oil all over his body

472
00:50:44,081 --> 00:50:45,670
So he can move faster

473
00:50:45,786 --> 00:50:48,323
so it's easier to get away if he is caught

474
00:50:49,231 --> 00:50:50,998
There isn't any oily maniac

475
00:50:58,102 --> 00:51:01,707
Hello, Hu Ly Fa Law firm. Please wait

476
00:51:02,243 --> 00:51:03,558
Sheng Yung. Your phone call

477
00:51:07,114 --> 00:51:08,667
Hello, this is Sheng Yung

478
00:51:09,445 --> 00:51:12,220
You did a great job last night.

479
00:51:12,332 --> 00:51:13,399
Mr. Sheng

480
00:51:13,759 --> 00:51:14,659
What are you talking about?

481
00:51:15,499 --> 00:51:17,480
Who are you?

482
00:51:17,795 --> 00:51:20,297
You don't need to know who I am

483
00:51:20,404 --> 00:51:22,800
I need 5,000 dollars now

484
00:51:22,910 --> 00:51:24,333
You'd better send it over...

485
00:51:24,440 --> 00:51:27,429
or I'll tell the police about you

486
00:51:27,536 --> 00:51:28,603
Is this a deal?

487
00:51:28,824 --> 00:51:30,483
Yes, it's a deal

488
00:51:31,260 --> 00:51:32,884
Please give me a little time to prepare

489
00:51:33,173 --> 00:51:37,336
On the docks at 12 tonight

490
00:51:37,452 --> 00:51:40,678
You'll die if you call the police

491
00:51:45,663 --> 00:51:49,304
What should we do if he calls the police?

492
00:51:49,420 --> 00:51:50,594
Will he? Ah Gou Chang

493
00:51:50,708 --> 00:51:52,060
I have planned it out already

494
00:51:52,169 --> 00:51:53,592
If they come from the sea...

495
00:51:53,700 --> 00:51:55,573
We could use the land route for escape

496
00:51:55,683 --> 00:51:59,324
If they come by land...

497
00:51:59,441 --> 00:52:01,694
We can jump on this boat and take off

498
00:52:02,955 --> 00:52:04,199
Great idea

499
00:52:05,077 --> 00:52:06,500
What time is it?

500
00:52:07,130 --> 00:52:08,138
It's almost 12:30.

501
00:52:10,052 --> 00:52:10,988
Where is he?

502
00:52:11,339 --> 00:52:12,133
Maybe he wouldn't come

503
00:52:12,244 --> 00:52:14,117
Don't worry! He will come

504
00:55:19,459 --> 00:55:21,012
Are you sleeping? Sheng Yung

505
00:55:21,685 --> 00:55:24,460
I'll talk to you tomorrow. I'm busy

506
00:55:42,664 --> 00:55:44,537
A battered male corpse found at Ba San dockyard

507
00:56:01,800 --> 00:56:04,432
Sheng Yung, are you free tonight?

508
00:56:04,549 --> 00:56:05,378
Yes

509
00:56:05,488 --> 00:56:06,732
Please come to my house at 8

510
00:56:06,845 --> 00:56:07,781
Sure

511
00:56:20,205 --> 00:56:21,485
I'm sorry for being late

512
00:56:26,363 --> 00:56:27,952
The food is cold. I'll heat it up

513
00:56:28,068 --> 00:56:29,526
No, I've eaten

514
00:56:31,234 --> 00:56:32,408
You ate?

515
00:56:35,270 --> 00:56:36,728
I was at little Yue's place

516
00:56:36,835 --> 00:56:38,531
She made curry chicken for me

517
00:56:38,644 --> 00:56:40,031
That's my favorite

518
00:56:40,315 --> 00:56:41,702
She can cook very well

519
00:56:41,810 --> 00:56:43,197
Have you tried it before?

520
00:56:43,306 --> 00:56:45,144
I only like hers

521
00:56:49,534 --> 00:56:51,158
What's the matter? Xiao Ly

522
00:56:53,014 --> 00:56:54,258
I'm sorry

523
00:56:54,370 --> 00:56:57,952
I also cooked curry tonight

524
00:57:07,278 --> 00:57:10,919
You have to forgive me. Xiao Ly

525
00:57:12,184 --> 00:57:16,038
Go to your Little Yue. You can leave

526
00:57:25,092 --> 00:57:29,955
It was my fault

527
00:57:30,345 --> 00:57:31,519
Please excuse me

528
00:57:31,875 --> 00:57:35,065
I'm sorry. It's my fault. I apologize

529
00:57:35,738 --> 00:57:36,769
Good bye

530
00:57:38,486 --> 00:57:39,766
Please stay a while

531
00:57:40,087 --> 00:57:41,640
I really need to talk to you

532
00:57:50,420 --> 00:57:53,895
I know that you like Little Yue

533
00:57:54,073 --> 00:57:56,290
But she loves someone else

534
00:57:56,404 --> 00:57:58,515
It doesn't matter

535
00:57:59,291 --> 00:58:01,235
I know it but I still love her

536
00:58:01,970 --> 00:58:03,879
Without any conditions

537
00:58:05,450 --> 00:58:07,323
But you forgot one thing

538
00:58:07,920 --> 00:58:09,023
What is it?

539
00:58:09,138 --> 00:58:11,047
Two days ago I was off work

540
00:58:11,155 --> 00:58:12,993
I went back to get my umbrella

541
00:58:13,104 --> 00:58:15,286
I passed by Mr. Hu's office

542
00:58:15,400 --> 00:58:18,104
I heard him talking to Fu Sin Chen

543
00:58:27,612 --> 00:58:31,740
We've settled with Tin Choi Yang

544
00:58:31,856 --> 00:58:34,287
Coconut oil Garden belongs to him

545
00:58:34,396 --> 00:58:35,676
This is the check of 3 million dollars

546
00:58:35,788 --> 00:58:36,368
Thank you

547
00:58:36,484 --> 00:58:39,224
You really knew how to handle it

548
00:58:39,337 --> 00:58:42,397
Ah Ba got mad and killed Tin Sho Yang

549
00:58:42,502 --> 00:58:44,790
I ripped the agreement

550
00:58:44,904 --> 00:58:46,219
It was well planned

551
00:58:46,991 --> 00:58:50,324
Tin Choi Yang will pay 3 million...

552
00:58:50,435 --> 00:58:52,344
to buy your coconut oil Garden

553
00:58:54,993 --> 00:59:00,829
The only unfortunate one is Ah Ba

554
00:59:02,091 --> 00:59:03,062
That's true

555
00:59:04,144 --> 00:59:07,334
You not only got the money

556
00:59:08,319 --> 00:59:10,371
But also his daughter

557
00:59:11,345 --> 00:59:13,041
When are you getting married?

558
00:59:13,606 --> 00:59:15,408
I'm not marrying her

559
00:59:15,520 --> 00:59:18,888
She will be given to Tin Choi Yang

560
00:59:18,999 --> 00:59:21,810
This was one of the conditions

561
00:59:23,244 --> 00:59:26,090
Why didn't you tell me earlier...

562
00:59:28,150 --> 00:59:31,660
Little Yue, Little Yue

563
00:59:59,114 --> 01:00:01,058
Little Yue, I'll wait for you at the office

564
01:00:01,166 --> 01:00:02,790
Please come to Coconut oil Garden

565
01:00:02,907 --> 01:00:03,938
Fu Sin

566
01:00:38,777 --> 01:00:42,845
Fu Sin Ge...

567
01:00:56,277 --> 01:00:59,230
Fu Sin Ge! Where are you?

568
01:01:05,184 --> 01:01:06,607
Fu Sin Ge!

569
01:01:17,396 --> 01:01:18,949
Let me go!

570
01:01:22,997 --> 01:01:24,241
Let me go!

571
01:02:39,295 --> 01:02:40,018
How is it?

572
01:02:40,131 --> 01:02:41,554
This is a great idea

573
01:02:45,766 --> 01:02:47,818
Come on! Let's have another drink

574
01:03:19,097 --> 01:03:20,306
Little Yue?

575
01:03:31,170 --> 01:03:35,132
Little Yue, Little Yue

576
01:03:40,738 --> 01:03:42,719
Little Yue...

577
01:04:02,761 --> 01:04:05,430
I'm too late! Little Yue

578
01:04:07,283 --> 01:04:12,359
I'm too late! I'm too late...

579
01:04:49,173 --> 01:04:50,488
What are you doing?

580
01:04:50,600 --> 01:04:51,987
What is he doing?

581
01:05:29,636 --> 01:05:31,474
Let's drink! Fu Sin Ge

582
01:05:35,203 --> 01:05:36,211
Please sit down

583
01:05:39,134 --> 01:05:42,158
Let's forget about the misunderstanding

584
01:05:42,509 --> 01:05:43,517
That's wonderful

585
01:05:43,622 --> 01:05:45,674
he not only sold you the Coconut oil Garden

586
01:05:45,779 --> 01:05:47,475
But also let you have his girlfriend

587
01:05:47,588 --> 01:05:49,734
You two are such good friends

588
01:05:52,320 --> 01:05:54,229
It's getting late. We have to leave

589
01:05:54,338 --> 01:05:55,547
You may chat at ease

590
01:05:55,904 --> 01:05:57,042
Would you be needing a car?

591
01:05:57,156 --> 01:05:59,753
That's very nice of you but I have a car

592
01:06:00,183 --> 01:06:01,427
He's gone

593
01:06:14,483 --> 01:06:15,977
Good bye

594
01:07:04,408 --> 01:07:07,325
Early tomorrow someone will come looking for me

595
01:07:07,435 --> 01:07:10,067
To sue his wife for adultery

596
01:07:10,184 --> 01:07:11,607
I should go home earlier

597
01:07:13,002 --> 01:07:15,255
I work for you day and night

598
01:07:15,367 --> 01:07:18,628
You're not appreciative and still thinking about your wife

599
01:07:19,542 --> 01:07:22,803
You'll have to finish your work tonight first

600
01:07:24,135 --> 01:07:27,717
All right! I'll listen to you

601
01:09:00,509 --> 01:09:02,347
Look, what is that?

602
01:11:43,856 --> 01:11:45,658
You should've realized the truth by now

603
01:11:46,604 --> 01:11:48,620
Yes. I do

604
01:11:49,005 --> 01:11:50,807
Why did you change? It's horrible

605
01:11:51,545 --> 01:11:55,649
I don't know either. I'm...

606
01:11:55,754 --> 01:11:57,485
I'm a killing monster

607
01:11:57,599 --> 01:12:00,101
Are you going to kill me?

608
01:12:01,078 --> 01:12:04,791
No. I won't kill you

609
01:12:05,566 --> 01:12:09,207
It's not worth living anyway

610
01:12:10,158 --> 01:12:13,384
I beg of you! Will you help me?

611
01:12:14,124 --> 01:12:16,235
You can destroy me

612
01:12:17,290 --> 01:12:20,314
I can't kill anymore

613
01:12:20,421 --> 01:12:22,080
They all deserved it

614
01:12:26,232 --> 01:12:31,831
My hands are full of blood

615
01:12:32,391 --> 01:12:33,980
You can hand yourself in

616
01:12:34,304 --> 01:12:36,000
No use

617
01:12:36,356 --> 01:12:39,546
No one can stop me when I turn

618
01:12:40,427 --> 01:12:42,300
Will you help me?

619
01:12:42,723 --> 01:12:45,712
No. I can't do it

620
01:12:46,237 --> 01:12:49,985
Then I'll destroy myself

621
01:12:53,543 --> 01:12:54,681
Are you going to kill yourself?

622
01:12:56,362 --> 01:12:59,386
No. Not yet

623
01:13:00,328 --> 01:13:03,767
I have two people to avenge for Little Yue

624
01:13:04,642 --> 01:13:05,401
Two bastards

625
01:13:05,512 --> 01:13:06,483
Who are they?

626
01:13:07,426 --> 01:13:12,467
Tin Choi Yang and Fu Sin Chen

627
01:13:13,548 --> 01:13:14,900
They have to die, one by one

628
01:13:23,116 --> 01:13:25,748
Mr. Hu and his secretary were killed

629
01:13:25,865 --> 01:13:28,082
We're looking for the killer

630
01:13:28,196 --> 01:13:29,892
Please co-operate with the police

631
01:13:30,006 --> 01:13:33,588
Inform us if there is any news

632
01:13:35,154 --> 01:13:36,469
You can go back to work

633
01:13:38,251 --> 01:13:41,275
Got killed? Are you sure?

634
01:13:45,001 --> 01:13:46,353
We suspect all the workers

635
01:13:46,462 --> 01:13:47,814
Except the crippled one

636
01:13:48,132 --> 01:13:49,199
Keep your eyes on them

637
01:13:49,314 --> 01:13:50,558
Tap their phones

638
01:13:50,672 --> 01:13:51,431
Yes

639
01:13:52,794 --> 01:13:54,323
Let me know if something comes up

640
01:13:55,473 --> 01:13:56,373
You two, come along with me

641
01:13:56,482 --> 01:13:57,656
The two of you stay here

642
01:13:57,769 --> 01:13:58,634
Alright

643
01:14:38,058 --> 01:14:40,525
Hello. Are you Mr. Yang?

644
01:14:40,632 --> 01:14:41,663
Yes, I am

645
01:14:41,780 --> 01:14:43,024
Who is speaking?

646
01:14:43,137 --> 01:14:44,417
You don't need to know who I am

647
01:14:44,529 --> 01:14:47,198
You're in danger. Leave now

648
01:14:48,982 --> 01:14:49,953
To where?

649
01:14:50,305 --> 01:14:51,763
Hello...

650
01:14:55,036 --> 01:14:56,139
The Oily Maniac?

651
01:14:57,994 --> 01:14:59,238
Ah Won, Ah Chai

652
01:15:00,708 --> 01:15:02,060
Send more people to here

653
01:15:02,169 --> 01:15:03,378
Ask them watch the area carefully

654
01:15:03,491 --> 01:15:04,320
Yes

655
01:15:05,857 --> 01:15:06,544
Who was calling?

656
01:15:06,656 --> 01:15:08,280
That lady

657
01:15:10,414 --> 01:15:13,782
Ms Ly. Please come with us

658
01:15:14,624 --> 01:15:15,691
OK

659
01:16:30,539 --> 01:16:31,819
Check the Garden

660
01:16:31,931 --> 01:16:32,939
Okay

661
01:18:05,799 --> 01:18:08,574
Let's go! Hurry up, altogether

662
01:18:53,325 --> 01:18:55,401
Don't let him through. Help me!

663
01:20:07,048 --> 01:20:11,875
Let's go! Hurry!

664
01:21:04,977 --> 01:21:06,744
Run! Hurry!

665
01:21:13,432 --> 01:21:15,899
Don't shoot! No

666
01:21:41,752 --> 01:21:43,175
Who else is he going to kill?

667
01:21:43,282 --> 01:21:45,570
Please tell us. We have to stop him

668
01:21:49,927 --> 01:21:51,136
You'd better get to Coconut oil Garden

669
01:21:52,050 --> 01:21:54,196
Hurry up! Let's go to Coconut oil Garden

670
01:23:08,070 --> 01:23:10,122
Who is it? Who?

671
01:23:11,862 --> 01:23:14,981
Show your face. C'mon, quick

672
01:23:28,319 --> 01:23:29,599
Fu Sin Chen

673
01:23:29,711 --> 01:23:31,063
Who are you?

674
01:23:34,094 --> 01:23:36,075
It's me. The Oily Maniac

675
01:26:19,181 --> 01:26:21,718
Don't kill them! Sheng Yung

676
01:26:22,799 --> 01:26:26,832
Let them go! Please! Sheng Yung

677
01:27:13,074 --> 01:27:14,248
It's all right now!

