Mr Fung, go to your next life
Next, it's your turn
Oh dear, it's dreadful, help!
Ms Dolly, go ahead
Bye...
Tsui Pan-han!
Godfather!
I've found you a good family
It has to be the best
Otherwise, I would rather queue again
OK!
When I was borne, the timing was bad
It ruined my singing career
Therefore I committed suicide
You want to be a top singer?
I've got a right family for you
You'll be a professional singer
You look!
The head of the family is Koo Ka-yan,
a Composer winning the most awards
His parents sing in Chinese operas,
his wife sings the soprano
Corazon...
Corazon, hurry...
Send me to St Mary hospital
My baby is coming...
You will be her daughter,
you can sing endlessly from then on
Remember to pick a good hour!
Tonight at 8 pm sharp
You'll be more famous than Teresa Tang,
Paula Tsui and Anita Mei
Really?
8 pm sharp
Be punctual, otherwise,
you'll be a chorus girl only
If you've query,
call me at 1, 2, 3, OK?
Thanks, godfather!
Go on!
Remember, St Mary hospital
See you in your next life
Good luck!
Taxi! Taxi!
You!
Mustard, damn mustard
Come back, not mustard, it's bastard
Bastard!
Taxi
Bastard, taxi!...
Taxi... Stop... Taxi...
Not for hire
Stop, bastard...
Corazon, come back!
Madam, you want to kill yourself?
No, I am pregnant
You're in labour?!
Hubby, I'm labour soon,
please send me to the hospital
I am not your husband
Send me to hospital, quick!
Hurry, please
Alright...
Get in the car, come on
Are you blind?
Can't you see this? "Not for hire"
Which hospital?
St...!
Sacred Heart hospital, right?
Hurry, doctor, the baby is coming!
Stop!...
Hubby...
Hubby, I feel painful
I am not your hubby!
Hubby, hurry, it hurts!
Stop for a while
Halt...
What's the matter?
What is it?
I've a date with my girlfriend
Hubby, hurry!
Hubby, come on!
- I'm giving birth now
- Don't pull the shirt!
My girlfriend gave me this,
I promise to wear this to meet her
Hubby, it's painful!
My girlfriend will kill me
Hubby, hurry...
Don't pull...
Godfather, where's my mom?
I couldn't find her
A silly man has sent
your mom to Sacred Heart hospital
Hurry, it's room I 8!
OK, bye!
You, irresponsible man,
now try to abandon her!
I'll teach you a lesson if I could!
Go to hell!
Sorry...
Sorry!
L8, this is it
Doctor, my stomach is painful
Mom, here I am
My tummy hurts, ouch!
I feel a baby is moving
A baby inside a man's womb?
There's something
That wants to come out
Incredible, a pregnant man!
Hurry get the matron here!
Oh!
Don't move
Something is blocking my chest. Now it's loosen
Let me check again
My stomach is still in pain
Why, doctor?
Godfather, you trick me?
My mom is a man?
The man mixed up the room number
Your mom's in the last room round the corner
There isn't enough time, look!
What then?
Wait for 3 more days
The best time is at 4 pm
Try again then
It's the silly man's fault
What's his name?
Hong Sam-kwai!
Mona, I'm late, sorry!
How late?
1 more minute to an hour
Lucky I'm here for only 5 minutes,
or my legs will be worn out
I'm S o rry !
What happened? You have a fight?
No, I came from the hospital
Because of the fight?
No, I've sent a pregnant woman there
You've a pregnant woman?
I've nothing to do with her
Just met and she torn your shirt?
Kwai, you're lying, think of a better story
I am not lying
You are!
I ain't!
If you don't admit it, don't ever see me again!
I am...
You admit you're lying now
Yes...
That's right, Young George Washington
confessing to cutting down a cherry tree.
Oh dear! I've hit the iron barrel
Come on, let's run
You said I shouldn't lie,
don't bull shit,
You silly man!
You've to be adaptable
Now while nobody is watching, let's go!
Come on, start the car
Let's go!
Mr Hong's car
Yes!
Well done, Mr Hong!
He has style
Hi!
Oh dear
He winked at me!
Damn him if he's my student
Stop... you're out of tune!
That's great
Quiet!
Too bad
What're you doing in here?
In here?
Of course for education!
I'm the new student
What's your name?
Cheung Chee-kit Leslie's Cheung
Ah Lam's Chee and Sam Hui's Kit
My Christian name is Alan
same as Alan Tam's
What a name!
I'm easy going, no bad habits
Occasionally I smoke, date gals,
girls and horse racing sometimes
but I'm still a good boy
My favourite is playing snooker,
$5 a frame, welcome to challenge me!
Have you finished?
Go sit to the corner
Damn it!
Here is a seat
Thanks dear
What's your name dear?
No here, over that corner
the corner, you're kidding
Where's my dignity?
If you don't, get the hell out of here
Do as he says,
otherwise he'll have a heart attack
I saw the worse students
I'll give you a lesson
Boring!
How old are you?
A year older than last year
The age?
Still at this class? What a shame!
Why changed school?
Must have expelled
Why expelled?
Must have bad behaviours
Why behaved badly?
Must have terrible conduct
Your logic is quite something!
What have you planned for your future?
You're incredible
Go ahead with your logic
Asking me to plan it for you?
You really have no brain
No ambition, no 1Q!
Attention!
Take him as an example
to warn yourself
You said I've low 1Q
can you spend the shortest time
to answer 3 simple questions
Of course
No 1, which months have 28 days?
February!
Wrong! Each month has 28 days
No 2, a bicycle is heading East,
the wind is blowing from North-east,
So which direction will the smoke go?
South-west!
Wrong! A bicycle doesn't emit smoke
These 2 questions,
even an idiot can answer
Tell me your 1Q now,
high or low?
Are you finished?
Not yet, one last question
What human organ, when stimulated,
will change in size
I refuse to answer such a question
The right answer is the pupil
When it is stimulated,
it will dilate 7-times
My god, I'm on a different track too
You refused to answer me,
what was on your mind?!
Mr Hong, why are you so angry?
Of course, I'm angry
The new student treated me badly
How?
Like a ball, being kicked and fooled around
You...
I only want a life
Let me off the corner of the street
At your age, you should get married
Really?
For a girl, external beauty is unimportant,
but, her personalities are
I agree
Kwai
Do I look like a suitable person?
I can't see anything
- I'm sorry!
- Where's my glasses?
I clean it for you!
It's OK now
Thanks!
This pair of glasses
makes me look younger, doesn't it?
Yes...
I don't know why,
I feel like having my own home
So I'm taking cookery lessons
Look at this cookery book
The photos are nice
They will be nicer when cooked
Maybe you drop in one day
I will cook you a few dishes
I will, here's you are
I will leave the book behind,
pick a few of your favourites,
and I can feed you personally
Your egg rolls
It's for you
They're your favourite
Stop it! Please!
Wait!
What's hurry folk?
Not me, but my wife is in labour
It's you again?
You know each other?
No...
I gave her a ride to the hospital before
She didn't make it last time
Please give us one more ride
My car broke down!
But I'm in a hurry!
That's right, me too!
You!
Start the car, quick!
Hubby, it's painful
Off your hand, I can't breath
Sorry for that
When she's in pain,
she thinks every man is her husband
Please drive faster
It's the fastest, the car can go
What's the matter?
A flat tyre!
Oh!
Come and help to change it
Godfather, where's my mom?
She's with the silly man again
He got a flat tyre just now
What shall I do now?
Go to his car and reborn there
It's awkward to be born in a car!
That's the way, it used to be
Go on, or it'll be too late
What a nuisance!
Ghost!
Come on, the baby is coming
Don't be nervous
Let's hear some music
Dear audience, tonight's song was from
Just on time
a singer who had been ignored
Her name is Tsui Pan-han
The singer wasn't popular
Her song wasn't popular either,
no one wanted her Ips,
no one dated her
So she killed herself, with gas,
when she died, she was 21
What a name she had chosen!
"Pan-han" sounds like "go to heaven"
Please listen to her only song
"The Crescent"
What a terrible voice! Sounds like a chick,
no wonder she wasn't popular
Not too bad, actually it's quite good!
That's your opinion I can't bear it
Stop hitting or I'll get it even
Quiet!
Let's hear the rest of the song
By my experience
Her song isn't bad, but it's a pity
Why?
She's borne much too earlier
If she's born in this era,
she'll be the most popular singer
It's afternoon 1 minute past 4
The traffic condition of HK and Kowloon
Here we are
Get her out please
Godfather, I'm late again
I cannot reincarnate again
That's bad
You have to wait for another month
Come back then
No, I won't
That silly man again!
I've to get it even on him
Mona... I'm sorry
What's your excuse?
The pregnant woman again
Why, the pregnant woman again?
It's the same one
After the first pregnancy,
how come second pregnancy that soon?
It's a medical question, I wouldn't know
Use your brain
You're too lazy in finding a good excuse
It's true
Bullshit
-ltisn't a lie
- It is!
- T isn't!
It isn't!
I'll go if you deny it
It I1sS...
Admit it is a lie?
I admit it
You should admit earlier
Let's go now
Rock Hudson!
I'll call you, OK?
Good-bye!
You know this transvestite?
What transvestite?
He's my cousin from USA!
What a name!
Remember aids?
Ask him to change his surname,
or his first name
Superstitious!
Why is so windy suddenly?
You read this?
It isn't mine, it belongs to the headmistress
That spinster?
She's interested in this lately,
and asked me to pick a few,
so she can teach me later
This belongs to her I suppose!
Yes it is, she took it off when she got in
and forgot when she left
How come she took it off?
She got some powder in it
So I took it off, and helped her to clean it
You took it off?!
Then she changed to a modern pair
and then she asked
whether she looked younger or not?
Isn't it funny?
What's so funny?
Why are you angry?
It's normal
You...
Needless to say, she left these
No these aren't hers, she left them for me
For you?
She knew, they're my favourites
Your...?
They're delicious
Try one yourself
Stop the car
Hong Sam-kwai, you're a sex maniac
You are abnormal
Don't come near me ever again!
Why, eating egg rolls is abnormal?
Mona!
AWA4546, it's you again?
Kwai, Kwai...
Give me a ride, OK?
It's my girlfriend's birthday, I'm in hurry
Last time, your egg rolls
caused me 3 days' explanation
Narrow mind
Happy birthday!
I'll slice the cake, sit over there
Don't turn round
Come, I'll show you something
What're you doing?
If you propose, face me
I love you, grant me super power
What are you doing?
I love you
When did you learn magic?
It isn't magic, it's super power
Super power?
I was a happy ghost in my last life,
he was good heart deeds me
super power since birth
It's fun, once more!
OK!
I love you!
It's fun
I hate you
I didn't mean it
You meant it!
No, I didn't!
You're jealous of my cousin!
No...
How come, Mona!
Mona, please stay Let me explain
Yellow card
What! Don't give me all those shit
No 2, out!
St York, St York,
you will lose like the egg yolk
Here, have some
Not now!
Kwai, you have super power right?
You're next in the game
I don't
If you don't join this game you'll be fired!
What did you say?
No, it's a shame to lose
Please, I beg you!
Alright...
Super power
I love you
You're still here, Sir?
I'm looking for my glasses
You're wearing it
I meant my gloves actually
Do your best
Do your best, Sir!
Wong Tai Sin, ball into the net please
We can't lose!
I can't disappoint them
I can only rely on my super power
Happy ghost, give me super power
Please, my super power
Come on, here's the ball
OK...
Good... Sir...
Wait and see!
"God bless you"
"Born free"
Lost again
What's wrong?
12 yards
"God bless you"
"Born free"
How come you've got the shoe?
I'm lost again
Let's go!
Pass it
It's hers. It's his
Sir!
Dear, after school have a movie, OK?
Sorry, I can't
I've a date tonight
The note wasn't from me, it's from him
You have special interest
Dating me and call me "dearie"
He isn't dating you, it's me
No, it's...
Who?
Me!
No! Alan wants to date prefect
OK, sit down!
I don't care who did this,
but within the class
concentrate on your books only
nothing else!
Prefect did a good job
An example of being a good student
Sir is right
I'm your example
Whatever I do, follow me
Now, I want to sing and dance
Follow me!
OK, I'll
"I want"
"I want you"
I want you, too!
"I want your love"
"Why don't you come near to me?"
Tai Chuk-yee!
This is the classroom, how can you do this?
Come and see me in the office
Shame on you, you're expelled
She usually behaves herself,
I think she is out of control
Why?
She is possessed by a spirit
A spirit?
Kwai, we are all educated
we should believe scientifically
As a teacher,
how can you so superstitious?
Headmistress!
If it is true
Why doesn't it possess me?
"I want"
"I want you..."
"I want your love..."
Oh dear!
"Why don't you come near to me"
Cut it out, wake up!
Damn you
Why you hit me?
You had been possessed
You show us your ass, shame on you
Kwai, oh hear
They saw everything
I have to do something
to get away this naughty ghost
How?
Happy Ghost
Who is Happy Ghost?
The temple of Happy Ghost was dismantled
He likes living in
a bungalow instead of a temple
Happy Ghost!
Where are you?
Be patient
Come in! Let's happy together
Are you alright?
Did the headmistress punish you?
She was insane just now
You had been insane too
What insane?
Ladies, how about a ride
I'm going. Are you going too?
If prefect goes, we will
Me too
No, I'm not going
Come on, don't feel upset
Get on?
That should be the right way
Yes!
Quick!
I don't feel like riding
Why don't we go get some excitement
Yes, I'll take you to a exciting place
A wonderful place
and you can earn money, alright?
We've to change first?
OK!
What is an amusement centre?
A porno centre
A kiss, $10
You got some new girls, my lady killer
You're that kind of person
Where is big brother?
In the room
Come, get in!
That's terrible. Let's go!
Don't be afraid, get in
It was scary!
Go!
Big brother
Sweet kid, you're really something
Tame 4 girls at the same time
They said they want some excitement
Surely, you will
And you can earn more than $10,000 per month
We don't want it
No one force you to do anything bad,
come here when you want
If you like it, come again
I don't want to do it
What's the matter?
That maniac, he bruised my leg
Send her to another client
But none of the girls wants to serve him
Let me go!
Don't!
Get some money, why not?
You've got the gut, send her to him
Charge double
Follow me!
Don't!
San, new girl
Your name, sir?
Come here. I'm Romeo, how about you?
Juliet!
So nice name!
Nice leg
A new girl indeed
You play me?
Damn kid, want to play a game
Beat her up
Damn it, know a bit of Kung-fu
Try to destroy my nightclub
You don't want to live any more
Big brother...
Beat them!
Yes!
I'll beat you up
You said to beat them up
Shut up. Turn on the light
You dirty maniac
I'm first time come here
Try to cheat those young kids,
you all should be shot
Big brother...
I'm not your big brother
I'm your aunt
Call me!
Auntie!
Good
Damn fools
not work hard at school
Selling your souls for that bit of money
Don't have a bit of shyness
Knock them up
Give me the telephone
Big... brother...
What's your plot?
Auntie!
Give me that phone
Don't go!
Let them go!
Lay down!
Go!
Auntie. How about me?
You shit on you
You're all shit
Shit on you
Auntie, your telephone
9,9,9
The police station?
Here is the "Jade" Amusement Centre
We practice of prostituting,
and hire the underage girls,
send two cars here,
there's a lot of people here
Let's go, auntie!
Stand still!
Who is the in charge?
Me, I made the call
Lock up all these crooks
Me too
Arrest all of us
Yes!
How come there are so many cops?
You called up the police
Bullshit!
Really
Damn you!
Really!
Thanks auntie, let's go to police station now
Although this frog already died
Its nervous system is still working
if it stimulate by electricity
it still has the reaction
OK
Now write out a report for me
Hello!
The frog is saying hello to me
How can a frog speak?
It's true
Anyone want to try again?
Yes!
Hello!
Sir...
What's the matter?
Everybody leaves the room except prefect
Show up now
Who are you?
I am what I am
Let me show you something real tough
You'll see
I love you!
Give me the power
I hate you!
"God bless you"
You know the same trick
Who are you?
I was a scholar
in Ching Dynasty name Chu Kam-chun
Everyone calls me The Happy Ghost
I'm his previous spirit
He is my personification
I don't care
Mind your own business
Don't blow up a small problem
It will never end
Forgive him
No, he delays
my schedule for reincarnation twice
I must seek vengeance
"Born free"
Hello!
"God bless you"
If you don't give me face, don't blame me then
I always care for girls
but I've to break my rules this time
I don't want it
If you promise not to humiliate him again
I'll give you a chance
"Born..."
" ..Free"
Stupid scholar, that's the end of the game
See you
Happy Ghost!
Nice to see you here, my previous spirit
Not to me, because of you
My plait is being cut
Without my plait, I don't have my super power
No super power, I can't help you anymore
How about my super power?
I don't have the super power
Of course you don't have it too
What are we going to do with her?
I don't know!
You delayed
her schedule for reincarnation twice
She will kill me
She doesn't want to kill you
She just wants to annoy you
That's even worse
Help me, please
Listen!
Win her heart with love!
Love?!
She didn't have an affair when she was alive
If there's a fool fall in love with her,
will solve this problem
I've a girlfriend, and she is a ghost
Don't talk about your girl .
You're so scared of her
Even I feel ashamed of you
Remember, she'll have a month time
Tell her you like her
no matter it's true or not,
you'll be free in a month time
Because of your students and yourself
I'm going to like her songs
"Like the crescent on the sky"
"Hanging alone in the air"
"Wish you could join me in the darkness"
"With you, the sky will lighten up"
"Now the crescent is disappeared"
"It is hidden behind the clouds"
Time's up...
Where are you going after class?
Whatever you like
Let's go watch some movies
What are we going to watch?
Yui King!
Did you see Tai, the prefect
She is alone in the hall
Thanks!
"Hoping that one day I'll be the moon"
"To light up the sky"
"I am so despair at this moment"
"How shall I fight against the misfortune"
"Look at the crescent"
Tsui Pan-han!
You finally find out
Stop bothering my student
She's innocent
If you still want to play this game, come to me
You want me to possess you?
Yes, Han!
This bunch of flowers is for you
I got a hard time
to have one of your record and your poster
And I listen to your song
each night I can't sleep
I've nightmare without seeing your poster
I know I'm in love with you
Miss, do you know where's Hon Sum-kwai?
Who are you?
I'm the headmistress of this school
I'm his girlfriend, Mona!
Headmistress, it is terrible!
What's happening?
Mr Hon is flattering a student
Trying to do something immoral
Possess me
Come to me
But your girlfriend...
I don't care about her
She's a dumb
How about the headmistress?
She loves me
But I don't, men scare her
she'll be a old maiden for her life
If you love me
show me something in action
Action?
Kiss me!
If you don't kiss me
that means all your words are flowering only
Kwai, damn you
Mona...
You are a teacher
and try to tempt an underage girl
You are not a human!
You're bastard
Listen to me
Now I know why you heckle me often
cause you want to pull my leg
You're doing this to the perfect
Why not me?
That's unfair
You all misunderstood
No need to explain, we are finished
You're fired
Listen to me
You ruined me
Are you happy now?
The No 1 in our Pop chart this week
is Tsui Pan-han "The Crescent"
No one noticed this old song 20 years ago
That's a miracle it's popular now
Let me tell you this story
A month ago
My programme for oldies I introduced this song
An audience called Hon
he loved this song
and came to visit me purposely
and asked me to sell this record to him
I was wondering then
I listened to this song again
and found that it was wonderful
so I'm introducing to the audience
and don't know it'll be accepted
"Like the crescent on the sky"
"Hanging alone in the air"
"Wish you could join me in the darkness"
You made me lost the job
and my girlfriend
now not even let me shave
what do you want?
Don't come near me
-I want...
- Don't...
Don't come over
I'm sorry
I don't mean it
to make you in such a bad situation
I only want to help you
Stop bothering my student
I wouldn't
You're so nice
Have a sip of wine to calm you down
I'm glad,
because of you, my song becomes popular now
I don't know how to thank you
Well, don't mention it
Stop fooling around me
I wouldn't
I wouldn't, I can swear
I'm sorry. Let me help you
I can do it myself
Strange, your song becomes popular now
Is it good or not?
Good!
I remember what you said I sang like a chick
But sometimes even a chick
can chirps well
Don't drink alone
Let's get something to eat
For what I did to you
I haven't eaten in the Street for a long time
my girlfriend thinks
it's too dirty, she doesn't like it
I like it. It is so traditional
Alone?
Two!
Two? Where is the other?
Only one at the moment
Charm them
Let them see you too,
otherwise, they think that I'm insane
Alright
OK
Here comes your girlfriend
What do you want?
You order
Fried beef with vegetable!
Egg and tomato!
Spareribs!
Anything else?
Have it first
Will be ready soon
Stop looking around
- Here is a seat.
- Right!
Actually a good timing
is not essential for reincarnation
A man's success depends on
how much effort you've worked hard
Who says that?
Why someone born to be a king?
And the others are beggars
If you still believe in this,
that's superstition
Hey!
That man is talking to himself
He must be crazy
Have a slice of tomato
No. That's her girlfriend
Eat
You busy body
Spareribs, you favourite
Madam!
Is that man crazy?
You forget to charm that one
Charm him then
It's none of your business
This is for you
Which one?
The one is strap
You're crazy
He is serving his girlfriend
Something's wrong with my eyes
Take me to a ophthalmology
You watched too much "World Cup" satellite
So sweet
"Happiness is romancing in the rain"
"Trying to be innocent, wind on my face"
"Happiness is whispering to lover at night"
"Not to fear or worry"
"Happiness is swimming together at night"
"Tear off the masks, frolic on the sand"
"Happiness is sitting alone in the rain”
"crying but it is fun"
"Everyone is nicely dressed up"
"Help yourself whatever you please"
"Nice legs behind the long skirt"
"Dancing crazily without fear"
"Lovers leave the foot-steps on the sand"
"Why the steps chasing after us"
"It makes my soul dancing onto heaven"
"It is fun to be so happy"
"Be happy while you're young"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"Try to understand what happiness is"
"Send away despair"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"You'll be in a state of fantasy”
"Be happy while you're young"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"Try to understand what happiness is"
"Send away despair"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"You'll be in a state of fantasy”
"Be happy while you're young"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"Try to understand what happiness is"
"Send away despair"
"Send away all your loneliness now"
"You'll be in a state of fantasy”
Pity, he becomes crazy because of me
Big brother...
How are you? Tomorrow will be better
You're not in a good mood
That woman stirred me up, my place closed down
I'm imprisoned for a month
I want the revenge
I suspect she knows witchcraft
maybe she have a possession
This cross can exorcise
can also diminish the charms
Then use this axe punch into her heart
she will disappear forever
Can never reincarnation again
Prefect, go to the back door,
don't get out at the front door
Why?
A bad guy is waiting you there
Let's get out at the back door then
When the crooked asks you
to get out at the back door
you've to take the front door
Let's go!
Go!
Prefect!
Get in, quick
What do you want?
You made me imprisoned
you have to pay for it
None of my business!
You ask for it, you deserve it
You shut up!
See what you can say?
You are such a bad guy
like cancer of the human
Bastard, Bastard
It doesn't work
she is so furious
Let me try!
Big brother, my cross is better
Damn kid, don't get high
I'll give you a injection
which make you feel so bad
You'll kneel down to beg me then
Good ideal!
Big brother, don't do that
Go away!
It will be your turn soon
Shit!
I'm sorry
Damn shit!
Give her another injection
Big brother,
we have no more, this is the last one!
But the pin is still in your ass
You are all jerks
Go and get me a basket of pins
I'm getting to like you more
Really?
If you help me to mend all these torn trousers
You're even better
Have a sip of soft drink
"I love you"!
Excuse me, I cut your previous spirit's plait,
you lost your super power
You want to open the door of fringe?
I'll help you
Your hands just like a magnet
you can pick up anything of iron
Really?
Open the ice box!
Soft drink!
Beer!
That's terrific
Cheer!
Who's coming?
Please hide up for a while
Kwai, are you alright?
I brought you some chickens
I'm alright
Go!
You look tired
It's because of me
so I am going to make you some chicken soup
Who is she?
You, go away please!
Kwai!
Who is she?
She is my mom
My mom used to be a singer
That's good
Let me prepare the soup
Kwai!
I'm doing Tai Chi
I beg you to the toilet please
Help...
Mona...
Stop playing
Don't be afraid, I get you a cup of hot tea
If you keep on using the super power
I'll not see you again
I'll fetch you a towel
Stop fooling around
How come there's a woman's invoice?
It's from the tap only
Go away!
I'm going to have a bath
I misunderstood you, Kwai!
In the bedroom!
No one is in
You're hiding that foxy woman?
She is not a fox,
she is a ghost
Stop lying to me
I already give you a chance
I'm so disappointed
Let's break up
I'll go to USA with my cousin
Mona, let me explain
Tsui, you go too far
You know a bit of those trick
and do what you like to do
You're jealous, narrow mind,
you're not cute at all
you think you can sing?
No, your voice sounds like a chicken
It's terrible I have a nightmare
Do you think I like you?
That's not true
I am cheating you,
SO you can reincarnate quicker
and leave me alone
Han...
Please don't go
Driver, stop...
Han, please stay!
Go on!
I don't mean it
You sing well
You're so cute
Han...
Han, you...
Sir, the prefect is being kidnapped
Go and save her
Let's go
Come on!
Hello!
Tonight at 10
It's a good time for reincarnation
You still have an hour
If you lose this chance again
you won't have another one
Choose a big one for her
This way!
Help!
Here they are
Let's go in
No, I called the police already
We better wait
It'll be too late,
if we wait for the police to come
No not
Sir!
Don't be afraid, the police is coming,
release her now
Throw him down the street
Yes!
Don't!
Throw him down the street
Keep quiet!
Hon Sir!
Damn you!
Han!
Han, Han, I come just in time,
otherwise, you will die for sure
Let's go up and save them
OK!
Catch him
"God bless you"
"Born free"
Go
Move
Big brother!
I'm so scared
Take off the strip
How come?
You're helped by a naughty ghost
Where's it?
She is right here
You can't see her
Only I can
Help me to get rid of this
Please don't...
Look!
No...
I don't want to continue
It's so painful
Help!
You go, son of a bitch
You've going too
Please don't!
Don't come over
Today is not my day
Ghost?!
Run!
Ghost!
You finally show up
You go to dead!
Help...
Godfather!
That's bad
How come you miss such a good time?
Godfather, I...
Don't waste time!
Listen, before 12 o'clock
you should arrive Sacred Heart Hospital
Otherwise, the pregnant woman will be in danger
You too!
How did you feel?
Godfather...
I can't fly
Help me!
I can't help you any more
I let this secret out, I broke the rule already
I have to look for a way yourself
Godfather...
What happen?
Before 12 o'clock,
I have to be at the Sacred Heart Hospital
if not I'll never reincarnate
Don't be afraid!
We'll take you to the hospital
Hurry!
Help!
Excuse me
Excuse me, please!
Only 7 minutes left, hurry up
I'm trying my best
What happens?
The car broke down
Try again
Hon Sir, look at her
What are we going to do?
She's looking very bad?
Don't try again
I'll go and get a car
Taxi...
Can you go to Sacred Heart Hospital
within 7 minutes
Are you kidding?
You want me speeding? No way
It'll take an hour at least
Get out then!
Hands off!
Get in. Hon Sir!
Drive as fast as you can
Steal my car!
Hurry up!
Why you steal my car?
Hon Sir, take a short cut
Police, they stole my car
We're borrowing your car only?
We are going to the hospital
That is my car
Borrow it to me, please?
Someone is stealing my car
That's your car?
The cap there?
Chase after the cap
Driving at your fastest speed
Get out of my way
Don't be stupid
How did you drive?
Lucky, I have seat belt on
This belt very good
Behind the car
Help me get rid of this damn belt
Hurry up!
Don't run!
You!
Get down!
You, get down!
Don't run!...
Don't hit!...
Bastard!
Go after him!...
You'll be alright? Hubby!
Will be OK
Go away!...
Up!
What do you want?
Crazy!
Attention
We found a dangerous,
mad man
Stole a cap no CC328
driving toward south east direction
If anyone finds him,
catch him and report to the police
This is it, arrest them
Be careful...
What happens to your hands
When all my skin colour fades out
I will vanish forever
People in the car,
get out and surrender!
Beware, the car is coming backward
If I don't help you,
you'll get into real trouble
It is my previous spirit, Happy Ghost!
After I change to this new hair style,
my super power is stronger!
Turn!
My eyes really have problem, honey
Driving license please
Please give me a chance, Sir!
Why do you give me a ticket,
not to him
Terrific, I can't believe it
We only have 2 more minutes left
Take a short cut
Flying up?
No, we go under the ground
If you can't have the baby out
you need an operation
No...
I'll have a scar
Your tummy will not only scar but mince
One more minute left
Take her to reincarnate now
Thanks!
What is that man doing?
Excuse me!
What room number to you are looking for?
Please, excuse me
Go to hell!
Not hell but reincarnation
Thanks, Ah Kwai!
Not at all
Because of me, you gave up a lot
Don't mention it, like what you told me
One's success
is depending on one's own effort
I have to go. Take care!
Wait for me
After 18 years, I'll marry you
Bye!
Here is Han. She is borne
My wife got a baby boy or girl?
A baby girl, good
Congratulation, Mr Koo!
You've got a baby girl
It's true, Han
It's really Han
Han!
That maniac
I will wait for you, Han
Are you crazy?
He is absolutely out of his mind
Take him to Castle Peak
I'll marry your daughter
Father-in-law!