This girl looks pretty
Why is she keep staring
They, wandering singers, could hardly earn their living,
seeing such a huge treasure
no wonder they envy so much
Well then, how many wives have I got?
One, two, three. . .altogether around twenty-eight
Very well, I'll make it twenty-nine
General!
Is this real?
Don't argue, stay calm!
Please keep in order
What happened?
No salary for this month
- Again? - Yes
Give us the money. . .
Are they going to start a riot?
No, they haven't got their salaries for three months
I've been too busy to remember
Tell them to stay calm, they'll got their money today
- Get out! - Yes
General, are you going to give them their salaries?
We've lost our money
to General Tsao
Where the hell can I have the money?
Go and tell all my wives and children
to get ready to run
Yes, General!
Well, we all get ready to run
Alright, you know it, but don't yell
Yes, no yelling
You're yelling even louder
Shut up!
Hurry up!
You're so clumsy, don't join us
Go. . .
It's mine
- It's mine - I should've my share
Let me take it!
Soldiers!
Bring me the jewel box
Bring to me!
Yes!
I must be dreaming. Don't wake me up
Go and take it!
The General tells you all go to the backyard
- Get on the car! - Yes. . .
We get off right away
- Take it for me, hurry - Or you'll be left behind
Wait for me, General
How dare you wear silk-cotton? Take it off!
Don't... Never wake me up!
Keep on dreaming, you'll gain more and more
You'll regret when you wake up
God, you're too good to me!
I swear, if I ever sing again for my living
I'll be a man no more
Car! . . .
I take no passenger
Please take me to the railway station
I have to catch a train
But Miss, it's not on my way
Take me to the station and keep this
Certainly!
There's a team of soldiers coming over
Go over there
There's no suspicious matter in the car
Search over there
What is it?
Stand this way!
I've got nothing with me!
Don't move!
- You stay here! - Yes
What've you seen?
- Somebody suspicious - Suspicious?
Go back!
Report General!
Are there any guerillas?
Can't find any proof from the man being shot
Are you alright, General?
I'm OK!
Wan, are you scared?
I'm alright, Papa!
You've been away and living in comfort for years
now you've to get use to
the way of living of your native land
I'll certainly make it
Commander
When playing Mah-jong game with you, General Tun
has lost all the salaries. He has already got away
The soldiers have started a riot
He has lost everything to me only in a few mah-jong games
send someone to settle his folks down
I'll move in his house right away
Let me search him
Stay away!
Let me do it
Yes!
There's nothing
You may go!
Go!
Stand aside
Chun Wo Ban, isn't it a repertory?
The Commander has gone
Don't know who's next?
Towel!
Chun Wo Ban!
Shape up. . . you've got to fight
Boss, the medicine's here
Hurry! Take it upstairs
No more delay. Hurry!
Folks...there's not enough actor to play the goods
For those who play the bads should change to play the goods
Change the costumes... Hurry!
Hurry up!
Do you know regulations? No attendance for women in theatre
Can I go back stage for someone?
No women there too,
if not, the men'll not disguise as women
You look down upon on women
you'll be castrated one day
Is that you who've just touched me?
Hardly, I'm searching my shoes
- Be quick. . . - Brother
I've got few more wrinkles
Forget them, the harder you count, the more you'll find
Fa's next
Go ahead, don't play with me anymore
He's prettier than the girl last night
Hurry up...
One by one...follow the hero!
Don't go wrong, hurry...
Oh, it's you?
Dad,
Kid Hung had a cold
I take his place...
Damn you!
Want them to know we've got a dame in the repertory?
I'll lose face?
Go and wash your face
You always dream to be on stage, what can you act?
If you want to perform, recarinate as a man!
The luggages and the medical kit are back
Go and wash your face
then wrap them up
Keep on fighting. . .
There's nothing special to see a woman plays a female role
Only you want
Mr. Liu, did you have your meal?
Boss!
Keep working
Boss, the Ticketing Officer's here
Commissioner, please!
Mr. Tun, did you see any guerillas?
How can I dare to have? Have some tea. . .
then bring it over
Yes, Captain!
When did the repertory arrive?
Just arrived yesterday
Go and search the back stage
Peking Duck
in three different dishes or the whole duck
So troublesome! Let me have it rare
Are you Comrade?
You are Comrade Sung
The man that you want to see is standing behind me
We have to find a more suitable place
I think here is more suitable
There's no one
Hold it!
You also!
What?
He's a traitor
We're looking for guerillas
Who's guerillas, get out by himself
Don't waste time
She doesn't belong here
How do you know?
She's General daughter
Everyone in Peking knows that
Stay calm, read this letter first
We invited her from abroad
As this matter has connection with her dad
Don't expose her identity
If not, we can't succeed
There's a woman, knock her up!
This mission is about President Yuen
President Yuen?
We've to steal a document
What document?
We suspect he loans money from foreign bank secretly
Loan money from foreigner?
He wants to build up his power to conqueror the South
Back to monarchism
Why me then?
We suspect
My dad is the middle agent for the progress
And the document is with him
We've to have that paper
So we can discover Yuen's conspiracy
Then we can have democracy
What's the matter?
We found an unidentity woman
In your repertory
She's my daughter
Doing such immoral thing
How can you prove she is your daughter
Her mother is my wife
Give me proof
Take her!
I'll go and find my wife
Write carefully, if not, they'll lose their temper
Give me money to save a man
- That's it! A serious matter - Yes
My wife's coming
You're cheating
She's so thin
How can she's such a big daughter?
Show be a fat one tomorrow
What are you performing outside?
The Stuber King
A good one
We want to watch
All women are guerillas,
how about your mom?
How dare you say that?
Take off the pants & give back to Kid Hung
Prepare supper!
We're having sukiyaki tonight?
Sukiyaki? Potato!
- Go away! - Be smart!
He's from Ticketing Office, they're everywhere
Be careful next time
Remember,
we'll meet at Sung's office
After I steal the document, you take it down to South
- No bad, - prettier than the guy next door
What's his name?
Fa!
Dad, you haven't money for supper
Where is the potato of last night?
Did you have enough?
Know eating only. Beware I'll break your leg
Courting again?
Don't pretend
as a gentleman
Dad, need me to wait for you?
Otherwise I won't ask you to stay?
I'll cut your ear
What are you doing?
Pretty car
What are going to do to that guy?
Where is the jewelry?
- I didn't take it - Really?
Tide him up
If he didn't say it, castrate him
Did you have another punishment?
Where's General?
He's having a meeting with foreigner
Miss, have a rest first
OK, get out
Yes!
Guanatee too do according to the contract
If we fail to do so
Then the 5 foreign banks have the right to take everything as penalty
Repeat what you said
How much can the President get?
The loan is 25,000,000 pounds
So he can have 1/3 of it
And 47 years later
We'll pay you back 67,500,000 pounds
That's 3 times of the loan
What will the world looks like 47 years later
Who knows?
Give me a pen for signature
I'll show President the contract in 2 days
There shouldn't be any problems
What are they doing?
They're tossing for the President
Great...
Tell them, I invite them for dinner
Wait me at the living room
Yes!
Captain!
- Hold it! - Who's that?
Is you?
How come is you?
Taking action without my order
You're too rough
Don't bullshit, go and get the document
Careless. Pack up the thing
How come is you?
Were in a group
Shouldn't be
Peking Buck!
Taste good
She's not our men
What's the matter?
I heard a shot
Problems inside
We'll get rich
How about this guy?
Don't waste time. Bring him along
- Is there a fire out there? - Yes
- Check it up - Yes!
Someone is coming. Find another chance another day
Madame!
I saw someone over there
Yes!
You can't run away
Wait me at the garage
I'll go to study room
General!
Wait, where are you going?
Protect me
Yes!
It's too high!
In the reading room, quick!
Quick!
General, is it a gun shot?
Why are you so late?
There're guerillas inside, search!
You listen, there're guerillas inside
- Go in and search! - Yes
This is the guerilla!
After him, quick!
You two protect the General
Listen, no one goes out or comes in
Or shoots him down
Yes!
He's gone?
Then I have to go!
The house is full of soldiers, you want to be caught?
Do you still want to go?
Sit down!
You tell me the truth
What is your mission in here?
What is mission?
You don't know mission? Why do you come here?
I don't know myself
I jump into the bucket
It's the bucket brought me here
Is that a mission? Is it?
I've saved you once, you must promise me
What happens tonight, you won't tell anyone
I will, I can swear
You don't have to do that
No trouble at all, I always swear
Jump over!
It's too high, I'm afraid
Are you fear of height or fear of dying?
Dying!
Then jump now!
Brother, a motor car!
Look, the head-light is shinning, how beautiful
It must be pretty expensive
Nobody's watching, let's move it away
- Good! - Quick, come!
Don't you know it's the General's car...
Give us a hand?
- Quick! - Come!
Take it to Tinjuin and sale it, then I'm rich
Captain!
I beg you Captain,
please don't tell anyone you see me here
Stay here!
If the thing gets spread out
We can never rob in this way again
How about we kill him!
If the General knows about it,
he will shoot me
I beg you, Captain, please don't tell...
What are you doing?
You guys don't
Go!
Don't be so ruthless!
Don't kill him!
Why is it like this?
We've been discovered by those bastards
Say no more, close the door!
Why do you take her along?
She came here by accident
Then we are going to take her by accident
If we are caught
Then she will take all our secret
OK!
Help me, I don't want to die
He's not dead?!
What're you doing?
He has saved me, I can't leave him like that
It's getting crowdy, get in!
Have we met somewhere before?
You hurt real bad, you are getting dizzy
Cover up the wound, quick
Madam!
- Open the gate - Yes!
Open it!
The oil-tank has a hole, the car can't move!
Listen, someone is coming!
It's from the Ticketing Office
If they see us like this, we are in trouble
May be we leave the car
Take them two to a safe place
Or there will be more trouble
So much blood, I will faint
Hold him!
Oh my dress! . . .
Damn, they've seen us
Don't take him with you
Dad!
Hey, who are you guys?
What are you doing here?
So you want to get away from these bastards
Right, lady, that's why you got to help us
My god, he hurts so bad
He needs an operation
- Find a place for him first - Operation?
I'll go to the car to get the tools
You first take him in
I'll take him in
Can't go there, go to my room!
I can't open the door and let everyone in
OK, our code is Peking Duck, you remember!
Peking Duck?
I'll come back immediately!
This is even more ridiculous
You've been searching all around, what are you looking for?
Do you know where's the box in the car?
Back-stage!
- Where is the back-stage? - Over there!
I'll find it!
Come back, no running around!
Girl, do you have a piece of cloth?
Take one and clean the blood for me
Get away! Bastard!
Tell your friend not to run around, will you?
I don't know her
Don't know her?
Don't know her then why are you together?
Is that strange, I don't know him either
What?
Do you know the woman who went out?
- I know her - I know
I really don't know what kind of game are you playing
I'll open the door
Don't bother, you two watch her
Peking Duck!
Peking Duck...
It's Tuna Fish!
Wrong, go away!
Open the door, I'm your dad!
Bitch, open it!
- Dad, - What Peking Duck...
- I'm sorry! - ...Niking Duck
Watch out or I'll tear your ear off
Dad!
Are you that hungry? Always think of food
Duck your head
Why yawn as you are calling for help?
- I'm too tired! - Just go to sleep
Go to sleep...
Damn, my dad is back, you must go!
Oh no, who is it this time?
I'm dead for sure
No, I must send them away
Peking Duck or Tuan Fish!
Peking Duck!
Right!
How came there is Tuan Fish?
Peking Duck is yours
Tuna Fish is my father, he's already back
My ears are going to be tortured again
You better be going!
- Take the wine and the cloth here - OK
- And heat some water - Yes
Shouldn't I send them away?
First tear off his clothes
Take the cloth and wipe off the blood
Why are you still standing here?
Go get the thing
OK, he is alright now!
It's too crowdy here, you take him out first
And you think the place is too crowdy, I'm going to blow up
Sit down!
You study medicine oversea?
I study gynaecology
I can go to back stage now.
Really, you can't even hold
Go to bad earlier, even your skin will be more beautiful
Where is my perfume, give me back
I know, stupid!
Oh no, those actress are coming back
Before anyone sees you, you better leave!
Go!
Go, be quick!
Where is the chignon?
Those actress are coming, go. . .
You look at this watchdog
- She's still laughing - Damn you!
I hate this!
Dad, you've not sleep yet?
There's problems raise up tonight
How can I sleep?
I thought about that night
It was exactly the same as tonight
She saved my life
If not, I'll not be alive
This pistol is a gift from a French
It's a dangerous around here
Take it with you!
Dad, I'll take care myself
Keep it with you
I've guards
I'm worrying about you
You are my only child
I worry there's no one
to inherit my country
I'm old
I see everything already
Remember, do anything for your ownself
Dad!
If I lose this key
We've to start from the beginning
Work like a dog
For this children
Pay attention to what I said
I've a companion, go to bed!
General!
Dad keeps the key with him
If we've to steal the key, and open the safe
At the same time
It'll be to obvious
You're right!
Unless we make a mode for the key
Then give back the key instantly
That's simple. . .
. . .steal while he's sleeping,it doesn't work
My dad has a woman
with him each night
That woman will notice
Is he alone when he's bathing?
Nowhere can hide in the bathroom
What else can we do?
Can I make a little suggestion?
Why is he here?
It's so easy to be caught running around
It's safer to stay here?
Can you stop arguing?
Listen to my suggestion first!
OK
You said the bedroom & you, the bathroom
Why not the toilet?
Toilet!
When the General leaves his house
Everyone has that necessity
If you can make him to go to the toilet
And you wait him there
Then he's trapped
I finish
If you've no other way
We can try this one
Really the toilet?
Which one?
I'm thinking!
Kwok Wo Building!
Mr Wong, they are the actors from Tinjuin
Show them to Fa
This way...
Have everything ready
Yes!
Go!
What are you doing? Come down!
Do anything you see
Just work
Quick!
Don't pretend to be miserious
Pearl...come out!
That way
The box is up there
I lost my money
Why are rubbing the stand
Almost full
Get away...we're celebrating
Big real?
Get away
Get away. . .
Celebrating
Ask your men to come for present
Put it down!
- Don't touch - What's the matter?
Don't move, I catch you at last
Who are you send the present to?
With Commander Liu's order
Send these to Fa
Who is looking for me?
Someone is sending these to you
When you are in good luck
Everything goes smooth
Even the council will take notice of you
Right, our Commander wants you happy
After you have these
He'll pick you up in 3 days
Then you'll be his husband
But I'm a man
He doesn't want to
That's it
I don't want to. . . go for someone else
- You do it? - Don't touch me!
If it spread out,
I couldn't get married
I can't
Sacrifice for you
Are you going to get married to commander?
No!
Beat him!
You cab your choice
You say that
Have to be happy
Can't by force
His skin is so soft
Woman needs soothing
Look at yourself
Flirting around
Too bad
Liu's present is here
Don't flirt anymore
Sacrifice yourself for the repertory
Get married in 3 days
Search around
My dear
Think of your comfortable lives afterward
General's here
He's here because of me?
If Fa is not with us
We'll be finished
Don't do that in front of General
General!
Master!
Pat Nell, you've to save me
I'm the Ticketing Officer Mr. Liu
Coming to protect the General
Are you trying to escape?
Where are you going?
Being a dumb in Chainam
We've to even act in small town
What are you doing?
Take more costume with you
You can make use of it
Take my place
Don't let anyone see me running away
You're alone
Take some medicine with you
Run
Run!
May be we won't see again! Take care!
Take care!
Put on the make up
The General doesn't like this kind of food
Change it
I like this dimsum
Who is she?
Your daughter
She makes me lose face
Look for Fa?
Yes!
General!
- Who is she? - I don't know
That's better
I can't find Fa back-stage
What? He's gone!
Don't let him go away
Yes!
She's fake, I'm real
Let's go
Chase!
Quick. . .
I go over that side
Wrong position
What am I going to do?
Follow me
Do what I do?
General, I'm hungry
Take a bite then
Miss, are you alright?
I'm fine
Take them back-stage
No need to explain
Yes Sir!
I'm hurt
You can't die, you haven't paid us yet
If they are women
They can become my wives
Boss, shall I die or not?
Since you like it so much, stay dead
No need to put on make up disguising as a corpse
We can get closer afterwards
General, I've a stomach ache
Go to the toilet then
What are we going to do?
- Take him away - Yes, Sir!
That's difficult
- Who is he? - So painful!
Taking advantage!
We're women, what am I going to now?
Commander Liu!
What's the matter, Miss?
Where's the toilet?
This way, I'll show you
No, thanks!
I can find my way, you say here to protect General
Pak Hoi!
You two go to protect Miss
By the way find out
why Miss Choi is late?
What's happening?
Because of me
Miss Choi!
Miss Choi passed out
Take her out
Yes!
- Here! - Yes
What happened?
A ghost, in the toilet!
Ghost?
Not ghost, is Fa
Protect the General
Threaten me?
Hold it!
Grab the guerillas
Freeze! Get up!
Beware!
Lie down!
Oh my box!
This way!
You flew excellent
Too bad you're not a bird
But you'll be in my hand
And keep in my cage
And teach you to fly!
Release him! . . .
If not, I'll give General a shot
Shot the guy in black
He's bad
No, he's my dad as the hostage
Hope these pistol wouldn't run out fire
I only have one bullet
You can't escape after shooting General?
I don't care, exchange hostage
Go there!
Grab him, don't shoot
Look at me!
Hold it!
Who do you think you are! Fire!
Don't, he doesn't think I'm a human
I did expect I can jump that high
There's guerillas in the theatre
The guerillas's coming, take them
Close down the theatre
Close down the theatre?
Dad!
I told you not to go on stage
You bitch, I'll kill you!
Stand still!
Run!
To where?
I've to kill her
Don't...
I told not to go on stage, but you did
I've to kill you
Don't hold me...
The theatre is closing down
Why are staying here for?
Dad, I left my thing in the back-stage
Go home first!
Protect Miss
Yes!
Found it!
It cold outside, put on a coat
I don't need your sympathy
Your performance was terrific
What for?
A woman performs on stage
Everyone will laugh at her
Don't be silly,
did you see the acclaims?
Don't get depress, you're excellent
Even you fail, try again
Don't get loose
Make us lose face!
Come here!
Quick. . .
Let's go for a drink
OK!
These clothes I used to wear abroad
How come all educated girls
Dress up so funny
Can't tell if a buy or a girl
To move more freely
What is this?
This is the scope
What?
This is our world
This is China
Look!
Where is Peking?
Here, as a dot
Where is Kwok Wo Building?
Inside the dot
Are you kidding, there's no houses?
Peking looks like a dot
The world is so big, where can I go?
Are you planning to go somewhere?
Everyone is running away
Run for life
I don't get it, this is a nice place?
Why have to run away?
We're running around
And finally we go back the same route
Dad!
Did you sleep?
Not yet!
They're my friend
I'm sending them home
They can stay for a night
I'll be back soon
Quick!
Who is it?
They were the actors on stage today
They are women?
Look!
How come you are here?
The Publishing Office is being watched
Officer told us not to go back there tonight
Right,
we need a place to hide up
So cold
Got only one bed & one blanket
How can we sleep?
Doesn't matter, we're all girls
We can sleep together
Come on!
We can share the blanket
Sleep
Come On! No seat here, don't come near
Boss...
What's the matter?
The General ordered to reopen the theatre
He's coming tonight
Look for your daughter
and that girl
Why?
If not, you'll die
Quick!
Pat Neil. . .
How come you didn't answer me
What? Are feeling alright?
Are you having a fever?
No, I'd a cold
If you'd a cold
Really!
Dad hits you
is for your good sake
Don't scare
Look at your hands, so rough
Dad!
Put the blanket on
I have performed for my whole life
Look, I've so much grey hair
Didn't expect you want to act too
Dad!
That'll be a waste if you don't act
You know I like acting
Yes, I know
Dad!
Good girl!
Daughter!
Dad!
Dad, I feel so bad!
You yawn differently each time?
Have a good rest
He's coming to see me?
Right,
also the girl last night
Where can we find her?
How come you are here?
Are you looking for me?
I didn't see you just now?
Dad!
You saw her already,
show your face!
We'll be on stage tonight
Why do you dress up like this?
Danger!
You really have to perform tonight
- I've a way. - What?
I've to act tonight?
Yes!
Do it
It's too hard, I don't want to do it
Continue
You mean Sheung Hung seducing my dad?
What? Ask me to seduce her dad?
And stay for a night with your dad?
That's the only to take off your dad's coat
The key is in the coat
That means I've to get married to your dad
And you'll call me mom?
You put this powder
in his drink
He'll wake up in 1/2 hours
She'll take you outside the door
Why am I helping you for?
Give me this first
Will pay you the balance afterward
Why not Pat Neil?
Because you won't
- resist on this - Right
What?
Nothing!
Sheung Hung, Pat Neil, your turn
Quick!
Pat Neil, Sheung Hung
Congratulation for your debut
Thanks!
Toss for your success
It's so danger here, you'll get caught?
I want to you the last time
Last time?
After the mission
Will you stay or go with us?
See you again
Are you worrying your dad?
He's my only relative
If he finds out you do all these
Will he forgive you?
No!
May be!
Absolutely not
He trusts me the most
The General invites you for a drink
You've to go too?
What's wrong, once a woman starts working
They all have this problem
If you don't go, we'll be finished
What are you going to do?
I go to fetch Mr. Ling
He can think for something
Where is the powder!
No need to find, take another one
Don't lose it, if not, don't come back
You're terrific, tell you something
That day in General's house, someone hit you...
Don't say it
I knew is you
I don't mean it
You hit it so hard
It doesn't matter
1/2 hours. . .
General's here
You two perform
excellent
Why don't you sit down?
Look at my hands
Your hands? Nothing
Another one, nothing too
See more clearly
Nothing
Do you think, it'll look better with rings
Bracelets, diamond, right?
You're so greedy and lovely
Let me see your hands too
Why are holding your palms?
Let me see...
Not bad
Another one, let me see. . .
Relax. . .
- What for? - General!
What are you doing?
Let have a game
What game?
Just guest
Guest?
Tell me!
It's finished
Fool me?
You're punished to drink
I don't know drinking
You've to drink
Hold it!
Don't!
Drink!
You've to finish it. . .
What did you do to my dad?
I only hit him slightly
Don't wake him up
How come?
Is it this one?
Where did you get it?
In his pocket
You opened it?
Is it this one?
Yes, it is
Open it
This is your balance payment
That's it?
What do you mean?
You'll fail
If I don't have a quick mind
You wouldn't get this papers
So I should have more
I got the papers already
You won't get more
You didn't know that
When I stole those papers, I kept 1/2
They are with me
Hand it out!
No!
You wouldn't shoot me
Pat Neil and I take this with our lifes
You've to pay her too
Don't be silly
One is for the paper by all means
One is for money without shame
Both of you betray your friend
I don't want to see you again
Pat Neil!
Don't pull me
You asked us for a drink
Because you wanted me to seduce your dad
I didn't mean that
You treat your dad that way
And your friend too, do you have conscience?
I'm not doing this for myself
Did you know that your dad will not let you off?
What am I going to do?
Help!
Release her
Sheung Hung, you'll be alright
Don't be afraid
He's from the Ticketing Office
He stared at us for a long time
I'll expose my identity
Dad. . .
Come in silently
That's Pat Neil
- Pat Neil! - Mr.Kam
Your dad and the actors are imprisoned
What?
The General is looking for you and Sheung Hung
What are we going to do
Run!
Where are we going?
Naking!
Our men will meet you there
Run!
How about my dad?
Don't worry, Tsao Wan will save your dad
Go!
Quick!
This way!
Sheung Hung, how come you're back?
Tsao Wan asked me to give you this
Where is she?
She said her identity was exposed
So she has to go back to her dad's
She'll sacrified
What?
Search all around
See if there anyone?
Yes!
Go over that side
Don't come out!
It's dangerous
Take care this paper
You go first
Go!
Don't!
Pat Neil, run!
Don't let them run away, chase them!
Chase!
Go separately!
Quick
- You two go over that way - Yes
That's not a way
Take care the paper
I lead them away
Hai!
Run!
You stay here, others follow me
Over there
Run!
Freeze. . .
If not, I'll shoot you
What are we going to do?
Don't scare, I'll find a way to save them
We've proof for Tsao's identity
Did you get her?
How are we going to handle General?
Who?
Dad!
Pack up
We all have to go tonight
If you go away with all these people
It's too obvious
And will start a fight
Dad lost an important matter, he needs to go
That's too serious
If your subordinates know you lose you power, there'll be a riot
It's saver
if you disguise
What?
If I afraid of dangerous, I'll not be an army
I fought with my life for years
Kill those who are supporting me
Dad, think of the others
Think for the whole situation
Talking about the situation without me
Sweet talking
All people are selfish
Talk louder with bigger power
Dad!
Dad,
if you council think that way
Why we need the government?
That's me, shoot those not agree with me
Dad!
No matter what's happening,
we'll be together
Pack up, time is running short
Alright I'll go!
Give me the key, you two get out!
Yes!
Quick, if not, it'll be too late
We got help...run. . .
We're save
Yes
Stop singing,
if not, I put you in jail again
Get away!
What are they running!
Quick!
Run!
Can't take a break
Dad!
Where is your luggages!
Not pack yet
Let's go without it!
- Report! - Yes?
The Ticketing Officers are here
Who do you think they are?
Who are you here? Go!
We want to invite your daughter to our office
As we suspect her has connection with the guerillas
You have no right
to say so
My daughter is not a guerillas
Anyone says that, I'll kill him
Dad. . .
She's not a guerillas
Wan, run...
Hide up the gun
General Tun run away with everything
How come he's back?
I don't understand politics
Before, Tsao used to have the power
Then Tun had to run away
Now Tsao was collapsed
Tun is back
That's simple
What did you say?
Social talking!
Take him back?
I'm an oversea Chinese
Even worse
Knock him up
Sand! Captain!
Where's the document?
I swallow it
In your stomach?
Hit!
Salt water!
Please stop
If not, I'll lose my temper
Wait!
Would you help me to test Tsao's daughter
You can do what you like after that
OK, send her to General's house
Tsao Wan...
You feel lonely
Sentenced them at night
Yes!
Report, someone wants to see you
I don't see anyone from now
till tomorrow morning
Shoot him if he insist
General!...
Oh, is you?
General, she's looking for you so badly
Even she's sick
So touching
Why don't you tell me that?
I did
Take her to study room
You can go
Wait me outside
Don't bother me, if not, I'll shoot you
Where am I?
Oh, is you, General?
You passed out just now
My heart is beating so fast
You don't believe me, listen
Listen!
What are you doing?
General!
Be patient
Come...
- Give me a kiss - Be patient
Hold it!
Don't fool me
Come...
Don't go! . . .
Come back...
Don't go . . . come back. . .
Hold it!
I don't trust you
What are you doing?
General?
What's happening?
General...
Don't
General, they come in without your permission
Get out?
Lead my sister to come in
General ask you to go in
Close the door!
Sheung Hung!
Tsao Wan, how come you are here too?
Keep quiet!
Sit down first
Why are crying?
Who beat you?
Tell me, who?
I'm fine, don't worry
They'll kill Pak Hoi and Tung Man tonight
The sun is setting, what can we do?
Find a way to save them
Did you see the window of the tallest bidg?
He's being knocked in there
Pat Neil, do you think you can climb up there?
I'm looking for a way
Go and get General's pistol
Faded!
Their lives are in your hand
You've to success
- Go - Be careful
Tide up the bed sheet
Tide it up?
Climb down!
Quick!
Open the door!
Patriotic Ling and Tung intimate to start a riot
Were sentenced death
Immediately
Ready. . .
Fire!
How are you?
OK!
Take the key
How about the soldier? Take a rest!
Go!
Go over that side?
The garage is over there
Quick!
Peking Duck!
Peking Duck is here
Pak Hoi, Tsao Wan!
Tung Man, Sheung Hung!
Are you OK?
I'm fine
Pat Neil?
Let's hug outside!
Get in the car
Captain!
Changing time
Patriotic, chase...
Where's the document?
In the theatre, let go back and get it
Is there any being lazy?
How come there's so little good guy?
Get out!
Mr Kam!
Pat Neil!
Where dad?
Mr Wong. . .
Pat Neil, you're back
Dad!
Are you alright?
I'm fine!
We're back for something, and will leave soon
We're leaving tonight
Captain, the car is ready
They must hide somewhere around
- Send a team here - Yes!
Follow me!
Block the street
Sit down
Continue!
Search the theatre
Yes!
They know we are here
Get out at the back door
The theatre's being surrounding
They block all exits
I've a way, tonight we perform the 8 fairies
We'll on stage
You?
The moustache's down
Can't find them anywhere?
Come over!
We get out from the roof
When?
The code is collapse
Captain, all men are here
In position
Yes!
I want all of them
I can't take of my shell
Why they are going up?
Catch them!
Collapse
Quick!
I'm afraid.
Help!
Don't be afraid
Keep quiet, they're just down there
Get up quick
Lie down!
Are you alright?
Doesn't matter, my shoulder is hurt
Be careful
Beware, Captain!
Bye!
Tsao Wan!
Wan!
Shit!
The bullet
Good shot
Go up!
That way!
Tsao Wan!
Is Commander Liu?
Who is shooting?
No one!
Must be the patriotic! . . .
We'll go South,
to hand this paper to the congress
Let them to handle Yuen
We see you off here!
Where are you going?
I'll keep singing
Leave China when I've enough money
But it's so turbulent
Then I'll go hometown, first
Don't feel sad
We'll see again
I'll fetch my dad in Tinjuin
After the revolution, meet you in Peking
See you then
Take care
OK