[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[Aegisub Project Garbage]

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text

Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.05,0:00:33.83,Default,,0000,0000,0173,,{\fn宋体\b1\i1\fscx120\fs30\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}嘉禾电影有限公司 {\fs20}出品
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.05,0:00:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0160,,{\fn宋体\b1\i1\fscx120\fs30\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}正東制作  有限公司 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.05,0:00:36.75,Default,,0150,0000,0090,,{\fn宋体\b1\i1\fscx120\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}制片
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.18,0:00:40.20,Default,,0000,0150,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}李\N连\N杰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.18,0:00:40.20,Default,,0000,0220,0130,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}领\N衔\N主\N演
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.50,0:00:44.10,Default,,0000,0239,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}杨\N紫\N琼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.50,0:00:44.10,Default,,0000,0310,0130,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}领\N衔\N主\N演
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.90,0:00:49.77,Default,,0000,0000,0115,,{\fn楷体\b1\fs100\c&H00FFFF&\3c&H1089DA&\4c&H1089DA&\bord5\shad5\be20}太極{\fs50\fscx150}張三豐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.80,Default,,0000,0300,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}钱\N小\N豪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.80,Default,,0000,0230,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}袁\N洁\N莹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.80,Default,,0230,0000,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}袁\N祥\N仁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.80,Default,,0300,0000,0108,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}刘\N    洵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.20,0:00:55.80,Default,,0000,0350,0130,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}联\N合\N主\N演
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}策 划  {\fs35}李 惠 民
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.50,0:01:31.75,Default,,0000,0300,0078,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs35\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}袁和平\N袁祥仁\N谷轩昭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.50,0:01:31.75,Default,,0000,0300,0130,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}武术指导
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.80,0:01:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}摄 影 {\fs35}刘 满 棠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.50,0:01:42.30,Default,,0000,0160,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}音 乐\N{ \fs35}胡 伟 立 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.50,0:01:42.30,Default,,0185,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}剪 接\N{\fs35}林 安 儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.35,0:01:45.58,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}编 剧  {\fs35}叶 广 俭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.05,0:01:50.10,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}制作总监  {\fs35}崔 宝 珠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.05,0:02:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}制 片  {\fs35}李 阳 中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.20,0:02:08.26,Default,,0000,0000,0180,,{\fn宋体\b1\fs20\c&H45D8FC&\3c&H1089DA&\bord1\shad0}导 演  {\fs35}袁 和 平
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.18,0:00:51.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}刀 光 剑 影 不 是 我 门 派
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.02,0:00:59.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}天 空 海 阔 自 有 我 风 采
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.07,0:01:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}双 手 一 推 非 黑 也 非 白
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.12,0:01:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}不 好 也 不 坏 没 有 胜 又 何 来 败
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.26,0:01:23.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 去 哪 有 来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.26,0:01:31.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.35,0:01:40.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.65,0:01:47.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 动 哪 有 静
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.37,0:01:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.34,0:02:04.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:16:21.28,1:16:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}刀 光 剑 影 不 是 我 门 派
Dialogue: 0,1:16:29.08,1:16:36.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}天 空 海 阔 自 有 我 风 采
Dialogue: 0,1:16:37.09,1:16:44.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}双 手 一 推 非 黑 也 非 白
Dialogue: 0,1:16:44.89,1:16:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}不 好 也 不 坏 没 有 胜 又 何 来 败
Dialogue: 0,1:16:53.15,1:17:00.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 去 哪 有 来
Dialogue: 0,1:17:01.03,1:17:08.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:17:09.08,1:17:16.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:17:17.46,1:17:23.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 动 哪 有 静
Dialogue: 0,1:17:24.35,1:17:31.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:17:32.31,1:17:39.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:33:33.01,1:33:40.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}刀 光 剑 影 不 是 我 门 派
Dialogue: 0,1:33:40.85,1:33:48.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}天 空 海 阔 自 有 我 风 采
Dialogue: 0,1:33:48.90,1:33:56.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}双 手 一 推 非 黑 也 非 白
Dialogue: 0,1:33:56.95,1:34:04.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}不 好 也 不 坏 没 有 胜 又 何 来 败
Dialogue: 0,1:34:05.09,1:34:12.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 去 哪 有 来
Dialogue: 0,1:34:13.09,1:34:20.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:34:21.18,1:34:28.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:34:29.48,1:34:36.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}没 有 动 哪 有 静
Dialogue: 0,1:34:37.20,1:34:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}手 中 无 剑 心 中 无 尘 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,1:34:45.17,1:34:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx130\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}随 缘 而 去 乘 风 而 来 才 是 我 胸 怀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.83,0:25:39.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx150\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}我 的 感 情 太 放 肆
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.50,0:25:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx150\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}容 不 下 任 何 一 粒 砂 石
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.20,0:25:49.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx150\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}一 直 到 爱 已 消 失
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.20,0:25:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fnsimhei\b1\fscx150\fs15\c&H80FFFF&\bord0\shad0}我 仍 然 不 愿 认 输 

Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.66,0:02:30.70,Default,,0,0,0,,以后你就是出家人啦 要守戒律
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.95,0:02:33.08,Default,,0,0,0,,不杀生 不吃肉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.29,0:02:36.13,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 弟子从小到现在都没有吃过肉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.96,0:02:38.38,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯 你还真有佛性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.59,0:02:41.17,Default,,0,0,0,,其实是我们家穷 买不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.38,0:02:43.18,Default,,0,0,0,,我也很想试试
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.47,0:02:45.93,Default,,0,0,0,,师父
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.14,0:02:48.14,Default,,0,0,0,,这是刚刚剃度的天宝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.56,0:02:50.27,Default,,0,0,0,,他就是你师兄君宝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.47,0:02:52.64,Default,,0,0,0,,以后有什么不懂的就问师兄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.89,0:02:55.73,Default,,0,0,0,,少林寺凡事讲规矩 你要听师兄的话哟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.98,0:02:58.15,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 待会你教他背一段经文
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.44,0:02:59.52,Default,,0,0,0,,背哪一段啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.77,0:03:01.48,Default,,0,0,0,,你好象只会一段
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.07,0:03:04.45,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝师弟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.41,0:03:07.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我比你高 而且我也比你大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.99,0:03:09.37,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么要叫你师兄啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.58,0:03:12.58,Default,,0,0,0,,我也搞不懂呀 师父说这是规矩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.79,0:03:16.00,Default,,0,0,0,,是这样的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.17,0:03:17.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我看这样好了 以后在人家面前我就叫你师兄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.67,0:03:20.17,Default,,0,0,0,,在没人的时候换你叫我师兄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.30,0:03:22.55,Default,,0,0,0,,你到底想不想当师兄啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.71,0:03:23.38,Default,,0,0,0,,想呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.63,0:03:25.18,Default,,0,0,0,,现在没人 快叫我师兄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.68,0:03:27.93,Default,,0,0,0,,师兄 乖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.18,0:03:30.26,Default,,0,0,0,,那我们去念经 先玩玩再说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.14,0:03:38.36,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在来练习少林拳三十六式
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.98,0:03:41.57,Default,,0,0,0,,单凤朝阳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.53,0:03:44.19,Default,,0,0,0,,金鸡独立
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.49,0:03:48.16,Default,,0,0,0,,师弟 快过来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.12,0:03:53.08,Default,,0,0,0,,哎 这么多人你怎么叫我师弟啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.29,0:03:55.66,Default,,0,0,0,,他们又听不到 反正这又没有人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.21,0:03:57.46,Default,,0,0,0,,说得也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.96,0:03:59.79,Default,,0,0,0,,雁落沙滩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.63,0:04:02.13,Default,,0,0,0,,豹子穿崖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.34,0:04:03.96,Default,,0,0,0,,如果我要有机会练武功的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.26,0:04:05.72,Default,,0,0,0,,要超过他们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.97,0:04:08.01,Default,,0,0,0,,这个嘛 我得先去问问师父
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.55,0:04:10.68,Default,,0,0,0,,八卦蛇形
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.76,0:04:14.39,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎么乱打人呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.60,0:04:16.31,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个正事不干在这边偷学武功?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.56,0:04:18.81,Default,,0,0,0,,我是你们大师兄 打你就打你啰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.73,0:04:21.27,Default,,0,0,0,,你打人?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.69,0:04:23.98,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.28,0:04:25.11,Default,,0,0,0,,叫你还偷学武功?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.11,0:04:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我要告诉我们师父
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.40,0:04:28.53,Default,,0,0,0,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.82,0:04:30.91,Default,,0,0,0,,你以为我会怕你们啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.12,0:04:33.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你们的师父还叫我师父大师兄呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.63,0:04:51.05,Default,,0,0,0,,这一草一木都有生命
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.26,0:04:52.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我们不可以因为个人的利益
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.76,0:04:54.81,Default,,0,0,0,,而伤害大自然的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.22,0:04:56.68,Default,,0,0,0,,这样太自私了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.85,0:04:58.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你们明白了吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.02,0:05:00.10,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.27,0:05:01.94,Default,,0,0,0,,就算你以后在太阳底下被烤糊了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.15,0:05:03.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我们都不用管你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.15,0:05:08.86,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 我想练武功
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.49,0:05:10.78,Default,,0,0,0,,练武功干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.86,0:05:12.16,Default,,0,0,0,,强身健体 不挨打
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.32,0:05:14.41,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个想好了再来跟我说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.91,0:05:16.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我们没有骗你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.20,0:05:18.66,Default,,0,0,0,,将来你们学会武功
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.08,0:05:21.75,Default,,0,0,0,,是要来帮助人的 千万要记住
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.96,0:05:23.29,Default,,0,0,0,,知道了 师父
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.38,0:05:33.39,Default,,0,0,0,,你们居然敢打我?等我出来我要你好看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.80,0:05:35.01,Default,,0,0,0,,快来帮我的忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.10,0:05:37.31,Default,,0,0,0,,我抓住他啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.52,0:05:39.14,Default,,0,0,0,,快打他… 快
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.56,0:05:42.14,Default,,0,0,0,,还不放手 我已经知道你是谁啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.56,0:05:44.52,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎么知道我是君宝?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.77,0:05:46.07,Default,,0,0,0,,是你告诉我的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.03,0:05:51.61,Default,,0,0,0,,这都要怪你啊 自己把名字告诉人家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.65,0:05:53.07,Default,,0,0,0,,真是饭桶兼白痴啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.28,0:05:56.03,Default,,0,0,0,,是他说知道的 我怎么知道会骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.28,0:05:57.10,Default,,0,0,0,,他说的话能相信吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.15,0:06:00.80,Default,,0,0,0,,害得我们俩从早晨跪到现在都没有东西吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.79,0:06:03.87,Default,,0,0,0,,肚子都快饿扁了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.08,0:06:05.88,Default,,0,0,0,,我也饿得咕咕叫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.34,0:06:08.42,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个混帐真大胆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.67,0:06:11.13,Default,,0,0,0,,叫你学武功去帮人 你们两个居然去打人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.38,0:06:13.22,Default,,0,0,0,,算我管教无方
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.26,0:06:14.47,Default,,0,0,0,,连师伯的徒弟都敢打
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.68,0:06:16.35,Default,,0,0,0,,师父我们 还敢顶嘴?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.64,0:06:18.85,Default,,0,0,0,,看我不打死你们才怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.10,0:06:20.47,Default,,0,0,0,,师伯罚你们已经够轻的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.68,0:06:21.81,Default,,0,0,0,,才跪三个时辰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.18,0:06:23.60,Default,,0,0,0,,现在通通给我面壁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.89,0:06:25.19,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 有没有豆沙包?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.40,0:06:26.69,Default,,0,0,0,,有斋包吃已经够好的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.90,0:06:28.98,Default,,0,0,0,,再跪半个时辰去打扫罗汉堂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.65,0:06:34.11,Default,,0,0,0,,都是你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.32,0:06:36.24,Default,,0,0,0,,又把师父的花瓶给打烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.53,0:06:38.16,Default,,0,0,0,,害得我们又要打扫罗汉堂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.41,0:06:41.87,Default,,0,0,0,,还不是你玩什么捉迷藏 蒙着眼睛怎么看得见花瓶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.12,0:06:43.71,Default,,0,0,0,,我早说过你是白痴兼饭桶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.71,0:06:48.13,Default,,0,0,0,,仙人指路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.63,0:06:50.71,Default,,0,0,0,,盘龙摆尾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.34,0:06:53.55,Default,,0,0,0,,前天你耍的那套棍法
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.84,0:06:55.76,Default,,0,0,0,,最后一招是怎么耍的?我忘了哎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.30,0:06:57.43,Default,,0,0,0,,这么简单都不记得
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.97,0:07:00.31,Default,,0,0,0,,仙人指路
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.27,0:07:04.69,Default,,0,0,0,,盘龙摆尾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.35,0:07:06.69,Default,,0,0,0,,横扫千军
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.19,0:07:08.02,Default,,0,0,0,,最后一招
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.27,0:07:09.11,Default,,0,0,0,,叫敲脑袋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.32,0:07:10.94,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你又耍我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.15,0:07:12.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你自己反应的慢嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.08,0:07:24.50,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.71,0:07:26.25,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 是你让我的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.25,0:07:31.67,Default,,0,0,0,,师父老是说 练功是用来帮人的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.96,0:07:34.42,Default,,0,0,0,,这里人人都会武功 那我们帮谁呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.63,0:07:37.55,Default,,0,0,0,,帮自己啰 我要做少林寺第一武僧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.05,0:07:40.80,Default,,0,0,0,,哼 说得容易?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.06,0:07:43.14,Default,,0,0,0,,什么时候才能坐这个位子?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.73,0:07:48.85,Default,,0,0,0,,打完十八铜人 出得了木人巷再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.81,0:07:53.11,Default,,0,0,0,,住持的位子 让人家看到惨了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.32,0:07:55.36,Default,,0,0,0,,未见则不知 不知也就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.74,0:07:58.03,Default,,0,0,0,,我不懂什么知不知的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.24,0:08:00.41,Default,,0,0,0,,你先下来再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.66,0:08:02.20,Default,,0,0,0,,你又耍我!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.41,0:08:03.79,Default,,0,0,0,,哎呀 打翻了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.50,0:08:06.29,Default,,0,0,0,,住持的位子你弄坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.58,0:08:07.92,Default,,0,0,0,,你惨了 我要去告密
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.08,0:08:09.54,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么 你以为就罚不到你啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.31,0:08:27.94,Default,,0,0,0,,少林拳打一条线
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.52,0:08:30.85,Default,,0,0,0,,拳有形 打之无形
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.23,0:08:33.61,Default,,0,0,0,,动如风 站如针
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.90,0:08:35.65,Default,,0,0,0,,反之如猛虎 守之若处女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.03,0:08:38.90,Default,,0,0,0,,马步要稳 出拳要猛 是本门功夫的基本要诀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.01,0:09:00.43,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么会吃饭吃坏桌子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.63,0:09:03.26,Default,,0,0,0,,前两天门也被踢坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.30,0:09:07.06,Default,,0,0,0,,我就跟你们说有白蚁嘛 你们又不信
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.35,0:09:09.27,Default,,0,0,0,,别把白蚁吃进肚子里呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.90,0:09:14.11,Default,,0,0,0,,要达到最高境界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.36,0:09:16.27,Default,,0,0,0,,先将身体练到如钢似铁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.01,0:09:40.76,Default,,0,0,0,,床也垮了?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.22,0:09:44.64,Default,,0,0,0,,睡吧睡吧 明天还要练铁沙掌呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.40,0:09:56.56,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 看剑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.40,0:10:03.20,Default,,0,0,0,,平时不练功 一点臂力都没有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.45,0:10:06.83,Default,,0,0,0,,先发制人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.42,0:10:16.75,Default,,0,0,0,,师兄啊 我去练功啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.42,0:10:19.88,Default,,0,0,0,,搞什么呀?门也烂了 桌子也烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.34,0:10:21.55,Default,,0,0,0,,现在连衣服都烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.84,0:10:23.13,Default,,0,0,0,,罗汉堂那些家伙可有的笑话说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.43,0:10:24.76,Default,,0,0,0,,哎呀 就说自己洗烂的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.97,0:10:27.22,Default,,0,0,0,,师兄为什么我们这两件没事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.43,0:10:28.64,Default,,0,0,0,,好的当然留给自己穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.01,0:10:30.06,Default,,0,0,0,,师叔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.06,0:10:32.60,Default,,0,0,0,,他们是怎么搞的?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.39,0:10:36.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我也搞不懂 大概是老鼠咬的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.94,0:10:39.69,Default,,0,0,0,,最近怎么这么多老鼠跟白蚁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.15,0:10:41.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个去抓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.36,0:10:48.12,Default,,0,0,0,,到哪去弄那些老鼠和白蚁呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.37,0:10:49.66,Default,,0,0,0,,说被麻雀吃了不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.41,0:10:52.12,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你的提壶功好厉害呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.33,0:10:55.25,Default,,0,0,0,,过奖…雕虫小技罢了 来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.96,0:10:59.46,Default,,0,0,0,,四大武僧你一定有份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.67,0:11:01.17,Default,,0,0,0,,承你美言 你也会有机会的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.46,0:11:02.55,Default,,0,0,0,,饭来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.76,0:11:09.05,Default,,0,0,0,,铁板桥功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.35,0:11:11.97,Default,,0,0,0,,好险啊 你去吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.89,0:11:14.10,Default,,0,0,0,,你敢用饭泼我?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.52,0:11:15.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你没看到我绊了一跤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.27,0:11:18.35,Default,,0,0,0,,饭是我泼的 你去师父那边告我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.65,0:11:21.44,Default,,0,0,0,,你想怎么样 我告诉你啊 这次考试是我师父主考
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.69,0:11:23.86,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个不要想考进达摩院啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.15,0:11:25.36,Default,,0,0,0,,放开我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.32,0:11:27.78,Default,,0,0,0,,我一定要打赢这个大西瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.41,0:11:31.20,Default,,0,0,0,,十二 十…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.49,0:11:32.79,Default,,0,0,0,,那块我敲过啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.99,0:11:35.08,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝呀 过几天寺里就要选武僧进达摩院了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.33,0:11:36.37,Default,,0,0,0,,你有没信心呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.79,0:11:39.71,Default,,0,0,0,,行就行 不行就不行 随缘啰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.00,0:11:42.59,Default,,0,0,0,,你说什么?我可是要当少林第一武僧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.84,0:11:44.30,Default,,0,0,0,,要不然干嘛练铁头功?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.76,0:11:47.13,Default,,0,0,0,,你现在敲第几块了?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.51,0:11:48.30,Default,,0,0,0,,十七啰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.63,0:11:49.84,Default,,0,0,0,,十八
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.34,0:11:52.60,Default,,0,0,0,,你什么时候练的后脑都不告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.89,0:11:54.10,Default,,0,0,0,,我还没练
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.94,0:12:04.57,Default,,0,0,0,,今天招式跟平常不同啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.99,0:12:14.20,Default,,0,0,0,,般若掌
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.50,0:12:22.13,Default,,0,0,0,,原来巧妙在运气的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.54,0:12:23.67,Default,,0,0,0,,今天我们要选出
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.88,0:12:28.55,Default,,0,0,0,,本年武功最好的四名弟子进入达摩院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.84,0:12:30.93,Default,,0,0,0,,修练本门的上乘武功
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.22,0:12:32.89,Default,,0,0,0,,记住 我佛慈悲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.10,0:12:36.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我辈弟子习武是为普渡众生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:40.06,Default,,0,0,0,,比武皆在切磋武艺 点到即止
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.85,0:12:45.11,Default,,0,0,0,,第一场由天宝对心宝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.90,0:12:47.49,Default,,0,0,0,,大西瓜倒楣了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.53,0:12:51.74,Default,,0,0,0,,请指教
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.82,0:12:53.99,Default,,0,0,0,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.80,0:13:15.05,Default,,0,0,0,,提壶功
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.64,0:13:21.19,Default,,0,0,0,,心宝 你输定了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.32,0:13:27.69,Default,,0,0,0,,尝尝我的铁拳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.91,0:13:34.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你耍诈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.78,0:13:38.49,Default,,0,0,0,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.96,0:13:44.50,Default,,0,0,0,,大胆 连我也敢打?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.08,0:13:46.34,Default,,0,0,0,,师伯 弟子不敢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.04,0:13:50.30,Default,,0,0,0,,你出招太狠毒 根本就不适合练武
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.59,0:13:52.22,Default,,0,0,0,,我要赶你出罗汉堂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.34,0:13:55.84,Default,,0,0,0,,师伯…求求你不要啊 是心宝先耍诈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.05,0:13:57.72,Default,,0,0,0,,那你说我不公正啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.06,0:13:58.97,Default,,0,0,0,,弟子不敢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.01,0:14:00.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你瞎啦 自己看不出来?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.31,0:14:02.69,Default,,0,0,0,,你侮辱长辈?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.44,0:14:04.60,Default,,0,0,0,,他不是有意的 走开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.07,0:14:11.36,Default,,0,0,0,,我要废你的武功
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.78,0:14:13.11,Default,,0,0,0,,师伯 不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.32,0:14:14.45,Default,,0,0,0,,走开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.99,0:14:22.20,Default,,0,0,0,,般若掌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.04,0:14:28.84,Default,,0,0,0,,你为什么会般若掌?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.17,0:14:31.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我就说你瞎了 偷学你武功都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.46,0:14:32.38,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.59,0:14:34.01,Default,,0,0,0,,他是不小心看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.22,0:14:35.93,Default,,0,0,0,,给我抓住这两个孽徒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.39,0:14:38.64,Default,,0,0,0,,罗汉棍阵 是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.03,0:15:00.03,Default,,0,0,0,,大家同门师兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.08,0:15:01.95,Default,,0,0,0,,稍安毋躁 有话好好说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.04,0:15:03.08,Default,,0,0,0,,小心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.29,0:15:06.16,Default,,0,0,0,,佛光初现 万棍降魔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.23,0:15:34.32,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 以棍还棍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.07,0:15:36.99,Default,,0,0,0,,破他棍阵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.67,0:15:58.93,Default,,0,0,0,,佛法无边 降龙伏虎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.58,0:17:10.04,Default,,0,0,0,,好滑呀 哎哟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.29,0:17:11.16,Default,,0,0,0,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.00,0:17:14.21,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.21,0:17:21.01,Default,,0,0,0,,小心呀 布阵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.18,0:17:24.93,Default,,0,0,0,,地这么滑 怎么布阵呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.22,0:17:30.64,Default,,0,0,0,,横扫千军
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.23,0:17:37.69,Default,,0,0,0,,同门师兄弟不好再踩 还踩?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.20,0:17:47.20,Default,,0,0,0,,别跑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.54,0:17:54.62,Default,,0,0,0,,不要让他们跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.55,0:18:05.01,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 还不快走?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.01,0:18:08.47,Default,,0,0,0,,觉远
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.51,0:18:12.10,Default,,0,0,0,,你纵容门徒 胡作非为
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.39,0:18:15.35,Default,,0,0,0,,徒弟是你的 看你怎么向方丈交代?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.57,0:18:24.57,Default,,0,0,0,,根本存心护短嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.61,0:18:26.24,Default,,0,0,0,,全世界都看到大肥猪耍诈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.49,0:18:28.62,Default,,0,0,0,,师伯却看不到 还说我出手重
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.41,0:18:30.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我做错了什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.79,0:18:32.20,Default,,0,0,0,,用罗汉阵来对付我们两个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.29,0:18:33.91,Default,,0,0,0,,不知师父现在怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.71,0:18:39.17,Default,,0,0,0,,是是非非 又有什么人能分得清?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.25,0:18:43.30,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 我们知道错了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.01,0:18:46.63,Default,,0,0,0,,缘尽于此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.88,0:18:49.93,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经没有能力再做你们的师父了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.30,0:18:53.56,Default,,0,0,0,,就把俗世的生活当作你们的师父吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.02,0:18:57.90,Default,,0,0,0,,烦恼即菩提 菩提即烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.23,0:19:03.90,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你天性善良 我很放心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.82,0:19:08.78,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你太好胜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.74,0:19:11.16,Default,,0,0,0,,这本「气功心法」
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.37,0:19:13.16,Default,,0,0,0,,并不是什么武林绝学
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.49,0:19:15.00,Default,,0,0,0,,但是当你心情烦乱的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.20,0:19:17.29,Default,,0,0,0,,它会带给你清静
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.50,0:19:20.42,Default,,0,0,0,,你要勤加练习
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.92,0:19:24.63,Default,,0,0,0,,记住 凡事要以清静心对待
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.13,0:19:29.51,Default,,0,0,0,,修行不一定要在少林寺 你们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.97,0:19:34.31,Default,,0,0,0,,是 师父
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.16,0:19:55.33,Default,,0,0,0,,哪一派的棍法?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.49,0:19:56.45,Default,,0,0,0,,他们是卖艺的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.41,0:19:59.67,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么只剃一半?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:01.38,Default,,0,0,0,,这么丑 一定是契丹人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.42,0:20:04.04,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 我好肚饿呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.38,0:20:05.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我也肚子饿 我们先去化缘
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.60,0:20:15.47,Default,,0,0,0,,那个唱歌的应该不会拒绝我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.89,0:20:17.35,Default,,0,0,0,,她要是有钱就不用卖唱啦 我们到那边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.81,0:20:23.36,Default,,0,0,0,,各位施主 长命百岁 永享太平
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.61,0:20:24.65,Default,,0,0,0,,难怪我今天会输钱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.90,0:20:26.78,Default,,0,0,0,,原来碰到你们两个臭和尚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.98,0:20:29.36,Default,,0,0,0,,希望施主福如东海 寿比南山
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.57,0:20:31.28,Default,,0,0,0,,不能讲这个 要讲逢赌必赢 一本万利
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.61,0:20:32.91,Default,,0,0,0,,少跟我啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.16,0:20:35.49,Default,,0,0,0,,不给钱不要这么凶嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.70,0:20:37.08,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思 没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.41,0:20:38.20,Default,,0,0,0,,请问两位大师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.41,0:20:40.33,Default,,0,0,0,,认不认识一个人叫慕容白的?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.54,0:20:46.09,Default,,0,0,0,,麻烦两位
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.38,0:20:50.47,Default,,0,0,0,,她是要找人 我们是要找吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.76,0:20:51.93,Default,,0,0,0,,我们不止要找吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.18,0:20:54.43,Default,,0,0,0,,还要找活干 去赚钱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.18,0:20:58.39,Default,,0,0,0,,快交保护费
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.60,0:20:59.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经交过了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.93,0:21:01.48,Default,,0,0,0,,你家拜观音 就不拜土地公啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.31,0:21:04.31,Default,,0,0,0,,拜神只拜一个 给我打
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.52,0:21:07.48,Default,,0,0,0,,我们家没钱…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.70,0:21:13.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我要去告县太爷
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.99,0:21:15.82,Default,,0,0,0,,县太爷是我表哥 你去告啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.70,0:21:21.54,Default,,0,0,0,,小姑娘别走呀 跟我去喝茶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.54,0:21:26.17,Default,,0,0,0,,她害羞啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.34,0:21:31.47,Default,,0,0,0,,老伯 赶快把钱收下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.42,0:21:33.84,Default,,0,0,0,,这是那个坏蛋还你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.22,0:21:35.89,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢姑娘呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.05,0:21:37.18,Default,,0,0,0,,我的钱呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.39,0:21:39.35,Default,,0,0,0,,是那个女的 抓住她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.56,0:21:40.56,Default,,0,0,0,,别让她跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.78,0:21:53.03,Default,,0,0,0,,去死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.90,0:21:55.32,Default,,0,0,0,,中！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.03,0:21:58.16,Default,,0,0,0,,又卖艺呀?  是打架
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.91,0:22:02.70,Default,,0,0,0,,以多欺少
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.91,0:22:04.00,Default,,0,0,0,,帮不帮呀?  帮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:09.04,Default,,0,0,0,,你们不要打她 要打打我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.38,0:22:10.34,Default,,0,0,0,,打就打
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.30,0:22:14.59,Default,,0,0,0,,你们先打我的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.51,0:22:19.05,Default,,0,0,0,,姑娘 你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.93,0:22:24.35,Default,,0,0,0,,你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.98,0:22:29.19,Default,,0,0,0,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.27,0:22:30.52,Default,,0,0,0,,第十五式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.19,0:22:32.28,Default,,0,0,0,,十六式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.65,0:22:33.90,Default,,0,0,0,,十七式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.32,0:22:35.57,Default,,0,0,0,,十八式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.28,0:22:37.91,Default,,0,0,0,,二十式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.11,0:22:39.45,Default,,0,0,0,,三十五式
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.70,0:22:41.41,Default,,0,0,0,,三十六
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.16,0:22:44.41,Default,,0,0,0,,三十六式…打完了没有呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.66,0:22:47.08,Default,,0,0,0,,还有最后一式 我自…创的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.92,0:22:55.67,Default,,0,0,0,,教你那套白眉棍嘛 怎么老是学不会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.77,0:23:05.10,Default,,0,0,0,,刘三爷 谁把你打成这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.31,0:23:07.14,Default,,0,0,0,,和尚别打了 快走 官兵来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.06,0:23:09.56,Default,,0,0,0,,给我抓住那两个臭和尚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.77,0:23:10.81,Default,,0,0,0,,追 是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.69,0:23:16.15,Default,,0,0,0,,他往马房那边跑了 快追
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.36,0:23:20.91,Default,,0,0,0,,谁家师兄谁家猜…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.03,0:23:22.74,Default,,0,0,0,,谁家师弟谁家猜…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.50,0:23:27.33,Default,,0,0,0,,你头发好难看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.58,0:23:28.54,Default,,0,0,0,,你也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.75,0:23:30.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你们猜的什么拳啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.08,0:23:31.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这个 是师兄拳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.84,0:23:32.96,Default,,0,0,0,,教我嘛 一路走一路教
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.25,0:23:35.55,Default,,0,0,0,,猜赢的当师兄 猜输的当师弟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.76,0:23:37.17,Default,,0,0,0,,可是他每次都当师兄
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.84,0:23:39.55,Default,,0,0,0,,只能怪你自己反应迟钝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.63,0:23:41.01,Default,,0,0,0,,你呀 八成是出花招赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.09,0:23:42.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你要是跟我猜 我一定当你师母
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.18,0:23:44.10,Default,,0,0,0,,师母?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.77,0:23:47.06,Default,,0,0,0,,让开
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.37,0:24:14.04,Default,,0,0,0,,威风 真是威风
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.46,0:24:15.92,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么他那么霸道?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.17,0:24:17.21,Default,,0,0,0,,做官的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.30,0:24:19.13,Default,,0,0,0,,他就是这里的土皇帝 镇守太监刘瑾
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.22,0:24:23.47,Default,,0,0,0,,如果我能象他这么威风就好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.93,0:24:25.22,Default,,0,0,0,,那你去当太监啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.22,0:24:27.43,Default,,0,0,0,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.44,0:24:36.65,Default,,0,0,0,,八爷 今天那么早呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.61,0:24:40.11,Default,,0,0,0,,我先弄几样小菜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.19,0:24:41.15,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢 谢谢啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.36,0:24:42.95,Default,,0,0,0,,先生 你印堂发黑呀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.11,0:24:44.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你才发黑咧 滚远点
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.82,0:24:46.70,Default,,0,0,0,,别理他
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.16,0:24:53.54,Default,,0,0,0,,姑娘 你印堂发黑 你是要找人是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.88,0:24:56.75,Default,,0,0,0,,就算找到 也未必是好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.96,0:24:59.05,Default,,0,0,0,,帮我买张灵符怎么样?  神棍
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.63,0:25:01.26,Default,,0,0,0,,不买就算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.80,0:25:03.59,Default,,0,0,0,,这里最出名呢就是烤乳鸽
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.93,0:25:06.51,Default,,0,0,0,,姑娘 佛笑楼没有卖斋饭的?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.89,0:25:08.10,Default,,0,0,0,,白饭一样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.31,0:25:10.56,Default,,0,0,0,,告诉你君宝 入境就要随俗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.81,0:25:11.73,Default,,0,0,0,,别管那么多了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.93,0:25:14.65,Default,,0,0,0,,你不记得师父说过嘛 要入世学佛
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.94,0:25:16.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我不入地狱谁入地狱?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.42,0:25:42.47,Default,,0,0,0,,Default  0000 0000 0035  来吃块豆腐 不要光吃白饭嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.05,0:25:45.09,Default,,0,0,0,,Default  0000 0000 0035  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.14,0:25:51.02,Default,,0,0,0,,Default  0000 0000 0035  哪 地狱给你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.94,0:25:58.02,Default,,0,0,0,,Default  0000 0000 0035  欢迎刘小姐大驾光临
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.27,0:26:00.36,Default,,0,0,0,,这边请 给您留了张桌子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.57,0:26:03.15,Default,,0,0,0,,您令兄好啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.11,0:26:06.53,Default,,0,0,0,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.53,0:26:11.20,Default,,0,0,0,,娘子 请 请
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.75,0:26:16.46,Default,,0,0,0,,娘子 想吃点什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.75,0:26:18.21,Default,,0,0,0,,随便啦 你做主
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.75,0:26:22.05,Default,,0,0,0,,慕容白 相公 真的是你?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.67,0:26:26.26,Default,,0,0,0,,你…秋雪 你怎么到京城来啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.30,0:26:27.43,Default,,0,0,0,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.59,0:26:30.68,Default,,0,0,0,,好一个千里寻夫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.89,0:26:33.06,Default,,0,0,0,,不过 他已经不姓慕容了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.27,0:26:35.18,Default,,0,0,0,,入赘我们家跟我姓刘
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.94,0:26:39.27,Default,,0,0,0,,如果不是我 他早就饿死啦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.94,0:26:42.02,Default,,0,0,0,,男人都是贱货
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.40,0:26:46.28,Default,,0,0,0,,谁能够给他风流快活 荣华富贵
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.57,0:26:48.74,Default,,0,0,0,,他就会留在谁的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.07,0:26:51.41,Default,,0,0,0,,这么简单 你都不懂啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.04,0:26:55.83,Default,,0,0,0,,秋雪 你走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.29,0:26:57.87,Default,,0,0,0,,哪有这么没良心的人?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.58,0:27:00.83,Default,,0,0,0,,慕容白已经变成了狗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.13,0:27:02.80,Default,,0,0,0,,就该跟着他的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.00,0:27:05.21,Default,,0,0,0,,以前我每晚抱着这个琴当宝
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.34,0:27:10.05,Default,,0,0,0,,不管再怎么苦 我都舍不得把它卖掉
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.22,0:27:14.68,Default,,0,0,0,,现在人事已非 把它还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.60,0:27:17.14,Default,,0,0,0,,垃圾
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.52,0:27:20.56,Default,,0,0,0,,我看你比较需要它
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.36,0:27:31.91,Default,,0,0,0,,骂狗也得看主人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.17,0:27:46.21,Default,,0,0,0,,他是刘公公的妹
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.42,0:27:47.76,Default,,0,0,0,,不要轻举妄动
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.32,0:28:16.33,Default,,0,0,0,,看好 再来我就不客气啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.32,0:28:51.49,Default,,0,0,0,,娘子 你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.57,0:28:53.03,Default,,0,0,0,,滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.83,0:28:59.20,Default,,0,0,0,,你闹够了没有?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.41,0:29:02.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经跟你恩尽义绝啦 你还不走?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.17,0:29:06.04,Default,,0,0,0,,你看什么?不识抬举 走呀
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.75,0:29:10.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我来帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.13,0:29:14.55,Default,,0,0,0,,姑娘 你流血啦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.47,0:29:17.80,Default,,0,0,0,,不行啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.56,0:29:21.06,Default,,0,0,0,,换个姿势比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.27,0:29:28.36,Default,,0,0,0,,罪过 罪过…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.65,0:29:30.86,Default,,0,0,0,,没良心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.82,0:29:35.16,Default,,0,0,0,,不要怕 有我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.53,0:29:38.16,Default,,0,0,0,,谁在这里打架 统统不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.41,0:29:41.08,Default,,0,0,0,,官兵来啦 快走啊 别打啦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.66,0:29:43.25,Default,,0,0,0,,害我整天被官兵追啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.46,0:29:45.83,Default,,0,0,0,,别让那两个契丹人跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.04,0:29:47.33,Default,,0,0,0,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.59,0:29:50.17,Default,,0,0,0,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.63,0:29:53.80,Default,,0,0,0,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.13,0:29:57.18,Default,,0,0,0,,死吧你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.72,0:30:01.18,Default,,0,0,0,,好重呀
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.39,0:30:02.97,Default,,0,0,0,,抱个女人抱那么紧 当然重啦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.10,0:30:05.64,Default,,0,0,0,,阿弥陀佛
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.85,0:30:07.31,Default,,0,0,0,,你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.98,0:30:13.86,Default,,0,0,0,,那两个契丹人跑这么快呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.08,0:30:26.08,Default,,0,0,0,,这里是什么地方?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.33,0:30:28.75,Default,,0,0,0,,哎呀 怎么又到佛笑楼啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.96,0:30:29.88,Default,,0,0,0,,这里是分店?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.08,0:30:32.46,Default,,0,0,0,,真的 远近驰名 只此一家
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.67,0:30:34.38,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 今晚你们两个在这打地铺
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.59,0:30:36.09,Default,,0,0,0,,我带她去疗伤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.14,0:30:40.80,Default,,0,0,0,,我还是觉得当和尚舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.22,0:30:43.22,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 我们不可以寄人篱下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.39,0:30:44.93,Default,,0,0,0,,苟且偷安
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.23,0:30:46.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我不是要白吃白住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.77,0:30:48.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我会在这好好干活的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.65,0:30:50.23,Default,,0,0,0,,你知不知道 人家只是让我们睡一会
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.65,0:30:52.52,Default,,0,0,0,,没说要养我们一辈子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.77,0:30:54.32,Default,,0,0,0,,一有机会我就要做官
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.36,0:30:58.28,Default,,0,0,0,,其实做什么人都一样啦 只要问心无愧…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.49,0:31:01.03,Default,,0,0,0,,开心就行啦 管那么多干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.32,0:31:02.37,Default,,0,0,0,,快点睡觉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.56,0:31:36.28,Default,,0,0,0,,刘瑾打死也想不到白天收刮来的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.36,0:31:37.90,Default,,0,0,0,,晚上却被我们偷过来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.11,0:31:40.36,Default,,0,0,0,,现在我们有这么多钱 做什么才好呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.57,0:31:42.41,Default,,0,0,0,,臭道士 怎么来就怎么去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.62,0:31:44.20,Default,,0,0,0,,把这些钱发给穷苦老百姓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.24,0:31:46.91,Default,,0,0,0,,对 他早上刮税 晚上我们就去偷
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.20,0:31:50.16,Default,,0,0,0,,他一天不死 我就偷他一辈子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.96,0:31:53.92,Default,,0,0,0,,佛笑楼这些人原来是叛党
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.13,0:31:56.05,Default,,0,0,0,,不要多事啦 赶快走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.13,0:31:58.13,Default,,0,0,0,,做个睁眼瞎 就一辈子没出息
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.34,0:31:59.63,Default,,0,0,0,,好啦好啦 回去睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.80,0:32:02.09,Default,,0,0,0,,又贴告示?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.18,0:32:04.10,Default,,0,0,0,,又一个蒙面飞贼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.72,0:32:07.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我看你嘴巴上蒙块布都可以去领赏了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.56,0:32:09.31,Default,,0,0,0,,你不要乱讲 要杀头的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.64,0:32:11.48,Default,,0,0,0,,哇 他们每个人都值五百两
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.69,0:32:12.98,Default,,0,0,0,,原来佛笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.77,0:32:14.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你别多事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.98,0:32:17.65,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯 这叉烧包好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.73,0:32:19.40,Default,,0,0,0,,人肉叉烧!  人肉叉烧包
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.15,0:32:22.36,Default,,0,0,0,,各位父老兄弟 街坊乡亲
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.57,0:32:24.70,Default,,0,0,0,,小弟今日来到贵宝地献丑了…
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.37,0:32:27.95,Default,,0,0,0,,那表演什么?铁锤打胸口啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.37,0:32:30.37,Default,,0,0,0,,不是 是人肉沙包
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.71,0:32:31.58,Default,,0,0,0,,吃的?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.79,0:32:34.58,Default,,0,0,0,,不是 一文钱任打一拳
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.88,0:32:36.71,Default,,0,0,0,,那有什么好处啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.92,0:32:39.88,Default,,0,0,0,,要是叫疼的话 那就赔三文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.21,0:32:42.17,Default,,0,0,0,,万一打到吐血怎么办?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.38,0:32:44.39,Default,,0,0,0,,吐血?那就赔六文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.55,0:32:45.80,Default,,0,0,0,,要是打死了呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.01,0:32:47.51,Default,,0,0,0,,要是打死…
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.35,0:32:50.43,Default,,0,0,0,,那就连命都赔给你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.27,0:32:56.56,Default,,0,0,0,,起码五十文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.06,0:32:58.94,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊 那就是足足五十拳
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.23,0:33:00.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你小心哪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.48,0:33:04.07,Default,,0,0,0,,打死你…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.74,0:33:07.37,Default,,0,0,0,,老板 可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.91,0:33:10.04,Default,,0,0,0,,我不信我还要再打 继续
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.54,0:33:13.62,Default,,0,0,0,,我打死你…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.46,0:33:19.34,Default,,0,0,0,,四十六、四十七、四十八、四…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.22,0:33:24.30,Default,,0,0,0,,是不真是很痛呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.55,0:33:26.43,Default,,0,0,0,,不装一下 他怎么会继续打呢?叫他继续
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.97,0:33:28.47,Default,,0,0,0,,老板老板…他撑不住啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.76,0:33:30.76,Default,,0,0,0,,快点 快起来 打他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.97,0:33:32.35,Default,,0,0,0,,不打他吐血怎么翻本呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.39,0:33:35.89,Default,,0,0,0,,家丁出来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.31,0:33:38.98,Default,,0,0,0,,我给钱 你们给我打死他们
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.65,0:33:44.07,Default,,0,0,0,,没费力气就赚这么多钱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.28,0:33:45.24,Default,,0,0,0,,不行 我要赚钱买房子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.45,0:33:46.82,Default,,0,0,0,,我什么都不想
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.03,0:33:48.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我只想好好大吃一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.53,0:33:49.53,Default,,0,0,0,,不只要买房子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.58,0:33:51.29,Default,,0,0,0,,我还要做老板
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.37,0:33:52.41,Default,,0,0,0,,干嘛?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.00,0:33:58.42,Default,,0,0,0,,把钱交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.67,0:34:00.50,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.67,0:34:04.01,Default,,0,0,0,,交税 个人所得税五十文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.21,0:34:06.34,Default,,0,0,0,,擅用官地税五十文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.43,0:34:08.26,Default,,0,0,0,,娱乐事业税五十文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.47,0:34:11.14,Default,,0,0,0,,一共一百五十文钱
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.22,0:34:13.22,Default,,0,0,0,,我不给
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.43,0:34:16.23,Default,,0,0,0,,抗拒交税?给我抓起来
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.60,0:34:18.85,Default,,0,0,0,,大人 我们身份卑微
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.19,0:34:21.69,Default,,0,0,0,,跟天斗 跟地斗 就是不敢跟官斗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.36,0:34:25.61,Default,,0,0,0,,这些钱 大人您收下
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.91,0:34:29.91,Default,,0,0,0,,算你识相
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.66,0:34:32.99,Default,,0,0,0,,大人 我们两兄弟初到贵宝地
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.45,0:34:34.91,Default,,0,0,0,,什么也不会 空有一身蛮力
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.12,0:34:36.66,Default,,0,0,0,,希望能够追随大人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.00,0:34:39.63,Default,,0,0,0,,满嘴油腔滑调 该打
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.04,0:34:43.13,Default,,0,0,0,,多谢大人赐打
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.89,0:34:52.43,Default,,0,0,0,,你可真会拍马屁
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.72,0:34:54.89,Default,,0,0,0,,刘公公要招兵买马
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.10,0:34:57.06,Default,,0,0,0,,好 你们跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.02,0:35:00.56,Default,,0,0,0,,多谢大人 君宝 我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.11,0:35:04.65,Default,,0,0,0,,你真的要走?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.28,0:35:09.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我不走
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.12,0:35:14.20,Default,,0,0,0,,等我做了大官 一定回来找你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.62,0:35:18.87,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你好好保重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.13,0:35:24.63,Default,,0,0,0,,希望你洁身自爱
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.80,0:35:34.85,Default,,0,0,0,,干嘛 喝多了伤身子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.47,0:35:36.47,Default,,0,0,0,,小冬瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.39,0:35:39.89,Default,,0,0,0,,有些事你想忘掉就越忘不掉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.31,0:35:42.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你不会明白的 还是一醉解千愁
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.95,0:35:50.86,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.66,0:35:54.32,Default,,0,0,0,,你看看我的遭遇 还想找男人呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.53,0:35:55.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我又没说喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.37,0:35:58.91,Default,,0,0,0,,不打自招 喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.54,0:36:02.50,Default,,0,0,0,,喝这么多 你当是茶?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.54,0:36:04.38,Default,,0,0,0,,就是茶也没人这样喝法的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.75,0:36:06.29,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 别再喝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.84,0:36:09.67,Default,,0,0,0,,碎了 没得喝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.71,0:36:12.59,Default,,0,0,0,,小伙子 人生失意须尽欢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.84,0:36:15.14,Default,,0,0,0,,难得糊涂呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.39,0:36:17.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你喝你的 少啰嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.72,0:36:20.89,Default,,0,0,0,,哇 你又乱来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.89,0:36:24.35,Default,,0,0,0,,好啦 不要再喝了好不好 不关你的事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.27,0:36:26.31,Default,,0,0,0,,喂?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.61,0:36:28.61,Default,,0,0,0,,打累了就会停手的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.07,0:36:32.40,Default,,0,0,0,,这里还有
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.99,0:36:34.28,Default,,0,0,0,,也不知道帮谁好
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.87,0:36:36.87,Default,,0,0,0,,放手 别再喝了  这条命是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.95,0:36:38.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我爱怎么喝就怎么喝
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.24,0:36:41.04,Default,,0,0,0,,打啊…继续打啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.46,0:36:44.00,Default,,0,0,0,,全部打烂就没得喝了 我帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.71,0:36:50.80,Default,,0,0,0,,你冷静一点好不好?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.01,0:36:53.09,Default,,0,0,0,,张君宝 
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.02,0:37:05.40,Default,,0,0,0,,你冷静一点
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.40,0:37:07.86,Default,,0,0,0,,过去只是人生经历
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.06,0:37:09.65,Default,,0,0,0,,而不是一种负担
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.02,0:37:10.86,Default,,0,0,0,,你再这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.94,0:37:12.82,Default,,0,0,0,,受伤害的是你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.51,0:37:37.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你干嘛每天玩那个球啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.47,0:37:41.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我在悟道啊 道家的道理是圆的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.60,0:37:44.10,Default,,0,0,0,,太阳是圆的 月亮也是圆的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.31,0:37:47.06,Default,,0,0,0,,所以做人也要圆滑一点才好
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.61,0:37:50.90,Default,,0,0,0,,谁是老板?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.69,0:37:52.94,Default,,0,0,0,,快滚出来
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.07,0:37:57.45,Default,,0,0,0,,税吏大人 这么早呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.53,0:37:58.57,Default,,0,0,0,,又来收税呀
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.82,0:38:00.07,Default,,0,0,0,,进来坐会儿 吃点东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.16,0:38:01.87,Default,,0,0,0,,废话 快交税
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.16,0:38:03.83,Default,,0,0,0,,前几天我们已经交过啦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.12,0:38:06.50,Default,,0,0,0,,前几天你也吃饭了 今天还要吃啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.87,0:38:08.33,Default,,0,0,0,,现在刘公公扩充军备
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.67,0:38:11.42,Default,,0,0,0,,要征收军人服装税 出入平安税
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.75,0:38:14.46,Default,,0,0,0,,安居乐业税 佛笑楼要交五百两
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.67,0:38:16.22,Default,,0,0,0,,那你干脆用抢的好了?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.51,0:38:19.01,Default,,0,0,0,,你是不是在搞反朝廷活动?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.09,0:38:20.34,Default,,0,0,0,,朝廷也要讲道理唉
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.18,0:38:25.81,Default,,0,0,0,,小不忍 则乱大谋呀
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.06,0:38:30.10,Default,,0,0,0,,谁身上有刀谁就能大声说话
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.11,0:38:34.53,Default,,0,0,0,,吃下去
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.69,0:38:37.65,Default,,0,0,0,,忍一下
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.86,0:38:39.95,Default,,0,0,0,,不吃我就封店抓人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.50,0:38:51.54,Default,,0,0,0,,不好呀 这里出事会连累很多弟兄的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.96,0:38:54.63,Default,,0,0,0,,如果没钱?没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.00,0:38:56.92,Default,,0,0,0,,只要跪下给我磕三十个响头
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.17,0:38:59.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我可以考虑过几天收你的税
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.05,0:39:01.84,Default,,0,0,0,,磕头啊 磕不磕?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.89,0:39:05.97,Default,,0,0,0,,跪下
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.47,0:39:07.56,Default,,0,0,0,,跪下呀
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.31,0:39:12.73,Default,,0,0,0,,你再不跪就是反抗朝廷
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.11,0:39:14.65,Default,,0,0,0,,我把你拉去斩首示众
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.23,0:39:16.65,Default,,0,0,0,,太过份了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.37,0:39:25.87,Default,,0,0,0,,你要造反 我把你们全部都杀光
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.25,0:39:29.37,Default,,0,0,0,,去死
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.54,0:39:34.38,Default,,0,0,0,,把门关上 一个都别让他们跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.32,0:40:46.24,Default,,0,0,0,,罪过 怎么杀这么多人呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.78,0:40:50.20,Default,,0,0,0,,打铁的 你去把这些尸首处理掉
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.38,0:41:00.34,Default,,0,0,0,,快把他抓回来 让他跑了我们就死定啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.67,0:41:05.43,Default,,0,0,0,,对了 怎么叫你倒着走?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.30,0:41:07.22,Default,,0,0,0,,你吃草 我吃斋
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.43,0:41:08.89,Default,,0,0,0,,大家也算同道 帮我一次忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.31,0:41:16.94,Default,,0,0,0,,糟啦 快到军营啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.19,0:41:18.81,Default,,0,0,0,,马大哥 你行行好 快点追嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.06,0:41:20.94,Default,,0,0,0,,追不到的话 佛笑楼就惨啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.99,0:41:24.07,Default,,0,0,0,,什么事呀?税吏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.44,0:41:25.74,Default,,0,0,0,,佛笑楼那批人想要造反
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.95,0:41:27.03,Default,,0,0,0,,我现在去禀告刘公公
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.61,0:41:30.12,Default,,0,0,0,,快帮我拦住他 遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.29,0:41:36.71,Default,,0,0,0,,我帮你把他杀啦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.38,0:41:41.38,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.59,0:41:42.80,Default,,0,0,0,,佛笑楼都不是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.01,0:41:44.38,Default,,0,0,0,,你最好不要跟他们在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.59,0:41:45.97,Default,,0,0,0,,我觉得他们很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.55,0:41:48.55,Default,,0,0,0,,我是兵 你是贼 早晚会碰头的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.93,0:41:49.80,Default,,0,0,0,,诶
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.18,0:41:51.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你在军营的生活怎么样呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.68,0:41:53.39,Default,,0,0,0,,有没有人欺负你啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.89,0:41:58.31,Default,,0,0,0,,从小到大 只有我欺负人 谁敢欺负我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.81,0:41:59.69,Default,,0,0,0,,你呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.90,0:42:02.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我?还是喜欢小时候的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.40,0:42:03.82,Default,,0,0,0,,每天无忧无虑
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.03,0:42:06.78,Default,,0,0,0,,有个豆沙包吃 我就很开心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.57,0:42:10.20,Default,,0,0,0,,我就不一样 我喜欢现在的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.37,0:42:11.91,Default,,0,0,0,,可以认识这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.28,0:42:16.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道自己需要什么 总有一天我一定要得到
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.63,0:42:25.96,Default,,0,0,0,,这匹马要怎么骑才跑得快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.38,0:42:27.30,Default,,0,0,0,,那还不简单
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.54,0:43:04.71,Default,,0,0,0,,这次我们教场比武的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.92,0:43:06.59,Default,,0,0,0,,就是要从八个副刀统当中
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.88,0:43:09.63,Default,,0,0,0,,选出一个武功最好的来做正刀统
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.88,0:43:12.43,Default,,0,0,0,,现在比武开始
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.86,0:43:33.28,Default,,0,0,0,,公公 这次赢得太容易啦 所以我要求
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.57,0:43:35.20,Default,,0,0,0,,如果有谁不服气可以上来向我挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.49,0:43:39.83,Default,,0,0,0,,公公 小人董天宝 敢请刀统能成全
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.96,0:43:43.04,Default,,0,0,0,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.64,0:43:56.76,Default,,0,0,0,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.28,0:44:13.86,Default,,0,0,0,,心狠手辣
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.32,0:44:15.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我会警告他
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.00,0:44:31.01,Default,,0,0,0,,公公
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.05,0:44:33.34,Default,,0,0,0,,解散
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.85,0:44:47.23,Default,,0,0,0,,以下犯上 你懂不懂怎么当兵的?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.61,0:44:49.52,Default,,0,0,0,,你这样叫我怎么提拔你
Dialogue: 0,0:44:49.90,0:44:51.82,Default,,0,0,0,,你知不知道犯了众怒
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.11,0:44:54.11,Default,,0,0,0,,在军营里是很难立足的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.40,0:44:56.07,Default,,0,0,0,,还好公公不计较
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.74,0:45:00.33,Default,,0,0,0,,公公…
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.49,0:45:01.99,Default,,0,0,0,,是我太急躁
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.29,0:45:03.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我不甘心只当个小兵
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.75,0:45:06.17,Default,,0,0,0,,请再给我一次机会 我一定好好表现的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.50,0:45:10.42,Default,,0,0,0,,那我就等着看你有什么好表现
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.84,0:45:20.22,Default,,0,0,0,,秋雪姐姐 你以后你可以在这里当酒保呀
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.47,0:45:23.14,Default,,0,0,0,,好呀 有酒喝 不过我不会再发酒疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.10,0:45:26.69,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝呢 我看可以当伙记
Dialogue: 0,0:45:26.94,0:45:27.73,Default,,0,0,0,,可以呀
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.27,0:45:29.61,Default,,0,0,0,,那洗茅房你干不干呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.81,0:45:30.61,Default,,0,0,0,,好 没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.82,0:45:32.28,Default,,0,0,0,,帮我洗内衣内裤好不好呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.48,0:45:33.40,Default,,0,0,0,,好…
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.61,0:45:35.65,Default,,0,0,0,,臭道士 内衣裤都懒得洗啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.53,0:45:39.45,Default,,0,0,0,,笑什么 有什么好笑的?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.03,0:45:42.79,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.04,0:45:44.12,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎么回来啦?
Dialogue: 0,0:45:44.29,0:45:45.91,Default,,0,0,0,,不要说那么多 快点走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.58,0:45:48.12,Default,,0,0,0,,上次你们偷刘公公的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.46,0:45:50.17,Default,,0,0,0,,还有杀税吏的事 已经泄漏啦
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.46,0:45:52.84,Default,,0,0,0,,刘公公带着人马 马上就要来杀你们
Dialogue: 0,0:45:53.80,0:45:54.80,Default,,0,0,0,,那我们快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:55.01,0:45:56.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你们走先 我进去把证据烧了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.67,0:45:58.30,Default,,0,0,0,,你小心呀 快走 走了…
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.81,0:46:09.69,Default,,0,0,0,,进去抓人 是
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.27,0:46:11.56,Default,,0,0,0,,老板呀
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.23,0:46:14.78,Default,,0,0,0,,是不是你杀了我的税吏?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:15.11,0:46:17.45,Default,,0,0,0,,阉贼 你欺凌百姓 想杀就杀
Dialogue: 0,0:46:24.33,0:46:26.04,Default,,0,0,0,,老板 你安息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.12,0:46:30.25,Default,,0,0,0,,上天之后一定要保佑我们
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.58,0:46:33.04,Default,,0,0,0,,岂有此理 老板的血绝不能白流
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.29,0:46:34.30,Default,,0,0,0,,明天我就单枪匹马
Dialogue: 0,0:46:34.50,0:46:36.84,Default,,0,0,0,,冲进刘公公的军营 把他碎尸万段
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.17,0:46:39.51,Default,,0,0,0,,你没计划怎么能做成大事呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:39.84,0:46:41.18,Default,,0,0,0,,上次没有计划也杀了很多人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.43,0:46:44.56,Default,,0,0,0,,这次我们人单势孤 怎么跟那十万大军斗?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:45.14,0:46:46.14,Default,,0,0,0,,常听你们说
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.47,0:46:48.68,Default,,0,0,0,,有些志同道合之士也反对刘公公
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.10,0:46:51.10,Default,,0,0,0,,可不可以想办法联络他们呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.60,0:46:52.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我打头阵
Dialogue: 0,0:46:53.56,0:46:55.44,Default,,0,0,0,,好 我来做内应
Dialogue: 0,0:46:55.77,0:46:57.65,Default,,0,0,0,,过两天 大部分的军队都过河操练
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.86,0:46:59.40,Default,,0,0,0,,这是杀刘公公的最好机会
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.65,0:47:00.65,Default,,0,0,0,,在这段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.70,0:47:02.45,Default,,0,0,0,,你们去联络所有反对刘公公的志士
Dialogue: 0,0:47:02.66,0:47:03.37,Default,,0,0,0,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.62,0:47:05.70,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯 我们里应外合 杀他个措手不及
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.95,0:47:07.79,Default,,0,0,0,,对 大家分头去准备
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.12,0:47:10.87,Default,,0,0,0,,是 天宝 小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.73,0:47:31.60,Default,,0,0,0,,过去
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.15,0:47:43.28,Default,,0,0,0,,谁啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.83,0:47:50.58,Default,,0,0,0,,是我 刚刚撒完尿 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:51.25,0:47:53.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我们也尿急 一块尿吧 好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:47:57.38,0:47:59.17,Default,,0,0,0,,好紧张呀 我也想尿尿
Dialogue: 0,0:48:01.55,0:48:03.13,Default,,0,0,0,,正事要紧…
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.14,0:48:06.43,Default,,0,0,0,,刘公公呢?  在那面
Dialogue: 0,0:48:33.96,0:48:36.38,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么会这样?  天宝呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:37.96,0:48:39.00,Default,,0,0,0,,杀
Dialogue: 0,0:48:39.34,0:48:41.13,Default,,0,0,0,,冲呀
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.23,0:49:03.61,Default,,0,0,0,,来呀 杀一个够本 杀两个有赚
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.74,0:49:05.70,Default,,0,0,0,,杀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.86,0:49:08.24,Default,,0,0,0,,打铁佬 我杀了五个 我赚到了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.37,0:49:14.00,Default,,0,0,0,,我死得好惨呀
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.83,0:49:15.79,Default,,0,0,0,,保留实力
Dialogue: 0,0:49:16.75,0:49:18.21,Default,,0,0,0,,生即是死 死即是生
Dialogue: 0,0:50:16.27,0:50:17.98,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 你出卖我们?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.07,0:50:33.28,Default,,0,0,0,,让我多赚一点
Dialogue: 0,0:50:55.05,0:50:56.14,Default,,0,0,0,,打铁的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:57.77,0:50:59.14,Default,,0,0,0,,是谁出卖我们?
Dialogue: 0,0:50:59.39,0:51:00.81,Default,,0,0,0,,打铁的 撑着点
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.53,0:51:09.99,Default,,0,0,0,,是谁出卖我们?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:18.58,0:51:21.21,Default,,0,0,0,,是谁出卖我们?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.13,0:52:15.47,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝?
Dialogue: 0,0:52:23.68,0:52:24.44,Default,,0,0,0,,走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:30.65,0:52:31.78,Default,,0,0,0,,秋雪
Dialogue: 0,0:52:32.28,0:52:33.57,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.34,0:52:56.38,Default,,0,0,0,,我还以为他们有三头六臂
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.59,0:52:58.51,Default,,0,0,0,,谁知道是螳臂挡车
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.72,0:53:01.81,Default,,0,0,0,,不过你这招抛砖引玉让他们自投罗网
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.10,0:53:04.23,Default,,0,0,0,,的确省了我不少工夫
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.23,0:53:07.77,Default,,0,0,0,,愿为公公效命
Dialogue: 0,0:53:08.19,0:53:09.56,Default,,0,0,0,,朋友你都可以出卖
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.77,0:53:12.53,Default,,0,0,0,,谁知道日后会不会出卖我呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.86,0:53:14.61,Default,,0,0,0,,公公是我的前途跟希望
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.86,0:53:16.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我怎么会自毁前程呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:18.03,0:53:20.82,Default,,0,0,0,,天宝 上次你打赢了刀统
Dialogue: 0,0:53:21.03,0:53:22.45,Default,,0,0,0,,本来应该升你的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.66,0:53:25.08,Default,,0,0,0,,但是你只是一个小兵 没立过功
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.29,0:53:27.33,Default,,0,0,0,,升你恐怕难以服众
Dialogue: 0,0:53:27.75,0:53:29.04,Default,,0,0,0,,不过从现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:53:29.25,0:53:31.42,Default,,0,0,0,,你就是锦衣卫镇抚使
Dialogue: 0,0:53:31.79,0:53:32.88,Default,,0,0,0,,多谢公公
Dialogue: 0,0:53:36.88,0:53:39.39,Default,,0,0,0,,刚刚逃走的那个功夫也挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.68,0:53:41.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我们正在用人之际
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.72,0:53:43.81,Default,,0,0,0,,如果可以招降就给我招降
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.01,0:53:45.47,Default,,0,0,0,,为朝廷出力
Dialogue: 0,0:53:45.52,0:53:47.43,Default,,0,0,0,,否则 就格杀勿论
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.94,0:53:58.49,Default,,0,0,0,,快点起来 我背你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.70,0:53:59.91,Default,,0,0,0,,你不要再出卖我们
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.20,0:54:01.66,Default,,0,0,0,,让他们都白白牺牲了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:02.07,0:54:03.16,Default,,0,0,0,,找你的好兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.37,0:54:05.16,Default,,0,0,0,,享荣华富贵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.37,0:54:07.29,Default,,0,0,0,,可怜那些兄弟死得好惨
Dialogue: 0,0:54:07.87,0:54:10.37,Default,,0,0,0,,你还在这喝酒?我打死你
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.79,0:54:12.29,Default,,0,0,0,,不要这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:12.92,0:54:15.17,Default,,0,0,0,,其实他是我们当中最惨的一个
Dialogue: 0,0:54:15.46,0:54:17.55,Default,,0,0,0,,他最信任的兄弟出卖了他
Dialogue: 0,0:54:17.76,0:54:19.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我们不应该怪他呀
Dialogue: 0,0:54:20.18,0:54:21.76,Default,,0,0,0,,如果不是你也不会弄成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.84,0:54:23.97,Default,,0,0,0,,你要负全责 我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:54:24.64,0:54:26.01,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.14,0:54:30.27,Default,,0,0,0,,好 我一个人把她救出来
Dialogue: 0,0:55:00.30,0:55:01.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道你会生气
Dialogue: 0,0:55:02.43,0:55:03.97,Default,,0,0,0,,但是我无非是想救你
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.89,0:55:06.30,Default,,0,0,0,,佛笑楼的人全部都是叛党
Dialogue: 0,0:55:06.56,0:55:08.02,Default,,0,0,0,,早晚要死
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.43,0:55:09.89,Default,,0,0,0,,反正现在最重要的就是
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.10,0:55:11.73,Default,,0,0,0,,你跟我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:55:39.38,0:55:42.01,Default,,0,0,0,,我看得起你是因为你也心狠手辣
Dialogue: 0,0:55:42.84,0:55:45.72,Default,,0,0,0,,没想到连个臭女人都摆不平
Dialogue: 0,0:55:46.30,0:55:48.85,Default,,0,0,0,,公公 内人一时冲动 请公公原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.81,0:55:51.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我杀了你这个淫贼
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.64,0:55:54.02,Default,,0,0,0,,董天宝 你出卖我们 你去死呀
Dialogue: 0,0:55:55.27,0:55:57.52,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎么可以收留一个叛党在军营里?
Dialogue: 0,0:55:57.94,0:55:59.57,Default,,0,0,0,,你这个镇抚使是怎么干的?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.41,0:56:09.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我之所以会成功 就是因为不需要这些臭女人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:09.45,0:56:11.33,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我没叫你杀了她
Dialogue: 0,0:56:12.00,0:56:13.08,Default,,0,0,0,,公公不喜欢女人
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.25,0:56:15.04,Default,,0,0,0,,我怎么可以为了女人耽误大事?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.25,0:56:17.63,Default,,0,0,0,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:56:17.88,0:56:19.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我有事跟你商量
Dialogue: 0,0:56:20.05,0:56:21.25,Default,,0,0,0,,是公公
Dialogue: 0,0:56:51.28,0:56:53.66,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 富贵之门已经打开
Dialogue: 0,0:56:54.50,0:56:56.25,Default,,0,0,0,,等你走进来
Dialogue: 0,0:56:56.50,0:56:58.50,Default,,0,0,0,,这种富贵我不要 放了她
Dialogue: 0,0:56:58.63,0:57:00.50,Default,,0,0,0,,你忘记了 这二十几年了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:00.79,0:57:03.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我们一直都是有福同享 有难同当的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.34,0:57:04.34,Default,,0,0,0,,难得有刘公公赏识
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.59,0:57:06.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我们会有很多机会
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.42,0:57:09.72,Default,,0,0,0,,一起打天下 做一番大事业
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.93,0:57:11.89,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经不认识那个出卖自己兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:57:12.18,0:57:14.85,Default,,0,0,0,,用人命来换取自己荣华富贵的天宝
Dialogue: 0,0:57:15.18,0:57:16.39,Default,,0,0,0,,嘴硬是没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.85,0:57:18.65,Default,,0,0,0,,看着那些叛党怎么死就知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.48,0:57:21.06,Default,,0,0,0,,他们会死是因为我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.31,0:57:23.15,Default,,0,0,0,,现在我要负起全部责任
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.23,0:57:25.03,Default,,0,0,0,,谁要是敢挡我的富贵
Dialogue: 0,0:57:25.82,0:57:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我就一定要他死
Dialogue: 0,0:57:27.65,0:57:28.86,Default,,0,0,0,,上 是
Dialogue: 0,0:58:51.03,0:58:52.53,Default,,0,0,0,,我再问你一次
Dialogue: 0,0:58:52.74,0:58:54.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你肯不肯跟我一起打天下?
Dialogue: 0,0:58:54.49,0:58:56.24,Default,,0,0,0,,我孤家寡人一个 没有什么好利用
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.01,0:59:18.56,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你不要再逼我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:19.39,0:59:20.93,Default,,0,0,0,,是你自己逼我们兄弟相残的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:21.52,0:59:22.98,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你打不过我的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:23.52,0:59:25.06,Default,,0,0,0,,为了死去的兄弟我一定要打
Dialogue: 0,0:59:25.48,0:59:28.19,Default,,0,0,0,,小冬瓜我都杀了 再少个兄弟又算得了什么
Dialogue: 0,1:00:38.51,1:00:40.89,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 看剑
Dialogue: 0,1:00:47.60,1:00:50.98,Default,,0,0,0,,先发制人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:08.96,1:01:10.25,Default,,0,0,0,,千斤坠
Dialogue: 0,1:01:27.23,1:01:28.31,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝
Dialogue: 0,1:01:52.63,1:01:54.75,Default,,0,0,0,,涂在他的伤口上 药效很强
Dialogue: 0,1:01:56.38,1:01:57.84,Default,,0,0,0,,忍耐一下 会很痛
Dialogue: 0,1:02:01.43,1:02:03.14,Default,,0,0,0,,他怎么一点反应也没有啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:02:05.60,1:02:06.77,Default,,0,0,0,,看着啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:14.61,1:02:15.82,Default,,0,0,0,,真的没反应诶
Dialogue: 0,1:02:18.65,1:02:19.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你很痛吧?
Dialogue: 0,1:02:20.11,1:02:21.57,Default,,0,0,0,,痛呀
Dialogue: 0,1:02:22.07,1:02:23.20,Default,,0,0,0,,忍耐点啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:25.53,1:02:27.54,Default,,0,0,0,,凌道长 你看他到底怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,1:02:27.87,1:02:29.70,Default,,0,0,0,,可能是受了太大的打击
Dialogue: 0,1:02:30.00,1:02:31.96,Default,,0,0,0,,连他最信任的兄弟都出卖了他
Dialogue: 0,1:02:32.21,1:02:33.67,Default,,0,0,0,,害死那么多人
Dialogue: 0,1:02:33.96,1:02:36.21,Default,,0,0,0,,所以才行为反常啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:36.59,1:02:38.00,Default,,0,0,0,,那他到底会不会好啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:02:38.21,1:02:40.05,Default,,0,0,0,,过两、三天可能会好吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:40.51,1:02:41.80,Default,,0,0,0,,阁下果然高人
Dialogue: 0,1:02:42.09,1:02:44.01,Default,,0,0,0,,知道我错信了天宝
Dialogue: 0,1:02:44.39,1:02:46.05,Default,,0,0,0,,又摇头 又叹气
Dialogue: 0,1:02:46.89,1:02:48.81,Default,,0,0,0,,佩服…
Dialogue: 0,1:02:48.97,1:02:51.43,Default,,0,0,0,,只怕再过两、三年也不见得会好啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:51.89,1:02:53.23,Default,,0,0,0,,佩服…
Dialogue: 0,1:03:09.54,1:03:10.75,Default,,0,0,0,,不是我出卖你们的 不是我出卖你们的
Dialogue: 0,1:03:10.95,1:03:12.71,Default,,0,0,0,,你没事了 只是做梦
Dialogue: 0,1:03:14.92,1:03:17.63,Default,,0,0,0,,不是 是真的…
Dialogue: 0,1:03:22.09,1:03:23.26,Default,,0,0,0,,他们全都坐在这啊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:23.47,1:03:24.93,Default,,0,0,0,,老板 打铁的…
Dialogue: 0,1:03:25.14,1:03:26.59,Default,,0,0,0,,喝点酒压压惊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:28.05,1:03:29.39,Default,,0,0,0,,压惊的?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:37.27,1:03:39.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道我吓着你们了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:41.15,1:03:44.03,Default,,0,0,0,,可是我也没有办法控制我自己
Dialogue: 0,1:03:45.95,1:03:49.28,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起…
Dialogue: 0,1:03:54.21,1:03:56.25,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 凌道长 行不行啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:03:56.79,1:03:57.96,Default,,0,0,0,,姑且试一试吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:59.96,1:04:02.30,Default,,0,0,0,,你引他说话 让我好下手啊
Dialogue: 0,1:04:03.97,1:04:05.05,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝
Dialogue: 0,1:04:06.88,1:04:08.76,Default,,0,0,0,,高人 高人?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:09.76,1:04:10.89,Default,,0,0,0,,死了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:14.48,1:04:17.19,Default,,0,0,0,,扎一下对你有好处的 是呀 有好处的
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.56,1:04:18.81,Default,,0,0,0,,好处我不要了 给你们吧
Dialogue: 0,1:04:19.02,1:04:23.36,Default,,0,0,0,,别扎我呀…
Dialogue: 0,1:04:29.45,1:04:31.16,Default,,0,0,0,,扎了几针 干嘛哭成这样啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:04:31.58,1:04:33.75,Default,,0,0,0,,我被他扎中哭穴了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:34.41,1:04:35.96,Default,,0,0,0,,你也被他扎中了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:38.62,1:04:40.71,Default,,0,0,0,,你被他扎中笑穴了
Dialogue: 0,1:05:05.36,1:05:06.65,Default,,0,0,0,,全部都是废物
Dialogue: 0,1:05:07.61,1:05:09.86,Default,,0,0,0,,何琨 你以前是怎么练兵的?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:10.32,1:05:11.91,Default,,0,0,0,,简直就是废物练废物
Dialogue: 0,1:05:12.28,1:05:14.37,Default,,0,0,0,,镇抚使 你又何必要侮辱我呢?
Dialogue: 0,1:05:14.66,1:05:15.95,Default,,0,0,0,,你这样的练兵方法
Dialogue: 0,1:05:16.20,1:05:18.62,Default,,0,0,0,,必有死伤 军心难服
Dialogue: 0,1:05:18.83,1:05:21.88,Default,,0,0,0,,适者生存 挺不住的死不足惜
Dialogue: 0,1:05:23.00,1:05:24.42,Default,,0,0,0,,包括你在内
Dialogue: 0,1:05:25.09,1:05:27.51,Default,,0,0,0,,董天宝 虽然兵权在你手上
Dialogue: 0,1:05:27.84,1:05:30.97,Default,,0,0,0,,可是你不要忘了是我一手提拔你的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:31.22,1:05:32.39,Default,,0,0,0,,军法不容情
Dialogue: 0,1:05:32.80,1:05:35.26,Default,,0,0,0,,何琨 现在不是套交情的时候
Dialogue: 0,1:05:35.35,1:05:38.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我认为不宜再练 我要去见刘公公
Dialogue: 0,1:05:49.11,1:05:50.53,Default,,0,0,0,,违抗军令者死
Dialogue: 0,1:05:51.66,1:05:52.66,Default,,0,0,0,,继续练
Dialogue: 0,1:05:56.58,1:06:00.08,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝…
Dialogue: 0,1:06:01.25,1:06:02.12,Default,,0,0,0,,他上哪去呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:02.29,1:06:03.96,Default,,0,0,0,,怪啦 难道会隐形啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:05.67,1:06:06.88,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝…
Dialogue: 0,1:06:12.13,1:06:14.39,Default,,0,0,0,,冷静…
Dialogue: 0,1:06:14.80,1:06:17.10,Default,,0,0,0,,冷什么静啊 看你脸色发青啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:17.31,1:06:19.06,Default,,0,0,0,,当心你的伤口又裂了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:20.06,1:06:21.56,Default,,0,0,0,,我的口没裂啊
Dialogue: 0,1:06:23.52,1:06:24.56,Default,,0,0,0,,你们也冷静一下吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:31.32,1:06:32.78,Default,,0,0,0,,出来
Dialogue: 0,1:06:35.16,1:06:36.58,Default,,0,0,0,,好痛呀
Dialogue: 0,1:06:36.95,1:06:38.33,Default,,0,0,0,,会痛 就是好啦?
Dialogue: 0,1:06:39.12,1:06:40.04,Default,,0,0,0,,师父
Dialogue: 0,1:06:41.66,1:06:43.25,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 我好怕呀
Dialogue: 0,1:06:43.46,1:06:45.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我不想练武功 我不想打人
Dialogue: 0,1:06:45.67,1:06:47.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我想吃豆沙包
Dialogue: 0,1:06:49.63,1:06:52.84,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 你瘦了 也高了
Dialogue: 0,1:06:53.43,1:06:56.10,Default,,0,0,0,,添了皱纹 不过还是英明神武
Dialogue: 0,1:06:56.60,1:06:57.76,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝…
Dialogue: 0,1:06:57.97,1:07:00.35,Default,,0,0,0,,师父 我怕...
Dialogue: 0,1:07:00.60,1:07:02.35,Default,,0,0,0,,别打我呀…
Dialogue: 0,1:07:06.65,1:07:07.86,Default,,0,0,0,,不要踢我
Dialogue: 0,1:07:20.79,1:07:22.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,1:07:22.37,1:07:24.92,Default,,0,0,0,,没…事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:26.54,1:07:28.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这样还说没事呀?  没事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:29.84,1:07:31.55,Default,,0,0,0,,看他的样子需要好好休息啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:36.51,1:07:39.81,Default,,0,0,0,,嘛呢嘛呢吽 快点睡觉
Dialogue: 0,1:07:40.22,1:07:42.93,Default,,0,0,0,,嘛呢嘛呢吽 快点睡觉
Dialogue: 0,1:07:46.10,1:07:47.81,Default,,0,0,0,,这张被被子太小不够盖哦
Dialogue: 0,1:07:48.19,1:07:49.15,Default,,0,0,0,,行不行啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:07:49.36,1:07:51.23,Default,,0,0,0,,其他不敢说啊 这次如果搞不定的话
Dialogue: 0,1:07:51.40,1:07:52.65,Default,,0,0,0,,我就自打十下耳光
Dialogue: 0,1:07:56.15,1:07:59.03,Default,,0,0,0,,好好休息 你一定会好的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:08.38,1:08:09.79,Default,,0,0,0,,哎呀 惨了…
Dialogue: 0,1:08:10.34,1:08:14.97,Default,,0,0,0,,该打…
Dialogue: 0,1:08:15.17,1:08:17.22,Default,,0,0,0,,你曾经帮我恢复信心 我也一定会帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:08:17.30,1:08:19.55,Default,,0,0,0,,再打四下…
Dialogue: 0,1:08:33.61,1:08:35.11,Default,,0,0,0,,大家不要辜负了镇抚使大人
Dialogue: 0,1:08:35.32,1:08:36.95,Default,,0,0,0,,对我们的期望 是
Dialogue: 0,1:08:37.32,1:08:38.49,Default,,0,0,0,,如果谁操练不力
Dialogue: 0,1:08:39.57,1:08:41.07,Default,,0,0,0,,就军法处置
Dialogue: 0,1:08:41.70,1:08:44.37,Default,,0,0,0,,众将士 听命 是
Dialogue: 0,1:08:45.41,1:08:46.71,Default,,0,0,0,,要练上乘武功
Dialogue: 0,1:08:47.12,1:08:49.75,Default,,0,0,0,,必须将身体练到如钢如铁
Dialogue: 0,1:09:03.64,1:09:05.18,Default,,0,0,0,,不要停 继续操练
Dialogue: 0,1:09:06.98,1:09:09.60,Default,,0,0,0,,张君宝 你害死好多人
Dialogue: 0,1:09:10.44,1:09:12.15,Default,,0,0,0,,该死 该死
Dialogue: 0,1:09:12.44,1:09:13.90,Default,,0,0,0,,打死你 打死你…
Dialogue: 0,1:09:14.19,1:09:16.44,Default,,0,0,0,,打死你呀…打死你
Dialogue: 0,1:09:17.99,1:09:20.61,Default,,0,0,0,,你要我的命啊 怎么大清早就发一次疯
Dialogue: 0,1:09:21.53,1:09:22.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你们懂不懂呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:09:23.58,1:09:26.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你懂啊?可是我听不懂你说什么
Dialogue: 0,1:09:30.17,1:09:31.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我懂啦
Dialogue: 0,1:09:32.04,1:09:33.63,Default,,0,0,0,,到了中午又发一次疯啊
Dialogue: 0,1:09:34.79,1:09:36.34,Default,,0,0,0,,黄昏还有第三次呢
Dialogue: 0,1:09:36.67,1:09:39.26,Default,,0,0,0,,一天疯疯癫癫的三次
Dialogue: 0,1:09:39.51,1:09:42.51,Default,,0,0,0,,不要叫君宝了 干脆叫三疯吧
Dialogue: 0,1:09:48.22,1:09:49.85,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 吃饭啦
Dialogue: 0,1:09:50.10,1:09:51.73,Default,,0,0,0,,你已经三天没吃饭了
Dialogue: 0,1:09:52.23,1:09:55.19,Default,,0,0,0,,饭是吃的 不是拿来闻的 三疯
Dialogue: 0,1:10:15.84,1:10:17.13,Default,,0,0,0,,吃呀
Dialogue: 0,1:10:22.18,1:10:24.22,Default,,0,0,0,,他还真准时呀 三疯
Dialogue: 0,1:10:33.60,1:10:34.73,Default,,0,0,0,,参见刘公公
Dialogue: 0,1:10:34.98,1:10:36.48,Default,,0,0,0,,这是我抓回来的叛党
Dialogue: 0,1:10:36.69,1:10:38.11,Default,,0,0,0,,另外还有征来的税
Dialogue: 0,1:10:40.65,1:10:43.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我要做的事都被你做完了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:44.11,1:10:46.28,Default,,0,0,0,,向公公学习 一辈子都学不完
Dialogue: 0,1:10:46.53,1:10:48.95,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是尽量让公公高枕无忧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:49.24,1:10:52.91,Default,,0,0,0,,现在各村各省都有大规模的民变
Dialogue: 0,1:10:53.58,1:10:55.12,Default,,0,0,0,,就我这没有
Dialogue: 0,1:10:55.58,1:10:57.63,Default,,0,0,0,,而且税收又丰富
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.92,1:11:01.59,Default,,0,0,0,,所以皇上要召我入京汇报佳绩
Dialogue: 0,1:11:03.47,1:11:05.01,Default,,0,0,0,,都是因为公公对属下关心
Dialogue: 0,1:11:05.26,1:11:07.43,Default,,0,0,0,,所以属下们都以死相报
Dialogue: 0,1:11:07.64,1:11:10.10,Default,,0,0,0,,满朝百官都应该效法
Dialogue: 0,1:11:10.47,1:11:13.68,Default,,0,0,0,,干脆你一起跟我入京 你跟他们说
Dialogue: 0,1:11:15.31,1:11:16.35,Default,,0,0,0,,多谢公公
Dialogue: 0,1:11:16.77,1:11:18.31,Default,,0,0,0,,不过入京之前
Dialogue: 0,1:11:18.69,1:11:21.53,Default,,0,0,0,,我不想再听到还有叛党滋事
Dialogue: 0,1:11:21.73,1:11:24.11,Default,,0,0,0,,或是有人对朝廷不满
Dialogue: 0,1:11:24.82,1:11:26.07,Default,,0,0,0,,是 公公
Dialogue: 0,1:11:31.79,1:11:35.37,Default,,0,0,0,,祝镇抚使大人入京面圣顺利
Dialogue: 0,1:11:51.81,1:11:53.43,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 这水很脏 不能喝
Dialogue: 0,1:11:53.64,1:11:54.73,Default,,0,0,0,,要喝喝这个
Dialogue: 0,1:11:55.81,1:11:56.85,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你啊
Dialogue: 0,1:11:57.23,1:11:59.27,Default,,0,0,0,,手好脏啊 刚好可以洗洗手
Dialogue: 0,1:12:00.82,1:12:01.73,Default,,0,0,0,,洗干净啦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:01.90,1:12:03.82,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 我跟你说很脏不能喝的嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:12:04.94,1:12:06.45,Default,,0,0,0,,你说我很脏啊 那我洗洗
Dialogue: 0,1:12:06.65,1:12:08.53,Default,,0,0,0,,不是呀君宝 不要 起来
Dialogue: 0,1:12:08.74,1:12:09.78,Default,,0,0,0,,让我洗洗嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:12:11.66,1:12:13.37,Default,,0,0,0,,出来晒晒太阳 呼吸点新鲜空气
Dialogue: 0,1:12:13.62,1:12:14.87,Default,,0,0,0,,对你自己有帮助哦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:15.29,1:12:18.00,Default,,0,0,0,,我站这边好了 小心被太阳烤焦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:19.21,1:12:20.13,Default,,0,0,0,,不会的啦?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:20.33,1:12:22.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这大地的一草一本都有他自己的生命
Dialogue: 0,1:12:26.80,1:12:28.09,Default,,0,0,0,,这棵树虽然枯了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:28.30,1:12:30.39,Default,,0,0,0,,但是另外一个新生命又开始了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:30.64,1:12:31.97,Default,,0,0,0,,你也可以这样啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:33.01,1:12:34.27,Default,,0,0,0,,大哥…
Dialogue: 0,1:12:34.47,1:12:35.68,Default,,0,0,0,,什么事呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:35.89,1:12:36.77,Default,,0,0,0,,大嫂刚生啦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:36.98,1:12:38.19,Default,,0,0,0,,你赶快回去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:38.39,1:12:39.77,Default,,0,0,0,,好好好 来…
Dialogue: 0,1:12:40.69,1:12:42.06,Default,,0,0,0,,也不知道该给孩子取个什么名字啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:43.07,1:12:44.73,Default,,0,0,0,,你背那么大担柴怎么走啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:45.03,1:12:46.57,Default,,0,0,0,,孩子还等着你回去抱呢
Dialogue: 0,1:12:46.99,1:12:50.07,Default,,0,0,0,,你赶快把柴放下来吧 贪心哪
Dialogue: 0,1:12:50.70,1:12:53.20,Default,,0,0,0,,对啊对啊 快走啦
Dialogue: 0,1:12:54.49,1:12:55.58,Default,,0,0,0,,等等我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:56.33,1:12:58.54,Default,,0,0,0,,放下负担 奔向新生命
Dialogue: 0,1:12:58.75,1:13:00.50,Default,,0,0,0,,是呀 希望他能很快到家
Dialogue: 0,1:13:02.17,1:13:05.09,Default,,0,0,0,,放下负担 奔向新生命
Dialogue: 0,1:13:06.42,1:13:12.51,Default,,0,0,0,,放下负担 奔向新生命…
Dialogue: 0,1:13:19.60,1:13:23.06,Default,,0,0,0,,这本「气功心法」 不是什么武林绝学
Dialogue: 0,1:13:23.36,1:13:25.19,Default,,0,0,0,,不过在你心情烦乱的时候
Dialogue: 0,1:13:25.36,1:13:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,可以带给你清静
Dialogue: 0,1:13:30.53,1:13:31.74,Default,,0,0,0,,视名利如过隙 
Dialogue: 0,1:13:31.95,1:13:34.78,Default,,0,0,0,,视前尘如梦境
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.12,1:13:36.45,Default,,0,0,0,,清静为……
Dialogue: 0,1:13:37.37,1:13:38.75,Default,,0,0,0,,清静为天下本
Dialogue: 0,1:13:39.08,1:13:42.37,Default,,0,0,0,,刚则折 柔恒存
Dialogue: 0,1:13:43.25,1:13:44.92,Default,,0,0,0,,柔羽胜刚强
Dialogue: 0,1:13:45.67,1:13:46.88,Default,,0,0,0,,无欲无求
Dialogue: 0,1:13:47.17,1:13:48.46,Default,,0,0,0,,淡泊之至
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.05,1:13:52.47,Default,,0,0,0,,终能疾雷破山而不惊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:53.09,1:13:55.10,Default,,0,0,0,,白刃交前而不惧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:56.56,1:13:59.06,Default,,0,0,0,,你到底还有什么招式啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:14:00.56,1:14:04.94,Default,,0,0,0,,气沉丹田 中正安舒 呼吸要绵绵 深入丹田
Dialogue: 0,1:14:05.77,1:14:09.40,Default,,0,0,0,,意行气行 意到气到 静中有动 动中有静
Dialogue: 0,1:14:12.82,1:14:14.53,Default,,0,0,0,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,1:14:15.16,1:14:17.74,Default,,0,0,0,,只不过有些牵挂放不下
Dialogue: 0,1:14:18.04,1:14:19.33,Default,,0,0,0,,过去只是人生的经历
Dialogue: 0,1:14:19.70,1:14:21.71,Default,,0,0,0,,并不是一种负担
Dialogue: 0,1:14:24.37,1:14:25.58,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 吃饭啦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:25.79,1:14:28.13,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊 你刚刚复原 要多吃一点啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:28.17,1:14:29.30,Default,,0,0,0,,三疯
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.88,1:14:37.80,Default,,0,0,0,,三丰 张三丰？蛮好听的诶 
Dialogue: 0,1:14:38.76,1:14:40.22,Default,,0,0,0,,是呀…
Dialogue: 0,1:14:43.98,1:14:45.56,Default,,0,0,0,,忘了过去吧 君宝
Dialogue: 0,1:14:51.78,1:14:53.32,Default,,0,0,0,,他为什么不躺着睡啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:14:54.24,1:14:55.86,Default,,0,0,0,,他失眠 所以不能躺着睡
Dialogue: 0,1:14:56.07,1:14:57.53,Default,,0,0,0,,不要乱说呀
Dialogue: 0,1:14:58.62,1:15:00.24,Default,,0,0,0,,他下面放着块铁嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:15:01.41,1:15:04.96,Default,,0,0,0,,中正安舒 气沉丹田
Dialogue: 0,1:15:11.63,1:15:14.01,Default,,0,0,0,,保持重心 借力用力
Dialogue: 0,1:15:19.01,1:15:21.10,Default,,0,0,0,,一个球转动就可以把周围的东西弹开
Dialogue: 0,1:15:21.31,1:15:22.60,Default,,0,0,0,,但本身很稳定
Dialogue: 0,1:15:22.97,1:15:24.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你害得我没饭吃啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:27.60,1:15:28.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:29.44,1:15:31.78,Default,,0,0,0,,动中有静 静中有动
Dialogue: 0,1:15:37.49,1:15:38.78,Default,,0,0,0,,他好象想到什么啦
Dialogue: 0,1:15:47.42,1:15:50.17,Default,,0,0,0,,无论我多用力打去 都会被水弹回来
Dialogue: 0,1:15:50.67,1:15:51.84,Default,,0,0,0,,遇强则强
Dialogue: 0,1:15:52.38,1:15:54.13,Default,,0,0,0,,想不到我连水都打不过
Dialogue: 0,1:15:54.42,1:15:55.92,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你怎么啦?
Dialogue: 0,1:15:56.09,1:15:57.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你是不是又发疯了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:57.97,1:16:00.30,Default,,0,0,0,,不是啊 中正安舒...
Dialogue: 0,1:16:00.51,1:16:02.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我好象有点心得啦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:07.89,1:16:09.27,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么那么脏啊 他是谁啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:16:14.10,1:16:14.80,Default,,0,0,0,,是我啊?
Dialogue: 0,1:18:05.18,1:18:06.51,Default,,0,0,0,,跪下
Dialogue: 0,1:18:07.89,1:18:10.18,Default,,0,0,0,,张君宝在哪里 有没有同党?
Dialogue: 0,1:18:10.60,1:18:13.73,Default,,0,0,0,,谁呀 谁是张君宝?
Dialogue: 0,1:18:13.98,1:18:15.15,Default,,0,0,0,,杀了他老婆
Dialogue: 0,1:18:15.77,1:18:17.73,Default,,0,0,0,,老婆 再不说连他女儿也杀了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:18.07,1:18:19.61,Default,,0,0,0,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,1:18:19.94,1:18:21.11,Default,,0,0,0,,不要杀我女儿 冤枉呀
Dialogue: 0,1:18:21.32,1:18:22.95,Default,,0,0,0,,杀
Dialogue: 0,1:18:23.40,1:18:26.49,Default,,0,0,0,,死狗官 你不得好死
Dialogue: 0,1:18:26.95,1:18:28.33,Default,,0,0,0,,你还嘴硬
Dialogue: 0,1:18:29.16,1:18:30.79,Default,,0,0,0,,谁要是敢包庇张君宝
Dialogue: 0,1:18:31.20,1:18:32.71,Default,,0,0,0,,就是跟我董天宝作对
Dialogue: 0,1:18:33.12,1:18:34.92,Default,,0,0,0,,来人 拉他游街
Dialogue: 0,1:18:39.05,1:18:40.63,Default,,0,0,0,,凌道士…
Dialogue: 0,1:18:40.84,1:18:42.26,Default,,0,0,0,,什么事呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:18:42.67,1:18:44.18,Default,,0,0,0,,董天宝现在势力越来越大
Dialogue: 0,1:18:44.38,1:18:45.97,Default,,0,0,0,,而且比刘公公还要残忍
Dialogue: 0,1:18:46.30,1:18:48.80,Default,,0,0,0,,刚刚诬赖粮行老板是叛党 杀他全家呀
Dialogue: 0,1:18:49.10,1:18:49.81,Default,,0,0,0,,是呀
Dialogue: 0,1:18:49.97,1:18:52.35,Default,,0,0,0,,他还说如果我们不说出君宝在哪
Dialogue: 0,1:18:52.56,1:18:54.31,Default,,0,0,0,,他还要杀更多的人哪
Dialogue: 0,1:18:55.23,1:18:57.10,Default,,0,0,0,,你们要当心呀 我们先走啦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:58.15,1:18:59.69,Default,,0,0,0,,你们也要小心点呀
Dialogue: 0,1:19:00.52,1:19:01.78,Default,,0,0,0,,修道之人要避祸慎行
Dialogue: 0,1:19:02.03,1:19:03.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我们还是快走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:19:03.61,1:19:06.36,Default,,0,0,0,,修道之人不可以只为自己 要普渡众生
Dialogue: 0,1:19:06.53,1:19:08.66,Default,,0,0,0,,但是现在天道宁论哪
Dialogue: 0,1:19:09.62,1:19:11.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我相信上天有好生之德
Dialogue: 0,1:19:12.95,1:19:15.25,Default,,0,0,0,,为了避免更多的人再受伤害
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.42,1:19:18.96,Default,,0,0,0,,我一定要想办法制止他再作恶
Dialogue: 0,1:19:19.50,1:19:21.59,Default,,0,0,0,,如果你们有什么不测…
Dialogue: 0,1:19:22.67,1:19:24.97,Default,,0,0,0,,生死有命
Dialogue: 0,1:19:25.17,1:19:26.55,Default,,0,0,0,,那我也一块去啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:27.05,1:19:28.97,Default,,0,0,0,,凌道长 我看你还是别去啦
Dialogue: 0,1:19:29.72,1:19:31.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道我会连累你们
Dialogue: 0,1:19:33.31,1:19:35.60,Default,,0,0,0,,这些符我平常写都不怎么灵啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:35.89,1:19:37.56,Default,,0,0,0,,希望这次能够很灵
Dialogue: 0,1:19:38.90,1:19:41.82,Default,,0,0,0,,我悟道几十年 还不及你一朝悟道
Dialogue: 0,1:19:42.11,1:19:43.19,Default,,0,0,0,,你将来
Dialogue: 0,1:19:43.40,1:19:45.44,Default,,0,0,0,,一定会成为一代宗师
Dialogue: 0,1:19:45.65,1:19:47.03,Default,,0,0,0,,我还是退休吧
Dialogue: 0,1:19:51.03,1:19:53.20,Default,,0,0,0,,恭喜大哥 请到长寿佛
Dialogue: 0,1:19:53.45,1:19:56.21,Default,,0,0,0,,大哥以后一定能够长命百岁
Dialogue: 0,1:19:56.50,1:19:57.75,Default,,0,0,0,,永享富贵
Dialogue: 0,1:20:22.19,1:20:25.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你们这些叛党 竟敢冒犯本公
Dialogue: 0,1:20:25.78,1:20:27.19,Default,,0,0,0,,跑到这儿来送死?
Dialogue: 0,1:20:28.70,1:20:30.53,Default,,0,0,0,,阉贼 你恶贯满盈
Dialogue: 0,1:20:30.74,1:20:32.45,Default,,0,0,0,,就算求到满天神佛也保佑不了你
Dialogue: 0,1:20:33.53,1:20:34.54,Default,,0,0,0,,杀
Dialogue: 0,1:20:48.51,1:20:49.84,Default,,0,0,0,,上天有好生之德
Dialogue: 0,1:20:51.64,1:20:53.39,Default,,0,0,0,,又何必动刀动枪?
Dialogue: 0,1:22:58.34,1:23:00.39,Default,,0,0,0,,不要杀我…
Dialogue: 0,1:23:00.81,1:23:01.89,Default,,0,0,0,,上天有好生之德
Dialogue: 0,1:23:02.06,1:23:03.39,Default,,0,0,0,,只想请你帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,1:23:03.48,1:23:04.64,Default,,0,0,0,,起来
Dialogue: 0,1:23:43.89,1:23:45.77,Default,,0,0,0,,不要乱来 刘公公呀
Dialogue: 0,1:23:45.98,1:23:47.31,Default,,0,0,0,,还不退后?
Dialogue: 0,1:24:05.75,1:24:07.50,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你变聪明了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:07.91,1:24:09.37,Default,,0,0,0,,懂得用刘公公来要挟我
Dialogue: 0,1:24:09.62,1:24:11.04,Default,,0,0,0,,我从小就很聪明
Dialogue: 0,1:24:11.25,1:24:13.63,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我不屑利用这小聪明
Dialogue: 0,1:24:13.84,1:24:14.88,Default,,0,0,0,,你们想怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,1:24:14.96,1:24:16.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我想告诉你
Dialogue: 0,1:24:16.55,1:24:19.26,Default,,0,0,0,,你的所做所为 只有死路一条
Dialogue: 0,1:24:21.89,1:24:25.35,Default,,0,0,0,,从小到大 讲计谋论功夫
Dialogue: 0,1:24:25.56,1:24:27.77,Default,,0,0,0,,你全都输我 还被我利用
Dialogue: 0,1:24:28.18,1:24:29.27,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎么跟我斗?
Dialogue: 0,1:24:30.27,1:24:31.69,Default,,0,0,0,,叫他跪下
Dialogue: 0,1:24:32.56,1:24:33.77,Default,,0,0,0,,跪下呀
Dialogue: 0,1:24:34.32,1:24:36.23,Default,,0,0,0,,还不跪下
Dialogue: 0,1:24:39.99,1:24:41.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你现在跪在地上跟我说话
Dialogue: 0,1:24:41.66,1:24:43.16,Default,,0,0,0,,你又怎么跟我们斗?
Dialogue: 0,1:24:44.33,1:24:47.25,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 你不是很喜欢帮助人?
Dialogue: 0,1:24:47.79,1:24:49.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我好不容易才有今天这个局面
Dialogue: 0,1:24:49.37,1:24:50.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我不能放弃这一次
Dialogue: 0,1:24:50.71,1:24:52.08,Default,,0,0,0,,就当帮我一次忙
Dialogue: 0,1:24:52.29,1:24:53.88,Default,,0,0,0,,快点放了刘公公
Dialogue: 0,1:24:54.21,1:24:55.88,Default,,0,0,0,,名利只是过眼云烟
Dialogue: 0,1:24:56.38,1:24:58.76,Default,,0,0,0,,这一次我是替天行道
Dialogue: 0,1:25:00.09,1:25:01.63,Default,,0,0,0,,我命由我不由天
Dialogue: 0,1:26:51.79,1:26:53.12,Default,,0,0,0,,这是哪门子拳法?
Dialogue: 0,1:26:53.37,1:26:56.58,Default,,0,0,0,,无根无极 万法自然
Dialogue: 0,1:26:58.04,1:26:59.67,Default,,0,0,0,,太极
Dialogue: 0,1:27:43.88,1:27:45.17,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 我不会输给你
Dialogue: 0,1:27:45.34,1:27:46.72,Default,,0,0,0,,我永远都不会输给你
Dialogue: 0,1:27:46.97,1:27:50.68,Default,,0,0,0,,你心浮气燥 利欲熏心 怎么能赢?
Dialogue: 0,1:27:54.26,1:27:55.47,Default,,0,0,0,,千斤坠
Dialogue: 0,1:28:53.57,1:28:54.95,Default,,0,0,0,,借力用力
Dialogue: 0,1:29:14.76,1:29:17.68,Default,,0,0,0,,上呀…杀了他 上呀
Dialogue: 0,1:29:17.89,1:29:20.31,Default,,0,0,0,,谁都不要动
Dialogue: 0,1:29:20.73,1:29:22.44,Default,,0,0,0,,谁动我就杀了谁
Dialogue: 0,1:29:23.40,1:29:25.56,Default,,0,0,0,,上呀 你们为什么不上呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:29:25.73,1:29:27.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你也不准动 我不动…
Dialogue: 0,1:29:28.40,1:29:29.32,Default,,0,0,0,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,1:29:29.53,1:29:31.40,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么不上?想死啊
Dialogue: 0,1:29:31.49,1:29:34.07,Default,,0,0,0,,董天宝 如果我少一根头发
Dialogue: 0,1:29:34.11,1:29:35.78,Default,,0,0,0,,我就把你脑袋砍下来
Dialogue: 0,1:29:42.54,1:29:44.71,Default,,0,0,0,,刘公公…  他杀了刘公公
Dialogue: 0,1:29:46.71,1:29:51.01,Default,,0,0,0,,公公…  公公…
Dialogue: 0,1:29:52.26,1:29:54.51,Default,,0,0,0,,刘公公已经死了 现在由我做主
Dialogue: 0,1:29:54.76,1:29:56.51,Default,,0,0,0,,你们上呀 上…
Dialogue: 0,1:29:56.72,1:29:57.68,Default,,0,0,0,,他连刘公公都敢杀
Dialogue: 0,1:29:57.76,1:30:00.01,Default,,0,0,0,,迟早把你们杀光 你们还帮他?
Dialogue: 0,1:30:01.22,1:30:02.68,Default,,0,0,0,,不要动
Dialogue: 0,1:30:03.35,1:30:04.81,Default,,0,0,0,,退后
Dialogue: 0,1:30:10.07,1:30:12.65,Default,,0,0,0,,你众叛亲离 没有人会帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:30:38.97,1:30:40.76,Default,,0,0,0,,打死他
Dialogue: 0,1:30:41.31,1:30:43.31,Default,,0,0,0,,日练夜练 欺上瞒下
Dialogue: 0,1:30:43.39,1:30:44.60,Default,,0,0,0,,不把我们当人看
Dialogue: 0,1:30:44.85,1:30:46.44,Default,,0,0,0,,只顾自己升官发财
Dialogue: 0,1:30:46.69,1:30:55.61,Default,,0,0,0,,打死他…
Dialogue: 0,1:31:14.63,1:31:23.22,Default,,0,0,0,,打死他…
Dialogue: 0,1:31:31.44,1:31:33.73,Default,,0,0,0,,在我临死之前 求你原谅我
Dialogue: 0,1:31:34.23,1:31:35.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我错啦
Dialogue: 0,1:31:36.19,1:31:40.11,Default,,0,0,0,,君宝 念在我们是多年的兄弟
Dialogue: 0,1:31:41.28,1:31:43.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你可不可以原谅我
Dialogue: 0,1:31:43.24,1:31:44.16,Default,,0,0,0,,从小到大
Dialogue: 0,1:31:44.20,1:31:45.91,Default,,0,0,0,,无论我做了什么你都会原谅我的
Dialogue: 0,1:31:49.08,1:31:50.79,Default,,0,0,0,,你不要相信他
Dialogue: 0,1:31:55.50,1:31:57.01,Default,,0,0,0,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,1:32:47.72,1:32:48.85,Default,,0,0,0,,你们走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:07.66,1:33:08.95,Default,,0,0,0,,你打算去哪里?
Dialogue: 0,1:33:10.12,1:33:12.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我要带天宝的骨灰回去见师父
Dialogue: 0,1:33:13.67,1:33:15.54,Default,,0,0,0,,我们以后还会不会再见面?
Dialogue: 0,1:33:16.96,1:33:18.09,Default,,0,0,0,,随缘吧
Dialogue: 0,1:33:22.72,1:33:24.18,Default,,0,0,0,,再会啦 张三丰
