Cat. Have Shan, KC and Avina call me.
Bye.
Hi, KC.
Did you draft the contract?
Great! Bring it to the meeting.
I'm on my way. Hold on.
Hello Shan.
I'll see you in half an hour.
Avina, make sure the financials are ready.
I have an announcement to make.
The meeting was a success.
We have reached an agreement with BIC.
When Mr. Lee comes here next week to sign,
we will have completed the merger.
What we need to review is their proposal
for a share swap merger.
But that's going to cost us 1 8% more.
And if the market changes,
it'll cost us even more.
The contract needs a lot of amendment,
we need a couple more drafts
before it's finalized.
We may not have the financials ready in time.
But if we get the PRC market share,
our profit will be very high.
Conservatively speaking,
we will net at least 5 billion.
Therefore we'll have to make it work.
You guys will have to slave it out
in the next few days.
By the way, in the last 2 weeks,
3 artifacts insured by us have been stolen.
The insured value is around 5 million.
We have someone verifying the claims.
Fine, approve their claims.
We don't need any distraction.
General...
I have a hot tip! Wanna order something?
Hear me out! A couple days ago
my friend took me to see the owner.
He's got a great horse!
People are watching...
That baby is a great performer,
Ioves a fast surface.
I couldn't believe my eyes...
That animal is the best sprinter!
It had the fastest time.
Next week...
Cut me a break.
Next week... I'll have it!
Friday!
I'll have the money!
Thursday!
How many times have you said that?
If no money, just jump off a building.
Assistant Commissioner.
What are you doing here?
What about you?
- Morning.
What's all this?
What's the big deal with these burglary cases?
Your investigation hasn't picked up
a thing for 2 weeks.
It's a waste of taxpayer's money!
There may be a rat inside the insurance company.
Just because the art objects
are insured by the same company?
Know what "coincidence" means?
You're over-reading it.
Wrap up the investigation
if you don't hear anything.
I did.
Angelina rejected Mr. Unfulfilled again.
For the ninth time?
What's her name again?
"Angelina". Nosy!
It is my business!
I'm Assistant Commissioner Wong Kai Fa!
This is for you, Inspector.
No sender's address again?
Yes Sir.
This is the third one.
Is someone upset with you?
Be careful.
Leave me alone!
Don't say I did not warn you!
Yes.
Thursday, I know...
I... will have it.
Of course not!
Sure! After work! 7!
He wouldn't talk to us.
No idea who he is.
Thursday...
What?
Did you check if he lives around here?
We have nothing on him.
Thanks, Captain.
Mister.
What's your name?
I'm Ken, the negotiator.
What's wrong? Can I help you?
Let's play a game first. Then I'll tell you.
Okay.
Head or tail?
Head.
Wrong.
Head or tail?
Come, let's play somewhere else.
You won't play?
No... Head!
Wrong.
Head or tail?
You thirsty?
We can get something for you.
You lost twice in a row. Don't you want to win?
Head!
Is that all you're going to say?
I have a 50/50 chance.
Let's see it.
Wrong.
You're kidding me.
Call your superior.
Yes, Captain!
Head!
Wrong.
Again!
Head!
Wrong.
Inspector Ho!
What are you doing here?
What about you?
I'm the negotiator.
What if the Commissioner wants a report on this?
I better have a look.
Fine. Just don't say a word up there.
Got it.
Inspector, something's wrong with your man.
He's been playing head or tail with our subject.
Give me a radio.
Inspector Ho.
Head!
Wrong.
Again!
Head!
Wrong.
Again!
This is Assistant Commissioner Wong Kai Fa!
How dare you, Ken!
You promised to shut up.
I couldn't stand it!
We don't know who the guy is.
I worry if Ken keeps losing
he'll jump off the building.
Why would he?
Yes he will!
We're bugged!
Ken's in great debt.
I'll talk to him
and grab him if there's a chance.
Notify the firemen.
Sure.
Inspector!
Don't curse!
I didn't!
"Looking for me? "
Head! No...
Head!
Wrong.
I'll toss!
See if you can win one out of three.
Don't fall for it!
I've been getting tail for 33 times, Inspector!
That's spooky.
It's just a game.
Quit if you're afraid losing.
It's just a game!
Remember what you came up here for?
It'll show head. Let me win!
Head!
Wrong again.
You can't win.
He means you don't have the luck.
What do you want?
Two chances left.
Head!
It can't be... Thursday...
Last chance!
I'll toss!
Head or tail?
It doesn't matter who does it.
It's destiny.
Have some confidence, Ken. Head or tail?
Head!
You got it! Yes!
Don't lie to him.
I didn't. It's for real.
Come see it for yourself.
I don't tell lies.
Come.
You lost, Inspector.
It's tail.
Then come see it for yourself.
So you can catch me?
You think you can get away?
Look at him.
Ken!
Bomb!
Why are you doing this?
You'll soon find out.
Calm down.
Call ambulance.
The pier please.
Where are you going?
The police station.
I'm charging you with aiding and abetting.
And setting trash cans on fire.
Sounds serious!
You're a smart guy, Inspector.
Didn't expect you to catch up with me.
It just happens. Every time I drive a taxi
I would pick up dumb bad guys.
No one would believe that.
I agree.
How about this
If I take you in, I win.
The station is far. It's not challenging.
How about the end of this block?
If you can drive me to
the end of the block, you win.
I won't stop no matter what!
Why did you call me?
Have the lab analyze the handkerchief.
There's a feather.
Take it too.
Calling center.
This is Assistant Commissioner Wong Kai Fa.
Teresa speaking.
The 3 stolen art objects are under my possession.
Are you interested in getting them back?
What do you want?
Notify Inspector Ho.
Have the money ready.
Call everyone to a meeting.
I'll be there in 1 5 minutes.
We should contact the authority.
No. If BIC finds out our company
is being extorted
they'll walk out on the deal.
It's going to hurt us.
Not if the cops put a lid on the case.
That's the risk we can't take.
But we don't know who we're up against.
This is a criminal we're talking about.
What choice do we have?
There's only a few days left.
Let's keep this confidential people.
Proceed with your work as usual.
Shan, call Central Bank
Call now!
Jackson? This is Shan from PFA.
Teresa wants to speak with you.
Hello, Teresa
I need a favor. I need 20 million dollars
in cash right now.
You two go over there.
Who are you guys? Clean the office later.
Mr. Unfulfilled.
Who are you guys?
I'm a cop.
Let's have a chat.
You know what's going on.
I need to see the person in charge.
Please cooperate.
Shan, get going!
You're...Teresa?
I'm Inspector Ho.
Can we talk in your office?
It's not true.
I'm here to help.
I don't think I can help you.
Shan!
Excuse me.
"The 3 stolen art objects... "
"...are under my possession."
"Are you interested in getting them back? "
"What do you want? "
"20 million dollars."
"Is this a joke? "
"Then I'll make more scores
to get the media's attention."
"That'll scare your clients away."
"Have the money ready."
It's illegal to bug my office
without my permission.
Your best option is to work with us.
Understand?
I know my rights.
I don't have to report the case.
I know my rights too.
I can invite you to come down the station.
You can come in your own car
or we can send one over.
It's up to you.
Teresa please.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Who is this?
- Teresa?
- Yes.
Met Inspector Ho already?
Inspector Ho please.
You okay? Don't worry,
the smoke was not poisonous.
It's you!
Remember you asked me why I'm doing all this?
You said I'll find out later.
If I pick up the ransom, I win.
- Where? When?
Tomorrow at 9 AM. The Inspector knows the place.
- Madam
- Yes
I have to get going.
Why?
Assistant Commissioner.
Please give this to Inspector Ho.
I was waiting for him.
Perfect.
Why ask you?
Listen to me.
Our suspect is at the station.
Seal off the premise now.
Make sure no one leaves!
- Thanks
- No problem
What?
Don't ask. Just do what I say!
Why do I have to do everything you said?
Back to the station!
Let's go get the money.
Remember what I told you on the phone?
Did you do it?
I couldn't make out what you were saying!
How was I supposed to understand?
Plus your friend was talking next to me.
The one on the rooftop...
with long hair and mustache?
There is resemblance...
It is him!
He is the suspect!
I didn't know that.
Told you you weren't making any sense.
Inspector Ho! Here's 20 million!
Where's the drop-off place?
What 20 million? What drop-off place?
- Write down the serial numbers.
- Yes.
All one thousand dollar bills.
500 bills per stack. Half a million.
Mr. Unfulfilled?
What?
Who is Angelina?
Central precinct. Please hold.
It's for you, Inspector.
Sorry it's me again.
What do you want?
Forget about real bills. I want color copies.
Make sure they are double-sided copies.
No problem. Any other requests?
No! Photocopying bank notes is illegal!
Why color copies?
I'll take full responsibility.
How much do you really want?
Can you stop complicating things?
Of course not. Right, Inspector?
Yes.
That's exactly what he wants to do, Teresa.
Kiddo! This is Assistant Commissioner Wong Ka Fa!
Either make your demand or hang up now!
Assistant Commissioner please.
It's him!
Yes?
Remember to give Inspector the envelope.
Otherwise he won't know
where to make the drop-off.
He'll have nowhere to go tomorrow.
I know.
What money?
Drop-off... 20 million...
Extortion?!
Why fake bills?
Wong Kai Fa!
Did you touch my things?
Did you forget to give me something?
Do you have it on you?
Inspector Ho!
What?
Morning!
Great day today.
Had breakfast yet?
Ate already.
You sound upset.
Stayed up all night?
Or couldn't figure out the puzzle?
I can set a new date.
No. I'm dying to meet you.
Same here.
Know where to make the drop-off?
Yes. Figured it out last night.
See you soon!
Good.
You had me worried.
Why didn't you say so last night?
They look real.
We'll be in trouble if they're out on the streets.
What building is in gray?
With no windows?
Warehouse!
There's one like it in Chicago.
You should get going. Where to?
Thought you already knew.
Looks familiar.
Of course.
The trash can?
Why would this be the drop-off place?
Don't touch it!
What?
He's here for the money!
Keep calm!
Stay where you are!
This is Assistant Commissioner Wong Kai Fa.
We need backup! We have a crisis here!
We have bigger problems here!
An organized attack!
Keep an eye on the money!
Where are you, Mr. Unfulfilled?
Don't answer!
Hold your fire!
We didn't fire!
Wong Kai Fa!
I didn't carry my gun!
The money is gone!
No! I have it here.
The windows are intact.
We didn't have to evacuate.
Are these bills real or fake?
They're color copies.
We're in trouble!
He got away with the money!
- Madam
You two come with me.
The Commissioner wants to know what happened.
What should I tell him?
A suspect detonated smoke bombs here.
Only smoke.
The counterfeits are all over the streets.
I'll take full responsibility.
Take a vacation.
A vacation?
I've approved it.
Assistant Commissioner, you'll take over.
Yes, Madam.
Here's the lab's analysis of the handkerchief.
Thank you.
You're on vacation. He'll handle it.
Take some time off.
See what you've done
I'll have the money.
I will see if you do or not tomorrow
What?
One person?
Ready to order?
That day...
Did you play tricks on me?
Did you cheat?
Head or tail?
Head!
Sorry.
Inspector Ho please
Finish?
One more time.
Inspector Ho please.
It's not hard to imitate.
"Inspector Ho please."
There she is... wait for my signal.
Okay.
- Hi Teresa. Going home?
- What do you want?
I'm a cop.
Please give me a minute.
I've got new leads.
None of my business.
I gave him the money. It's over.
But think about it, Teresa.
Why go through all the trouble?
Besides the trash can,
he sent me two other things.
It's not over yet. He'll call you again.
I can contact you superior!
If this guy can pick up money from your station,
what more can you do?
Listen to me...
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Teresa.
Inspector Ho please.
This is he speaking.
I'm not afraid of you.
Don't harass her over the phone!
We found feather on the handkerchief.
It belongs to American Bald Eagle.
It's not found in Hong Kong
Unless it's in captivity.
What does it mean?
If we find the eagle, we'll find its owner.
Could the feather belong to a specimen?
That's not what the lab says.
Where can we find it?
I've seen it!
So that's why. I thought that eagle lost its way.
You observe wild birds?
I majored in ornithology in college.
What is it?
"Ornithology". The study of birds.
Last time I spotted the eagle by the harbor.
If I get my bird watching buddies
to the buildings around the area,
we'll be able to find the eagle!
A Grey Plover! It's a fat one!
Haven't seen one Tercel all day.
Didn't fall migration begin already?
Didn't you see the news?
Northern Japan is experiencing a heat wave.
Look at the sailboats!
Paul, what are you doing?
Sorry...
Black-faced Spoonbill! Can you see it?
It normally migrates to Taiwan,
hardly comes to Hong Kong.
Did it lose its way?
It's beautiful...
Shan, what are you doing?
Sorry...
I see it!
Inspector, the eagle is heading
toward Bank of China. You see it?
Yes!
Teresa.
Get in, let's go.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Don't lose the eagle!
Straight ahead!
That way!
It's gone!
I thought you kept your eyes on it.
Shan, where is it?
I lost it.
How can you lose it? What the hell are you doing?
Fanny, do you see it?
It's behind the skyscraper.
It's flying too low.
Should be around Queen's Road.
Open the sunroof and take a look.
Do you see it?
Yes, it's there!
Where? Left or right?
Left!
No... Right!
No, it turned that way!
Which way?
That way!
Left or right?
That way like I told you!
Which is left?
Can you tell left from right?
You'll drive.
You first.
Please hand me the binocular.
Please drive...
Please pull over.
Please wait here.
Throwing a concert?
Think you're Robin Hood?
You're just a thief!
No. I'm a magician who brings joy to people.
You got the wrong audience.
I always hated magic shows.
They're fake.
I want you to be my assistant.
Every magician's got one.
Should I wear a sexy costume
and do the opening dance act?
That's not your role.
You're going to help me to finish this illusion.
I prefer arresting you more!
Watch where you're going!
Water please.
5 dollars.
Ice cream please.
Taking a stroll, Sir?
I'm pursuing a suspect.
You're joking, right?
Inspector, your determination impresses me.
Thanks. I'll catch you no matter where you go.
Finish line is the end of this road.
If I win, you'll come with me.
If I win, the game continues!
Hi, Teresa.
We've talked before on the phone.
Nice to meet you.
I have something for you.
What is it?
He returned the money.
He gave it to you?
It was left in your car.
Sit.
He raised the ransom to 1 00 million.
How did you know I was here?
He told me.
Ate already?
It's really late.
You told me to wait...
Want one?
One wonton noodle please.
BIC is going to sign on Friday.
We can't have any troubles.
Can you help me?
- We'll sign...
- understand.
What do you want?
He wants you to deliver the ransom.
So I've become his assistant!
Your leg...
I'm sorry.
It's part of the job.
You okay?
Call BIC as soon as I leave,
tell them I'll arrive early.
See if they can move up my meeting
with Lee Wen-Qi.
Have a good trip.
Keep your eyes on the company.
I will, good luck!
Inspector Ho!
- Wait here.
- Yes sir
The money doesn't matter.
Be careful.
- What are you doing?
What did she say?
What's it to you? Nosy.
What?
Morning!
Sorry to make you get up this early.
What now?
The money is pretty heavy.
I got you a back pack to save you the trouble.
Where is it?
Figure it out yourself!
You have the key.
What is this?
Why do you have my key?
It's yours?
I recognize the key chain.
I bought it last time when I went to Japan alone.
What is it for?
My locker at the station.
Sorry.
Head.
Again.
Hurry! You're not supposed to be here.
Yes.
"Triangle Garden"
- Madam, I was just looking for you.
- Asst. Commissioner.
I need your help on this.
Sergeant Lee wants to move to a new desk.
He's superstitious...
You have to see it for yourself.
But now Sergeant Chan is upset.
He claims it's bad Fong Sui.
The two are arguing everyday.
What should I do?
Inspector.
Morning.
What is it? What's in the bag?
I've been asked to deliver the ransom.
I knew you won't take time off.
Give me a report tomorrow.
Yes, Madam!
Inspector Ho.
Be careful.
What did she say?
She said you should be careful.
Don't make more troubles.
I thought you were on the lookout.
Where were you?
I...
You're never reliable!
Head.
Wrong.
Again.
Head.
Wrong.
Again.
Wait, I have to make a call.
Sorry, Inspector,
I've changed my mind.
Say it.
Be at Central at 1 1.
Let's go!
Where to?
Don't keep it a secret!
Central!
Head.
Wrong.
Again.
Head.
Wrong.
Inspector Ho?
Yes.
Party of nine? Your table is ready.
Head.
Again.
Let's take a break.
Order something.
Running around all morning,
should make you hungry.
Have lunch with your men.
The food here is good. Try it.
How considerate of you!
Remember to pick up the bill for me!
Fine. Enjoy.
So?
Lunch break.
Great food! I'll come here again.
Again.
Head or tails?
How many times have we played?
372 times.
I lost 372 times.
Why keep playing?
Right.
Excuse me.
Bye
Finished?
Now it's time to take a stroll.
Please make a donation.
Thanks.
Thank you.
So? Where to now?
Are you afraid to show yourself?
It's late, I'm tired!
What? You're upset?
Why don't you try it?
Carrying a big bag around all day,
and you'll see why.
Tired? Then throw the bag away!
I'll really do it!
Asst. Commissioner.
Wong Kai Fa
What are these?
The 3 art objects he stole.
He's got the money!
Call the coast guards!
Yes, Sir!
And call the dive team!
The money is fake.
Hold off your calls.
What a relief!
You made counterfeits again?
I will meet you on the rooftop.
Be there before dawn.
If you don't come,
Teresa will complete the merger.
And you'll end up with nothing.
You think he can hear you?
We're ready, Asst. Commissioner!
I'm not scared of your smoke this time!
Give me a mask later.
Yes Sir!
We're ready.
There's no way he'll get away!
Tell your men to leave.
It's a private date tonight.
sure.
You guys can leave now.
Yes, Sir!
Hurry! Get moving!
And you?
Me too?
Thought this is a private date!
Go now.
You just have to be like this.
Inspector Ho.
Be careful.
Asst. Commissioner, all the lifts are going up!
Who can it be? I already locked the lifts!
Who's inside them?
The security cameras are down.
We have no visuals.
Listen up everyone. The suspect is in the lifts.
Make sure he doesn't escape!
Lift A stopped on the 12th floor.
Watch closely, I'm coming down!
There's no one inside!
Get out of my way!
Lift B stopped on the 25th floor.
I'm coming up!
The lift is empty!
Lift C stopped on the 1 8th floor!
I'm coming down!
Lift C is empty!
Lift D stopped on the 30th floor.
I'm coming up!
Lift D is also empty!
Understood! I'm coming down!
What floor is this?
25th floor.
This is too weird!
You're amazing.
Kids would love to see you.
So are you happy to see me, Inspector?
Yes!
But catching you will make me happier.
I'm almost there.
Be careful, don't fall over.
If I pick up the ransom, I win.
Of course. A promise is a promise.
Thanks.
I got the ransom, I win.
But I'm happy because I've caught you.
If I fall, you'll come with me.
I won't let you go!
Where's Wong Kai Fa?
28th floor, almost there!
I arrested the guy. Hurry!
I'm on my way!
Inspector!
Why call me to the rooftop
if you ended up down here?
Where is he?
He fell.
He fell? Then?
Maybe broke into pieces?
Broke into pieces?
You've been fooled again!
Where to now?
I'm hungry.
You've always like this.
Always say you're hungry at the end.
Asst. Commissioner, what do we do now?
Have the men standing by.
Merry Christmas! Gifts for everyone!
You'll get one! Naughty!
You'll get yours!
"Local citizen Ho Shong Sang donates 1 00 million"
"dollars worth of sweets to children in need"
Give them candies instead of food?
They'll need dentists!
Hi!
Congratulations on the merger.
Thank you for your help.
Don't mention it, It's part of the job!
Inspector Ho!
Merry Christmas!
Happy New Year! Teresa!