Serious crimes in the first half year...
were done by the "Big Circle".
The ratio of conviction was low.
The Commissioner
is waiting for your plan.
He has been waiting for 3 months.
what do you want to do?
we have to admit one thing.
we need the informers!
The "Big Circle" group is cohesive.
They don't trust Hong Kong people.
The informers can't do much!
I have got an idea,
we have to use their own men...
for undercover!
Li Ho Tung, 34 years old.
Shandongese; son of senior cadre;
rasied in Guangzhou.
Used to be platoon leader, company
commander and battalion commander of PLA.
Quit in 1982.
And become the Captain of
Guilin's public security bereau.
Qi King San, 31 years old.
Cantonese; son of senior cadre;
graduated from Qinghua University.
Joined PLA at the age of 22.
Promoted to commander in 1979.
Seriously injured during Vietnamese war;
having been awarded third-class merit.
Recovered in 1982
and become a police security inwuhan.
Guo Hok Kwan, 27 years old.
Cantonese; son of senior cadre.
went to Beijing and settled there
with his father at the age of 12.
Graduated from Beijing Sports Academy.
Being a public security in Beijing
starting form 1982.
In April, 1984, all three were arrested
as they headed towards freedom.
They were sent to the
reform-through-labour farm in Chini.
On July 14, 1986,
they fled away from prison.
On July 16, 1986.
They stealthed into HK and were
waiting to be sent back to Mainland.
You are lucky, you have got two choices.
1, to be sent back, 2, work for me!
what do you want us to do?
Undercover!
work for two years and be legalized!
Do you like to stay in HK?
Seems that we don't have a choice!
wigs, one each!
An undercover police...
...will help you!
His name is "Biggy"!
To be a police in Hong Kong...
is more difficult
than have a driving license.
They only take 30 out of 10,000...
and you need to be out of college.
Fluent English!
Because the instructors speak English.
well, you can't
learn anything in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong is a mixed society.
Even if you spend 8-10 years here.
You only see the surface.
I tell you...
Better get some
cheap electrical appliance,
watch some sexual movies,
You'll have a proper pride
when you back to China!
Not sure if I am lucky
with the three of you!
Isn't it!
Big Boss!
wait! I can't bear it!
Just call me Biggy!
Biggy, we are confident to be good.
we want to stay here!
I see! I see!
well, you like this
Kentucky Fried Chicken?
This is the pager!
It vibrates like frog!
we call it space machine, too.
The wave goes into space
then reflects back!
And then "Do..."!
Impossible, it's only a receiver!
You know nothing!
I was a radio operator!
I can fix your pager!
Your friends?
Self serve meals are "Buffet"!
Buffet?
"Buffet" is the English spelling!
The first time I went for a buffet.
I didn't eat for 3 days!
And my stomach was all empty.
Get as much as you like?
Yes! Take it easy, don't be rude!
After I've finished this meal,
can I wait and have dinner as well?
You can even have supper!
And have breakfast...
in the morning!
You didn't eat in your last life?
I feel hungry without rice!
A lobster over there!
Only one left, take it!
You take it, Big Boss!
I can't have prawns, you have it!
Thanks!
Have you finished looking at it?
The lobster is for decoration!
what for putting it there?
wanna scare me?
The hill out there is Cheung Chow.
The place for stolen goods.
The turnover is around $50M!
Do you know him?
No, but we say hello!
You are smart!
He has got a lot of information.
Try to talk to him!
You give the order, boss!
Stop kidding, Biggy!
we are good friends!
Don't mention friendship!
I am only your temp commander.
I have a suggestion, commander
Everyone should have a pistol.
Undercovers don't have guns!
It's dangerous to work in H.K.!
Don't worry, I know how to get the guns!
You are criminals,
don't try to get the guns.
Don't try to get the guns.
Hire from the guns smugglers!
Two.45 government,
fifty thousand dollars each.
One.44 Magnum, twenty thousand dollars!
10 bullets each.
It's too expensive!
Hay, you have these three pistols!
You can make
a few hundred dollars in a second!
It wouldn't be too expensive?
He is reliable!
Pay if you want it!
Hok Kwan, pay!
Your usual rule!
Say it again!
Right, the 30 rounds of bullets?
I get them for you!
Negro Tong?
Negro Tong!
Biggy, I have waited for 3 years!
Don't move!
what, upset I didn't visit you in jail?
Rubbish, last time you helped me.
I ended up in jail!
Bastard, betrayed me!
Me, bastard? I betrayed you?
The police got me too!
I broke my ribs as well!
I wanna sincere!
You would spend 3 more years.
If I told the cops!
what do you mean, wanna frame me!
It's no use how you say it!
I wanna kill you today.
Look at these three pistols.
Go...over there!
Don't move!
Tong!
Chick Lai?
I came here two months ago.
which prison camp?
Kin Luen!
who was in-charge?
Uncle Pong, the man from San Tung!
He really is a pimp!
He is still alive. That bastard!
Tong, in Chick Lai 7 years ago.
You were the head of the 5-1 riot!
The old ones always talk about you!
You have heard about my name?
Yes, you were famous!
He is your friend?
Yes, we are old friends!
Shut up! who the hell is your old friend.
Don't forget you are our temp commander!
You are an informer, you bastard!
Give me back the money!
You said we have it all!
Give it to me!
Don't spoil our friendship
because of the bastard.
You tell me one thing!
we didn't see anything.
we are here to swim!
I want your life.
I am sorry, I forgot my trunks!
what trunks?
Don't, please! Let me go,
take the pistol!
I have seen nothing.
I...I go to swim!
No...
Betrayed me?
Thanks.
Come over, my left ear can't hear!
It shouldn't, cover your right ear.
Hok Kwan, speak loudly on his left.
- See if he can hear!
- Yes.
I can't hear a thing!
Come closer, try to speak loudly!
You bastard, fool me! I have enough!
I heard you told
Negro Tong the other day...
"Shut up, I am not your friend!"
I thought I would finish!
I thought you leave me alone!
You fool, don't be narrow minded!
we are comrades!
Tung!
I met my good friend
in the army and his sister.
Beautiful girl?
He saved my life in the war.
He invited me for dinner,
I hope I can go!
when did he come?
He got the permission five years ago.
Be careful, don't expose yourself.
Inspector Ching!
The crimes under the property of HK...
is really amazing!
we have a "Self-kidnapping" case!
A jewelry shop owner rubbed his own shop.
And tried to get the compensation!
His partners got away with the jewelry.
And blackmailed the owner.
Through Biggy...
The owner asked us
to get the jewelleries back.
Boss, this is the deposit!
Hok Kwan, check it.
Sorry, we're late!
Let me kiss you!
Let's change.
No...!
Excuse me!
Your boyfriend?
He is my cousin!
He always comes here
cause he likes dancing!
I thought you were his.
what did you say?
I am sorry!
I know what you are thinking.
Don't listen to what people say!
Not every girl goes out
with the guests here.
There are bad ones in a good family too!
Every job is the same here in H.K.!
Some of the stars "work" for money!
It all depends!
I do behave!
I don't really like money!
Am I too mean?
No, I respect you!
Thanks!
I want to see Siu Hing.
what?
- Dear Hing!
- Is that you?
I am camel, Siu Hing is my superior!
Hing, that bastard is coming.
I am Li Ho Tung, from China.
I represent Boss Yeung!
who are you talking to?
who is he talking too?
what has he got in hand?
That Yeung bastard, sent a fool over.
what does it mean?
This means he doesn't respect you!
I want you to hand over your stuff,
to us in two days' time!
That's my paging number!
Think it over,
contact me in these two days!
Do you know who you are talking to?
My status in T.S.T.
is the same as a mayor!
Everyone has to salute at me!
Only I can give the order.
You can't tell me what to do.
- Do you understand?
- I understand!
It's my mum's birthday tomorrow,
we'll wait.
You are lucky!
Tell Mr. Yeung not to negotiate anymore.
I have to celebrate my mum's birthday.
Then I will put his mum to sleep,
understand?
I understand!
Stupid!
I don't wanna see you
in T.S.T. anymore. Understand?
Understand!
what are you looking at?
If I see you again, I chop yours off!
Let's go!
The target tonight
is to insult Siu Hing publicly!
If we succeed.
we can build up our fame instantly!
And joint the Hong Kong underground.
They have more people,
so they are better off.
But they have their weak point too.
They are not ready to fight!
And because Siu Hing is selfish.
People may not help him!
That's Hong Kong people,
and we have to attack fast!
and retreat quickly!
The whole operation
is no more than 5 minutes!
I understand!
Great, a military operation!
we don't need outside support!
we get drawn easily!
Main point attack!
Four of us only better play Mahjong.
we will surely die!
Your job is "Two Electrics".
Give me orders!
No, I sincerely ask you to join in.
I didn't say no!
But tell me.
what "Two Electrics" is?
That's the phone and the switch!
why ask me to do such silly things?
Because it's safe for you!
- You two sneak in first!
- Yes!
Boss Kwan, good on you!
Congratulations!
Boss Shing, Tang Sir,
thank you for you coming!
You get lost!
I said before seven,
now it's eight already!
what time is it?
I thought you got run over!
Mum's back hurt when coming!
She had to take the drugs!
The guests were having prawn noodles!
I earn nothing today!
I said no celebrations before!
why talk to me that loud!
The clothes are for corpse only!
That brings bad luck!
Stop that!
Damn it, respect me will you!
Go to hell!
No.1!
Everybody, it's Mrs. Ko's birthday today.
Let's celebrate by singing!
Go to hell!
Hing, your call, it's from Mr. Yeung!
Happy birthday to you...!
Get down on your knees!
Give me the signal!
Hit the drum!
Come, let's go!
You chicken!
The whole place is under our control!
well you don't have to use the pistols!
Put down your gun, let's talk!
Get down on your knees!
Everybody we've to solve our problem!
And hope that I get the respect.
Please stay out of it?
- Understand?
- Understand...
Tell us your sin!
I was wrong to take people's goods.
I promise to hand them back!
Read it loud!
Me, Siu Hing is a pimp.
It's not my mum's birthday,
I wanna rip off!
I am bad to my family!
I am a beast!
Louder!
I deserve what I should!
If not, you chop me!
Retreat!
Hit the drum!
Let's go!
Please stay out, let's go!
- Are you alright?
- You betrayer!
Mum, a cup of tea!
Let's drink!
I'm very happy!
All working people had
a debt written in blood and tears.
They want to take revenge!
They wanna avenge!
Finish the power, release the people.
To be the master, and see the sun again!
Good!
we need one more person to play Mahjong!
You match with my sister.
Come, meet my good friend!
we were like brothers in war!
King San!
- Nick name "wolf"!
- Boss Yeung!
Just call me "wolf"!
- Li Ming Pal!
- How are you?
- Boss Pal!
- Come, sit down!
we done well at Tung wong!
How did you know?
we got rich in few years time.
Guess what we do?
Friend's friend told me that.
Let's play Mahjong!
You suspect their l.D. since Sunday?
why tell me after 3 days?
Don't forget that we are cops!
No sympathy on criminals!
Ah Fu and I were in 169 squad.
we stayed together.
He may be a criminal now.
He is upsetting the society.
Don't be too passionate!
when we were fighting
with the Vietkung in 79.
I was hit by a bomb!
And Ah Fu was shot too.
But he carried me for four miles!
And he had saved my life!
My job is to charge him today!
I feel guilty.
I didn't get to sleep lately?
People look down on the men from China,
all because of people like Ah Fu.
They commit crimes here!
They become thieves here!
They should be kept in jail!
Shut up, father is dead?
Shut up your dirty mouth!
You can never be a gentleman.
I am sorry, my dad is in the hospital!
I hope that he will recover!
Boss, your shrimp dumplings are good!
Did your dad teach you?
Yes, my dad is from Shan Tung!
To have shrimp dumplings now
is meaningful!
we can pay our respect to your dad!
King San, you said you like my dumplings.
I had spent a whole day, do have some!
Come, it's cold!
It's a chance Cheung Chow
asks for our help!
He has been a sales representative!
Try to press him to tell us!
Then we will have a lot of cases!
Please come in!
Cheung Chow!
Thanks for coming!
The deal was $350,000!
The Kwong brothers said I lied!
Obviously they put pressure on us?
They don't keep their words!
That's why I hate "Big Circles"!
No, I mean the people!
That spoils your image!
Some one is fooling around.
The Kwong brothers are very mysterious.
They seldom fix up
with other men from China.
The usual place they go
is the Mahjong house.
They play for high stakes,
minimum is $500.
The source of money is unknown.
It's the 1st time
they wanna trade with Cheung Chow.
How many people will go together?
The four of them make up an army!
The Kwongs won't be
afraid of Cheung Chow.
Don't know who will
stand for Cheung Chow!
So they will have their guns.
Pal, keep calm!
what? I am not an executor!
I am afraid your mind
is filled with killings,
and no passion!
I have the mid-night show tickets!
Remember to pick us up in this area!
I know, you have said a hundred times!
I have got the mid-night show tickets!
Right, the four Kwongs
are really brothers?
Yes!
why?
How is it?
I had grabbed a rubber
called Kwong in Kong Sai!
But he should have two brothers.
was it that co-incidental?
The data have no trace
that they are in H.K.
I don't think so!
Heung Tung! King San!
Hok Kwan! Come on...!
- Come in!
- Please!
Please come in!
No body here!
what would you like to drink?
Po Lee, Sau Mei, Jasmine, all of them!
Right!
This way please!
- Damn, it really is he!
- what shall we do?
Be alert, get ready at any time!
Remember, never expose our identity!
Come in, please!
The bosses have gone to call you!
Come...please!
This is Boss Hoi, Boss Hok,
Boss Ming, Boss Chu!
Tung! San! King!
we are of the same origin.
we can feel free! Alright?
- Hoi, what would you like?
- Lung Chan!
Lung Chan, get me a bottle of Lung Chan!
Yes!
They just came out?
They are from Check Lai.
They had no alternative, so they left.
The fight at Tung wong restaurant
was done by them!
Tung, you look familiar!
where did we meet before?
I can remember even just seeing once!
Have you ever stayed
in Kwong Sai Kwai Lam?
No chance,
I stayed in Canton all the time!
How come you stayed there all the time?
what did you say?
You should know
the language of Kwong Sai!
Pals, are you talking
business or kidding?
Can you tell me?
You had worked at
the Kwai Lam Security Dept?
It's you, can't escape!
You have gun wound on your arm,
what does it mean?
I told you that
politeness can make money already!
- He asks me to look for you!
- How is he?
He won't get through!
Ah Kong...I am Leung!
what do you want to tell me?
who did this?
I will finish them for you!
Kwong Sai Security office,
"Big Circle" undercover!
Ah Kong!
Hide the instrument!
Call the police,
say he came here himself.
I have not been here, understand?
Understand!
FUCK! FUCK!
what's that meaning?
The headline-4 got killed in the public!
Trouble this time!
Sir, they discovered that
Heung Tung is a cop.
If their identity got revealed.
They can't carry out their duty anymore.
They have to go back to China!
Shut up, none of your business here!
First in Tung wong Rest.
It's the second time.
So what if they recognize you?
A cop back there,
a thief here is the same.
Many cops turn to be thieves here!
You are too nervous!
It's impossible!
China cops will never be thieves.
They have pistols!
Can't we self-defend ourselves?
we're a policeman!
It's our job to fight crime,
we have to be tough!
Here is Hong Kong,
it's a place of law and order.
we can't just kill the thieves.
You are only a sneaker!
I sneak in only for freedom.
Please do respect me!
Shut up, or I put you in jail!
And send you back
to Mainland China. Fuck.
Yours friends could be
the ones we look for!
They killed 2 guards and a pedestrian!
Hurting four policemen,
keep an eye on them!
Catch them alive!
Sir, how is Cheung Chow!
I hide him in an isolated room.
He has nightmares everyday!
Let's go!
Let's go to have some bear!
Beer! Not bear! FUCK!
will Ah Fu come back?
He is missing for a few days.
So hot!
The air-cond. is no good,
you want some beer?
I get it myself!
So hot!
Don't be shy, you are old enough!
Put on your clothes,
I got to talk to you!
Actually we can talk about anything!
It wasn't time to let Ah Fu tell you!
I think you can guess!
we plan to rob the bank!
There will be around $7.0M.
I hope you two can help me!
Some beer!
why look for us suddenly?
well, you are cruel enough!
And because of Ah Fu, we can trust you!
Our old partners are gone!
And they can't have the share!
God, come again!
Madam, help, madam...Come again!
It's O.K., Mariana!
Him, my darling, O.K.!
OK, I see!
That team of people?
who knows who did it?
There was no uniform, no writing!
The "Big Circle"!
Because of your Mariana!
You let people in so easily!
I was drying my hair when they rushed in.
Did they insult you?
No!
But hit me, ask me where
Cheung Chow was hiding.
Look at my fingers!
Oh no!
I don't care, they have taken anything!
YOU STUPlD!
I was going to kill myself!
Stop that darling, don't cry!
How much did you lose?
Altogether is more than $200,000!
That much?
where are you going?
Anywhere, just to leave this place!
How can I face them, they trust me!
Let me think!
I can protect you, don't go!
Can you protect me for my whole life?
Those people warned me
of telling the truth.
Or they will hurt me on my face!
I know you were involved
in Cheung Chow's case.
I won't betray you!
Because I can't help loving you!
Forget it, Hok Kwan!
we better break up!
Darling, don't leave me alone.
I will die without you!
My heart breaks without seeing you!
But shorten the pain!
It won't be good if we stay together.
You don't have a steady income!
And I worry about your life!
It's only my fancy!
I will go with you if I had $350,000!
we go to Hawaii!
And start all over again!
$350,000 is not a problem!
But I can't leave!
Don't you have a passport?
I can get you a forge passport!
Then we can go anywhere!
It's no use having the passport!
why?
I can't tell you!
So you lie to me!
You only play with me!
I can swear...!
I really want to marry you!
Go to hell, I won't trust you!
O.K. I tell you!
But you have to keep to secret!
I am an informer!
The police wants us to be undercovers!
what?
what's wrong?
Nothing!
I didn't know that you love your parents!
My mum died early!
I live with my dad!
He is proud of me as a cop!
He is a good teacher!
This time I sneaked into Hong Kong!
He was questioned real hard.
So, if my dad died because of me.
what do I do?
It looks like raining!
Nothing I can do!
Let's talk business!
who is behind the four brothers?
Don't know?
It was said that I was responsible!
It gets on me!
But nobody will know you did it!
I will hide away in the New Territories!
For how long?
Hard to say!
I wait till things calm down!
I am used to this way of living!
Sorry!
I now realize your way of life!
I am tough, I survive!
I haven't been to wars.
But look at me!
I have stitches allover my body!
Some by thieves, some by police.
To do my job it's been 1 3 years.
Don't know what I look like!
An informer will die sooner or later!
The cops think that I am a thief.
The thief may think that I am a cop!
I worry all the time!
You can stay on for two years and change.
As for me?
I have no friends and my wife is gone!
To be pessimistic!
I won't have the national salute!
what do you think?
You say it!
Damn it!
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand!
Do you know!
But you were quite smart!
I know you look down on me!
You said that I was a worthless coward.
Right? Don't deny that!
I felt that you were bad!
And now?
But you are a real pal!
I know, you don't have to say!
I will retire after this year.
I have saved more than $100,000!
I can run my own business!
This is for you!
For me?
Really?
Your dumplings are good!
Give me some more other time!
How many can you have? 50?
80!
Kill me...!
Kill me, I don't know anything!
Bastard, something wrong here?
I give you a chance, tell me who did it!
I'll fulfill your wish to be a hero!
I...I don't know!
Let me punch him and let the rats...
get into his mouth.
Then he will talk!
O.K. have you got back your memories!
I want you to tell me a few names!
Damn it!
I'll kill you!
You want to be a hero!
Is it worthwhile?
They have saved my life.
I have put myself to death already.
How is it?
He won't tell, kill him!
You have got guts!
Tung!
- what? Is he die?
- Yes.
I tell you all!
Biggy was actually killed by you!
I don't want promotion because of you!
I'll be fired soon!
The commissioners
wants you under custody.
The legal dept. wants to prosecute you.
If no prosecution,
they send you back in 24 hrs.
- Sir!
- Stop.
I am useless!
I can't control the three of you.
we have finished many cases!
So I ask for amnesty!
Go to fix up wolf's team,
there could be a chance.
How are they now?
They ask us to be
ready the job in 24 hours.
- The same bank you said before?
- Yes!
Do as you are told!
And your dad is dead!
There was a telex at your place...
Sorry!
Sir, was there any word from my father?
I don't know! Sorry!
Damn it, we work hard for him!
Now he send us back, what does it mean?
You say it!
Tung, Mr. Ching is cunning!
we stop Ah Fu's operation!
No!
we have started, we have to insist on!
I don't know what for!
He has no mercy, your dad just died!
You betrayed your friend.
why? why finish the cases?
There are 20,000 police in H.K.
why we have to do the investigation?
Just for staying here?
Mr. Ching has got our weak point.
Even if we worked for 2 years,
he won't let us go.
He will force us to carry on.
And he gets promoted!
And we have more enemies.
we will end up like Biggy!
I'm afraid!
I dreamt we went to Hawaii!
And sun bathing on the beach!
In pairs!
Me and Diana, King San with Hung!
You won't believe it Tung.
Your girl has good figure!
Hok Kwan, we can't go anywhere
without a passport.
I was dreaming!
we have nowhere to go!
I am sorry, miss!
Don't worry, it's O.K.!
Thanks!
Let's go!
Immigration?
I wanna report a Chinese male,
using a Li Tai Chung passport...
He will take flight BC-100!
He is 5'4", short hair, big eyes!
The money has been exchanged?
It's in the bag!
would the customs look at immigration?
H.K. has no financial control!
Let's go!
what's upsetting?
No, I am happy.
You don't miss me?
Don't worry, it's O.K.!
Let's go!
You line up first, I go to get the drug!
will be a change your passport!
Mister. Can I have your passport?
Mister. Please come with me,
we want to talk with you!
Don't go!
My heart beats fast, go quick!
Don't worry, it's O.K.!
He knew the end at To Kwa wan!
I'll kill you!
Get away! Get away quickly!
Oh no!
what are you doing?
You want to die!
- You take a look over there!
- No!
And you check the taxi station!
Tung!
He's take the money gone?
Hok Kwan, open the door!
The money is evidence,
what do you want to do?
I thought Diana really loved me!
She said she would follow me!
why did you come back?
She deceived me!
She has another man,
she betrayed me at the airport.
She told the immigration
that I had a forged passport!
I managed to escaped!
And fought with the police.
I snatched a gun and hurt the man.
How dare you!
Cheung Chow's case is under proceeding.
we have to return the money in two days.
The money is now lost.
And you made a mess in the airport.
we will end up in jail?
- Tung!
- Go away!
I know I was wrong, I am sorry!
I don't deserve surviving!
I die for my wrong doings!
Go away!
It doesn't help
even if you shoot yourself!
when we came here,
we said live and die together.
You kill yourself
at this critical moment.
That proves you are a chicken!
You are irresponsible...
you should be sorry to me and King San!
If you have the guts, pull the trigger!
Those ballroom-girl,
do they know about you?
I have told her!
Hok Kwan!
Ah Fu!
Get in!
Ah Fu, you've come here at night!
Are you ready to get rich?
we gather here and do it tomorrow!
we have a meeting tonight.
Cheer up, let's go!
It's here, come in!
Leave your pager here, and stay here!
Come, sit!
The few million dollars are over there.
we go over after seeing the armor truck.
we can see if anything goes wrong.
No traffic jam, good spot!
I'll tell you the details!
Relax!
Come, sit!
$100 or $200?
Yes!
what are you doing here?
To cook!
Be careful tomorrow for your first time!
My brother will take care of you!
I'll be careful!
whenever my brother commits a crime.
I can't sleep for weeks!
I have to worry about you too.
Promise me you'll be alright!
Bad smell, go to hell...
Is he alright?
O.K.!
Something wrong with you?
He's like this every time!
To be ready for the fight!
It's O.K. if we had one less.
Don't worry, it will be O.K.!
He is very brutal doing his job!
I do whenever my brother tells me!
If he wants me dead, I'll kill myself!
See, he is bloody mad, Pak Man!
Nine blocks already, be careful!
Can't contact him!
They have joined the gang!
And they will go along with the project.
we carry out our plan before dawn!
The three Kin-Luen bastards!
will be trapped with the gang tomorrow.
If there was exchange of fire.
would they be hurt too?
An hour ago, the special task force!
Have got their pictures!
But it's hard to say if it is chaotic!
I want to talk to you alone!
About the incidence
at the airport tonight.
It was done by Hok Kwan!
Your understand was a total failure.
In the past year,
they had commit a lot of serious crime.
In other words, if it got revealed.
The police will be attacked by the media.
we don't have our future anymore.
Lucky only you and I know about it!
If they all get killed tomorrow!
Then nothing has ever happened!
Do you know what I mean?
Yours!
They are from America!
I made this out of copper!
It is a little bit heavy.
Normal pistols can't make a hole on it.
Come, King San, look!
I don't trust this!
You are freshman, you wear it!
Something wrong with him!
Miss, we're the police.
Can we stay on the balcony!
Nobody's home!
we're special task force!
we wanna stay on the balcony...
to keep an eye on the bank!
My mum is out, can't let you in!
I wish that you can help, it's fatal!
I am a woman, not convenient!
Next door would be O.K.
Impossible!
A police was attacked at the airport.
A suspect with forged passport.
Snatched the police pistol
and hurting a man.
Our reporter has
interviewed the two victims.
It's him, he has robbed my money!
He is a cop from China!
He said he was a Chinese policeman.
Now working as an informer.
what did the police respond?
They deny it, but I don't believe them!
The police is not trying to catch him.
He is at large
and can always threaten me!
I want 24 hours protection
from the police.
Police from China?
You killed the Kwong brothers.
Hok Kwan, they have the lighter.
They killed Biggy!
Open the door...what's happening inside?
Tung, are you alright?
Look Hok Kwan!
Send someone to search the top!
Hok Kwan!
Ah Fu...!
You betrayed me!
King San...!
Don't move!
The ones in the alley,
you have 3 minutes!
Drop your weapons or I forced out!
Sir, they are coming out!
Don't shoot!
I'll kill him whoever fires!
I am Hok Kwan!
Is Mr. Ching here? I wanna see him!
Move back, did you hear me?
Or we die together!
Fire!
Mr. Ching.
Don't come over, move back 20 yards.
Move back 20 yards, it's an order!
You betrayed us?
If you fire, you get shot!
I don't care!
It's no use killing me!
It's not my idea to kill Hok Kwan.
It was an order, I didn't agree.
I had argued with them,
but they wouldn't listen.
Your were a soldier,
you should understand.
The lower ranks
have to obey all the time.
And Hok Kwan made such a big mess...
he was surely sentenced to death.
To sacrifice him,
I've got an alternative.
Then I can help you!
Li Heung Tung, trust me!
I promise you be alright!
That's an order, but don't have to obey!
If I was ordered to kill a kid!
I won't obey!
I am conscientious!
You gave the order,
so you are responsible!
Li Heung Tung, do you want to stay?
Don't lie to me, I won't trust you!
what did we say when sneaking in...
to live and die together!
Goodbye!