[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,STKaiti,20,&H00E0E0E0,&HF0000000,&H000D0500,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.41,0:00:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0001,,--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--\N更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.30,0:00:20.52,Default,,0000,0000,0001,,影片压制: 犇犇    字幕制作: 犇犇\N招募Q号: 76846146
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.58,0:01:42.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,七十年代 潮州大亨 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.58,0:01:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雄霸一方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.50,0:01:46.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢嘅得力手下入边有两兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.45,0:01:49.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大佬阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.20,0:01:52.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,细佬阿国
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.91,0:01:56.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国系剂哥嘅指定继承人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.25,0:02:01.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大佬阿勇好妒忌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.66,0:02:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了讨好阿剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.08,0:02:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就将自己单恋嘅对像介绍俾阿剂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.08,0:02:19.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一次阿勇为了钱 杀了剂哥嘅恩人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.33,0:02:22.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国不惜同剂哥翻面来保阿勇条命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:25.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥一怒之下就将佢两兄弟赶走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.25,0:02:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国觉得好对剂哥唔住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.29,0:02:32.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又同阿勇发生了严重嘅冲突
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.29,0:02:39.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是就决定退出江湖 远走马六甲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.45,0:02:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重新做人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.16,0:03:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,八十年代
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.50,0:03:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥以心狠手辣嗰起江湖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.16,0:03:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢发誓要将剂哥赶尽杀绝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.66,0:04:26.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.25,0:04:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愿主耶稣基督嘅恩惠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.58,0:04:32.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,节哀顺变
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.08,0:04:38.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣灵嘅感动 常在我等众人之中 阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.70,0:04:41.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啱啱收到风 冯三唔系意外死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.37,0:04:42.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系邓家勇派人对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.29,0:04:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇喺那边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.50,0:04:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 除帽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.33,0:05:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李阿剂嚟了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.25,0:05:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.62,0:05:21.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有冇收到我寄俾你嘅圣诞咭？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.00,0:05:23.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你年年都咁有我心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.33,0:05:27.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥带我出身
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.95,0:05:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我嘅全家人都受过佢好多恩惠
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.41,0:05:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后见到剂哥 要第一时间立正见礼知吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.75,0:05:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系 剂哥 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.62,0:05:38.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有事走先
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.70,0:05:48.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我旧时唔听话 剂哥打了我一枪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.70,0:05:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家番风落雨仲系有啲痛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.95,0:05:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我永远都会记住 警惕吓自己做人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.95,0:06:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那枪我都有啲后悔 打歪啲就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.50,0:06:17.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李阿剂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.91,0:06:21.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,睇你得戚得几耐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.54,0:06:23.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出年唔驶寄圣诞咭俾佢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.87,0:06:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系 勇哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.95,0:06:51.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜咁得闲 表姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.75,0:06:53.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚟搵阿爸坐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.25,0:06:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜你唔驶服侍阿剂 帮佢老婆洗底衫裤？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.41,0:06:59.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你做埋咁多阴侧事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.83,0:07:02.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜擒日行雷冇将你劈死咩？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.33,0:07:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你车阿爸去边？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.62,0:07:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舅父去马六甲 同你细佬一齐住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.87,0:07:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜你系佢个仔都唔知
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.41,0:07:18.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系嘛 阿爸去游埠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.58,0:07:21.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,游你个屎忽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.16,0:07:23.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇你啲咁嘅衰仔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.66,0:07:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做埋啲伤天害理嘅事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.75,0:07:30.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算俾你搵钱多李嘉诚 有鬼用咩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.91,0:08:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚系佢地结婚周年
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.91,0:08:03.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜系屋企摆酒呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.29,0:08:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系 我地几个人简简单单咁食饭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.70,0:08:09.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.79,0:08:11.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉叔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.00,0:08:13.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉叔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.91,0:08:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.25,0:08:23.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠又冇话我听 我地人情都冇做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.08,0:08:24.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔驶客气啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.50,0:08:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系勒 听日你去马六甲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.16,0:08:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系呀 我专登嚟同你辞行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.00,0:08:33.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉叔 我执定啲高丽参
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.87,0:08:35.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔该你同我带过去俾阿国
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.33,0:08:38.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿嫂你真有心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.25,0:08:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 阿勇太过对你唔住
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.45,0:08:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唯有代佢向你认错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.54,0:08:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠就唔同啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.33,0:08:54.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢话如果你一路请佢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.66,0:08:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢话你做到绉晒皮佢都做喎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.62,0:09:00.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠真系好帮得我地手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.12,0:09:04.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系呀 宝儿 有份礼物送俾你倩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.25,0:09:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢喎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.45,0:09:10.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老婆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.66,0:09:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你估我今年送乜野礼物俾你？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.16,0:09:17.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你叫乜名呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.79,0:09:19.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我？我叫宝儿罗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.79,0:09:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好靓呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.66,0:09:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥真系浪漫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.25,0:09:45.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.83,0:09:48.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,写啲乜野？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.37,0:09:50.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿呀 我妈咪个名
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.87,0:09:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿号呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.20,0:10:19.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.75,0:10:23.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.20,0:10:26.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.16,0:10:29.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢系我老婆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.91,0:10:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你老婆阿花？好靓女喎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.04,0:10:36.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行勒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.08,0:10:37.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我阿爸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.95,0:10:39.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.04,0:10:40.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马拉仔呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.37,0:10:43.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢系马拉仔呀？咁高大了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.62,0:10:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上车 阿爸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.83,0:11:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.95,0:11:24.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成班马骝上晒你架车
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.25,0:11:26.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢地都系我啲仔女嚟呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.87,0:11:28.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系咩？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.12,0:11:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸 上车先勒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.12,0:11:39.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国 后边成班细路系你收养的？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.00,0:11:41.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.54,0:11:51.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后面有条细路
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.83,0:11:54.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,十足十你细果阵时咁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.70,0:12:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次见你阵时 你都系咁细个咋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.95,0:12:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁快三十年咯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.83,0:12:19.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正衰仔 你阿哥虽然系我亲生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.66,0:12:21.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系佢一啲都唔似我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.25,0:12:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,专门做埋出卖朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.20,0:12:29.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢再系咁搞落去 迟早佢有报应
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.29,0:12:33.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我临走嘅时候同佢嘈了一场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.91,0:12:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睇佢系想整死剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.91,0:12:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真系替剂哥担心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.58,0:12:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜发财 恭喜…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.62,0:12:46.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万事如意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.04,0:12:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生意兴隆
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.79,0:12:50.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吗？我地过那边倾吓
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.62,0:12:52.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.00,0:12:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿 俾啲利是细路
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.79,0:13:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫AUNTIE
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.33,0:13:02.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.58,0:13:07.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地档海城酒楼搞吓搞吓咁搞了成年
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.91,0:13:09.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地早啲合作就好勒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.79,0:13:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔知可以搵几多钱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.20,0:13:16.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谂番起以前斗生斗死 真系赣居
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.66,0:13:20.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界唔同勒 而家乜野都讲企业化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.16,0:13:25.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都仔大女大 唔通郁啲讲打讲杀咩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.62,0:13:29.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我个女成日落DISCO
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.70,0:13:32.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又唔俾心机读书 激死我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.25,0:13:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就够运勒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.00,0:13:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,条靓仔系圣保罗男女校读 年年都考三名之内
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.66,0:13:41.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下个礼拜仲参加演讲比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.45,0:13:46.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上个月冯三出殡 唔见你来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.83,0:13:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲同佢唔妥呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.20,0:13:53.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲有乜妥唔妥呀 呢啲场面可免则免
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.45,0:13:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话勒 同我个时候蒲出来嘅大佬
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.20,0:14:00.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死吓一个 死吓一个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.87,0:14:04.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩番我勒 耀保 肥秋咯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.41,0:14:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坐埋都唔够一台麻雀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.66,0:14:09.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我地呢班老野死晒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.25,0:14:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啲后生就坐馆 咁就蟹咁行勒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.95,0:14:18.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要睇住呢个阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.33,0:14:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢排佢同班年轻人行得好埋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.62,0:14:30.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都知道呢个契弟佢系养唔熟嘅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.12,0:14:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我夹紧佢 睇佢几时作我反
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.29,0:14:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇呢条友仔仍然一路都唔妥你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.29,0:15:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一饮大两杯就话要买起你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.62,0:15:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我闹过佢几次 最近就冇提
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.50,0:15:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过成日系我背后搞搞阵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.08,0:15:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢好想连我都买起埋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.62,0:15:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你打算点呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.12,0:15:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要佢唔过得呢个正月
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.87,0:15:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要谂清楚 呢啲嘅免得就免
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.00,0:16:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.50,0:16:15.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱老大 安排好晒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.70,0:16:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.87,0:16:38.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过去一年多得大家咁帮得手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.91,0:16:41.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁住今日春茗 我敬大家一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.58,0:16:48.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,邓家勇 你发鸡盲？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.29,0:16:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你睇唔到我坐系度咩？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.62,0:16:53.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我请春茗 你抢住嚟敬酒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.54,0:16:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新正头 同班兄弟饮番杯 咁都有罪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.08,0:17:03.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你讲有罪 叠叠埋埋厚过本数簿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.75,0:17:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你楂Fit嘅生意 那啲数唔清唔楚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.08,0:17:08.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,旧年你吞三百六十七万公数
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.37,0:17:16.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又同啲台湾佬勾结 系公海度抢番公司嘅货
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.95,0:17:20.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁都未算呀 跟了我廿几年个阿祥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.62,0:17:23.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上个礼拜顶你几句 你就买起佢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.70,0:17:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟住埋佢条尸系水塘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.79,0:17:28.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你简真系当我死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.66,0:17:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,契弟呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.41,0:17:38.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家话 佢咁嘅行为抵唔抵死？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.58,0:17:41.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我而家就处置你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.37,0:17:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你地作反哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.50,0:17:59.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇错 我地系作反 老野
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.66,0:18:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地净系识勇哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.29,0:18:05.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家唔好开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.25,0:18:09.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己人 无谓两败俱伤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.04,0:18:11.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,摆低枪先再讲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.00,0:18:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,婆佬你以后跟我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.37,0:19:05.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做啥？有啥事呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.04,0:19:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱老大饮醉酒打勇哥 勇哥避得两避
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.83,0:19:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朱老大跌了落地
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.50,0:19:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔觉意插落个酒樽度 插死咯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.16,0:19:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.70,0:19:39.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔系想过问你生意上啲野
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.37,0:19:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系咁多年嚟 我未见过你好似呢轮咁多心事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.91,0:19:48.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你可唔可以同我讲呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.16,0:19:50.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地唔止系夫妻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.33,0:19:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲系好朋友嚟 系唔系？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.20,0:20:01.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最近先知道原来阿勇以前曾轻追你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.37,0:20:05.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直对呢个人都冇好感
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.08,0:20:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,近年来嚟佢啲所作所为仲更加乞我憎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.33,0:20:13.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢而家搞你呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.00,0:20:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢最近拉拢啲人嚟对付我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.50,0:20:19.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当年佢为作讨好我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.62,0:20:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然将自己心爱嘅人都介绍得俾我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.79,0:20:25.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话呢个人几冇人性
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.37,0:20:29.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁你而家谂住点做？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.91,0:20:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打算约佢出嚟倾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.83,0:20:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你主动去约阿勇出嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.41,0:20:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢会觉得你怕了佢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.62,0:20:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且一向冇咁低威
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.50,0:20:47.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂 你系唔系为了我地两母子？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.08,0:20:49.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就系担心佢会搞你地
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.16,0:20:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔需要咁做
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.79,0:20:57.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔开心 我地都唔会开心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.66,0:21:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果为了我同安仔 要你夹硬委屈自己
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.83,0:21:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会觉得唔安乐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.12,0:21:27.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安仔 点嘛 钟唔钟意呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.91,0:21:28.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,钟意
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.91,0:21:29.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就买佢叻
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.79,0:21:30.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.91,0:21:39.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚟 安仔 我地走
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.33,0:21:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.95,0:21:46.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪 系咪走呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.83,0:21:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等阵先
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.25,0:21:54.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你个仔生得咁高大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.75,0:21:57.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年几岁呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.12,0:22:01.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成个古惑仔咁 似十足你个衰老豆
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.41,0:22:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你MIT得我好痛呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.41,0:22:10.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话如果个仔系你帮我生嘅 你话几好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.12,0:22:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对唔住 阿勇 我地赶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.12,0:22:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.66,0:22:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就快情人节啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.08,0:22:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,预早送定张咭比你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.25,0:22:29.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已轻结了婚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.54,0:22:32.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真系唔明
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.00,0:22:35.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实李阿剂有乜野咁好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.50,0:22:38.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行路脚挣都唔到地 实短命
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.87,0:22:41.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你尊重啲 唔好再咒我老公呀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.95,0:22:43.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.66,0:22:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢 唔该
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.41,0:22:49.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿嫂 走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.70,0:22:51.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啲野办齐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.91,0:22:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安仔 乜野事呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.29,0:22:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个唔知乜野阿勇嘅 MIT到我块面瘀鬼晒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.37,0:23:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又讲啲野撩阿妈 又咒阿爸短命添
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.45,0:23:05.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.95,0:23:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,邓家勇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.04,0:23:43.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 等我地
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.83,0:24:08.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.25,0:24:10.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.83,0:24:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿 你冇事呀嘛？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.45,0:24:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行开呀 唔好掂我妈咪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.20,0:24:17.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你冇事呀嘛？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.70,0:24:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走开 衰人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.29,0:24:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪 你点呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.04,0:24:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好打了 仲打乜鬼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.37,0:24:33.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲打
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.83,0:24:51.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,千祈唔好话俾剂哥听
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.70,0:24:53.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔想呢件事搞大
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.29,0:24:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知唔知？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.20,0:25:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.87,0:25:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坐
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.45,0:25:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李生 饮乜呀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.95,0:25:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,俾杯咖啡我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.04,0:25:25.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.66,0:25:27.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.58,0:25:29.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我死唔去喎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.87,0:25:34.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我系罗湖桥调番出来 仲扎职添
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.08,0:25:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对你嚟讲 系唔系坏消息？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.83,0:25:40.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系咩？恭喜你喎 张SIR
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.25,0:25:43.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,张SIR 你阻住我喎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.79,0:25:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对唔住…原来约了侯警司呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.20,0:25:48.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 佢骚扰你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.16,0:25:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇 我啱啱讲我自己啲赣居野
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.50,0:25:55.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又唔识擦鞋 又唔收黑钱
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.08,0:25:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,俾人整蛊 炖了几年冬菇咯
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.66,0:26:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点似侯SIR你咁发啦 系纽约开几间餐厅
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.58,0:26:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你咁讲 我告你毁谤呀
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.87,0:26:08.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潮流兴废话 我唔阻你地
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.41,0:26:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地各有各埋堆
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.37,0:26:13.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我呢返过去个啲廉洁警务人员个度
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.91,0:26:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,侯SIR 你同呢个流氓大亨好倾
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.33,0:26:19.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我听日打电话俾你老细
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.95,0:26:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你呀侯SIR
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.25,0:26:24.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 我会夹住你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.95,0:26:27.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你出街唔好泵烟头落地
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.12,0:26:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢个世界真系物以类聚 你睇吓佢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.33,0:26:46.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老侯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.12,0:26:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你估好不好由你出面 约阿勇出来大家倾
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.45,0:26:56.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明你意思 剂哥 放心
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.54,0:26:58.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同你做了咁耐兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.66,0:27:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我实帮你整死阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.12,0:27:16.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 今日咁高兴 几大要饮多杯
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.66,0:27:17.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.41,0:27:21.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.00,0:27:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胜嘅
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.29,0:27:29.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,添啲呀
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.54,0:27:31.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.79,0:27:35.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火呀 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.41,0:27:40.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔该
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.66,0:27:46.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你都知道 海城同埋海天酒楼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.91,0:27:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系我同朱老大搞开
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.79,0:27:51.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做酒楼我系外行
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.12,0:27:53.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后有乜野 剂哥你楂主意得嘅
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.79,0:27:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家有商有量好啲嘅
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.20,0:27:58.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一路落嚟 我地有啲误会
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.54,0:28:01.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想趁侯SIR系度 大家讲清楚佢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.50,0:28:03.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇 冇误会
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.54,0:28:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家好朋友嚟嘛 侯SIR哦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.20,0:28:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系呀 当然系好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.58,0:28:09.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好朋友要饮三杯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.04,0:28:12.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我差唔多啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.54,0:28:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系呀 剂哥你不褛都好饮得
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.12,0:28:18.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系年纪大了 连酒量都差埋
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.58,0:28:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,睇你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.79,0:28:24.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.87,0:28:38.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后就大家和平相处
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.75,0:28:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 乜你讲到同我一齐 好似唔太平咁
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.87,0:28:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做乜呀 你惊我郁你呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.37,0:28:51.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔怪得带埋咁多残兵上嚟啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.08,0:28:55.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇的 我一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.54,0:28:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家饮酒之嘛 又唔系打交
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.66,0:29:03.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驶乜带咁多人上嚟啦啦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.79,0:29:06.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又唔好咁讲 佢地都系你嘅老友
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.95,0:29:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁耐冇见 大家上嚟见吓面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.91,0:29:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系 我地以前都系跟剂哥搵食
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.33,0:29:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实剂哥冇乜野 叫佢地吩咐我做得嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.95,0:29:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使乜亲自上嚟咁客气
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.12,0:29:28.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你真系惊我郁你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.66,0:29:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁你就唔好咁屎忽鬼 教朱老大嚟杀我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.50,0:29:38.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家杀我唔到 自己发弟腾
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.91,0:29:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以前冇咁衰仔
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.83,0:29:46.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做乜 而家又唔饮得
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.66,0:29:48.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连胆都冇埋呀
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.45,0:29:53.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 讲说话 唔该你客气好喎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.54,0:30:09.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我根本就唔知道 你同朱老大之闲搞啲乜野
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.04,0:30:12.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人地嘅家事 我从来唔俾意见
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.20,0:30:14.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好以为我怕你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.70,0:30:18.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我系唔想我同你之间嘅事 搞到见血
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.50,0:30:21.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜话 又同我讲打讲杀
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.62,0:30:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你够胆 系侯SIR 呢个高级警务人员面前
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.83,0:30:27.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,公然话同我大出血
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.50,0:30:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真系无法无天
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.08,0:30:36.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇 啲小姐嬲啦 要人等咁耐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.66,0:30:38.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啱晒 妈咪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.37,0:30:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地剂哥今晚好火呀
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.16,0:30:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同我执两件劲嘅 今晚陪佢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.70,0:30:47.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听朝一早同我报告剂哥嘅性能力
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.29,0:30:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,侯SIR 我有啲事 我走先啦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.12,0:30:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系老了连呢家野都唔掂系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.45,0:31:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 以前性能力好掂
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.50,0:31:04.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连我女朋友都俾佢抢走埋
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.08,0:31:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢而家嘅老婆咯
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.29,0:31:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过都系执我二摊 襟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.62,0:31:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老马都有火喎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.37,0:32:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我真系去错咗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.75,0:32:08.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,睇阿勇嘅态度 我地两边始终都要摊牌
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.29,0:32:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我嘅睇法就系要郁手先
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.16,0:32:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大眼讲得啱 要郁就郁到佢尽
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.16,0:32:16.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好俾机会佢地番身
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.83,0:32:20.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢几年嚟 大家啲心机挤晒落正行
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.79,0:32:25.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地最打得几位兄弟都变晒老人家
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.04,0:32:37.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家街度已经好多人同阿勇楂晒手
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.04,0:32:40.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话郁起上嚟 边个蚀底呀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.25,0:32:43.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果以快打慢 仲有啲机会
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.37,0:32:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话下下咁捱打 就死路一条
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.25,0:32:49.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.20,0:32:53.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安仔发烧呀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.54,0:32:54.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点解会这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.66,0:32:56.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今日落雨湿了身
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.08,0:32:58.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿已经俾了退烧药佢食
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.04,0:33:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系啱啱探热就一百零一度
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.08,0:33:01.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我即刻同佢去医院
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.08,0:33:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮我CALL齐啲人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.04,0:33:07.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搵挞静地嘅地方开会 到时先讲
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.91,0:33:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六 剂哥嘅人变晒 咁唔系办法
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.33,0:33:20.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睇我地要有啲打算先得
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.00,0:33:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驶唔驶叫阿泉预备车呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.75,0:33:29.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿泉睡了啦 我自己楂得啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.91,0:33:35.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 鞋带甩了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.50,0:33:39.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.12,0:33:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国打长途电话返嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.58,0:33:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话阿勇寄张咭给他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.20,0:33:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说外面有很多人想杀你
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.66,0:33:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇话保你唔住
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.66,0:33:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢叫阿国为你祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.33,0:33:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇又系度发神轻啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.54,0:34:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驶唔驶叫阿国返嚟？
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.50,0:34:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好神轻过敏啦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.66,0:34:05.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打个电话俾阿国听
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.33,0:34:11.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暑假我地成家过去住几日 早啲抖
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.41,0:34:40.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿哥
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.87,0:34:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,表姐打电话俾我 话你好唔妥阿剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.54,0:34:51.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我专登返嚟劝你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.20,0:34:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望你唔好咁做
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.41,0:35:02.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你错了 应该话你系嚟求我 放过李阿剂
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.95,0:35:04.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.58,0:35:07.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 就当我求你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.50,0:35:10.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你凭乜呀
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.66,0:35:13.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话晒我地咁多年兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.37,0:35:17.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟好应该俾面 自己人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.70,0:35:20.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你唔好唔记得
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.54,0:35:24.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你去马六甲之前 你讲过啲乜野呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.00,0:35:27.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你话过以后同我冇兄弟做嘅
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.54,0:35:32.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家有事兄弟 冇事契弟
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.37,0:35:41.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过咁
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.16,0:35:46.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你肯斟茶认错 我咪应承你咯
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.87,0:36:10.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 饮茶
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.20,0:36:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我系你大佬 你跪得低 我受得落
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.08,0:36:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跪啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.95,0:36:31.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿哥同你讲吓笑
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.45,0:36:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,细路 咪当饮杯新抱茶
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.12,0:36:39.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,娶个马拉妹都唔请我饮
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.29,0:36:49.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我讲明先 如果李阿剂撩事斗非先 唔关我事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.37,0:36:54.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到时你仲帮佢 我冇人情讲
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.79,0:36:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.33,0:37:08.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点嘛 啲马拉鸡皮肤好粗哦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.79,0:37:15.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你咁耐先返嚟一次
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.70,0:37:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饭都冇同你食过 你就话要走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.08,0:37:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,表姐 我嚟次返嚟求阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.33,0:37:23.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好话俾剂哥知
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.95,0:37:27.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知勒 不过阿勇系唔系 真系有诚意？
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.83,0:37:29.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢个人好冇口齿喎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.75,0:37:32.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睇暂时冇乜问题
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.04,0:37:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真系关心阿剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.04,0:37:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你成三十岁人 一路咁暗恋阿剂哥都唔系办法
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.29,0:37:47.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好理我 鬼叫我钟意佢咩 冇乜办法
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.70,0:37:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我呢个秘密千祈唔好话俾人听
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.33,0:37:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我俾两年时间你 如果你仲嫁唔出去
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.62,0:37:58.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就周街唱你嘅啦
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.79,0:38:16.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六 你去郁阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.66,0:38:18.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,需唔需要讲俾剂哥听？
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.29,0:38:20.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇第二个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.20,0:38:24.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我返唔到嚟 帮我睇住缸鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.33,0:38:27.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好难埋身嘅喎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.54,0:38:30.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盏冇命
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.41,0:38:33.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我上个礼拜问过盲公陈
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.91,0:38:36.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢话我最少有七十岁命
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.25,0:38:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.25,0:42:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六死了 系大眼出卖佢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.95,0:42:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家除了你 我都唔知可以信边个
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.79,0:42:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 够钟开会啦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.87,0:42:51.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得啦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.95,0:42:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮我睇住我老婆同我个仔
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.33,0:43:04.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,握住 必要时有用
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.75,0:43:35.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿泉 阵闲唔驶返嚟接我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.08,0:43:37.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你去接安仔放学啦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.00,0:43:39.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:44:14.45,0:44:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜事呀 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.58,0:44:17.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你出卖阿六
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.83,0:44:21.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇呀 我点会咁做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.08,0:44:23.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打电话去差馆CHECK过
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.50,0:44:27.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六穿了避弹衣 佢一枪都冇开过
Dialogue: 0,0:44:28.16,0:44:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系就俾人打到蜜蜂巢咁
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.79,0:44:33.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以佢嘅身手系绝对冇可能系咁
Dialogue: 0,0:44:34.12,0:44:37.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除非有人通水 等阿勇有晒准备
Dialogue: 0,0:44:40.79,0:44:42.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿六份人最口紧
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.91,0:44:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢件野佢只会俾两个人听
Dialogue: 0,0:44:46.70,0:44:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个就系我 一个就系你
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.45,0:44:53.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系你 系边个？
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.33,0:44:56.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 佢冇同我讲…
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.29,0:45:01.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我错
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.25,0:45:06.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好杀我 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.29,0:45:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我几咁希望自己嘅判断系错
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.70,0:45:11.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,估唔到你咁对阿六
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.33,0:45:15.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你系唔系癫了…你癫了呀…？
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.25,0:45:18.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我见你个人变晒
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.33,0:45:21.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知大家迟早玩完
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.91,0:45:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地实揽住一齐死 我啲仔女又细个
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.87,0:45:35.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔错都错了 我无话可讲 剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.08,0:46:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:46:58.29,0:47:01.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一而再 再而三咁 让邓家勇为了乜
Dialogue: 0,0:47:02.12,0:47:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系为了大家以后可以食多几年安乐茶饭
Dialogue: 0,0:47:06.29,0:47:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔驶吓吓要用条命出嚟搏
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.54,0:47:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好以为我阿剂真系变咗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.20,0:47:12.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变得俾人恰到面都唔敢横拖
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.79,0:47:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我而家就要对付阿勇
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.08,0:47:18.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望大家同我一条心去搏
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.83,0:47:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,边个想退出 可以即刻行出去
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.70,0:47:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系出卖兄弟嘅人 我系绝对唔放过
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.50,0:47:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 大炮华啱啱CALL我
Dialogue: 0,0:47:32.04,0:47:34.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢话飞龙会俾阿勇啲人搞到七彩咁喎
Dialogue: 0,0:47:35.33,0:47:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁大济 西环货仓俾人放火
Dialogue: 0,0:47:39.08,0:47:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 坚尼地道闲俾差佬封了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.75,0:47:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲拉了我十几个兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.50,0:47:48.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 电话
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.91,0:47:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.54,0:47:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜话 系老侯自己带队？
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.41,0:47:58.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去安仔学校度截住阿泉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:01.58,0:48:02.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.08,0:48:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老侯带队去我屋企切我生猪肉 话抄到粉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.54,0:48:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲带了我老婆返差馆
Dialogue: 0,0:48:08.87,0:48:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇夹埋老侯 想煲我一锅熟
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.58,0:48:15.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同佢地两个死过
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.41,0:48:18.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜你地开会带埋枪嚟嘅？
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.41,0:48:20.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你叫我地带嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.33,0:48:22.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇叫你带呀
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.62,0:48:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地个个带晒
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.04,0:48:26.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大眼话剂哥你吩咐
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.25,0:48:32.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 有差佬
Dialogue: 0,0:49:18.66,0:49:20.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 而家点？
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.37,0:49:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽量利用地形 准备突围出去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:49:24.62,0:49:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系
Dialogue: 0,0:49:25.75,0:49:29.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,入边啲人听住 你地已经被包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:30.20,0:49:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我限你地三分钟之内弃械投降
Dialogue: 0,0:49:33.62,0:49:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果唔系我地会用武力
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.91,0:49:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 出边架爬山车
Dialogue: 0,0:49:42.37,0:49:44.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我而家去抢过来 系后山个边冲出去
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.45,0:49:45.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一架车坐得几个人
Dialogue: 0,0:49:45.79,0:49:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只紧要剂哥你走得甩嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:49:47.20,0:49:48.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拳头 跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.12,0:49:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根叔 唔好呀 危险呀
Dialogue: 0,0:49:59.75,0:50:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好开枪 唔好
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.75,0:50:08.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根仔 你老豆中了枪
Dialogue: 0,0:50:08.54,0:50:11.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根仔 你老豆唔知死唔死得
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.62,0:50:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:15.91,0:50:16.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.16,0:50:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 如果冇你 我就冇今日
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.12,0:50:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同你抢架车返嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.91,0:50:24.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔准去
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.16,0:50:25.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔怕牺牲 唔准去
Dialogue: 0,0:50:28.16,0:50:29.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贺宾
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.20,0:50:29.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.91,0:50:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你地嘅枪罗晒嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:50:32.54,0:50:34.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲唔去 系
Dialogue: 0,0:51:12.50,0:51:16.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我而家自首 呢批枪系我
Dialogue: 0,0:51:16.58,0:51:21.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔关入面啲人事 要拉嘅拉我勒
Dialogue: 0,0:51:22.20,0:51:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好阻时候 我希望你叫白车
Dialogue: 0,0:51:24.91,0:51:26.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我有两位朋友伤得好紧要
Dialogue: 0,0:51:29.08,0:51:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫白车
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.20,0:51:34.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫白车嚟啦
Dialogue: 0,0:51:37.33,0:51:38.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根叔
Dialogue: 0,0:51:38.58,0:51:41.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 我冇用
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.00,0:51:45.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我抢唔到架车你
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.45,0:51:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心了 根叔 你好快冇事
Dialogue: 0,0:52:45.50,0:52:46.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老板
Dialogue: 0,0:52:47.75,0:52:50.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老爷 老爷
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.75,0:53:00.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你去拿车
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.33,0:53:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你地返出去先啦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.50,0:53:18.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.91,0:53:30.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 好对唔住 戏梗要做足
Dialogue: 0,0:53:30.12,0:53:33.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你同我嘅关系 唔驶讲啦
Dialogue: 0,0:53:34.25,0:53:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有乜野可以帮到你嘅？
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.66,0:53:42.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇录音机
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.37,0:53:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你几时认了邓家勇做契哥？
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.08,0:53:52.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 今日单野唔关我事
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.50,0:53:56.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三个月前总部已轻开了红皮File
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.33,0:53:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,话明要打你
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.70,0:54:01.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今日出到十三队人 我都系照ORDER做
Dialogue: 0,0:54:01.91,0:54:05.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 我都唔想赶尽你
Dialogue: 0,0:54:05.29,0:54:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老侯 你好野
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.41,0:54:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 我俾啲意见你
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.00,0:54:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你啃了藏毒 藏械两件
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.54,0:54:21.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其余我则则膊罗
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.45,0:54:27.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过到上堂果阵 你识点讲
Dialogue: 0,0:54:27.12,0:54:28.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔驶我教你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:54:30.79,0:54:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,识…你咁多年 你侯SIR点样擦我鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:54:36.41,0:54:38.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点样包庇我嘅档口
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.08,0:54:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一共嗒过我几多水
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.50,0:54:48.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你估你系咩呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:54:49.00,0:54:51.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你系绅士呀？你系烂鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:54:53.45,0:54:56.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上到法庭 法官信你定信我呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.25,0:55:00.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一共嗒过我几多水 我有晒纪录
Dialogue: 0,0:55:00.41,0:55:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜话 你抛我呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.75,0:55:08.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去到廉署饮咖啡果阵 睇下边个抛边个
Dialogue: 0,0:55:46.29,0:55:47.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死仆街
Dialogue: 0,0:55:50.58,0:55:52.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.79,0:55:59.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠
Dialogue: 0,0:56:19.91,0:56:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咪郁
Dialogue: 0,0:56:27.66,0:56:28.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.83,0:56:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,追佢
Dialogue: 0,0:56:52.29,0:56:53.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果边…
Dialogue: 0,0:57:15.33,0:57:16.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠
Dialogue: 0,0:58:13.20,0:58:15.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惠珠
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.08,0:58:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刘宝儿
Dialogue: 0,0:59:05.54,0:59:06.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有人保释你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:59:10.41,0:59:11.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我嘅当事人系入边
Dialogue: 0,0:59:12.08,0:59:14.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系佢保释你出嚟 请入嚟
Dialogue: 0,0:59:24.83,0:59:26.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你老公打死了侯SIR
Dialogue: 0,0:59:27.12,0:59:31.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲拒捕 袭警 俾差佬打了好多枪
Dialogue: 0,0:59:32.12,0:59:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家失了踪 唔知生定死
Dialogue: 0,0:59:36.91,0:59:37.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔信
Dialogue: 0,0:59:38.29,0:59:39.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,康律师
Dialogue: 0,0:59:40.62,0:59:41.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,件事系真
Dialogue: 0,0:59:51.66,0:59:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我呢世人只系做错一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:59:57.62,0:59:59.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就系将你介绍俾阿剂
Dialogue: 0,1:00:01.95,1:00:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁多年 我有好多女人
Dialogue: 0,1:00:08.79,1:00:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢地系我心内边冇地位
Dialogue: 0,1:00:14.29,1:00:19.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿 我一直都唔肯结婚 都系为了你
Dialogue: 0,1:00:23.04,1:00:24.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论你点误会我都好
Dialogue: 0,1:00:26.66,1:00:28.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你有乜野需要
Dialogue: 0,1:00:29.87,1:00:34.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算沕水舂墙 我无条件帮你
Dialogue: 0,1:00:40.04,1:00:41.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我太爱你啦
Dialogue: 0,1:00:45.58,1:00:49.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你呢种咁自私嘅人 系边个都唔会爱嘅
Dialogue: 0,1:00:50.66,1:00:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你净系识得爱你自己
Dialogue: 0,1:00:53.54,1:00:57.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前我唔钟意你 伤了你自尊心
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.62,1:01:02.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔忿气 系都要得到我先至心息
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.16,1:01:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你死条心啦
Dialogue: 0,1:01:10.12,1:01:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你睇吓你扮痴个衰样
Dialogue: 0,1:01:13.50,1:01:15.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我感动到要呕呀
Dialogue: 0,1:01:42.62,1:01:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你癫 你以为自己系皇帝
Dialogue: 0,1:01:45.20,1:01:46.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢度系差馆
Dialogue: 0,1:02:33.66,1:02:34.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安仔
Dialogue: 0,1:02:35.79,1:02:36.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪
Dialogue: 0,1:02:40.08,1:02:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿
Dialogue: 0,1:02:46.33,1:02:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我冇事
Dialogue: 0,1:03:12.91,1:03:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,1:03:20.95,1:03:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,1:03:44.95,1:03:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:02.08,1:04:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做咩？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:06.41,1:04:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我中了两枪
Dialogue: 0,1:04:08.83,1:04:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,驶唔驶叫医生
Dialogue: 0,1:04:10.62,1:04:14.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,食野先 几日冇餐饱
Dialogue: 0,1:04:20.08,1:04:21.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿
Dialogue: 0,1:04:26.54,1:04:27.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你冇乜变喎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:29.08,1:04:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老了好多
Dialogue: 0,1:04:33.95,1:04:35.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,个仔都咁大个
Dialogue: 0,1:04:35.66,1:04:36.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫叔叔
Dialogue: 0,1:04:37.54,1:04:38.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖
Dialogue: 0,1:04:39.45,1:04:42.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你离开了香港都有好多年
Dialogue: 0,1:05:29.54,1:05:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行山路上巴叻村都要三个几钟头
Dialogue: 0,1:05:33.87,1:05:36.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外边啲人根本搵唔到
Dialogue: 0,1:05:37.00,1:05:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必要时呢度风声紧 我带你去果度暂时避一避
Dialogue: 0,1:05:42.04,1:05:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇用嘅 而家周围都通缉我
Dialogue: 0,1:05:45.00,1:05:46.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁样匿法 匿到几时先得
Dialogue: 0,1:05:46.87,1:05:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,横掂都系死嘅啦 做乜咁鬼鼠
Dialogue: 0,1:05:50.83,1:05:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下个礼拜我就返香港整镬杰
Dialogue: 0,1:05:52.66,1:05:54.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同阿勇揽住一齐死
Dialogue: 0,1:06:02.29,1:06:03.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁好啦
Dialogue: 0,1:06:03.29,1:06:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你系都要返香港 我陪你一齐返
Dialogue: 0,1:06:06.91,1:06:09.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今次过嚟系将安仔同老婆交俾你
Dialogue: 0,1:06:09.95,1:06:11.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔系度睇住佢地 我点放心呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:11.79,1:06:13.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁你一个人返去送死 我会放心咩
Dialogue: 0,1:06:13.12,1:06:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好同我拗啦 好唔好？
Dialogue: 0,1:06:16.16,1:06:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我求吓你啦
Dialogue: 0,1:06:19.16,1:06:21.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好地帮我凑大安仔
Dialogue: 0,1:06:21.20,1:06:23.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等佢同我传宗接代
Dialogue: 0,1:06:23.66,1:06:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁我死都死得眼闭 系唔系？
Dialogue: 0,1:07:23.66,1:07:24.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笑吓勒
Dialogue: 0,1:07:35.20,1:07:36.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国过嚟影相了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:36.87,1:07:38.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚟 我去后边帮手
Dialogue: 0,1:07:40.16,1:07:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,企埋嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:07:41.33,1:07:42.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,1:07:42.66,1:07:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿问我 你系咪瞒住佢返香港
Dialogue: 0,1:07:45.50,1:07:46.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我话唔系
Dialogue: 0,1:07:48.20,1:07:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国
Dialogue: 0,1:07:49.75,1:07:51.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己慢慢影吓先
Dialogue: 0,1:08:07.70,1:08:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一去到巴西
Dialogue: 0,1:08:10.70,1:08:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就要即刻打个电话俾我
Dialogue: 0,1:08:15.16,1:08:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你食开个啲药 我摆落个红色盒仔入面
Dialogue: 0,1:08:23.37,1:08:26.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系美国转机果时
Dialogue: 0,1:08:28.70,1:08:30.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,记住拿件大冷衫出嚟着
Dialogue: 0,1:08:32.95,1:08:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因住冷亲
Dialogue: 0,1:08:37.50,1:08:38.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得勒
Dialogue: 0,1:08:45.20,1:08:47.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你其实系咪瞒住我返香港？
Dialogue: 0,1:08:49.16,1:08:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系唔系呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:08:53.12,1:08:54.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系唔系呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:08:56.33,1:08:58.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好呃我呀
Dialogue: 0,1:09:00.58,1:09:02.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都话唔系啦 傻女
Dialogue: 0,1:09:03.70,1:09:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好咁啦
Dialogue: 0,1:09:06.08,1:09:07.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我点会呃你呢？
Dialogue: 0,1:09:16.00,1:09:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,落嚟 落嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:09:30.00,1:09:33.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安仔大个仔啦 阿爸唔系度时候
Dialogue: 0,1:09:33.62,1:09:36.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮阿爸照顾妈咪 知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,1:09:37.62,1:09:38.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叻仔
Dialogue: 0,1:09:45.04,1:09:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,宝儿
Dialogue: 0,1:09:47.83,1:09:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对唔住呀
Dialogue: 0,1:09:55.33,1:09:57.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔可以冇你
Dialogue: 0,1:09:58.87,1:10:01.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我好爱你
Dialogue: 0,1:10:02.45,1:10:03.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知
Dialogue: 0,1:10:15.20,1:10:16.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好喊
Dialogue: 0,1:10:17.20,1:10:18.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好走呀
Dialogue: 0,1:10:24.54,1:10:28.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉叔 事头叫我拿手信嚟俾你
Dialogue: 0,1:10:28.70,1:10:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系佢亲戚
Dialogue: 0,1:10:32.79,1:10:35.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜咁客气 我打个电话多谢佢
Dialogue: 0,1:10:35.83,1:10:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔驶打勒 事头全家都去晒医院
Dialogue: 0,1:10:40.33,1:10:41.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乜事呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:10:42.00,1:10:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忠伯昨晚撞车入了医院
Dialogue: 0,1:10:44.91,1:10:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听讲话佢就快死
Dialogue: 0,1:10:47.33,1:10:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点解冇人话俾我知？
Dialogue: 0,1:10:49.54,1:10:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉叔 我而家去探事头
Dialogue: 0,1:10:52.00,1:10:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你驶唔驶我车你去睇吓佢咁
Dialogue: 0,1:10:56.12,1:10:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:11:00.29,1:11:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,1:11:02.12,1:11:04.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿剂哥 我老友出了事
Dialogue: 0,1:11:04.75,1:11:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我出出去即刻返
Dialogue: 0,1:11:07.54,1:11:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去开车
Dialogue: 0,1:11:16.08,1:11:19.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖地 你地食先 我即刻返
Dialogue: 0,1:11:28.29,1:11:30.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 我有啲野同你讲 出一出去
Dialogue: 0,1:11:54.33,1:11:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火车飞 船飞 护照
Dialogue: 0,1:11:57.79,1:11:59.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,护照里面用嘅名系陈永富
Dialogue: 0,1:12:00.45,1:12:02.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听日我飞返香港先
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.33,1:12:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到时我会同阿泉嚟接你船
Dialogue: 0,1:12:07.79,1:12:09.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你咁辛苦系呢度捱到自己嘅餐厅
Dialogue: 0,1:12:09.62,1:12:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个咁好嘅老婆 有成班细佬
Dialogue: 0,1:12:14.33,1:12:16.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你陪我返去冒险值得咩？
Dialogue: 0,1:12:18.00,1:12:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了剂哥你 我觉得系值得
Dialogue: 0,1:12:24.12,1:12:26.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来 同我地一齐食
Dialogue: 0,1:12:32.58,1:12:33.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔好争
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.29,1:13:58.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢度系我发了誓要拉嘅十个恶人
Dialogue: 0,1:14:00.87,1:14:04.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥你就系排第一位
Dialogue: 0,1:14:05.41,1:14:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,张SIR冇咁严重卦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:08.41,1:14:11.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成个FILE 最头痛啲CASE
Dialogue: 0,1:14:11.25,1:14:13.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都同你老哥有份
Dialogue: 0,1:14:14.91,1:14:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 唔该你交出你嘅旅行证件
Dialogue: 0,1:14:17.75,1:14:22.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我咁多生意 成日要飞嚟飞去 好唔方便
Dialogue: 0,1:14:22.91,1:14:24.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马六甲都有生意咩？
Dialogue: 0,1:14:31.41,1:14:34.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,张SIR 我地做个朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:36.58,1:14:40.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,九年前 李阿剂又系想咁同我交朋友
Dialogue: 0,1:14:40.29,1:14:42.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喷到佢一面屁
Dialogue: 0,1:14:42.33,1:14:44.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果我守了罗湖桥三年
Dialogue: 0,1:14:44.62,1:14:47.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系学堂教班猪仔教了两年
Dialogue: 0,1:14:47.29,1:14:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但系天有眼 我卒之坐到呢个位
Dialogue: 0,1:14:52.04,1:14:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就折随咯 你啲仇口多个蜜蜂巢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:56.66,1:14:59.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一收到风 李阿剂返嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:15:00.16,1:15:04.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就惊到睡唔着 出入要十几廿人磅住你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:05.25,1:15:08.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做人做得咁辛苦 不如死了佢咯
Dialogue: 0,1:15:13.20,1:15:14.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我系
Dialogue: 0,1:15:22.00,1:15:23.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我系张铁柱
Dialogue: 0,1:15:25.16,1:15:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,1:15:28.33,1:15:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,带佢出去办手续
Dialogue: 0,1:15:41.37,1:15:44.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥 你搵我想自首啊？
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.91,1:15:46.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想同你讲讲
Dialogue: 0,1:15:46.75,1:15:48.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿勇有大把律师帮佢做
Dialogue: 0,1:15:48.79,1:15:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有法律保护佢
Dialogue: 0,1:15:50.41,1:15:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你成日搵人吊住佢都冇用
Dialogue: 0,1:15:52.50,1:15:54.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞到我落唔到手 冇机会郁手
Dialogue: 0,1:15:54.58,1:15:56.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如驶开晒啲伙计
Dialogue: 0,1:15:58.08,1:15:59.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点解我要咁做呢？
Dialogue: 0,1:16:00.50,1:16:02.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今次我返得嚟 就预了冇命
Dialogue: 0,1:16:03.41,1:16:06.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到我郁手的时候 我会叫你帮我执尸
Dialogue: 0,1:16:07.45,1:16:09.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到期时你可以立番大功罗
Dialogue: 0,1:16:10.29,1:16:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,张SIR 以前我整蛊过你
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.83,1:16:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而家当我送番个大礼俾你
Dialogue: 0,1:16:16.45,1:16:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都好服你做人可以咁有原则
Dialogue: 0,1:16:20.41,1:16:23.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,守罗湖可以守得云开见月明
Dialogue: 0,1:16:23.87,1:16:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好野
Dialogue: 0,1:16:26.54,1:16:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好野 你做人咪仲有原则
Dialogue: 0,1:16:30.83,1:16:33.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞到家散人亡都死唔悔改
Dialogue: 0,1:16:35.87,1:16:37.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇乜好悔改呀
Dialogue: 0,1:16:38.20,1:16:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,七 八岁我老豆就带我入呢行
Dialogue: 0,1:16:40.25,1:16:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咁多年我都唔知见尽几多人家破人亡
Dialogue: 0,1:16:44.66,1:16:46.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做呢样野预了啦
Dialogue: 0,1:16:46.66,1:16:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反以我唔会怨天怨地 更加唔怨我老豆
Dialogue: 0,1:16:50.79,1:16:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为佢都系用条命去搏 好辛苦养大我
Dialogue: 0,1:16:55.87,1:16:57.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,食得咸鱼抵得渴
Dialogue: 0,1:16:57.54,1:17:00.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,整定我阿剂要家破人亡 冇办法
Dialogue: 0,1:17:02.75,1:17:05.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,张SIR 你准备帮我收尸了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:30.83,1:17:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 搞定晒
Dialogue: 0,1:17:32.00,1:17:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饮呀
Dialogue: 0,1:17:33.33,1:17:37.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点嘛？我阿爸有冇同埋阿剂 阿国佢地见面
Dialogue: 0,1:17:38.79,1:17:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已轻择低晒喺本簿度
Dialogue: 0,1:17:42.91,1:17:44.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 饮杯酒呀
Dialogue: 0,1:17:47.50,1:17:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在跟你报告一下
Dialogue: 0,1:17:49.79,1:17:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你阿爸一早系弥敦酒店出嚟 争啲俾的士车亲
Dialogue: 0,1:17:54.79,1:17:58.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后就去坟场拜你表姐 系度大喊一场
Dialogue: 0,1:18:00.79,1:18:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟住佢坐系码头睇人钓鱼 睇了五个钟头
Dialogue: 0,1:18:05.91,1:18:09.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系度口吸吸自己同自己讲
Dialogue: 0,1:18:12.20,1:18:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第二早去求签 求了支下下签 梁天来
Dialogue: 0,1:18:18.12,1:18:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你唔好系度讲埋啲废话 得唔得呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:18:20.66,1:18:23.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟有冇见到阿国同阿剂蒲头呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:18:23.95,1:18:25.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔知勒
Dialogue: 0,1:18:26.29,1:18:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你仲系度食 讲清楚
Dialogue: 0,1:18:31.66,1:18:36.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个钟头前你阿爸出酒店上了架的士
Dialogue: 0,1:18:36.66,1:18:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿二就跟紧你阿爸
Dialogue: 0,1:18:38.87,1:18:41.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能仲没到终点 所以没有报告
Dialogue: 0,1:18:42.83,1:18:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 你阿爸坐架的士嚟 话要见你
Dialogue: 0,1:18:55.75,1:18:57.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔该你系度等我一阵间
Dialogue: 0,1:18:59.91,1:19:00.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟我嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:19:08.08,1:19:12.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,个个俾你炸到啲头同手手脚脚 断到成地都系
Dialogue: 0,1:19:12.04,1:19:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,分唔到边个打边个
Dialogue: 0,1:19:14.25,1:19:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我晚晚睡唔着
Dialogue: 0,1:19:16.83,1:19:19.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我自己问自己 做错了乜野事
Dialogue: 0,1:19:19.54,1:19:21.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生了你咁嘅衰仔
Dialogue: 0,1:19:23.83,1:19:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我情愿你炸死埋我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:28.08,1:19:31.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点解唔炸死埋我 点解…？
Dialogue: 0,1:19:31.87,1:19:34.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦…停手
Dialogue: 0,1:19:40.41,1:19:42.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你咁大个人冇脑咩
Dialogue: 0,1:19:43.33,1:19:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搵只耳仔嚟做人
Dialogue: 0,1:19:45.41,1:19:46.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人地乱咁答你又信
Dialogue: 0,1:19:50.04,1:19:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我几个月冇离开香港
Dialogue: 0,1:19:52.87,1:19:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有人系马六甲见到你呀衰仔
Dialogue: 0,1:19:56.16,1:19:58.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我啲旅证件俾警察局收晒
Dialogue: 0,1:19:59.54,1:20:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马六甲 我点去呀？我识飞呀
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.12,1:20:10.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢啲就系差馆收了我证件个啲收条
Dialogue: 0,1:20:12.20,1:20:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不识字 要问下别人
Dialogue: 0,1:20:18.50,1:20:20.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔系你 咁系边个呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:20:20.87,1:20:21.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我点知呀
Dialogue: 0,1:20:22.95,1:20:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,李阿剂啲仇口多过蜜蜂巢
Dialogue: 0,1:20:25.91,1:20:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我点知几时有人郁佢
Dialogue: 0,1:20:29.04,1:20:31.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想知 我咪帮你查咯
Dialogue: 0,1:20:38.29,1:20:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸 唔好咁劳气啦
Dialogue: 0,1:20:43.41,1:20:44.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,食了饭未呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:20:45.75,1:20:47.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我地系出面打紧边炉
Dialogue: 0,1:20:48.25,1:20:50.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如我地两仔爷嗒番杯 好唔好？
Dialogue: 0,1:20:50.75,1:20:53.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 我正话见到你老豆系美孚落车
Dialogue: 0,1:20:53.91,1:20:56.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国同阿剂系人堆里边忽然间闪出嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:20:56.62,1:20:58.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眨吓眼就唔见了
Dialogue: 0,1:21:00.95,1:21:02.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢地喺边呀？
Dialogue: 0,1:21:06.58,1:21:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔会话俾你听嘅
Dialogue: 0,1:21:09.62,1:21:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔会话俾你听嘅
Dialogue: 0,1:21:12.62,1:21:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔妥喎勇哥
Dialogue: 0,1:21:15.20,1:21:17.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你老豆今次摆明嚟收风
Dialogue: 0,1:21:24.04,1:21:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死老鬼 手指拗出唔拗入
Dialogue: 0,1:21:27.87,1:21:29.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮啲外人嚟害我
Dialogue: 0,1:21:31.16,1:21:34.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,枉我仲一片孝心 唔舍得炸死你
Dialogue: 0,1:21:35.00,1:21:39.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,专登搵人驶开你 你够胆嚟收风
Dialogue: 0,1:21:43.41,1:21:47.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真系你 真系你做
Dialogue: 0,1:21:48.20,1:21:53.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你个死仆街仔 死仔
Dialogue: 0,1:21:58.91,1:22:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,郁佢
Dialogue: 0,1:22:03.16,1:22:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,郁佢呀
Dialogue: 0,1:22:05.95,1:22:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,郁佢
Dialogue: 0,1:22:28.95,1:22:32.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你扯呀 你躏呀 唔系我拿你命
Dialogue: 0,1:22:37.66,1:22:41.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搵人跟住佢 打伤个老野
Dialogue: 0,1:22:42.62,1:22:44.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我唔惊佢地唔蒲头
Dialogue: 0,1:22:54.91,1:22:55.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开车呀
Dialogue: 0,1:22:56.83,1:22:58.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢打你呀
Dialogue: 0,1:22:58.87,1:23:00.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跌亲嗜
Dialogue: 0,1:23:01.12,1:23:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同佢讲定数
Dialogue: 0,1:23:03.20,1:23:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冇事 算数
Dialogue: 0,1:24:15.41,1:24:16.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿泉
Dialogue: 0,1:25:48.50,1:25:51.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿剂 你好野 扳咁大碌炮嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:28:23.58,1:28:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,1:29:24.83,1:29:26.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剂哥
Dialogue: 0,1:29:56.95,1:30:01.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇哥 我地唔掂 一定要走啦
Dialogue: 0,1:30:02.12,1:30:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,点嘛？
Dialogue: 0,1:30:03.25,1:30:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你走先啦
Dialogue: 0,1:30:27.95,1:30:29.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:30:30.83,1:30:32.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔够胆出嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:31:29.20,1:31:33.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你开枪打死我 你点同阿爸交待？
Dialogue: 0,1:31:48.08,1:31:49.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸…
Dialogue: 0,1:31:53.45,1:31:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿爸 阿国系你个仔 我唔系你个仔呀
Dialogue: 0,1:32:02.79,1:32:04.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你个死仔
Dialogue: 0,1:32:19.79,1:32:22.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你炸烂我间屋 炸啦
Dialogue: 0,1:32:24.54,1:32:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,炸我间屋
Dialogue: 0,1:32:26.41,1:32:29.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我话了今年唔驶寄圣诞咭俾你
Dialogue: 0,1:32:32.79,1:32:34.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过你放心
Dialogue: 0,1:32:36.20,1:32:39.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会烧张落阴闲度问候你全家
Dialogue: 0,1:32:41.62,1:32:49.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你老婆同个仔俾我炸死 系下边做鬼
Dialogue: 0,1:32:50.29,1:32:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,系唔系做油炸鬼呀
Dialogue: 0,1:33:59.29,1:34:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,推我落去 挞死我啦 我唔惊？
Dialogue: 0,1:34:03.20,1:34:06.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你背到成身都系子弹
Dialogue: 0,1:34:06.87,1:34:09.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跌落去 爆起上嚟
Dialogue: 0,1:34:09.37,1:34:11.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲死得惨过我老婆同个仔
Dialogue: 0,1:34:12.12,1:34:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你呀做鬼同埋做人都系一样屎忽鬼 屎忽鬼呀
Dialogue: 0,1:34:40.54,1:34:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿国 你点嘛？阿国
Dialogue: 0,1:34:48.66,1:34:51.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢唔死得嘅 不过就会坐成世监
Dialogue: 0,1:34:53.70,1:34:55.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呢度嘅人全部都系我杀
Dialogue: 0,1:34:55.79,1:34:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔关佢地两仔爷事
Dialogue: 0,1:34:57.91,1:34:59.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都叫佢地两仔爷唔好嚟睇热闹
Dialogue: 0,1:34:59.95,1:35:01.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佢地系都唔听
Dialogue: 0,1:35:03.00,1:35:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道佢两仔爷被逼咁做
Dialogue: 0,1:35:05.58,1:35:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上法庭果阵时我会尽量帮佢地啦
Dialogue: 0,1:35:09.12,1:35:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 快点上白车 我都唔想你死
Dialogue: 0,1:35:14.70,1:35:16.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仲有好多口供等住你落

