[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由互联网转载，如有类同尽请谅解！！
; // 欢迎访问字幕库网站 http://www.zimuku.net
Title:zimuku
Original Script:zimuku
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,5,5,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.22,0:03:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晨  早晨 欢迎收听"朝朝早精神好"
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.99,0:03:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先送上一首超级动感的音乐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.53,0:03:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 来使你精神一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.13,0:03:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  你的早餐谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.50,0:04:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要什么呀?我要喝奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.40,0:04:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要两个奶油包
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.11,0:04:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧你们哇  又会这么快的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.51,0:04:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你出声就知你要叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.15,0:04:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见你一身排骨  营养不良的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.08,0:04:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 怕你倒在我店里呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.52,0:04:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不赶快热一杯牛奶呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.58,0:04:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表姐  让我来捡这么凶的!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.12,0:04:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有好处
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.19,0:04:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stella今晚有没有空陪我去散步
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.60,0:04:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老处女老处女你也肯要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.40,0:04:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老处女也不便宜你呀  死鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.97,0:04:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追我的男人  排队排到尖沙嘴呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.50,0:04:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲜奶和奶油包  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.70,0:04:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天多来几个叫了不吃的 我就发财了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.71,0:05:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.28,0:05:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来了没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.48,0:05:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时间上学了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.39,0:05:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不起来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.85,0:05:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.76,0:05:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.39,0:05:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.73,0:05:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.55,0:05:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真行啊  书倒了都能读
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.22,0:05:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我故意倒过来  看看能不能读
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.39,0:06:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别装蒜了  刚才怎么那么吵啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.76,0:06:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊!隔壁那个霹雳仔 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.45,0:06:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把收音机开得那么大声
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.36,0:06:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么现在又没声音了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.36,0:06:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听听  又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.14,0:06:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你的音乐真够劲 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.69,0:06:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的怎么样  够不够劲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.27,0:06:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  不知道你姐姐在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.11,0:06:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拜托你学学你表妹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.98,0:06:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家西巴拉又勤奋  又听话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.78,0:06:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  整天就知道玩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.05,0:06:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到时间上学了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.42,0:06:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动作快一点  又不是叫你唱大戏!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.89,0:06:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡须仔你可真有眼光 我以前是唱京剧的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.89,0:06:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在没有用了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.26,0:06:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么脏  鬼才买呢!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.14,0:06:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不买我就自己吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.51,0:06:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照相呀  我摆个好看的姿势给你!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.66,0:07:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前演京剧没人欣赏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.63,0:07:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你  我再玩些拿手的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.75,0:07:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久没玩了  喘气了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.89,0:07:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍我的丑态
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.83,0:07:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藩王看枪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.99,0:07:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我戳  我挑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.23,0:07:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇茅丈八枪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.91,0:07:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藩王  什么时候可以看照片
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.64,0:08:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察来了别跑..
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.78,0:08:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个摊子是谁的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.01,0:08:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是你的  是你就跟我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.85,0:08:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了十块钱你买甘蔗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.15,0:08:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没找钱给我  就这样跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.58,0:08:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 是不对的  找回钱给我…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没意思  这次有得啃了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.03,0:08:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血本无归了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.57,0:08:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有两块钱 今晚那餐不知道怎么办?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.77,0:08:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  阿珍  我先走了拜拜…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.15,0:08:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样冲过来  让我追到 你就死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.15,0:08:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Eddie呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.16,0:08:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我追  我追…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.56,0:08:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的追到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.50,0:08:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hi  Eddie  那么巧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.93,0:08:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊Anna
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.90,0:09:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在马路中间骑单车  嫌命长呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.24,0:09:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大只妹  如果不是给面子Anna
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.83,0:09:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 我就揍你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.37,0:09:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骑单车去广场啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.74,0:09:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你到了都散场了  让我帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.87,0:09:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么帮啊就这样呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.81,0:09:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停车  停车呀…想勒死我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.08,0:09:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  不要玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.29,0:09:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样很危险的不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勒死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.19,0:09:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.29,0:09:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.66,0:09:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开呀  四眼佬
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开啦  四眼佬 走不开呀  走不开呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.51,0:09:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么开车的  哎呀  面包呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.11,0:09:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的面包呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.15,0:09:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的面包…真倒霉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.36,0:09:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莲  你太过份了  停车
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.43,0:10:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心  撞墙了  撞墙了全散了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.90,0:10:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧! 我就没事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.13,0:10:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,  不过我的单车有事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.47,0:10:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死大只妹  你赔我的单车
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赔  看一下怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.11,0:10:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赔给你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.37,0:10:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些钱  不够我买惊风散的 我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.01,0:10:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小心一点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.06,0:10:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准笑  我是在表演
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.03,0:10:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.41,0:10:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.71,0:10:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  我们跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.52,0:11:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是鸡骨头
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.36,0:11:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是你呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.70,0:11:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你捡回鸡腿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.40,0:11:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都脏了  不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.00,0:11:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.97,0:11:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才撞倒你真不好意思 我请你吃东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.84,0:11:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我吃鸡啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.88,0:11:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认不认识我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.58,0:11:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七彩癞痢头
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.69,0:11:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七彩  他是我朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.93,0:11:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想吃桌面的东西 就要会玩两下子才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.01,0:11:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.61,0:11:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样是故意为难他嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.85,0:12:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是好人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.79,0:12:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的朋友跳得不错呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.89,0:12:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么朋友  是我徒弟来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.07,0:12:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.47,0:12:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又白干了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.31,0:12:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收摊了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.71,0:12:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.05,0:12:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.02,0:12:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先回去  我去看看我徒弟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.49,0:12:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徒弟  徒弟  徒弟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.43,0:12:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你够了吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.66,0:12:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你千万别误会  我想做你的徒弟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.93,0:12:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学一点高难度的动作威风一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.07,0:12:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,误人子弟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.07,0:12:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当了二十几年的学徒 穿梭机都会做了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.67,0:12:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么不好学  学人家唱京剧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.71,0:13:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没落了  搞到卖甘蔗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.38,0:13:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找钱都来不及了  哪有心情教你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.45,0:13:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用怕  我叫姐姐给你一份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.28,0:13:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是真的?走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.32,0:13:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我姐姐很好商量的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.69,0:13:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你信我吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.86,0:13:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.02,0:13:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这儿等一等  我先进去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.73,0:13:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很快出来的好!…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.83,0:13:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.37,0:13:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西巴拉在楼上等你补习呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.90,0:13:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀!我跟Stella又要读书 又要补习
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.71,0:13:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一个人做事很辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.71,0:13:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.21,0:13:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.18,0:13:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果找到一个跟我一样 有力气的人来帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.18,0:13:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就轻松多了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.82,0:13:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.58,0:13:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.42,0:13:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你想就好办了 我已经帮你找到人了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.86,0:13:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那个人老老实实 又机灵  包你喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.56,0:13:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子  居然帮我找老公啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.73,0:13:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.80,0:13:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我考虑一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.50,0:14:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用考虑了  我马上带他来见你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.87,0:14:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.31,0:14:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  为什么我的心 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.06,0:14:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崩崩崩的跳个不停
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.55,0:14:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么多泡沫啊  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.19,0:14:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这洗洁精弄的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.89,0:14:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀!这种洗洁精泡沫很多的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.43,0:14:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  他是大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.29,0:14:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是这里的老板娘  也就是我姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.70,0:14:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.30,0:14:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便坐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.94,0:14:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来…坐吧谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.97,0:14:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.14,0:14:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说我姐姐很好商量的 没问题了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.24,0:14:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不知道怎么感激你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.11,0:14:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你又不用那么紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.31,0:14:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是紧张  我内心激动嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.52,0:14:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我长这么大 真的…我没有试过说…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.36,0:14:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先坐一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.49,0:14:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  我没介绍错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.39,0:15:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说 交往看看  先互相了解一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.66,0:15:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧!我带他回来见工的 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.53,0:15:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想着和他交往的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.27,0:15:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是服了你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.27,0:15:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神经病呀你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.17,0:15:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  你交朋结友要多了解一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.01,0:15:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 你你…你什么  不说了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.45,0:15:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没好介绍的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.95,0:15:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不请人了  你叫他走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.92,0:15:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢这种人姐姐..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.52,0:15:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.36,0:15:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.13,0:15:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你没地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.43,0:15:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.33,0:15:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带我去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个窗可以爬进我房间的  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.97,0:15:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里进去  姐姐就不会知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.21,0:15:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好饿  不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.78,0:15:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要问问他有没有东西吃才行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.75,0:16:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有没有人  你出来吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.45,0:16:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我学下你的动作  多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.92,0:16:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的肚子 肚子落地嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.89,0:16:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲤鱼打挺  三脚顶  像不像呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.64,0:16:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有顿海鲜吃就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.58,0:16:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  这么大条的石斑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.02,0:16:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的好不好呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.12,0:16:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  要是清蒸就更好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.49,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抓石斑  我先把它抓出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.66,0:16:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不见了  石斑不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.51,0:16:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角巧克力呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.61,0:16:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是巧克力来的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.21,0:17:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大钢牙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.15,0:17:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样呀师父  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.29,0:17:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噎到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.29,0:17:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么用巧克力盒装图钉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.26,0:17:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废物利用嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.16,0:17:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肚子很饿吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.37,0:17:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早点说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.24,0:17:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没有机会说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.94,0:17:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.68,0:17:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.95,0:17:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是我师父大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.82,0:17:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是表姐整晚在骂的那个混蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.49,0:17:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大胆子  居然敢到我们家来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.69,0:17:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我去告诉表姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.26,0:17:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.23,0:17:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是这么没人情味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.59,0:17:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么没有人情味呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.96,0:17:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥  人又老 又没钱  长得又土
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不同情他吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.60,0:17:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你想怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.24,0:17:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别告诉表姐就什么都行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.44,0:17:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是你说的是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.37,0:18:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要每天晚上帮我补习行…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.04,0:18:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学狗叫三声行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.64,0:18:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我是男人来的  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.14,0:18:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我学狗叫 这么老土  一定不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.81,0:18:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.45,0:18:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  我替他学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.39,0:18:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太过份了 算了…最多我不告诉表姐了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.63,0:18:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.77,0:18:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有东西吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.63,0:18:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啦…坐下慢慢吃吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.21,0:18:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气的  狂吃  吃得下就吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.64,0:18:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿这么多东西来吃  我怎么开账啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.41,0:18:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当没看见就行了  有你一份的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.38,0:18:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 一家人  坐下来慢慢享受
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.25,0:18:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝一杯  帮帮忙啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.96,0:18:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么帮呀  这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.89,0:18:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啊  我是叫你帮忙说服姐姐 收留他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.40,0:18:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  表姐好讨厌他的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.73,0:19:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  有机会再帮他好了是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.35,0:19:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你慢慢吃吧  小心噎到了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.02,0:19:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弟  西巴拉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.62,0:19:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不关门呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.19,0:19:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好危险的对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.06,0:19:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道你们在搞什么鬼?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.70,0:19:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.16,0:19:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剪刀在哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.33,0:19:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.87,0:19:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明摆在厨房的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.01,0:19:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是有些人用完了就没放好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.56,0:19:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个吃这么多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.46,0:20:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿嘛是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.43,0:20:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有只蚊子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.10,0:20:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挖一挖鼻孔  好痒呀  好痒呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.84,0:20:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剔牙  剔牙  咸咸的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.34,0:20:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是大吃鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.68,0:20:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  搞什么鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.01,0:20:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是肠子  又是薯条 鸡翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.26,0:20:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,  鸡腿  汽水  汉堡包
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.68,0:20:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这么个吃法  不把我吃穷才怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.82,0:20:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  我给回钱你 你的钱不就是我的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.69,0:20:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小明小明  小小明  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.57,0:20:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双双… 这样也好玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.40,0:20:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点出来快点呀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.63,0:20:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点躲起来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.27,0:20:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲到衣橱里去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.94,0:20:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表姐  我放好水给你洗澡了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.04,0:20:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一会吧  我先把阿弟的衣服洗了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.84,0:20:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表姐说要帮你拿衣服去洗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.85,0:20:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她进来拿衣服呀  出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.35,0:20:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么办?阿弟
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.48,0:20:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么大声干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.18,0:20:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲到床底下吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.79,0:21:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张关头一定是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.39,0:21:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  洗衣服呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.20,0:21:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你拿衣柜那些
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.17,0:21:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么多了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.07,0:21:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那洗澡水可以的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.95,0:21:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表姐进去了  快点走吧  走…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.22,0:21:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西巴拉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.45,0:21:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点躲回房里去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.56,0:21:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装模做样  走开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.63,0:21:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西巴拉搞什么鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.00,0:21:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说放好水叫我洗澡的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.57,0:21:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水我先用了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.97,0:21:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.61,0:21:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道你们在搞什么鬼?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.18,0:21:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打完球满身臭汗  就先用了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.08,0:22:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么鱼缸的水那么少啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.72,0:22:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鱼都喝光了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.45,0:22:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡扯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.39,0:22:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我拿水加满它  不然鱼会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:22:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.45,0:22:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她浇花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.62,0:22:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  浇花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.49,0:22:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浇花要那么多水啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.02,0:22:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把地都弄湿了  出去…!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.39,0:22:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.77,0:22:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个地面都湿了  有得拖了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.62,0:23:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么呀你们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.35,0:23:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.75,0:23:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我顶不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.52,0:23:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.83,0:23:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.43,0:23:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都给我出来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.93,0:23:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点推他出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.01,0:23:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还睡得这么舒服  起来!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.42,0:23:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还摆好架势
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.95,0:23:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想打我是不是啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.52,0:23:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是啊他抽筋而已
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.19,0:23:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们扶他过去坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.59,0:23:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  坐在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.16,0:23:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你吃的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.70,0:23:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.10,0:24:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算  我当然要跟他算
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.91,0:24:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.18,0:24:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着吧!不用了!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.88,0:24:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连鱼缸一起308块  给钱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.82,0:24:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不够呀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.19,0:24:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把小猪给你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.66,0:24:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西巴拉  过来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.76,0:24:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是不够了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.40,0:24:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  他有钱就不会到这儿来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.67,0:24:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你虽然是一家之主
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.47,0:24:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我想留下他 你也不要那么专制啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.34,0:24:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我专制  我这个人最民主 对不对?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.24,0:24:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道怎么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.54,0:24:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  好了  大家来表决
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.80,0:24:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 少数要服从多数
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.25,0:24:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁赞成他留下来的举手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.38,0:24:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不算啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.86,0:24:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你一个
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.96,0:25:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个  那就留下吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.97,0:25:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀…姐姐万岁!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.93,0:25:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们先不要开心
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.64,0:25:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个月是试用期
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.37,0:25:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欠我的钱月底从薪水里扣
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.11,0:25:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到工作了恭喜你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.25,0:25:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀…大眼哥好样的…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.38,0:25:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我头..
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.12,0:25:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是鸿运当头了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.86,0:25:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.12,0:25:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么粗鲁的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.71,0:26:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  那么久不见 你越来越正点了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.38,0:26:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小意思  还有更正点的呢  你看看
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.96,0:26:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正点啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.36,0:26:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.06,0:26:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正点!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.66,0:26:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个过时了  拿去玩吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.73,0:26:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢老大!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.17,0:26:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.44,0:26:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够劲吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.41,0:26:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说根本是浪费唇舌
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.98,0:27:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  我把他唬得一楞一楞的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.55,0:27:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我去哪儿玩呀? 我知道怎么做的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.35,0:27:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.29,0:27:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发还没有长齐  
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.54,0:27:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你伯伯我 露两手给你见识见识
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.31,0:27:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我顶 顶..
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.99,0:27:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子  敢在我面前班门弄斧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.92,0:28:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的  好样的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.86,0:28:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个后浪推我这个前浪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.96,0:28:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  愧是我老大  今晚宵夜算我的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.83,0:28:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的话那就走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.37,0:28:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十个手指头都不够你切的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.17,0:28:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩下一块胶布了谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.12,0:28:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这里是大酒店啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.82,0:28:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小吃店而已  还不招呼我们老板
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.96,0:28:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这里是大酒店啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.46,0:28:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小吃店而已  你自己招呼自己吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.06,0:28:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板 我走到哪儿都有人招呼我的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.80,0:29:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有资格跟我们老板说话
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.27,0:29:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…Hi  Anna
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.54,0:29:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.64,0:29:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去打网球吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.07,0:29:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.18,0:29:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.61,0:29:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚刚买的新球拍
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.35,0:29:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摔伤了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.48,0:29:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.45,0:29:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很痛呀  我的背很痛  很痛..
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.69,0:30:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你下不下流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.16,0:30:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀  地下是脏了点
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.30,0:30:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真离谱
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.90,0:30:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.11,0:30:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hi  我叫Kenny
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.04,0:30:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫小莲
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.58,0:30:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kenny哥  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.32,0:30:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hi  我叫Eddie!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.13,0:30:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.83,0:30:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要误会
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.43,0:30:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡是我不认识的人伸出手来 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.14,0:30:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都会当他是乞丐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.50,0:30:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,施舍一块钱给他 因为我很喜欢做善事的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.91,0:30:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收起来吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.88,0:30:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.15,0:30:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无福消受
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.62,0:31:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条毛巾你用过了  要消消毒
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.43,0:31:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  他糗你!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.90,0:31:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散散热吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.30,0:31:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打得好  打得好呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.54,0:31:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.04,0:31:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.14,0:31:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吹牛吹爆了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.71,0:31:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有胆就跟我老大打一场
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.59,0:31:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用单车车轮当球拍跟你打
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.99,0:31:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你自找倒霉的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.60,0:31:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一球定输赢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.70,0:31:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是你说的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.51,0:31:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神龙摆尾
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.44,0:31:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌龙抬头
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.88,0:32:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黄龙转身
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.92,0:32:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猛虎伸腰
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.96,0:32:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小意思  哎呀  我的脚呀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.30,0:32:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狮子摇头
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.03,0:32:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来不及了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.57,0:32:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞龙在天
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.78,0:32:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好球呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.45,0:32:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口气这么大  不知道是谁自找倒霉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.02,0:32:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气  有机会再赢回他
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.66,0:32:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie  你打的真好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.59,0:32:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还可以
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.43,0:32:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去吃饭吧  我请客
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.39,0:32:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  和我们一块去吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.73,0:32:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要算我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.80,0:32:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也不要算我  等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.27,0:32:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.14,0:32:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二号桌
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.20,0:32:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二号枱
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.38,0:33:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.81,0:33:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.92,0:33:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.15,0:33:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起就可以啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.95,0:33:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么赔
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.60,0:33:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.43,0:33:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人一次  算扯平了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.40,0:33:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神经病
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.67,0:33:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没什么事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.03,0:33:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.94,0:33:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大信封
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.95,0:33:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碰钉子的次数比吃饭还多
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.18,0:33:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.25,0:33:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜  今天是三十号 
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.17,0:33:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你这个月的薪水
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.29,0:33:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后用点心去做
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.29,0:33:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.87,0:34:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚认识她的时候觉得很凶
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.84,0:34:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看惯了又不觉得了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.27,0:34:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是越看越顺眼  不错  不错
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.95,0:34:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么Eddie这么晚还没回来  大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.55,0:34:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是在那边吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.82,0:34:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是大表姐嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.65,0:34:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.56,0:34:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒泻茄汁了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.56,0:34:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来啦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.90,0:34:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.70,0:34:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么大包礼物 不知道是不是送给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.60,0:34:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.54,0:34:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼力差了点  仍到我这儿来了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.74,0:34:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.98,0:34:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.91,0:34:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥  是我买给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.02,0:34:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这多不好意思呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.19,0:34:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我送给你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.99,0:34:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.93,0:35:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是男人用的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.00,0:35:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥  她是小女孩  你不用理她的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.97,0:35:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你姐姐我老板娘发薪水给我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.60,0:35:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以我特意
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.55,0:35:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 买了这些漂亮衣服给你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.97,0:35:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚和你出去玩  快去换来看一下
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.74,0:35:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.71,0:35:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舍得回来了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.35,0:35:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你不要整天在外面闲逛 
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.93,0:35:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽点时间帮帮我店里忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.46,0:35:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅透了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.79,0:35:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有毛病啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.13,0:35:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几十岁的人穿得红红绿绿的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.73,0:35:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像马戏团小丑似的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.93,0:35:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还以为很好看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.80,0:35:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弟买给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.94,0:35:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去重新给他买套衣服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.31,0:35:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.11,0:35:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点撞爆了  哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.12,0:36:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的灯光好漂亮 
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.18,0:36:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hello  两位  欢迎欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.00,0:36:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去洗手间  你跟她去吧 来 这边坐
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.13,0:36:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 请坐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.30,0:36:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  你第一次来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.87,0:36:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  第一次来 有没有认识的小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.27,0:36:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 没有我就介绍一个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.04,0:36:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好先生  照张相好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.47,0:36:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照相  让我摆好姿势
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.88,0:36:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么你这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.94,0:36:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.85,0:36:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便拿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.75,0:36:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有烟送啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.33,0:36:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便拿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.46,0:36:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来根粗的  我能不能多拿一根
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.10,0:36:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  你通通拿去都行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.50,0:36:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位先生  多谢你  苏丝小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.24,0:36:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好招呼这位先生好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.11,0:36:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚来呀!是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.84,0:36:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就好了  一个人坐那么大的台子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.85,0:37:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的姐妹们都没有枱坐 
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.80,0:37:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫她们过来坐好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.22,0:37:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.52,0:37:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友  你的朋友真够吸引力
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.89,0:37:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.90,0:37:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次被这么多女孩子围着
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.93,0:37:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破产了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.67,0:37:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你搞什么鬼呀  那么多小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.04,0:37:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们没枱子坐  来这里搭枱嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.51,0:37:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要付钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.88,0:37:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,付钱  走
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.24,0:37:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.58,0:37:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说走人的走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.18,0:37:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小气  肯定是没什么钱
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.92,0:37:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…  留一个 让我们两个人看一下也好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.12,0:37:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦掉你的口红吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.49,0:37:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天来找你打网球的 那个女孩很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.73,0:37:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的同学
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.23,0:37:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她一块来的那个是谁啊 好嚣张
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.67,0:37:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的保镖来的  有机会我要整整她
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.87,0:38:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那简单  我帮你出个点子  我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.18,0:38:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  算帐
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.54,0:38:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢一千八百块
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.38,0:38:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么贵呀
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.61,0:38:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连雪茄一起
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.62,0:38:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不过一根而已呀
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.92,0:38:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道要付钱的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.92,0:38:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片呀  谢谢八十块
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.06,0:38:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我晕了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.01,0:38:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是了  今天她要倒霉了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.89,0:38:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.01,0:39:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道怎么做的  这样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.55,0:39:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…好牙力  咬我
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.93,0:39:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬  我说你咬不动
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.73,0:39:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他小看你  咬他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.57,0:39:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知死活
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.34,0:39:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会咬得动的?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.67,0:39:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么痛的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.31,0:39:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.91,0:39:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说女人练得那么壮有什么用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.75,0:39:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做男人婆
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.52,0:39:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是又怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.39,0:39:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们男人做得到的事  我也做得到
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.49,0:39:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.83,0:40:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你玩玩吧  看看谁厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.70,0:40:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五秒定输赢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.54,0:40:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预备  开始
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.31,0:40:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一秒  一秒半
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.98,0:40:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.45,0:40:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三秒  四秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.08,0:40:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间到
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.65,0:40:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十一下  该你了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.72,0:40:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该你了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.43,0:40:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一点嘛  不敢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.76,0:40:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.07,0:40:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.70,0:40:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.24,0:40:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.74,0:40:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四秒
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.32,0:40:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器发生故障
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.02,0:41:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就不算了是呀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.69,0:41:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就对了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.56,0:41:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举重  比谁重谁久
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.20,0:41:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经先举了  你占便宜了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.31,0:41:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看情形  她一定先倒下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.19,0:41:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么不小心呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.79,0:41:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吹倒我这么卑鄙  不玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.64,0:41:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打沙包也行
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.07,0:41:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一成功力就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.26,0:42:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝一口压压惊  嫌脏呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.76,0:42:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  她嫌脏  我喝
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.23,0:42:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如来神掌
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.24,0:42:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于找到高手了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.31,0:42:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打..
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.71,0:42:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人做得到的事情 女人很多都做不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.11,0:42:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像脱衣服吧  
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.33,0:42:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢什么时候脱 就什么时候脱
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.95,0:42:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在已经脱了  
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.93,0:42:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有本事 你站起来脱给大家看看
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.12,0:42:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说男人做得到  她也做得到  吹牛
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.89,0:42:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.12,0:42:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莲  你做什么呀!你白痴呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.23,0:42:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板  我不干了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.43,0:42:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是这样的啦  送我回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.17,0:42:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.50,0:42:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要了!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.97,0:42:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们走吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.14,0:43:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道  刚才有个笨蛋叫我咬他
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.88,0:43:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有没有咬他呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.08,0:43:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我咬得他叫救命
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.92,0:43:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了  这里就是我家了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.52,0:43:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错呀  挺漂亮的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.19,0:43:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.89,0:43:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有事呀  你快点上来吧! 没事
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.63,0:43:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.66,0:43:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.59,0:43:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.63,0:43:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  全身湿淋淋的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.93,0:43:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 幸亏我包里带了衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.50,0:43:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你上去换哦!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.07,0:43:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先换衣服吧!哦!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.78,0:44:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,压得我好痛呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.58,0:44:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么玩我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.82,0:44:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不是故意的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:19.19,0:44:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 我只想请你吃核桃
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.16,0:44:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教我跳舞呀
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.29,0:44:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也好!
Dialogue: 0,0:44:31.70,0:44:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跳得这么快  我怎么跟你学?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:44.14,0:44:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么好像茶壶一样?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:45.78,0:44:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像不像是提着一壶茶
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.95,0:44:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你提错茶壶嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.05,0:44:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.07,0:45:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是拉裤链  这你也跟着做
Dialogue: 0,0:45:20.38,0:45:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:21.41,0:45:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好坏!
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.05,0:45:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做对了  就按这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.67,0:45:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  老板
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.50,0:45:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想过了  没有你我过不了日子
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.04,0:45:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定不走了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.68,0:45:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你我就过不了夜  我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.75,0:45:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你就没好事Eddie..
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.12,0:45:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上这次 你已经是第十八次说你不干了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.32,0:46:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓不会有第十九次
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.65,0:46:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啦..
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.56,0:46:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么走路呀我帮你捡起来
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.10,0:46:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你打开让你顺顺气
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.23,0:46:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还射我
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.93,0:46:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,l闯祸了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.50,0:46:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.54,0:46:19.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要做垃圾虫呀
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.57,0:46:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高手
Dialogue: 0,0:46:22.98,0:46:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃..
Dialogue: 0,0:46:32.22,0:46:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  怎么黑漆漆的  开灯
Dialogue: 0,0:46:34.52,0:46:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什么鬼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.32,0:46:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你说熄灯的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:46:38.92,0:46:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sitdown就是坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:46:44.86,0:46:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻开第十三页
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.17,0:46:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十三页…
Dialogue: 0,0:46:51.04,0:46:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天教的是Manandwoman
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.81,0:46:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我是Man  你是Woman
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.21,0:47:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是girl
Dialogue: 0,0:47:02.11,0:47:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.72,0:47:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说最好是不是呀! 是的  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.36,0:47:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好不是叫GoodGood
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.09,0:47:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.09,0:47:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Best
Dialogue: 0,0:47:16.46,0:47:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.63,0:47:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么?…叫…
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.00,0:47:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.43,0:47:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bestman是伴郎的意思呀  姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:47:25.10,0:47:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的人应该是TheBestMan
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.21,0:47:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的意思就是说 
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.49,0:47:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的人就是伴郎  对不对?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.21,0:47:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  我就是这个意思 他最了解我了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.79,0:47:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们继续
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.32,0:47:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 你们继续了解吧走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.59,0:47:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我有一个字不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.09,0:47:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个字怎么读啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:55.20,0:47:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stella  在干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.67,0:47:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你补裤子  破成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.70,0:47:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:47:59.37,0:48:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你刚才到哪儿去玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.84,0:48:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.34,0:48:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是去Anna家罗 
Dialogue: 0,0:48:04.12,0:48:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫我教她跳霹雳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:05.58,0:48:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么知道跳着跳着  
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.18,0:48:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜跳成什么 就跳成贴面舞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:09.82,0:48:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点跳成脱衣舞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:12.48,0:48:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对我多热情呀  真是开心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.09,0:48:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.52,0:48:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,补好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.06,0:48:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煮碗面给我吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:20.76,0:48:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看补得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.00,0:48:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么大的洞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.40,0:48:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会你就知道  跳贴身舞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:27.77,0:48:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就叫你跳辣椒舞
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.77,0:48:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃面啦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.31,0:48:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.91,0:48:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又煮得挺香的嘛  死鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:48:38.18,0:48:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么开心
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.52,0:48:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好辣呀  水..
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.46,0:48:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:48:53.73,0:48:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又辣又烫
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.83,0:49:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘  你走路的姿势可真好看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.17,0:49:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还用说  我当学生的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.00,0:49:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 曾经是竞走冠军来的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.37,0:49:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你玩一下才行
Dialogue: 0,0:49:12.64,0:49:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我长这么大  还没给女孩子追过
Dialogue: 0,0:49:21.85,0:49:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  是我追她才对  我原地踏步
Dialogue: 0,0:49:29.13,0:49:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.40,0:49:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停…
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.58,0:49:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你的样子已经受不了 休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:00.76,0:50:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得这么大风呢
Dialogue: 0,0:50:11.74,0:50:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝杯水吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:16.48,0:50:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很口渴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.18,0:50:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜  我不是口渴 
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.96,0:50:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说多喝水对身体好
Dialogue: 0,0:50:21.85,0:50:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就喝多点了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:26.79,0:50:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这杯子怎么这么多心的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:29.35,0:50:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:51:07.66,0:51:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸亏没摔坏
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.03,0:51:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们干吗要请Eddie来
Dialogue: 0,0:51:16.10,0:51:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想了个妙计 这次一定叫Eddie出丑
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.94,0:51:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家里不是有两间厕所吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:51:23.21,0:51:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在两间厕所都装上了电视录影机
Dialogue: 0,0:51:26.48,0:51:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一间装的是红色电线
Dialogue: 0,0:51:29.51,0:51:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一间装的是灰色电线
Dialogue: 0,0:51:33.45,0:51:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就不会弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.35,0:51:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我在酒里放泻药  你拿给他喝
Dialogue: 0,0:51:41.79,0:51:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喝了就会拉肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.80,0:51:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候他走进哪一间厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:51:45.44,0:51:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 我就插哪一根电线
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.00,0:51:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放到电视机上给大家欣赏
Dialogue: 0,0:51:49.00,0:51:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还不糗大了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:51.67,0:51:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妙计  妙计聪明吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.15,0:52:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻仇
Dialogue: 0,0:52:13.99,0:52:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就知道你不服气了 我早有准备的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:26.14,0:52:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀鸡焉用牛刀
Dialogue: 0,0:52:35.21,0:52:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锋利吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:52:41.75,0:52:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放马过来
Dialogue: 0,0:52:43.92,0:52:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:52:49.26,0:52:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还带了帮手来  我才不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.40,0:52:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个当一双  你看一下
Dialogue: 0,0:52:53.90,0:52:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我满身都是刀  每把都很锋利
Dialogue: 0,0:52:56.57,0:52:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老土  叫Eddie出来
Dialogue: 0,0:52:58.37,0:53:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了  寻仇就找我吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:53:02.24,0:53:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie  可以走了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.44,0:53:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么有型呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:53:07.88,0:53:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Anna是来接我们去舞会的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.12,0:53:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.48,0:53:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  姐姐叫我带她一块去
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.25,0:53:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要去舞会就打扮漂亮一点
Dialogue: 0,0:53:18.59,0:53:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我们老板的朋友丢脸
Dialogue: 0,0:53:27.60,0:53:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个小女孩  那你怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,0:53:31.20,0:53:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:32.94,0:53:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie不要浪费时间了  我们走吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.98,0:53:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要发脾气  我有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:53:47.75,0:53:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐  干杯谢谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.82,0:53:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家随便玩好呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.37,0:54:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  你看
Dialogue: 0,0:54:06.07,0:54:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死Eddie  又缠着Anna
Dialogue: 0,0:54:09.07,0:54:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要保持风度
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.54,0:54:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他神气不了多久  待会儿他就会出丑
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.75,0:54:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.55,0:54:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hi  欢迎欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.95,0:54:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hi  生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.89,0:54:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kenny哥
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.53,0:54:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:54:36.33,0:54:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  这杯加了料的
Dialogue: 0,0:54:41.07,0:54:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们两人喝一杯 少的给你  多的给我
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.15,0:54:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你吃亏的
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.15,0:54:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二一添做五  大家一样多才公平
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.46,0:54:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢喝呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.99,0:55:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有泻药吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:00.89,0:55:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正出丑的是你  好  陪你一起喝
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.53,0:55:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会不会  我先干为敬
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.60,0:55:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.92,0:55:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有人啊  好急呀
Dialogue: 0,0:55:31.62,0:55:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么推不开呀!
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.29,0:55:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是用拉的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:40.23,0:55:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灰色电线  你糗大了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.00,0:55:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有戏看…请各位过来… 
Dialogue: 0,0:55:47.73,0:55:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家快点过来…听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.34,0:55:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚有神秘节目招待各位嘉宾
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.45,0:55:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请各位千万不要眨眼了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:58.35,0:55:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.06,0:56:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红色对红色
Dialogue: 0,0:56:14.20,0:56:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:17.70,0:56:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好看吧  不过你们看不到我
Dialogue: 0,0:56:21.34,0:56:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:23.68,0:56:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:24.48,0:56:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie出丑了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.95,0:56:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反应挺好的嘛 难看死了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:37.82,0:56:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,  以为自己很有型
Dialogue: 0,0:56:39.39,0:56:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过瘾吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:40.79,0:56:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:56:41.99,0:56:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才精彩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:56:43.93,0:56:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下流
Dialogue: 0,0:56:45.23,0:56:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一流
Dialogue: 0,0:56:46.70,0:56:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:48.40,0:56:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么她要打我?
Dialogue: 0,0:56:49.97,0:56:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  刚才的主角是你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.97,0:56:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧你
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.89,0:57:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想死呀你  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:15.59,0:57:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  我扶你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.80,0:57:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  都倒泻了  
Dialogue: 0,0:57:18.11,0:57:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什么鬼 对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.94,0:57:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起泼得我全身都是
Dialogue: 0,0:57:35.01,0:57:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.38,0:57:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人好面熟
Dialogue: 0,0:57:38.48,0:57:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样舒服多了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:42.75,0:57:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐  我请你跳舞好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:57:47.09,0:57:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样的德性也学人家泡妞 行不行呀你
Dialogue: 0,0:57:49.39,0:57:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看我  高大威猛
Dialogue: 0,0:57:52.10,0:57:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英明神武  一表人才
Dialogue: 0,0:57:56.30,0:57:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:58:00.31,0:58:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你这么有魅力的小姐 来参加我的舞会
Dialogue: 0,0:58:05.08,0:58:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stella你穿得怪模怪样的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:07.69,0:58:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 像只鸡一样  快回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:58:18.49,0:58:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本没把我这个表哥放在眼里
Dialogue: 0,0:58:20.76,0:58:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我交个男朋友都不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:58:23.03,0:58:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:58:24.03,0:58:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开点  不要在这里碍手碍脚
Dialogue: 0,0:58:38.68,0:58:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在十足像个舞女  快点回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:40.88,0:58:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以来  我不可以来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:58:42.61,0:58:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再打扰我的舞伴
Dialogue: 0,0:58:50.15,0:58:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:52.49,0:58:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:58:55.16,0:58:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放手  你放手我跟你回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.30,0:58:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不回去
Dialogue: 0,0:59:02.20,0:59:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打我
Dialogue: 0,0:59:06.91,0:59:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我走  我再也不要见你
Dialogue: 0,0:59:09.94,0:59:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走啦  我送你
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.95,0:59:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气了  这种人是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.12,0:59:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:59:18.05,0:59:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手动脚  你是不是想动武
Dialogue: 0,0:59:19.82,0:59:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动武就动武
Dialogue: 0,0:59:21.29,0:59:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒挺有吸引力的嘛 
Dialogue: 0,0:59:23.24,0:59:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我服了你了  还装蒜
Dialogue: 0,0:59:27.23,0:59:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么比啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:59:28.16,0:59:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁比输了  就打断谁的脚
Dialogue: 0,0:59:32.03,0:59:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你准备拐杖吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:59:33.30,0:59:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你用的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:36.00,0:59:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦让一让
Dialogue: 0,1:00:32.89,1:00:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  胡子呀
Dialogue: 0,1:00:43.57,1:00:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我骑着马..
Dialogue: 0,1:00:56.11,1:00:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骑错野马了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:04.32,1:01:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑什么…不许笑
Dialogue: 0,1:01:24.61,1:01:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是蜘蛛
Dialogue: 0,1:01:39.22,1:01:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这只金丝猫要吃你这只蜘蛛
Dialogue: 0,1:02:43.86,1:02:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斗耐力
Dialogue: 0,1:02:46.06,1:02:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便
Dialogue: 0,1:03:13.75,1:03:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到很多星星呀
Dialogue: 0,1:03:20.69,1:03:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了  他输了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:27.43,1:03:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着  去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:30.80,1:03:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大  接棍
Dialogue: 0,1:03:35.47,1:03:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我你不要这样嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:03:38.64,1:03:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stella你听我说
Dialogue: 0,1:03:48.85,1:03:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要找高手比武
Dialogue: 0,1:03:52.69,1:03:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的不好意思要你帮我剪指甲
Dialogue: 0,1:03:54.89,1:03:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别做梦了  我是怕卫生局来查牌
Dialogue: 0,1:03:58.16,1:03:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剪好了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:01.33,1:04:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先去洗澡了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:22.42,1:04:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:30.46,1:04:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人在爱恋中未知恋爱也在斗
Dialogue: 0,1:04:36.47,1:04:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情场遇对手才知爱是极难受
Dialogue: 0,1:04:42.67,1:04:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它消失如轻烟  只恐怕难相见
Dialogue: 0,1:04:48.81,1:04:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱恋令人真恶受
Dialogue: 0,1:04:55.02,1:05:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难觅你影踪万般失意似木偶
Dialogue: 0,1:05:01.66,1:05:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前事像泡影甜和苦我愿尽承受
Dialogue: 0,1:05:07.77,1:05:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只想你回身边  可保证情不变
Dialogue: 0,1:05:14.04,1:05:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美好光景盼再逗留
Dialogue: 0,1:05:20.24,1:05:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必再不揪不睬大家将气斗 (情逢敌手)
Dialogue: 0,1:05:26.45,1:05:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必将气斗  争吵实在难受
Dialogue: 0,1:05:32.72,1:05:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得有知己  
Dialogue: 0,1:05:34.87,1:05:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知己消失不再有 (情逢敌手)
Dialogue: 0,1:05:39.23,1:05:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不顾一切定要将你留
Dialogue: 0,1:05:57.92,1:06:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人在爱恋中未知恋爱也在斗
Dialogue: 0,1:06:04.62,1:06:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情场遇对手才知爱是极难受
Dialogue: 0,1:06:10.76,1:06:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它消失如轻烟  只恐怕难相见
Dialogue: 0,1:06:16.83,1:06:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱恋令人真恶受
Dialogue: 0,1:06:23.14,1:06:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难觅你影踪万般失意似木偶
Dialogue: 0,1:06:29.65,1:06:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前事像泡影甜和苦我愿尽承受
Dialogue: 0,1:06:35.65,1:06:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只想你回身边  可保证情不变
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.06,1:06:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美好光景盼再逗留
Dialogue: 0,1:06:47.90,1:06:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必再不揪不睬大家将气斗 (情逢敌手)
Dialogue: 0,1:06:54.34,1:07:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必将气斗  争吵实在难受
Dialogue: 0,1:07:00.61,1:07:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得有知己  
Dialogue: 0,1:07:02.64,1:07:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知己消失不再有 (情逢敌手)
Dialogue: 0,1:07:06.88,1:07:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不顾一切定要将你留
Dialogue: 0,1:07:11.52,1:07:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘  快点开门  西巴拉要走了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:13.89,1:07:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什么鬼  
Dialogue: 0,1:07:14.83,1:07:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在洗澡 你跑进来想死呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:07:21.33,1:07:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他肯出来向我道歉 就什么事都没有了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:24.70,1:07:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了  不知道他会不会出来
Dialogue: 0,1:07:28.61,1:07:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走呀  你快去把西巴拉找回来
Dialogue: 0,1:07:30.66,1:07:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,, 找不到就不要回来见我
Dialogue: 0,1:07:34.48,1:07:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,1:07:39.15,1:07:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没走啊
Dialogue: 0,1:07:43.92,1:07:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我穿好鞋而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:07:51.63,1:07:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  原来这么少哇  美女
Dialogue: 0,1:07:54.60,1:07:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  我们一起去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,1:07:58.74,1:07:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走开啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:00.20,1:08:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie…救我呀
Dialogue: 0,1:08:04.81,1:08:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Eddie呀
Dialogue: 0,1:08:08.71,1:08:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的马子挺漂亮的
Dialogue: 0,1:08:10.88,1:08:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进得厨房出得厅堂
Dialogue: 0,1:08:12.75,1:08:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还上得电动圆床
Dialogue: 0,1:08:15.09,1:08:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  别乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:16.75,1:08:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么  你咬我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:18.49,1:08:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:19.29,1:08:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:21.13,1:08:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打我啊
Dialogue: 0,1:08:30.03,1:08:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬
Dialogue: 0,1:08:32.64,1:08:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点咬
Dialogue: 0,1:08:35.67,1:08:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬
Dialogue: 0,1:08:39.81,1:08:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该你了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:41.71,1:08:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的是假牙
Dialogue: 0,1:08:45.95,1:08:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,1:08:50.09,1:08:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从四岁开始就和人打架
Dialogue: 0,1:08:52.42,1:08:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在做了拳王  我从来没输过
Dialogue: 0,1:08:55.53,1:08:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得很失望  直到我遇见你
Dialogue: 0,1:09:06.14,1:09:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我一定要和你较量  来吧!
Dialogue: 0,1:09:11.04,1:09:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:09:15.51,1:09:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了  现在时间地点都不合适
Dialogue: 0,1:09:18.32,1:09:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明天一早在大雾山 的山顶分个高低
Dialogue: 0,1:09:22.02,1:09:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  一言为定  不见不散
Dialogue: 0,1:09:27.19,1:09:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的要跟他打
Dialogue: 0,1:09:28.63,1:09:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑  跟只牛打架  我骗他的
Dialogue: 0,1:09:31.80,1:09:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好坏!刚才吓死我了
Dialogue: 0,1:09:33.66,1:09:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只牛回来了
Dialogue: 0,1:09:37.84,1:09:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去吧  姐姐很挂念你的
Dialogue: 0,1:09:57.96,1:09:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋  补充体力
Dialogue: 0,1:10:06.46,1:10:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年青人  不要玩得太多
Dialogue: 0,1:10:09.03,1:10:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不然吃再多鸡蛋都补不回来
Dialogue: 0,1:10:12.87,1:10:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吓鬼呀!我都没怕过
Dialogue: 0,1:10:28.09,1:10:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先穿件衣服
Dialogue: 0,1:10:30.89,1:10:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都这么撞  很容易撞坏脑子的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:35.96,1:10:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:37.66,1:10:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馊的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:45.64,1:10:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多脏衣服  我来帮你洗吧!
Dialogue: 0,1:10:48.67,1:10:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,1:10:50.21,1:10:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服这么脏  不洗怎么行
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.21,1:10:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有事呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:10:58.35,1:10:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事没事
Dialogue: 0,1:11:10.19,1:11:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了  照片
Dialogue: 0,1:11:20.97,1:11:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么?
Dialogue: 0,1:11:22.71,1:11:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己洗行了  老板娘
Dialogue: 0,1:11:25.41,1:11:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是自己人  还叫什么老板娘啊
Dialogue: 0,1:11:28.21,1:11:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我阿英就行了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:32.88,1:11:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿英..
Dialogue: 0,1:11:37.32,1:11:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我洗衣服了
Dialogue: 0,1:11:41.49,1:11:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:11:43.79,1:11:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先
Dialogue: 0,1:11:50.23,1:11:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣服不用愁  阿英她会帮我的忙
Dialogue: 0,1:11:55.07,1:11:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣机她有  洗衣粉她也有
Dialogue: 0,1:12:02.38,1:12:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这么脏啊  一块洗了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:12:15.46,1:12:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿英
Dialogue: 0,1:12:19.36,1:12:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三杓洗衣粉够不够
Dialogue: 0,1:12:22.07,1:12:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌少呀?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:23.37,1:12:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿英是你叫的吗?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:25.10,1:12:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦?
Dialogue: 0,1:12:26.20,1:12:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这种照片你下流 藏这种照片你更下流
Dialogue: 0,1:12:33.18,1:12:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了…
Dialogue: 0,1:12:35.88,1:12:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然照这种照片  你不怕羞我怕羞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:12:40.82,1:12:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次去夜总会照的照片仍了就算了
Dialogue: 0,1:12:43.99,1:12:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金丝猫
Dialogue: 0,1:12:45.06,1:12:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己又去了另外一间
Dialogue: 0,1:12:47.46,1:12:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是该死  我没办法了 你自己解决
Dialogue: 0,1:13:01.61,1:13:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘
Dialogue: 0,1:13:06.11,1:13:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把它撕烂了
Dialogue: 0,1:13:07.95,1:13:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人靠得住  母猪也会上树  你滚吧
Dialogue: 0,1:13:15.72,1:13:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓以后再也不去那种地方
Dialogue: 0,1:13:18.16,1:13:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你原谅我一次吧  就一次
Dialogue: 0,1:13:22.73,1:13:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要呀  老板娘走…
Dialogue: 0,1:13:24.80,1:13:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不敢了滚…
Dialogue: 0,1:13:40.44,1:13:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋
Dialogue: 0,1:13:44.88,1:13:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鸡蛋都变成小鸡了  傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,1:13:46.62,1:13:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从天亮等到天黑 难道还要等着看月亮
Dialogue: 0,1:14:02.63,1:14:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来是我不对  老板娘对我这么好
Dialogue: 0,1:14:05.47,1:14:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不应该去那种地方玩的  我该打!
Dialogue: 0,1:14:12.88,1:14:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打得我那么痛… 
Dialogue: 0,1:14:14.23,1:14:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥  干吗你自己打自己啊
Dialogue: 0,1:14:16.71,1:14:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在打蚊子而已嘛…
Dialogue: 0,1:14:18.78,1:14:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  有蚊子飞过来了
Dialogue: 0,1:14:22.25,1:14:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别玩了  心情不好
Dialogue: 0,1:14:24.32,1:14:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小意思了  姐姐还心痛呢
Dialogue: 0,1:14:27.39,1:14:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我有办法
Dialogue: 0,1:14:29.06,1:14:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么办法?
Dialogue: 0,1:14:30.79,1:14:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办法就是你自己去解决吧
Dialogue: 0,1:14:33.83,1:14:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门没有锁的!我很快就回来
Dialogue: 0,1:14:44.94,1:14:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿弟  很晚了  还不去睡
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.22,1:14:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘
Dialogue: 0,1:15:04.29,1:15:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来干什么?
Dialogue: 0,1:15:06.93,1:15:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个杯子很好用吧
Dialogue: 0,1:15:09.97,1:15:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还给你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:16.44,1:15:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫高手  出来
Dialogue: 0,1:15:19.71,1:15:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个是高手啊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:20.64,1:15:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不就是罗
Dialogue: 0,1:15:21.98,1:15:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不快出来
Dialogue: 0,1:15:22.98,1:15:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱人的杯子  你也敢打破
Dialogue: 0,1:15:28.59,1:15:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像铁这么硬
Dialogue: 0,1:15:32.22,1:15:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事  大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,1:15:34.69,1:15:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样  大眼哥
Dialogue: 0,1:15:39.86,1:15:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我  你抓得我好痛
Dialogue: 0,1:15:43.27,1:15:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大眼哥  你怎么样?
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.40,1:15:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要带我去哪里
Dialogue: 0,1:15:46.37,1:15:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫高手来太平洋体育馆找我
Dialogue: 0,1:15:49.64,1:15:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,1:15:53.51,1:15:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这样做不是办法  是犯法
Dialogue: 0,1:15:56.35,1:15:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放你走  但你一定要叫高手来见我
Dialogue: 0,1:15:59.02,1:16:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不然我每天都会来抓你
Dialogue: 0,1:16:10.93,1:16:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.96,1:16:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他…
Dialogue: 0,1:16:14.20,1:16:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家再说吧!
Dialogue: 0,1:16:56.67,1:16:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这次来不是跟你决斗的
Dialogue: 0,1:17:01.78,1:17:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我摆了你一道 你也打伤我的人  扯平了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:05.12,1:17:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我对不起你  我并不是什么高手
Dialogue: 0,1:17:07.58,1:17:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后你不要再缠着我  再见
Dialogue: 0,1:17:09.85,1:17:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要再见了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:16.96,1:17:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还说不是高手
Dialogue: 0,1:17:23.77,1:17:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,1:17:29.01,1:17:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打吧!
Dialogue: 0,1:17:40.25,1:17:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊  上来啊
Dialogue: 0,1:17:56.27,1:17:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拳王又赢了  他从来没有输过
Dialogue: 0,1:18:02.64,1:18:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又赢了  我又赢了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:05.44,1:18:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊!你赢了 你又赢了  你了不起
Dialogue: 0,1:18:09.98,1:18:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好棒  我可以走了吗
Dialogue: 0,1:18:14.65,1:18:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我打倒的人 
Dialogue: 0,1:18:15.52,1:18:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远都不可能起来的  你骗我
Dialogue: 0,1:18:17.65,1:18:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认输都不行啊!
Dialogue: 0,1:18:18.96,1:18:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  要被我打倒才行
Dialogue: 0,1:18:28.77,1:18:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,1:18:38.91,1:18:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掉了…掉不了
Dialogue: 0,1:18:41.68,1:18:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用你帮我
Dialogue: 0,1:18:42.95,1:18:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是帮你掉下去
Dialogue: 0,1:18:46.42,1:18:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我上
Dialogue: 0,1:18:47.92,1:18:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弹
Dialogue: 0,1:18:58.03,1:19:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么我老上不去啊
Dialogue: 0,1:19:01.00,1:19:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想出一个好办法上去了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:04.84,1:19:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打我呀  打我呀…
Dialogue: 0,1:19:37.37,1:19:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,1:19:46.91,1:19:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢碰我的银杯
Dialogue: 0,1:19:50.11,1:19:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道
Dialogue: 0,1:19:51.21,1:19:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我捱了多少拳头
Dialogue: 0,1:19:52.72,1:19:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒多少拳师
Dialogue: 0,1:19:54.55,1:19:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是这只杯子
Dialogue: 0,1:19:56.95,1:19:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我用命拼回来的  你知不知道
Dialogue: 0,1:20:00.39,1:20:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是厨师  不是拳师啊
Dialogue: 0,1:20:02.33,1:20:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢侮辱我
Dialogue: 0,1:20:05.33,1:20:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些杯子都不是你的  你是不是傻的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:07.83,1:20:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人说我傻  只有人说我痴
Dialogue: 0,1:20:09.97,1:20:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  让个神经病玩了
Dialogue: 0,1:20:11.90,1:20:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要杯子  我要你跟我打
Dialogue: 0,1:20:19.98,1:20:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁?
Dialogue: 0,1:20:21.48,1:20:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说来帮我忙的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:24.08,1:20:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识你了  你是三一万能侠
Dialogue: 0,1:20:25.98,1:20:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你走开
Dialogue: 0,1:20:45.17,1:20:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不跟我打  就不准走
Dialogue: 0,1:22:35.01,1:22:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绳子
Dialogue: 0,1:23:08.88,1:23:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小意思  小意思
Dialogue: 0,1:23:11.38,1:23:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这条粗绳子绷断才叫有本事
Dialogue: 0,1:23:15.45,1:23:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我绷断给你看看
Dialogue: 0,1:23:18.66,1:23:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来
Dialogue: 0,1:23:22.53,1:23:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我绑
Dialogue: 0,1:23:24.63,1:23:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  当然  来…
Dialogue: 0,1:23:27.50,1:23:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绑紧一点…
Dialogue: 0,1:23:33.87,1:23:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绷吧
Dialogue: 0,1:23:51.45,1:23:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绷不断啊
Dialogue: 0,1:23:53.12,1:23:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放了我  我们再打
Dialogue: 0,1:23:56.26,1:23:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放了你  那可难了  让我打个够
Dialogue: 0,1:24:01.33,1:24:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打我 为什么不还手  还手..
Dialogue: 0,1:24:07.84,1:24:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过瘾啊  好过瘾啊
Dialogue: 0,1:24:10.71,1:24:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又想到个办法了  我滚开它
Dialogue: 0,1:24:13.08,1:24:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我滚…怎么滚不开的
Dialogue: 0,1:24:23.79,1:24:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发神经病就好了  别把我扯上嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:24:26.62,1:24:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高手  有胆你就放了我再打 我还没输的
Dialogue: 0,1:24:32.16,1:24:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护士小姐  103号房在哪? 转弯就是了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:38.00,1:24:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板娘
Dialogue: 0,1:24:38.80,1:24:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就知道你个贱骨头 没伤得那么重的
Dialogue: 0,1:24:42.91,1:24:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是呀
Dialogue: 0,1:24:45.38,1:24:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说我伤得很重
Dialogue: 0,1:24:51.58,1:24:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的头也穿了  我的手也断了
Dialogue: 0,1:24:56.02,1:25:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心也碎了  我不行了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:00.66,1:25:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,1:25:06.13,1:25:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心电图没反应的?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:08.10,1:25:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心电图?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:15.41,1:25:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了?
Dialogue: 0,1:25:19.28,1:25:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你送给我的 
Dialogue: 0,1:25:20.81,1:25:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看  我把杯子粘好了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:23.71,1:25:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见没有?你不能死
Dialogue: 0,1:25:33.76,1:25:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算修理好了  好  收工
Dialogue: 0,1:25:38.86,1:25:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是心电图啊
Dialogue: 0,1:25:40.43,1:25:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么心电图呀  不是
Dialogue: 0,1:25:43.40,1:25:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是心电图  那我不用死了
Dialogue: 0,1:25:46.87,1:25:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你..
Dialogue: 0,1:25:49.97,1:25:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气  以前都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,1:25:53.78,1:25:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:26:03.09,1:26:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好讨厌
Dialogue: 0,1:26:04.32,1:26:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才大眼哥也是这样亲姐姐的
Dialogue: 0,1:26:06.66,1:26:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才表姐是这样打的
