Why are you sighing?
I'm just worried about you.
I've been waiting here more than a decade
for an opportunity.
You've just arrived,
with no idea how long you'll have to wait.
Not necessarily,
maybe my luck's better than yours.
I thought the same way, too.
But then even my bones grew uncertain.
I don't want you to be like me.
Uncle, you're so nice.
You don't know
just how hypocritical people up there are.
If everyone were like you,
I wouldn't be down here.
Is that right?
All that's left of me are these old bones.
You're still young.
I also hope you'll make it one day.
Uncle, how are you?
I'm fine.
Maybe this hole's getting bigger,
and I've caught a bit of a chill.
Move over here when I'm gone, then.
Help yourself.
Someone's coming.
It's a fat guy.
The fatty's mine.
Uncle, you're wrong to say that.
How am I wrong?
I've been waiting for this day.
Why are you such a hypocrite?
This isn't hypocrisy,
it's reality.
You old bastard!
Young man, don't be impetuous.
Don't be hasty.
If I'm not hasty, I'll have to wait
decades just like you said!
All things must have
a beginning and an end.
Ghosts must never fight ghosts.
Let's see who has the means.
Fine.
Old man, don't be greedy!
That was really scary!
You trying to scare me to death?
More like you scared me to death!
- You see a ghost?
- How did you know?
If it wasn't a ghost, you wouldn't
be screaming like a man possessed!
Those two ghosts,
don't know if they were crazy,
but they just kept chasing me!
You're this scared
from seeing ghosts in your dreams.
Aren't you always saying you've got guts?
Like that needs to be said!
Who in this village doesn't know
your husband's name is big guts cheung?
Ghosts, that's all!
- You'll definitely be seeing some.
- Why?
As the saying goes:
Poorer you are, the more it haunts you.
The way I see it,
you'll soon be crushed by your own demons!
You're the one
who'll be crushed by demons!
Better crushed by demons
than crushed by you!
This dress...
Does it make you look bad?
Where did you get such a beautiful dress?
- Bought it.
- Bought it?
This dress looks very expensive.
It's not like I used your money.
What are you so stressed about?
You didn't use my money...?
Whose did you use, then?!
Used? I used my own!
Yours?
How come you've got so much money?
If you're thrifty...
If you're thrifty, you'll have money!
You'll have money?
Aren't you going to work?
Today's the ghost festival.
Master tam said he won't be going out,
so I don't have to work.
- Want to go for tea?
- No.
Suit yourself.
I'm going, then.
Pork buns!
Hey...
Ah dou, here so early?
Eat what you like.
The meal's on me.
Big guts cheung, you're great!
They really named you right.
You don't say?!
In this town, who doesn't know
I've got the biggest guts?
Pfft, what's so great about
tempting the spirits of unmarked graves?
Think you're clever?
I know of a game that comes from the west.
It's already scared
plenty of foreigners to death!
We're scaring foreigners now?
Hey, how do you play it?
Peel an apple.
So long as...
Peeling an apple?!
And here I thought you had something.
Don't go cutting in midsong.
Let him finish first.
Alright, finish chirping then.
Midnight. Take an apple.
Light a candle. Face a mirror.
Peel with a knife.
Don't break the peel.
When you're done peeling...
What then?
You'll see what you want to see.
That for real?
What if the peel breaks?
Then some horrific things will appear,
the likes of which you've never seen.
Maybe even...
Who you trying to scare?
I don't believe it.
So arrogant!
You have the guts to give it a try?
If someone's treating me to tea,
I'll do it any time.
Ok. Tomorrow's meal is on me.
- Tonight, you come to my house.
- Ok.
Now, help yourself.
Eat all you want.
This meal's on me.
Someone's paying.
Hey, waitress,
set one more place.
Hey, there's another meal tomorrow.
Don't forget.
Go.
I broke the peel.
I wonder what horrific things
will happen now?
Come on...
Why's a female ghost wearing men's shoes?
Why are those eyes so familiar?
Turns out, it's ah do...
You're finished!
Come out...
Quickly, come out!
Coming out...
How dare you make a fool of me?!
I'll beat you up!
I was only joking with you.
Joking?!
You could've scared me to death!
How could that be?
You've got some real big guts, remember?
Hey, stop the fanning now!
We've been busted!
We've been busted?
Hey, you can stop fanning!
- How come you got busted?
- Oh, so you teamed up to scare me?
Say no more.
Go light the candles.
- You...
- Actually, we didn't mean it.
There's no denying it,
you really have big guts!
My god,
you only had to light them again!
Hey...
- Hey... what's wrong?
- There's a ghost! Let's go!
How did you come out of the mirror?
I have a way, of course.
Come.
The mirror's manoeuvrable.
Slide it down and you can see me.
I slide it back up...
How can you see me in the mirror now?
Listen, I'm telling you,
I'm not afraid of real ghosts.
But there's no cure
for scaring someone to death!
You ever do anything like this again,
I'll...
Alright, I admit defeat.
Tea's on me.
Don't lose your temper.
I'll pour you tea to apologise.
Come on, forgive me.
You really live up to the name
big guts cheung.
- They really named you right.
- There's no more to be said.
- Drink up.
- After this, we're even. But never again!
Hey, that's enough!
Hiding to try and scare me again?
I'll lose my temper!
He's not here?
If I find you, you're a dead man!
Where'd he go?
Ah mou! Ah pang!
What's this?
Ol' cheung!
What is it, master tam?
Remember,
don't tell anyone where I'm going.
Don't worry, master tam.
I, big guts cheung, am no fool.
Once you tell me something,
I'l remember it forever.
You needn't tell me again.
You know I'm a rich and respectable man,
and now I'm running for mayor.
If people knew of these affairs,
it would have a major impact
on my reputation.
Yeah, a major impact.
As long as you're smart,
I won't treat you shabbily.
Sure.
Oh yeah, master tam.
I don't understand.
A rich and powerful man like you
can have any woman.
Name her, she's yours.
Why go to all this trouble?
I'm a squire, to say the least.
There are things you don't want
people to know or see.
What's more, the flowers at home aren't
as fragrant as the ones in the wild.
I agree with that sentiment.
We're here.
Be careful, master tam.
I'll come pick you up
in one stick of incense's time.
Master tam, please...
Smoothest of the smooth tofu pudding!
Hey.
Uncle fook,
give me a bowl of that smooth.
- Coming up.
- Why are you so late today?
I'm waiting for master tam.
Hey, the incense's almost burnt out.
Get going or your boss will whine.
Thanks, uncle fook.
- Thanks.
- Go on.
- Hurry up.
I never thought so many young men
would still be in this line of work.
Oh, what's so bad
about this line of work?
We come and go on wheels, yeah?
It's leisurely.
We get a lot of tips, too.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Well, it is quite a lot.
Here, let me tell you a story.
Great...
- Old biddy!
- What is it?
Go buy some sugar for me.
Aren't you worried
I'll have a bit on the side?
If you've the appetite,
snack all you want!
Hurry up and go!
Now, back in the day,
there was a guy in your line of work.
He came and went on a set of wheels.
Everyday he lived his life
to a stick of incense.
It was most leisurely.
You lot are squatting here
eating tofu pudding.
He on the other hand
went looking for fresh meat.
One day,
he unexpectedly knocked off early.
He got back home and saw...
My goodness!
Can you guess what his wife was doing?
What was she doing?
What the hell was she doing?
Making love.
His mind was set.
He quit being a coachman,
and with wife in tow
sold tofu pudding instead.
That's a true story.
You old bastard!
You're dragging up something
that happened decades ago!
You're telling people I had an affair.
You think you're a big shot?!
No, I didn't say you had an affair.
- I only said you were making love.
- You still want to argue?
You said I made love to someone.
That means you're saying I had an affair!
My goodness, wife! Would I dare?
- Even if I had the courage...
- Here's your money.
I wouldn't say that about you!
Fine.
Just wait till I get you home!
- Quit yelling... get back to work...
- Old bastard!
- Don't bother me!
- Hey!
- Good stuff!
- Yeah...
Good, yeah?
What're you peeping at?
Get lost!
Open the door...
Hurry!
Be careful.
- Where's that man?
- What man?
The man who was in bed with you!
The man who was in bed with me?
So you're saying
I'm sleeping with other men, then?!
Here, you take a look.
Look for this other man.
I saw him with my own eyes.
Saw him, my backside!
Oh, I know
you're no longer satisfied with me.
You want an excuse to divorce me.
Fine! Divorce me!
Huh? Divorce!
Here, write the divorce letter...
Write it...
I...
You think you're so appealing?
That I like being with you, huh?
I work hard day and night,
so went to take a nap.
And you say I'm sleeping around?!
Oh, you've even got a knife
to chop me up, huh?!
Chop me...
You're heartless! Chop me, then!
Whose shoe's this?
It's so big, it doesn't fit me.
Where's the other one?
Because it wouldn't fit,
I exchanged it for you.
This shoe's old.
When have you had money for new shoes?
You've always worn old ones!
See?! You've wronged me
in front of so many people.
How can I ever face anyone again?
I don't want to live!
Just kill me! Kill me!
Hey... alright, wife.
Don't be like this.
My goodness!
I won't make it on time.
Wife, let's just say I was wrong.
I have to hurry to work now.
I'll see you later, then.
You're leaving just like that?!
Don't you go!
My goodness!
What are you all gawking at?
Let's go.
Makes no sense.
This shoe must be the adulterer's.
What do a husband and wife argue about?
The less words the better.
Master, you're looking for me?
Are you tired of playing
with fat cheung's wife?
But fat cheung
almost caught me red-handed today.
How could that be?
Didn't you ask someone
to keep an eye on big guts cheung?
I don't know what
got the lad so riled up today
that he would think his wife
was sleeping around,
and go home to check.
He didn't see you?
Nol
if he saw me,
would I have made it back alive?
However,
he picked up a shoe I left behind.
Pfft! It's no big deal.
There's nothing on the shoe
to identify you.
My biggest fear's that his wife
will get spooked again,
and reveal everything.
Oh, you can rest easy then.
I can't speak for anyone else,
but this woman isn't someone
big guts cheung can handle.
Even so.
It doesn't bear thinking about.
Master, you mean...?
Big guts cheung...
However... this type of thing
needs to be done cleanly.
Otherwise, there'll be even more
loose ends to wrap up.
Don't tell me you didn't know
that fat cheung's no push-over.
That's right.
I know of a friend who's a maoshan master.
You're talking about maoshan sorcery?
That's right.
Does that kind of thing actually work?
If not, would so many people in this
village believe in maoshan sorcery?
- What's his name?
- His name's chin hoi.
This chap's willing to do anything
as long as he's paid.
Daoist master chin, this arrangement...
- I've thought about it.
- And...?
I can agree to do it.
- But...
- But what?
The altar must be set up at your place.
That so?
It's all for safety's sake.
Alright.
I'll leave it all to you.
Daoist hall of daoist master chin
come in.
Senior.
This is advisor la...
He's my junior.
- That's all for now.
- Fine.
- I'm going.
- Please...
Oh, yeah.
Senior, you were in a hurry to find me.
What's the matter?
Some guy's offended a rich man.
The rich man discussed with me
having said guy bumped off.
Murder?
It's not like
we'd have to get our hands dirty.
We just have to set up an altar
and that'll be that.
Senior, the purpose for our learning
maoshan sorcery was to save people.
We've saved so many people.
Killing one of them would only be right.
Senior,
according to our sect's doctrine...
First taboo: Insatiable greed.
Second taboo: Unscrupulous killing.
Third taboo:
Blasphemy of the three luminaries.
- Fourth taboo...
- Nefarious collusion with cronies, right?
Aren't you foolish?
In this world, money is the only truth.
Besides,
master has been dead such a long time.
- Senior, you...
- That's enough...
All you need say
is whether you'll help me.
I'm sorry, senior.
Don't help, then!
But I'm warning you,
don't tell anyone about this.
Otherwise, there'll be no mercy,
even between brothers.
Doesn't appreciate my favour.
Master, martial uncle, he...
Hey, that's big guts cheung.
Go on.
How can you go looking like that?
Change your clothes first.
Change quickly! Go on!
Excuse Mel!
Aren't you big guts cheung?
You are...?
It's old dog fa!
Old dog fa?
Yeah, that's me.
We've even gone out drinking together.
- Really?
- Really!
Hey, are your guts
still as big as they used to be?
I've now claimed the number two spot,
so nobody dares claim they're number one.
I don't believe it.
If you don't believe it,
there's nothing I can do.
Hey... now, how about this...?
I bet you ten taels of silver.
- Ten taels of silver?
- Right.
What's the bet?
The bet's that you spend the night
at the ma family ancestral hall.
Spend the night
at the ma ancestral hall?
It's as simple as that.
Do you dare?
It's not like I'm facing a firing squad.
I'm all in.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, no matter.
My friend...
Have we been out drinking together?
Nol
then there's no problem.
Hey!
May I ask
where ma ancestral hall is?
Now, pass through the forest,
turn left, and there's a small path.
At the top's ma ancestral hall.
I'm going to ma ancestral hall.
Why's he going?
Hey...
Why are you going to ma ancestral hall?
- To collect a body.
- Huh? Collect whose body?
Some fat guy's spending the night
at ma ancestral hall.
He's definitely done for.
I'll be collecting his body tomorrow.
I'm going now to check out the location.
Hey, do I count as fat?
You don't just count as,
you really are fat!
Hey, then I'm the fat guy!
He's done for!
Done for?!
Did old dog fa ask you to come?
I don't know any foreign dogs,
Chinese dogs, or mixed-breed dogs.
My senior said you're done for
and asked me to collect the body.
Your senior, who's that?
- A maoshan sorcerer.
- Maoshan sorcery?
Five ghosts carrying wealth
kind of stuff?
I don't believe in it.
Now, I'm poor enough.
If you can conjure up some silver taels,
I'll believe in it.
If I could do that,
I wouldn't need to work!
Now,
I can turn blank paper into hell money.
Then let's see you change it.
Hold this.
Watch this.
See, one piece, two pieces,
three pieces, four pieces,
five pieces.
Change!
One, two, three, four, five.
One note, two notes,
three notes,
four notes, five notes.
That's great!
Hey, big brother,
are there any ways to save me?
There aren't any!
You believe me now?
You changed blank paper into hell money.
Now I believe everything!
Ok, allow me to enlighten you.
When at ma ancestral hall,
wait until nightfall.
First interval:
Nothing will happen.
Second interval:
Climb up onto the tallest beam.
No matter what happens,
don't make a sound.
Third interval's quiet.
Fourth interval's...
What happens then?
You must lie under the coffin.
And the fifth interval?
By then it'll be dawn.
At dawn you'll be fine.
I guess so. Let's go.
- I'm not going.
- Why?
You're not going to die,
so why do I have to go?
I haven't asked your name.
My name's tsui.
I live on the nine miles trail.
If you ever need anything,
come find me.
Remember what I just told you.
Of course, I'll remember.
I hope I've met a noble man.
You'd better not be a scoundrel!
Hey... big guts cheung!
Are you kidding me?!
You're driving me crazy!
Hurry up! Get a move on!
- It's getting dark.
- I get it!
Now, go in on your own.
Hey, go on!
Get inside!
Hey...
It's a while until dark.
I'll find a place to rest first.
Master, the cinnabar's ground.
- Fire it up.
- Yes.
The time has come.
Why can't I find him?
It's ready.
Water...
- All gone.
- All gone?
Daoist master chin,
are you up to this?
Damn! It's daybreak!
I command you: Get back!
Big guts cheung...
Maybe he's kicked the bucket?
Cheung...
Big guts cheung!
Here, let's make another bet.
Sleep in there for one more night,
and I'll give you another 50 taels.
- 50 taels?
- That's right, 50 taels!
- Right!
Great, it's a deal!
See you later, then.
Hey... come back!
Hey... hold on!
Shit!
This time my life really is on thin ice!
Oh... it's all good!
Now it comes down to whether you've
got enough luck and enough balls!
Enough luck? Enough balls?
What time have you arranged to meet?
The hour of the rooster.
What time's it now?
The hour of the monkey.
You have one more hour.
In this hour,
see if you can find...
A pot of black dog's blood,
four dog paws, and fifty chicken eggs.
Remember,
be sure they're chicken eggs!
Boss, please give me fifty chicken eggs.
I'll be back for them later.
- Fifty?
- They must be chicken eggs!
- Alright, pick them up later.
- Thanks.
Ten.
Twenty.
Thirty.
Forty.
Oh, damn! Not enough.
Duck eggs
not one less.
Slaughterhouse
Boss, are they ready yet?
All done. Here.
Thanks.
First of all,
place everything inside ma ancestral hall.
Everything's settled.
- All done?
- What now?
Where do I sleep tonight?
Tonight,
you sleep on top of the coffin.
You scared?
I'm not scared... but I am afraid!
You're in no position to be so afraid!
Remember, sleep on top of the coffin,
holding the chicken eggs.
Once it's night's second interval,
the coffin will go "lak"...
When the coffin lid opens,
throw in a chicken egg right away.
The coffin lid will then close.
Now, anyway, just remember this:
When it opens, throw one in.
You have to use all 50 eggs.
By then,
the sun will almost be up.
Pow! He'll then use all his strength
to throw the coffin lid up.
You'll have to pour that pot of black
dog's blood and four dog paws over him.
What a relief!
At which point the vampire
won't be able to hurt you anymore.
That's seriously bad!
Also, I'm leaving here tonight.
No matter what,
don't make any more bets.
Where are you going?
If you get the chance,
come find me at man fook mortuary
over at ten mile town.
How cruel...
I'm going to bed first.
You stay here and watch.
Ok... you get some rest first.
What flipped me over?
It makes no sense.
Master, are you alright?
Piss off!
Come onl
Water.
None left.
How did you even end up like this?
So what now?
Can it work?
For surel
master tam, that was quick.
I'm a bit worse for wear lately.
Then you need to nourish your body.
Once you've taken me home,
you can call it a day.
Thanks, master tam.
You have to be a serious man.
Stop being so immature.
You understand?
Just try and get away this time!
Blood?!
How come my house's in such a mess?
Wife...
Wife!
Out of the way.
Chief constable,
I was just looking for you.
You weren't looking for me.
You wanted to cut and run.
No,
it looks like my wife's been killed!
Not looks like; Definitely has.
Fatty, where's the body?
I couldn't actually find the body.
Oh, you got rid of the body
and destroyed the evidence?!
Nol
where's your proof?
Where were you
when the crime was committed?
- I was...
- Say it!
I was at uncle fook's
eating sweet tofu pudding.
- Men, bring in uncle fook.
- Yes!
Fatty.
See if they match.
It fits?
Fits perfectly.
Needless to say,
this is also yours?
I guess so.
Fatty, you murdered your wife,
and moved the corpse to the kitchen.
You wanted to pull off a 'stash the
corpse under the stove' type deal,
but couldn't manage it.
So you shifted the corpse
through the window.
- I...
- Why did you murder your wife?
Hate, fun, love, money?
You only need to
answer with one word.
I didn't!
We really loved each other!
We brought witnesses!
You speak first.
You speak.
Chief constable, this couple
fought and argued all day.
A few days ago, big guts cheung
even slashed his wife with a knife!
- Right!
- A-a-also...
That's enough... get out...
- Did you hear that?
- 1...
Uncle fook's here.
But he's had a stroke.
Your last hope's right there.
Uncle fook,
please tell the chief constable
that I went to your place
to eat tofu pudding today!
I...
Uncle fook, how could you have a stroke
at a time like this?
If you don't speak up,
I'm a dead man!
Uncle fook, you must talk!
Uncle fook!
Fatty, you're interfering with the witness
and obstructing justice.
I'm not!
You can't talk, can you?
Men, bring a pen and ink.
Now, all you have to do
is write 'yes' or 'no' on the paper.
Yes...
He said you didn't!
The evidence is irrefutable
and you're still denying it?
Men, take him back!
I'm innocent!
Master tam. Advisor la...
Fat cheung,
how could you do such a thing?
Master tam, I'm innocent!
When my wife died, I was still waiting
for you at the front of the inn.
I haven't told anyone.
Master tam,
please think of a way to save me.
I don't think fat cheung's
that kind of man.
Our master's doing what he can
to help you.
I've spent a lot of money
to try and help you.
So just be calm and wait.
For death!
Thank you, master tam.
Alright. We're leaving now.
I'll see you out.
No need.
I won't bother, then.
Master tam,
drop by whenever you're free.
Whoa! So plentiful!
Master tam really has his ways.
Fatty, indulge to your
heart's content tonight.
You'll be gone after tomorrow.
You're letting me out tomorrow?
We'll let something out.
But it'll be your blood.
Boss, what do you mean by that?
You've got such a big head,
your brow's beaded with sweat.
Understand?
Eat up!
Makes no sense.
Makes no sense, at all!
Boss,
did you send it to the wrong cell?
It's not the wrong cell.
Are you going to eat it?
If not, I'll take it away.
I won't!
Master tam has spent a lot of money on me.
It makes no sense.
I'll eat alright!
Yeah, eat till you're full!
Give us some...
Don't steal... that's mine...
It hurts!
It hurts, hurts like hell.
I'm dying...
Hey, he's got a bellyache!
Let him have it.
Best he messes up his guts
and drops dead.
That way we won't have to collect his body
from the execution ground tomorrow, right?
Hey, he hasn't had enough.
Let's give him a little more.
Go in.
Damn fatty,
destroying public property!
- Beat him good!
- Don't beat me! Don't!
These death row prisoners
are always like this.
- They always need a good beating.
- Beat him up.
I wouldn't dare!
Don't hit me! Don't!
Don't hit me!
I wouldn't dare!
He's as good as dead.
- Leaves less work for us to do.
- Yeah, forget those death row inmates.
Yeah, tonight we knock off early.
- Where are we going to play?
- We'll decide after we knock off.
Boss,
I didn't mean to knock over your coffin.
I'm sorry...
I don't know who's the unlucky one,
you or me?
How fragile is this?
Next time you come across some cash,
don't spend it at this coffin shop!
Excuse me.
There's no place to sleep.
Here, old friend,
you've got four and a half planks.
Let me borrow one to sleep on.
Come daybreak I'm gone.
I'm sorry.
How did he escape?
Don't ask me.
At any rate, we were unlucky.
- Then thanks for all your trouble.
- Track him down.
Where is he?
He's disappeared.
He must've absorbed some of my qi,
so whatever I do,
he does as well.
You're shrewder than a ghost!
I'm afraid of you!
Ok! Let's see what you're like
when day breaks.
It's like there's wolves to the front
and tigers to the rear!
It's big guts cheung!
He's coming this way.
With me here,
he has nowhere run.
Come on.
He's coming...
Give me the swords!
Men!
Yes...
Hurry up!
- Hurry, lift him off!
- Yes...
Hurry up!
Burn him!
Are you ok, boss?
Of course, I'm alright.
Go after him!
Yes...
Whoa! This kind of thing again?!
Big guts cheung?!
Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm in some real hot water.
I've got the bailiffs on my tail.
Hey,
is there any place here to hide?
I think the bailiffs
will catch up with me soon.
Follow me.
Hey... what are you doing?
You're going in the coffin.
Hide in the coffin?
But the thing inside...?
It's decomposed into nothing.
Hurry up!
Hurry up and lie inside.
This way!
Anyone there?
You can't see such a big man sitting here?
Have you seen anyone come in here?
Sure!
Where is he?
Right beside me.
I meant before we came in.
Oh, then no.
- Search everywhere.
- Yes...
- Hey, there...
- Hey...
- Anyone there?
We've searched everywhere
and there's no one here.
You guys, go and take a look
inside the third coffin.
Yes!
Boss, you should go...
So useless!
That one's been dead for a long time.
It's overgrown with bugs.
My god...
It's really disgusting!
Now, think it through carefully.
- Right?
- Yeah...
Whoa!
It's truly disgusting!
It's truly disgusting?
- I told you...
- Say no more.
If you see this fatty,
notify me at the court.
Sure...
Let's go.
Hey, come out.
- They've gone?
- Yes.
Hey,
what are you going to do now?
I don't know what to do.
How about you stay here and assist me?
That's actually what I meant.
Thank you very much.
- This is for you.
- Thanks.
No need to see me off.
Here.
Did you actually murder your wife?
Absolutely not!
Do you know who did kill her?
Oh, of course I do.
It was the owner of this shoe.
- Who's that?
- It's...
I don't know.
Nonsense! Don't talk so much.
I'm as hungry as a ghost.
Let's find a place to eat first.
Good. I'm a bit hungry, too!
What tea would you two like?
Pu'er.
Here, the water's boiling
and the tea's good.
The dim sum isn't bad either.
This place's speciality is pot rice?
- Yeah, you in?
- Sure!
- Waiter!
- Oh, what can I get you?
- Two pork rib rice.
- Oh, of course.
Coming up,
two pork ribs with rice.
How many?
Big guts cheung
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
My pot rice?!
What are you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
- I don't know what's going on!
Why's this happening?
How can this be? Could it be...?
It's nothing to do with me!
Stop!
I'm alright!
You...
Senior, you've gone too far!
I am no longer your senior!
Those are your words,
not mine, senior.
If you still think of me as your senior,
then don't go against me.
You shouldn't be so quick
to kill an innocent man.
Received their payment,
remove their ailment.
- Senior...
- Spit on you!
Senior,
you will not control him again.
Or else...
I won't! T won't!
Fine. I'm going.
You...
You beware!
Astrological birth chart?
Sorry...
- Let's go!
- That's the fatty who broke everything!
Get lost!
Big guts cheung,
let's see you escape this time.
I told you,
I didn't murder my wife!
If you can't bring him in alive...
Bring him in dead.
Gol
No matter what,
you must kill him!
Bailiff
Kill him!
Truly useless!
Step aside!
What are you doing?
Constable
get him!
How did this happen?
Hey, still standing around?
Have you all
been possessed by evil spirits?
Hey, big guts,
who knows your astrological birth chart?
Astrological birth chart?
Except for my wife and master tam,
no one else knows.
Master tam?
He has an advisor named lau?
Yes, how did you know?
Then it must be your boss
who hired someone to kill you.
Master tam? Impossible.
He treats me so well.
Why would he hire someone to kill me?
In this world, there are many people
who appear benevolent,
but harbour evil intentions.
If it wasn't for him, how could my senior
have your astrological birth chart?
- What do we do now?
- Change your clothes, pack up our things.
We're going to look for master tam
and get to the bottom of this.
Let's go.
Hey... this is just a run down temple.
What are we doing here?
I'm going to cleanse you.
Pfft! Why would I come all this way
just to take a bath?
I'm going to cleanse you,
not bathe you!
I must cleanse you
till only past lives remain.
Formally induct you into the dao.
Accept you as my disciple.
Accept me as your disciple?
That's right.
Because my senior's magic power
is greater than mine,
I can't always protect you.
If I'm negligent,
your life can't be guaranteed.
You should've accepted me
as your disciple ages ago!
I should warn you,
once you join my sect,
you can no longer have children.
Hey, now! Rein it in for a sec!
If we don't act now...
You're dead for sure.
Get a move on!
Daoist master chin,
will it work this time?
Master tam, don't worry!
This time,
either he dies or I perish!
Master.
What are you doing out here?
I came out to see
how big guts cheung's going to die.
However you look at it,
he's going to die.
Go back inside now.
Yes, go back inside.
What's it to do with you?!
Big mouth...
Master, the hour has come.
Light the candle, raise the altar.
Vastness of heaven,
vastness of earth...
Ancestral patriarch shines bright for you,
light reflecting the vastness of heaven.
The body has golden light,
enveloping its entirety.
Look without seeing,
listen without hearing.
Encapsulate the world,
nurture a collective heart.
White paper is your face,
coloured paper is your body.
Until your awakening, it is but paper.
Upon your awakening, it's divine power.
Open your left ear,
listen to the land of the dead.
Open your right ear,
listen to the world of the living.
Open your mouth and recite the talisman.
Ghosts stricken with terror,
ghouls lose their heads.
Vajra manifest,
with haste as though compelled by law.
Please, you mustn't move.
My senior's now sending his curses.
Y
You've painted talismans on his body?
Master,
from now on we're of the same people.
It'll be fine.
Now we're of the same people.
How come?
We of maoshan are shabby
and trample the ground.
The shabby never wear pristine clothes,
never keep money overnight.
Why trample the ground, then?
Those who trample the ground
keep divinity by their side,
borrowing divine powers
to attract luck and avoid calamity.
- What are you doing?
- It doesn't work!
These things don't happen overnight.
It's going to take at least
seven times seven days.
It'll take as long as 49 days?
I'll make it through, then?
Put it on.
Does wearing this red dudou mean you
don't worry about being cut by blades?
You still worry,
you just won't die.
Put it on now.
Master, more weird stuff's coming!
Rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon, snake,
horse, goat, monkey, rooster, dog, pig.
Good luck, great success!
Wooden sword breaks the seal.
Heavenly spirits, earthly spirits,
demons and ghosts hear my command.
My spoken instructions are clear.
10,000 buddhas' mighty power revealed,
with haste as though compelled by law.
Where did you raise the altar?
Talk!
Longevity inn.
Longevity inn?
Daoist master chin, is it done?
My junior broke my spell again.
They're coming here now.
Coming here?
Hurry up and think of something.
Ask your men to elevate the altar at once.
Did you hear that?
- Ask the men to elevate the altar now.
- Right.
Let's go inside first.
Go inside and get your money...
Daoist master chin?
Even if they come now,
there's nothing to fear.
The one named tsui,
if you've arrived then crawl out here!
Master tam!
It really is you!
- Big guts cheung!
- Don't be afraid!
Senior, your altar's pretty tall.
Tall, isn't it?
Have you forgotten that master once said:
With two people
who are more or less evenly matched,
the one with the taller altar
will have the upper hand.
How could I forget master's words?
- Then today you will die.
- Maybe not.
- Big guts cheung, raise the altar.
- Yes!
- Raise the altar.
Senior, my altar
isn't that short either, no?
- Light the incense, raise the altar.
- Yes.
Five thunder palm?
Big guts cheung?!
Inviting the gods?
I invite arhat to the Jade palace,
appear at the altar by emperor's decree.
Invite immortals with mantras and curses,
reveal power to slay dragons and tigers.
Tiger-subduing arhat,
heed my call and come.
Your disciple reveres before the furnace.
May arhat please descend soon.
Divine soldier make haste
as though compelled by law.
Bright sky, spirited earth, god descend
to the altar, reflecting the bright sky.
Monkey king make your presence known,
manifest before the altar. Manifest.
Manifest as clear as the sun and the moon.
With a Sincere heart I invite monkey king.
Divine soldier make haste
as though compelled by law.
You're no match for me.
What do you mean? You big ape!
Everyone knows my kung fu's much better.
Prove it to me!
You'll regret you said that!
Got you! You'd better surrender!
No way! Just watch me!
Want to have another round?
I give up!
I wish I'd stayed home.
See what you got me into now?!
I'm leaving!
A red dudou!
Flags, drums, and incense
penetrate the three sanctuaries.
First beat of the drum shakes heaven,
second beat shakes earth.
Bang the gong, heaven and earth move,
light incense to invite Dharma master.
Invite demon-slayer, master lu dong-bin,
sword in hand, to appear before the altar.
Divine soldier make haste
as though compelled by law.
Sharpen the sword!
Haze of incense reflects the cosmos,
burning incense penetrate heavenly gate.
Divine dragon walks the big Dipper,
body clothed in protective red dudou.
Red-tasselled thunderbolt spear, penetrate
heaven, shake earth, ghosts and gods fear.
Above and below, your true form's seen.
I reverently invite red boy to descend.
Divine soldier make haste
as though compelled by law.
Master, what's wrong with you?
Master?
Big mouth...
You little brat!
Same to you!
Go to hell!
After you!
I wonder if that shoe's master tam's?
Big guts, throw up the shoe!
Not this one,
the one on your back!
What happened to my foot?
Don't...
Master!
Master, are you alright?
You try climbing up and falling down,
and see if you're alright?
Master...
Master!
Big guts!
Are you alright?
Wife?!
Wife!
I'm so scared!
Your boss wanted to rape me!
I know...
I know you're a slut!
You bitch!