This is for Jin ju!
Hey, you fool
- What, me?
- Yeah you.
What now?!
You should write down
where it is going.
I just told you.
You are hired
to do these things.
Don't just sit there
and do nothing.
Soon you will get fired.
I am sure of that
Go to hell!
It's only a cigarette.
You piece of shit.
Cherry Tomato
Sin Gu
Kim Hyang Gi
Kim Young Ho
(Special appearance)
Director Jung Young Bae
When did you move away?
Your last house was empty.
You seemed to have lived
pretty well there.
We moved right after
you went to prison.
She's listening.
Water them everyday.
Keep it under sunshine.
Are you giving me this?
Does she go
to school these days?
I'm only 6.
Then you must go to kindergarten.
Don't you see she can't?
Poor people like us can't
put her to kindergarten.
Then why does she
have the backpack?
To look like one!
Do you want tofu?
Do you get something out
of demolition thing?
I get so tired earning
day's worth money.
Chun sam...
Your dad's age is 70
as of this year.
I am too tired to live my life.
Now you take care of your
daughter on your own.
I curious, do you still
get your pension money?
What money?
How can you think of
stealing my pension money?
I was just curious if you
could make living with it?
Take all the money you can
from the government.
I would even leave my daughter
if they gave me money.
You son of a bitch.
Why make your only daughter
become an orphan?
Crazy bastard.
Stop you old man.
I couldn't even get injection
when I was a child.
You had money for tavern
but you didn't have
money for my injection.
I wouldn't be crippled
if I had one.
She always tumbles
down like that
What about the money
selling house?
Get her a pair of glasses?
I saved it to go to Hong Kong
You have problem with that?
I would have known.
Stingy old man.
I am so tired.
I searched the whole
town looking for you.
Go to sleep.
And find a job
in your dreams.
Soon I will throw
you out of here.
Hey daughter.
Lie with me for old times sake.
No thank you.
Stop that
I have already found them
under the mat, drawer
and blankets.
I have conscience too.
I won't steal them again.
You can guard your money
after three days
when I steal them
I can't get any
sleep because of you.
You might as well
lend them to me
if you don't want
me stealing it.
I should tie your lips
of tie your feet.
Why would you handcuff
my foot?
Father.
I am coming back even if I had
to go way round the other way.
I am coming back, okay?
Pops, Dad's gone.
We held hands so tight
but he's gone.
Hey, pops.
You go inside.
And don't wait up.
Pops, are you going to work?
Are you huh?
You have go to work, okay?
Are you kidding me?
You think this is a joke?
My house was robbed.
He took everything, it's true.
I went to the bank this morning
and I have nothing left.
Even your face look yellowish.
And his face looks also yellow
I can't get hold of myself.
I won't do it again.
That's enough. Say sorry?
How many times have you said that?
You have bad reputation
around here.
You can stop coming here
from now on.
Bong soo, forgive me.
I want to live.
I am too old to work
but I have no one to take
care of me but myself.
Hey, you three.
I messed up my kid
but you are worse.
You thoughtless piece of shit.
From now on I won't
even look this way.
What did I tell you?
Do yourself a favor
and make eyes for dolls.
You are pouring gas on a fire.
He was waiting for you
to make trouble.
You worked for a year
and I think it's long enough.
Find a job for me.
I will come back here again.
My cigarette.
Think again,
you are not young.
You will die working so hard.
Where is he going?
Why wouldn't she eat?
I only did it for her.
Why left overs?
Helpless child.
What?
- Hey.
- What is it?
- Please let's not do this.
- What do you mean?
Don't you know work ethics?
It's my district from this alley
to that village office over there.
Who asked you?
I am tired so stop it
I am busy
so make space here.
You don't know it yet
but we have zone
divided up for this job.
Here.
Fine?
Dame it.
You think this cart is
some sports car?
Stop blocking the road.
I can honk too.
It's 15 kilograms.
750won.
2, 4, 6, 8, 38.
780 won.
You are illiterate still
you count so well.
Why did you bring in so little?
It's annoying
to give you change.
Your scale is broken.
You forgot about all the numbers
behind this number here.
I am taking that much.
So see you tomorrow.
You took
one thousand won more.
What are you doing?
Stop it, you'll get hurt
- Pops.
- Why are you out here?
Give me that
Thank you.
No, no. Get out of here.
Da Sung.
Where are you going?
Hey pops,
what are you doing?
Secure our living.
Secure the living.
How can you collect
bottles at this time?
Just one more okay?
I was not going to say this.
but I heard you signed on
the demolition agreement form?
They would have some idea
as to where we should go.
If they did, we wouldn't
be here going so crazy.
We are going to have
to live on the streets.
They can't run the house
down if we are living in them.
Jong Douk, come here.
You'll get hurt
Attack.
Shit, those bastards
broke my cart.
Kill the bastards.
What would I do without my cart.
You fucking morons.
Stop!
Why are you so late?
We are all out of meat
My cart broke down.
But did you say meat?
This is our last day so we
prepared enough meat
Last? What last?
There it says suspension
of free lunch.
We can't work here anymore
because this is demolition area
Then where should we go?
It's far away. It takes
40 minutes from here.
I can walk 40 minutes
if I can eat
No, you have to take
the subway for 40 minutes
Subway? Damn it.
Eat two meals and you
won't have for nothing.
Hurry and find
the shelter old man.
I don't have to stay together.
You don't have to stay together.
Send her to orphanage.
Sister, do you know any shelter?
Have you ever worked there?
Send her to somewhere else
till you find good place
to stay with her?
I think she knows
what you are saying.
Jong Douk!
Hey, sit down.
Stop that
Jong Douk, Jong Douk.
Pops, you and I need to talk.
I'm gonna go to the president's
house and deal with this.
Come with us.
You coarsened an illiterate old man
to get his signature, you jerks.
Son, where are you?
Stop the demolition.
We will fight.
Yeah.
We received calls
and we got orders.
- Stop the demolition.
- No demolition!
- We will fight for our lives.
- We will fight, fight.
Everyone lie down.
Why didn't you give us
something to lie on? Why?
He said lie down.
- Arrest them.
- Yeah.
I won't go.
I am not going.
Take him instead.
Why aren't you arresting them?
Don't go grand father.
Don't take him.
The policeman was very kind.
You think he's good?
Then give him an award
why don't you?
But Pops,
did you see the tree?
Don't talk about your Dad.
I saw apples on the tree
What was it?
Shut up.
Walk fast
and don't tumble down
Please use
the measuring spoon.
My husband won't like it
if he sees you doing
clumsily with your hands.
And please put vitamin
and nutrient.
Two months has passed
and still Tanya
is not comfortable.
It's not easy for us
and it is same for Tanya.
Leave her alone.
She'll get used to it.
I met Dr. Chang.
Wife, only care about Tanya.
And don't think
about having a child.
I only want you
to care about Tanya.
How did you do with
the insecticide?
I did well.
We need strong insecticide.
Mites get fat in winter.
We should do them now
before the spring comes.
But be careful around Tanya.
Prepare to give bath to Tanya.
Yes, sir.
What now?
- What happened to your glasses?
- I broke them a while back.
Get up.
- 500 won, really?
- Yes, want some hot pancakes?
Sure. Give me one?
Here we go.
- Thank you.
- It's big.
Have some first.
You go ahead and
don't spill the honey.
What did I tell you.
Don't spill it.
What is this?
What?
That blood sucking fraud.
Liar.
What did you say?
It says here that it's
a liar pan cakes.
It's all empty inside.
Please learn to read.
I am sending you to orphanage
if you keep on misbehaving.
Foolish girl.
Stop crying.
I can't take it anymore.
Why are you
doing this to me.
This way, can't you see?
What are you doing?
Hold still.
Don't make me spank you.
- Da Sung.
- Hey, Jong Duck.
Where were you?
I got a call from
your son a minute ago.
I don't know how
he knew my number.
He said he did something bad.
He said it's so damn bad thing.
Anyway he's going to come back
after he's done with his business.
Did he leave his number?
No, he just told me to give you
his message and hung up.
I don't know if we would still have
electricity and telephone till then.
It's a long day today.
- Da Sung, I am coming soon.
- What are you talking about?
Da Sung.
Come quick.
Hurry.
I am starving.
- Look there?
- Where?
- There?
- What is that?
Dried fish.
I can do this.
Let's sell them and earn big.
I was not always lucky.
I was a bad luck since when
I was in my mother's womb.
But this time
the luck is on my side.
Yeah, it's about time.
This way or that way.
Wherever, who cares?
This is a gold mine.
We need to get some more.
Let's drive with these
sitting on our laps.
You said there's no one here.
Oh, shit...
Start the gear.
Be careful.
It's only used car.
Let's go.
This is my daughter
and my father's life truck.
You do it again
and I kill you.
Okay, okay.
Let's go now.
What is this smell?
Is this your smell? Or the fish?
Whatever.
You look like you
are going to burst.
I will order the meal for you.
This is my first success.
Why was I so foolish?
But anyway I did it okay.
Wait for me Da Sung.
Da Sung, I am gonna
send you to kindergarten.
We will meet soon.
Pops.
- Pops, my tree and our house.
- Say it again?
Come quick, our house.
Hey you, what are you
doing nailing the house?
Stop that!
How dare you.
- What do you mean?
- Stop.
Don't hit my pops.
- You poor bastards.
- Go over there.
Hurry.
Don't do it!
My house...
Dad, I miss you.
It's a waste of time.
Come and eat some meat
- Did he hurt badly?
- His arm broke.
Crazy girl.
Are you a bagger?
Why are you picking up
things like that?
It's not like you starved
for couple of days?
Only a day.
You only missed three meals.
Stop whining.
I am hungry.
I will buy you lunch.
So don't talk about that tree.
- But that's what Dad gave us.
- Shut up.
Don't talk about him.
- I want that
- What are you talking about?
We want that one.
It's 2000 won.
Give us plenty.
What about you?
I won't eat yours.
- It's too hot.
- Drink some water.
- It's burning.
- Drink more water.
I said drink water.
Let's go.
See you later.
Hey, old man.
Keep your feet to yourself.
It was delicious thank you.
See you all tomorrow.
- There's meat, eat
- No, it's dirty.
You won't get any food.
Is that what you want?
Shit.
Stay here.
Let me go with you.
I will be right there.
Now eat
- I am going with you.
- I won't run away.
I will kill those morons.
What will you do?
I am going to end it
once and for all.
Wow, it's bigger
than our kindergarten.
You have never been
to kindergarten.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
I don't care
if you freeze to death.
Don't try to blame me.
Do whatever you wish.
We are not thieves.
You are just like your mother.
Stubborn child
Now that we are here.
I gotta get money for my cart.
3000 won?
8000 won?
They must be mad.
They spend my daily
payment on one yogurt
Hey look here.
I am eating an ice cream
And I am eating them
all by myself. So good.
And you pretended
like you were a lady.
Pops, here take it.
Leave it there.
We don't take money.
Press it. Do it later.
You fart just like your mother.
You smell so bad.
Yes, just a moment. sir.
Hello.
Meat delivery.
Good bye.
I can't take it anymore.
Where do I pea?
don't fart.
How come?
Squeeze you ass as hard
as you could and don't fart.
Yes, boss.
I left the house to walk Tanya.
Are you there now?
How is Tanya doing?
And the meat?
- Yes, I am giving them to her.
- Take care of it.
- What about the quality?
- They are good.
He's gone.
Come on.
You can breath now.
- How should you know?
- My ears are not for decoration.
Didn't you hear what he said
just now? They are gone.
We will leave before that noisy
bastard comes back.
But the door's locked.
Damn it.
The dog and his owner
must be crazy.
- Park, are you going?
- Yeah.
- See you.
- I am envious of you.
Take care,
don't work to hard.
You should take it easy
And don't work too hard.
How do I get it open?
Darn.
You didn't get
it open before.
I was startled.
You are doing it all wrong.
How did you do it?
What did you press?
The dog doesn't bark.
Why are you so frightened?
Haven't you never
seen a dog before?
Tell me, what did you press?
Can we take this too?
Pops, I want to take these.
I have ruined an angel like you.
I have to send you away.
What are you doing?
Aren't we going yet?
Little thing, don't you want
to go to kindergarten?
- Kindergarten?
- Yeah, don't you want to go?
Of course. My friends
must be in upper class by now.
We don't have place to go
when we get out of here.
Let's stay here.
Don't be so scared, If we get
caught we just leave here.
Doesn't matter
if they throw us out.
Just stay here for a while.
So we are not leaving yet?
Then I will bring in the bag.
Hello, it's me.
I am going out.
Do you think I am their slave?
Yeah right.
See you there.
Deep your head in.
You are not touching the water.
I am doing it.
Here's water.
Come here.
It's warm.
Hey, come here.
Where?
It's bubbly.
How much does this cost?
I can't read.
It's all so scrambled.
It's like a boat
Isn't it?
Take off your glasses.
Why are you wearing them?
- I can't see.
- Don't talk back.
Wow, Pops.
It's so nice. I like it.
You are all wet.
My child.
So wonderful. Isn't it the
first time for you too?
- Ya.
- Stop that, you little brat
I will come back soon.
You have to stay here.
Please let me go before the
subway stops working.
Take me with you.
I am scared all by myself.
What are you talking about.
Stop, I will miss the train.
Let me go with you.
Are you trying to run away?
Then are you going to sleep on
the streets and freeze to death?
I won't.
Then don't sleep.
And don't open
the door to strangers.
I will knock on the door twice
and ring a bell.
Open the door then.
Then say roar?
Roar?
Say them like the tiger.
I am not in the mood for it.
Stop it.
You do that to me.
Say roar.
Da Sung, Da Sung!
Pops.
Did you miss me?
Stay here and eat
I won't be late.
- Are you coming back soon?
- Yeah.
Pops.
Then come back very fast.
Princess,
you should lie down.
Yes, bring some milk.
Here's your milk.
Thank you child.
I am sorry.
So sorry.
I am sorry more.
So don't ever say that again.
Pops.
It's late, the train won't come.
- We are here.
- Get out.
Close the door.
Are you afraid of
your boss that much?
Why come back here
and not go to your house?
I am missing the old days.
Da Sung, it's me.
Open the door.
It's okay.
Da Sung.
It's me.
I'm your grand father.
What is taking so long?
Delivery meat
Get up.
Hey.
Hey, hey
The bell's ringing.
Hi.
Meat delivery.
- Come back day after tomorrow?
- Yes.
Okay, good bye.
Hello? It's me.
Yes, I just fed her.
Yes, I am
receiving them everyday.
I come back late at night
because Tanya
is receiving check up.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Is it okay to leave the house
empty for two days?
Let's go.
Are you really going?
Is it okay?
I going to go crazy if I don't
have wind blowing at my face.
Eat up, boy.
Slow and nicely.
Da Sung, hey.
Open the door.
Roar. It's your grand
father so open up.
Are you going to keep
on being stubborn like this?
Damn. You are dirty.
I already know
how ugly you are.
Okay, I am not mad.
Really, I am not.
I brought some meat
and left them on the yard.
I'll get them.
Why aren't you eating?
Don't worry about me.
This is big.
Have some.
- And drink this too.
- I like these.
But pops,
where did you get these?
I worked all day at the
steak house yesterday.
Really? You found a job?
I got laid off.
Keep on chewing.
Eat them all.
Where are you going?
I have a stomachache.
Rich people should eat meat
You are not used
to eating them.
Nothing left in here.
Shit.
Fucking jerk did it again.
Get me a glass of water.
Dame it.
Here.
It is better this way.
She will like it here.
Da Sung, let's go.
What do you think you are?
I said give Tanya meat
I didn't say feed yourself.
What?
Are you a man?
You shameless moron.
You should
be treated like dogs.
You understand?
Huh? Do you?
Get out.
I said get out!
Pops,
where are we going now?
We don't have a home.
It's nice out here.
It's not even cold.
Pops, isn't it fun?
- Isn't it fun?
- Hey don't make me so dizzy.
Now you are saying something.
I was going to give
them to you.
You like me that much?
You like me even when
you starve to death?
We are here.
Walk a little bit more.
- This is mine.
- It's not yours either.
Lee, gave it to us.
Let go of it.
Who's going to prove that
Huh?
Pops,
did you meet your son?
What son?
Have you had dinner?
Have some.
It's warm.
I said eat
You have a bad cold.
Did you feed her?
I don't know what to give her.
She's so sick
Give her some fat
Like meat
She's so weak so give her
something nutritious.
It won't do her any good.
Your son is seriously a jerk.
What did the doctor say?
She's gotten worse,
she's on fire.
It doesn't taste good.
Still eat some.
We are so worried
about you two.
I don't wanna eat
Why are you still sick?
The owner come out here.
What now?
I don't need you.
I need to see your boss.
What?
Oh you. You are the monster
who ate up my house.
Don't make noise and leave.
I will call the police.
Go back? To where?
I don't have a house
to go back to.
Spit up my house.
I won't go till you give it back!
I think it's already
taken care of.
I don't care.
Just give back my money.
Give my cart back!
My money!
I want to live.
You push me into the
corner with nowhere to hide.
Here, have a meal on the way.
This is meat too.
Why don't you eat?
I want the same meat
that I ate there.
It's meat too.
They are not different. Eat
I won't.
- Eat
- I won't.
Eat!
Stop crying.
Stop.
Now eat
I won't eat meat
I won't ever talk about it.
- Oh, my god.
- Excuse me.
Let me ask you
a favor madam
May I have some of those meat
that you are giving your dog?
What?
Give me bones.
It's fine.
Go away.
What are you doing?
Oh, my god.
I will only take little bit.
Da Sung, get up.
I got you what you wanted.
Hurry and eat
I won't eat
It's okay.
Eat now little one.
I said I won't eat
You eat meat and get well.
This will be your last.
Don't ever say
you want this meat
That's it.
Eat them.
Hey, son.
Where are you?
My son.
Son...
The more you eat
the more you get sick.
It's only for a while.
They go nuts but everyone
gives up at the end.
They don't last for long.
What are you here for?
Is she sick?
Bring the doctor in very fast.
Please show us your
medical insurance.
Bull shit.
Call the doctor now!
You did a patriotic work.
What did you feed her today?
Ribs.
Really?
Was she sick before she eat
meat or after she ate them?
She's always sick
but she likes meat
You will only spent more
money with check ups.
It's not because of food
she ate so give her a ringer.
I will be upstairs.
Call me if anything happens.
But why is she so sick?
Children tend
to say those things.
Here, have some water.
- Pops.
- Yeah?
Don't go anywhere.
My baby. Get up.
Da Sung!
Open your eyes.
Get up.
Da Sung.
Open your eyes?
Meat
What?
I want meat, pops.
You drive the car.
Don't wait up.
It's the last. It really is.
I will only take little bit.
Shit.
So bite me. Bite me I said.
My poor little thing
only wants dog food.
My precious baby.
Seeing her like that
I can't live anymore.
I am going to kill you.
Baby. Open your eyes.
Baby hey, Da Sung.
Here's meat
I brought them for you.
Hurry open up your eyes.
Baby...
Here's your meat
I brought them here.
Why aren't you eating?
Get up and eat
Baby, come back.
Hey, Da Sung.
Baby, my baby.
Da Sung, get up.
You said you wanted meat
and why aren't you eating it?
Get up.
I wish I didn't go.
I should have stayed here.
You were always scared
of being alone.
Why did you go by yourself?
You might even get tumbled
down on the way.
I should have stayed here.
How can you go
there by yourself?
Da Sung...
He said he will come.
He said he will even
if he had to go way
round the other way.
Subtitles by LeapinLar