Produced by Shanghai Tian Ma Film Studio
This is a war story about heroines.
It took place on Hainan Island
in south China, in 1930.
It was a period when the Chinese people greatly suffered.
It was also a period when the young Red Army laid its foundation in China.
The Red Detachment of Women
Screenwriter: Liang Xin
Director: Xie Jin
Military Advisor: Ma Baishan
Photographer: Shen Xilin
Composer: Huang Zhun
Art Designer: Zhang Hanchen
Sound Engineer: Gong Zhengming
Editing: Wei Chunbao
Make-up: Wang Tiebin
Fireworks: Chen Yonggeng
Assistant Director: Wang Jie
Film Producer: Ding Li
Musical Performance:
Shanghai Film Orchestra
Instructor: Chen Chuanxi
Cast: Wu Qionghua... Zhu Xijuan
Hong Changqing... Wang Xingang
Fu Honglian... Xiang Mei
Division Commander... Jin Naihua
Company Commander... Wang Li
A'Gui... Tie Niu
Xiao Pang... Niu Ben
Elder Sister... Zhang Weiming
Dan Zhu... Shi Shugui
Da Ying... Jiang Yifang
Uncle... Weng Shuying
Nan Batian... Chen Qiang
Great Manager... Yang Mengchang
Lao Si... Feng Qihuang
Zhenshan... Liang Shan
Big Golden Teeth... Yu Feng
Brigadier Chen... Chen Shu
Battalion Commander Hu... Yu Mingde
Big Slave Girl... Zhang Sha
Hey, who is this?
Hey, this must be the hatchet man of the local tyrant Nan Batian.
Well, the Coconut Grove is ahead. Watch out.
Stinking lackey, where are you running to?
I feel so suffocated to see the enemy tyrannize us.
If we were on the battlefield, I would beat them.
Don't mess things up, little devil. We will eradicate the enemies one day.
Crossing this barrier, we'll be at the Soviet District.
Stop! Where are you from?
Guangzhou.
What do you do?
Stop shouting. We are overseas Chinese from Southeast Asia.
Open it up.
Let them examine it.
Take it away.
You still want to run away, you son of a bitch, stinking lackey?
I'm running away because I can't bear it!
Go!
Go quickly!
Go over there!
Fourth Master.
Who are they?
They are overseas Chinese.
They have lots of money.
Your local militias are simply brigands.
Go get your commander-in-chief.
You are simply blind.
He is a high-ranking overseas Chinese who can create miracles.
He has made a pile abroad and came back to build ancestral halls.
As you can see, the president of Guangdong province,
and chief of security and directors of every department are on the list,
let alone the rich and powerful families of Hainan.
Old Four, what's the matter with you guys?
Thinking him a wealthy man, they caught him.
Bring him here and let me talk to him face to face.
Old Four.
No, bring my coat.
Comrade Changqing.
She suffered a lot from the beating.
She said she tried to run away several times.
Why did she want to run away?
I didn't understand clearly.
She said she wanted to become a female soldier so as to take revenge.
The trend of forming a women army has swept through here.
Here comes the master.
How can you treat Mr. Hong like this?
The servant knows nothing. I'm sorry for the offence. Please.
Here are Master's things. Please check them out.
No need for that.
Let's take away the donated money and return home tonight.
Leaving tonight will leave us open to suspicion.
Hold still. If he dares to importune us,
we will never let him be at ease.
Take advantage to get his friend's number.
It can help us leave here in the future.
Entertain him fairly.
We must captivate this big fish,
and use his connection network to buy
ammunition in Guangzhou and Southeast Asia.
Look at this fellow.
There may be no difficulty to ask him for 500 guns.
Though the world belongs to the Chiang family now,
Hainan Island is still too far away for the Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek,
to control for the moment.
I mean this is a chance of a lifetime.
You're right.
Here comes Master Huang.
Master.
Come here.
This is a great hero, Lu Li, who rarely appears in public.
Huang Zhanshan, it's my pleasure to meet you.
It is a great pleasure to meet you.
This is my steward and brainpower.
Master, the meal is ready.
To help Mr. Hong recover from the shock, serve the meal.
Yes.
Serve the meal.
Please, please.
Put out the light.
This is my servant's humble idea for entertainment.
Two Dragons Playing With The Pearl.
These are family dishes.
Mr. Hong, please drink this cup of snake bile wine.
Double Bile For Honorable Guests.
Thank you.
Come on. Come on. To a wealthy life, please.
Please, please.
Mr. Hong, why didn't you bring Baorun?
It is not peaceful on the road. It is inconvenient to bring women.
To tell you a joke, some mistakes happened when I passed by your village.
But for the help of hospitable Brother Nan, would I...?
Come on. Help yourself.
Please.
You are selling people at night again.
We can go to the brothel after selling her.
Come up.
I have found you a husband.
Come up, you...
Catch her. Qionghua intends to run away.
Catch her. Don't let go.
Currently, there are only a few central armies on the island.
The commander-in-chief Mr. Jiang is busy
encircling and annihilating the Communist Party on the mainland.
These are mostly armed forces of the local militia from the counties.
It is like Chinese opera.
All the lords divide the territory and one dominates an area.
Yes, yes. However, we only have one enemy.
That is the Communist Party on Hainan Island.
Its so-called Red Army was formed hastily this summer.
Only one regiment has arms.
The others are pieced together.
But, the Communist Party is our serious trouble.
We must eradicate it before it gets strong.
Brother Hong.
If you want to accomplish something at home,
you must annihilate the Communist Party first.
If you and I unite, we can conquer Hainan.
I ought to devote myself to this wonderful plan.
However, I have to do my filial duty and build the ancestral hall first.
Oh, yes. Filial piety is a fundamental duty.
Qionghua ran again just now.
This slave girl has run away many times.
I want to ask you a favor.
Tell me. Tell me.
My mother and the commander-in-chief Mr. Nan are from the same town.
My mother is staying in Zhuangzhou.
She wants to buy a slave girl who can speak our native language.
Could you please do me a favor?
It's nothing. I can handle it for you.
Since the slave girl is for your mother,
we need to pick one with good character and appearance.
You see?
Master, in my opinion, you can give up what you favor.
I dare not snatch your favorite.
How about the girl dragged inside just now?
It's nothing. She violated some family rules.
Oh, the girl looks terrific,
but she's a little rude.
She's just a slave girl. Having a loose manner is inevitable.
She is so lucky that Brother Hong likes her.
Go pack for her and ask her to go with Mr. Hong tomorrow.
Fine. I will wait for you.
We will talk in detail after you have shown filial piety to your family.
OK. OK.
Please get on the horse.
OK. Let's meet again some day.
Have a nice journey.
Madam, please have mercy on me.
Comrade Changqing, shall we take her back to our division?
No, our division station shouldn't be exposed.
Doesn't she want to join the women's army?
Show her the way to our Stone Village.
She can go along the branch road ahead.
OK.
What are you doing?
Young lady, please turn around.
What do you want, Master?
He is not a master at all.
You are free now.
That means you can go anywhere you want.
Really.
Absolutely.
Hey, wait a moment.
What?
I wonder where you are going.
It's none of your business.
I don't mean to interfere your life.
I just wonder if you have a place.
I'm afraid you are alone.
Where's your home?
Home...
I have no home.
What? You have no home?
Three years ago,
the commander-in-chief Nan Batian killed my father.
My mother was beaten until crippled and driven away.
She probably starved to death.
Why did I mention this to you?
Would you like to join the women's army?
I'd love to.
All right.
Tell you,
now you go along this road and turn left.
You'll see Red Stone Village.
If they are forming a women army, they must be there.
Do you know how to get there?
I can find it.
What's your name?
Wu Qionghua.
All right, Qionghua.
This is for you to buy something to eat on the way.
Take it.
Let's go.
Secretary Hong, Xiao Pang, you are back.
Yes, we're back.
Secretary Hong.
Xiao Niu, where's the division commander?
Over there.
Division commander!
You are back!
-Division commander.
-You finally got back!
-We are back.
-Look at you. Interesting.
We have brought back all the money.
-Little devil.
-Division commander.
Give it to me.
Let's go.
How's it going?
Xiao Wang, prepare the meal quickly.
How can you make it so fast?
How could I delay?
Come on. Drink some water.
Fine.
With these amulets and the help of the underground party,
we went through the White Zone in disguise.
Division commander.
The workers in Guangzhou, Haikou and Ao'men were so zealous.
They said, though their donations were limited,
they belonged to the working class.
It was to show that they support the Red Army.
They were so enthusiastic, hearing we are preparing for the revolution.
Go get your commander-in-chief Mr. Nan here.
Comrade Changqing.
We must stay calm and hold still.
When the old fellow Nan Batian comes here
we should serve him cigarettes and wine to show our respect.
We will go to Red Stone Village together after eating.
They are ready for the opening ceremony tomorrow morning.
This is the first revolutionary armed force of the Red Army.
I had thought you, as the party representative of the women's army,
couldn't show up at the ceremony.
Early tomorrow morning, Qiong Hua...
I can make it.
Don't drink that.
Come in my house. There is water here.
Come on.
Don't shut the door.
What for?
Oh, don't be afraid.
Here is the money. I got four coins.
I'm also female.
Sit down. Still hungry? Here you are.
Why are you so hungry?
I escaped from prison.
I haven't had anything for three or four days.
You escaped?
A benefactor rescued me.
I met many nice people today.
There are few good people this time of year.
You must be very careful because you are alone.
I'm nearly there.
Is Red Stone Village on the side of the mountain?
You are going to the Soviet District?
Yes, there's no other way.
But why do you dress up like a man?
I'm also going to the Soviet District.
That's great. We're going the same way.
Why are you home alone?
My parents-in-law has gone to burn joss sticks and pray in town.
You have parents-in-law, so you have a husband?
You can say so.
Where's your husband?
Behind you.
Don't scare me.
That's true. The one lying in bed.
Dead?
He has never been alive.
This is my husband.
I married him when I was ten.
I have already lived with this dead wood for ten years.
There is really no way out.
No way out.
Let's go.
We are late. Run fast!
Brother A'Gui!
You got out after all.
I got out.
What's the matter with you two?
He is my old neighbor, who ran away the year before last.
Does she belong to the propertied class?
Go quickly, go!
I can't go now.
Comrades!
The reactionary party led by Chiang Kai-shek has deployed 100,000 mobsters
to fiercely attack our central District in Jiangxi.
Workers and peasants all over China
are fighting hard every second, every hour and every day.
Therefore, our party calls on you.
All suffering women to take up arms
and open fire on the extremely evil old society.
Down with feudal rule!
Carry out land reform!
Overturn the feudal system!
Now, on behalf of the Hainan Independent Division of the Red Army,
the Hainan Special Committee of the Chinese Communist Party,
I confer on you the flag of our army.
Is the flag receiver a female official?
There are no officials in our party. She is the company commander.
Company commander?
How powerful is the position?
She's in charge of all the women soldiers.
I will go find her.
It won't work.
It will.
Forwarch march.
Forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
There was Hua Mulan in ancient times who joined the army
taking the place of her father.
There is a women army's using guns to protect the people nowadays.
Forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
Communism is our creed. The Communist Party is our leader
Slaves get freedom. Slaves get freedom.
Forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, one, one, two, three, four.
Common people, don't follow us.
We are parading here.
One, two, one, one, two, one.
Why are you still following us?
This is a troop.
Stand at attention.
Turn left, put down the guns, stand at ease.
Company commander!
Two common people appeared for no reason.
Stand at attention and report.
How do I report it?
Report!
Two common people came here.
What do you want?
We came here to join the women army.
You came here when the troops were parading.
You are very brave.
I'm brave. I dare to do anything.
Are you a member of proletariat?
What?
Do you own land?
I'm a slave girl. I own nothing.
Good. You pass.
What about you?
I'm not sure whether I own land or not.
I was sold to others at the age of ten.
You are certainly a proletarian.
Pass.
Quiet!
You should go through some formalities now.
Aren't you the company commander? You can make the decisions.
Calm down, calm down.
You go to apply and explain clearly why you are here.
Why did I come here? There's no need to ask why.
Just for this.
I want to rebel and take revenge.
I will kill the officials, those big bellies,
who eat human beings.
I will rip off their dog skins.
I, I...
Secretary Changqing.
Division commander, this is the female comrade I told you about.
OK, let her stay.
OK.
You can stay.
I have an elder sister.
Fine, stand in the troop.
Let's go!
Stand at attention!
Now the party representative will give a speech. Stand at ease!
Comrades, you are the first armed force of the Chinese women's revolution.
In the past, you are female workers who suffer from lots of oppression.
You lived a bitter life like cattle.
You were looked down upon.
But from now on, you 120 persons
no, 122 persons, have become honorable soldiers
Most importantly,
remember that Nan Batian has newly built the firepower positions
of the blockhouse at the southern gate.
OK, let's go.
Don't expose your identity as women soldiers.
Let's go.
Come here quickly. You see.
Their project is nearly completed.
They've added three firepower positions.
Some people are coming.
They are visiting the graves to cherish the memory of the dead.
Take cover for a moment.
OK.
What are you going to do?
Nan Batian!
No. You will violate the scouting rules.
I'm violating the rules.
I, I will kill him, kill him! Let go!
Put it down, hurry, put it down!
Master, try the bullets of your servant.
Go get the Communist Party. Quick. Go catch them quickly. Go!
You are exposed. Withdraw.
In your head there's only revenge, revenge. You feel exhilarated!
But don't you know the scouting rules!
Why didn't you stop her?
I tried to stop her, but failed.
You failed, which is equal to not taking action.
I regret it.
What?
I didn't shoot well and there were not enough bullets.
or else I would kill them all!
Do you think this is brave?
You are not the wild girl of three months ago.
You are a soldier.
Do you think as a company commander I would love your bravery?
You go out and break your path by yourself.
You don't need me?
Company commander, you still let me stay though I'm two years older than her.
Go first.
How could you do this?
I?
What's the matter with you?
I just wish iron could turn into steel.
It is not so good to take such a measure.
Don't cry.
I violated the rules, but I won't leave.
I can't leave the women's army.
But why did you shoot?
It concerns my family's two generations of animosity.
Do you think only you have animosity?
Every proletarian bears tears in his heart.
If everyone rushes like you, can it work?
You are a revolutionary soldier.
I got it. I won't violate the rules when scouting.
Not only when scouting, you mustn't violate the rules for the rest of your life.
Go to the Confined Room and reflect upon your mistakes.
Yes.
She violated the scouting rules,
but I didn't handle it well, I apologize.
-I will go reflect upon my mistakes.
-Go quickly!
I'm also to blame. I will go to the Confined Room with her.
This is new.
All right. You go and help her.
Yes.
Sister Lian.
Enlightened?
Actually, I'm quite fond of our company commander.
She is frank and outspoken.
But she wants to drive me away.
I always take the lead in our work, such as military training and fighting battles.
You took the lead in violating rules, too.
It's only three months since I joined the army.
In terms of years, Secretary Changqing has been in the army only for two years.
Can we conclude that men are better than women?
How can you say that?
-You see, Secretary Changqing is really...
-Really what?
Secretary Changqing also teaches us lessons and punishes us.
However, when he punishes us, we are sincerely convinced.
Secretary Changqing has made such rapid progress.
Qionghua, we must learn from him.
We should try our best and make progress.
Sister Lian, let's discuss it little by little.
OK.
Why didn't you fall asleep?
I'm thinking.
What are you thinking about?
Sister Lian, could you tell me why Secretary Changqing
and our company commander are more knowledgeable and farsighted?
Because they are communists?
Yes.
Sister Lian, we will be senior soldiers two or three years from now.
We will act like our company commander and Secretary Changqing.
At that time, we both can also join the Communist Party.
Yes! To fight for the common people who suffer a lot!
Sister Lian, we joined the army together.
We will join the Communist Party together, too.
Do you believe in me? I will straighten out.
I believe in you. Qionghua, I believe in you.
Sleep.
One, one, two, one.
You're making use of every minute! Dinner is here.
Thank you, elder sister.
Take your time.
Qionghua, we will attack that Nan Batian you mentioned.
-Really?
-Really.
The mayor has approved. We will attack him tonight.
Attack him tonight?
I have to attack Nan Batian myself.
Can I walk out of the door?
Hey, nobody is watching you. You can go.
No. I must be aware.
I will beg for leniency for you.
She is really the right person to go.
Why didn't she come herself?
She said she couldn't go out of the Confined Room. She had to be aware.
All right. You tell her to go back to her platoon and wait for the order.
OK.
Nan Batian is still waiting for me to discuss
some big matters together.
I think we can use this plan again.
Oh, it's been more than three months.
After watching the geomantic omens
and repairing the ancestral hall, it's the right time.
Now many independent regimes are setting up by force of arms everywhere.
Nan Batian cannot know my whereabouts.
I will pretend to be an overseas Chinese merchant prince again.
Let's catch Nan Batian so that the enemy will lose their commander-in-chief.
What do you think?
We will be safer...
but Secretary Changqing has to take the risk.
Don't worry.
The mayor has already approved our plan.
The time for general attack is one a. m.
If we succeed in the city, then 6:36.
Check hers.
Go away. Go away!
Brother Hong, why did you give me such great presents?
Just local products.
Old majordomo, dispense them to the underlings to share in the master's good fortune.
Express my thanks to him on my behalf.
Why does Brother Nan feel uncomfortable?
Because of the attempted assassination by the Communist Party.
Oh, they really did that?
I swear not to stop if I cannot avenge the animosity of a bullet.
Old Four, have you caught the murderer?
I caught more than 20 suspects.
Well done. Use third degree for me.
Yes.
It's the right time for Brother Hong to come.
As regards the issue we talked about last time,
I wonder whether you...
I have made up my mind.
Even if I dissipate my fortune, I will do my best to help govern Hainan.
Oh! My dear friend is so courageous and resolute.
Prepare the wine. Give a dinner of welcome to Mr. Hong.
I happened to catch a cold.
I am afraid I can't have dinner with you. Moreover, Brother Nan?
Since Mr. Hong is not very well,
being travel-worn and exhausted
please go to bed early.
How are things going with the attack?
Nothing special.
Then... why did Qionghua begin to obey the law
and behave herself?
Don't worry about her.
She has become the senior slave girl who found favor with her master.
It seems that the stratagem of sending Qionghua is right.
We still don't know the exact details of Mr. Hong.
He has to pass through the Communist area whenever he comes and goes.
Why can he pass through so freely?
What's more, this time he came so suddenly.
So... you think there is something wrong with him?
I am not sure now.
But to say the least, Mr. Hong is noble and arrogant
when making friends with others.
He can't be a person to work together with for long
and be willing to be a subordinate.
If he is a blockhead, why did I make friends with him?
Master.
Getting hold of such a plutocratic person can help me to succeed.
Master, if you accepted my advice the day before yesterday,
there wouldn't be accidents when you visited the cemetery to honor the dead.
Just to avenge the animosity, I must take action immediately.
Otherwise the Communist Party may rush into my house.
Someone come here!
Hurry to the mountain and invite Huang Zhenshan to discuss the big plan with me.
Yes.
You are over-suspicious.
How can you be victorious being indecisive?
Master don't be too careless, or you may lose everything.
The back door is near the kitchen.
I'm coming.
Old majordomo,
Why don't you rest?
Are you still busy? What about coming in to sit for a while?
No, no.
It looks like somebody is watching us.
Xiao Pang, you go back to Guangzhou first thing tomorrow.
I will discuss something with the commander-in-chief Mr. Nan.
I've decided to stay here for a few more days.
Master, isn't elder Mrs. Hong waiting for you?
Take her here to stay for a few days, too. She can relieve her boredom this way.
I heard it clearly. There is nothing suspicious.
They even said they wanted to bring elder Mrs. Hong to stay here.
Xiao Pang.
Freeze.
Along the small road, you can find the way behind the blockhouse.
Master, sad days will follow for you to cry.
We are ready.
Light three fires right away.
Compatriots, grandmas and sisters,
come here and see!
Isn't he the squire, evil gentry, vampire
and commander-in-chief of the local militia, Nan Batian?
All of you know me, right?
I'm his lackey. He is my master.
My dad kicked his dog once
so he was beaten to death by Nan Batian.
Qionghua.
Stop talking about it.
Go.
The Communist Party advocates emancipation.
Emancipating collectively.
Men and women are on an equal footing.
I can't believe as a lackey I can have the chance to liberate my life.
Down with local tyrants and evil gentry!
Xiao Pang, help maintain order!
Hey, fellow-villagers, stop fighting!
Be quiet!
Fellow-villagers, hurry to the gate of Nan's house.
There will be a big meeting.
Execute Nan Batian by shooting him!
Take him inside under escort.
Don't move.
I want to go to the toilet.
Be quick.
-Where is he?
-Inside
Come out!
Come on.
Dare you run?
Master!
Hurry up. Hurry up.
There he is.
Qionghua!
I'm finished.
How is she?
She can bear it without an anesthetic.
How strong the girl is!
Qionghua, how do you feel?
Nothing.
It's much better than the the landholder's whip.
Secretary Changqing.
Qionghua.
Have you recovered from the wound?
Yes.
Come here. Sit down and take a rest. Give it to me.
We passed by this place again.
Yes. It was last autumn when we left Nan Batian's home.
It seems that it happened long ago.
The change is quite dramatic.
Now the District has expanded. Everything has changed.
So have the people.
You know at that time, I hated you and suspected you.
It was... was interesting.
There is one thing I am a little afraid to tell you.
What is it? Tell me.
I want to go into the county after dressing up.
And I will get the head of Nan Batian while at the temple market.
How many people will go with you?
I can handle it alone.
What if you can't?
He will kill me.
The reason I go to kill Nan Batian is for the glory of the women's army.
Isn't that right?
Even individual sacrifice is glorious, isn't it?
Uncle.
-You're back.
-Yes.
Come here and sit down beside me.
I want to talk with you.
Qionghua, find our Hainan Island.
It's here. Look at it.
It is so small.
Then point out our Coconut Grove.
I can't find it.
You are right. The place we passed just now is so big.
But on the map, it's nothing.
Qionghua, think about it.
Only depending on personal courage, can we liberate such a big country?
You are good at enlightening people.
Don't laugh. I am being honest.
I don't know why you know so many things...
read so many books...
have so great knowledge.
I'm not knowledgeable at all.
I went to Southeast Asia for business by ship with my father in my childhood.
I went to school when I was over ten years old.
The Ocean Trade Union of Guangzhou offered me money for school.
I wanted to go to the middle school.
But...
the trade union was broken by the reactionaries.
They put my father into a gunny-sack and threw him into the Pearl River.
What about your mother?
I don't know.
After my father died, she became blind.
Every proletarian has a sorrowful history.
Only for this reason the proletarian can light up the landlord's house
and let the fire burn it down.
But if you want to cause a conflagration to burn down the old society
you need to firmly rely on the collectivity, the entire class.
I've remembered every word you said.
Forever.
The entire class.
Comrades! Comrades!
We are celebrating the bountiful harvest.
Meanwhile we congratulate A'gui and Honglian on their marriage.
We hope this revolutionary couple will be together till the end of their lives
and thoroughly stick to the revolution.
Hey! Let's sing!
In conclusion, our army must seize
the key point of the island campaign.
That's a sudden and strong attack with concentrated military strength.
Then even the enemy would notice the central troops have already landed.
It will be too late for them to withdraw
the populace and property in the new district.
Because it is on an island
from here to the central zone only takes one day and one night to reach.
Please make a decision.
Friend, don't say anything more.
This time Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek has transferred our army
from the battlefront against the Communist Party to Hainan.
Obviously he has made up his mind to kill
all the Communist Party members in Hainan.
I'm very glad for the favorable cooperation
between the central and the local governments.
Just now this is?
My family name is Nan.
We should pay attention to what Mr. Nan said.
The infantry will be divided into three corps.
Start tonight respectively in the left, middle and right.
We must attack at once.
All right. Take action.
-Comrade Changqing.
-Yes.
The order from the commanding division.
The enemy is besieging the District from several directions.
Our main force should cut to the rear of the enemy and attack them.
The women's army should transfer two platoons to the main force.
Leave one platoon to intercept the enemy
at the mountain range dividing line which leads to the Soviet District.
Be sure to hold Nan Batian's army off
so as to cooperate with the main force to annihilate the enemy.
In order to counter encircle and suppress thoroughly
the Party calls on all the comrades to defend
the foundation of the revolution with their lives.
You lead Platoon One and Platoon Two
to the rear of the enemy following the main force.
Platoon Three and other companys follow me and go to the dividing line mountain range.
No, I will go to the dividing line mountain range.
You bring the troops to support the main force.
Don't argue. We don't have time.
You have heavy responsibility, too.
Everything is to counter encircle and suppress.
Take action right now.
We will see each other when we successfully join forces.
Goodbye.
Xiao Pang, you go back to the commanding division right now.
Report our situation to the director of the division.
Yes. Comrade Changqing, the enemy is coming.
Don't worry.
It's getting cold. Be careful not to catch cold on the way.
OK. Go.
Go quickly.
I'm going to the rear of the enemy following the main force.
You have been pregnant for seven or eight months.
At this time I...
Oh, don't worry about me.
The baby will accompany me this year.
How about your health?
I feel good, sisters.
You have a fighting mission, so leave the work to me.
I am sure that I will move the wounded and family numbers to a safe place.
All right. Let's go.
Go.
Take a look.
Let's go.
Take cover quickly.
Quick. Aunt Bai, here.
Be ready to fight.
If we miss the chance, the main force
of the Communist Party will start to move.
I have experience with the army of the Communist Party.
Fighting in dark is not good for us.
Only if their main force is truly here, can we use the bombardment.
Centralize firepower. Rush to the floor of the bridge.
They are not the main force. There are women in the battlefield.
This is a tactic of the Communist Party. Don't look down upon these women.
Master, they don't look like the main force.
Save the bullets.
Comrades, we absolutely cannot let the enemy march.
The enemy was beaten back by us again.
Concentrate the bullets.
Be ready for the enemy's counterattack.
The wounded in Squad One and Squad Two withdraw right now.
Yes. But...?
We have finished the mission. Squad Three and I will cover you.
No, all of you withdraw. I will cover you.
Follow orders, Comrade Qionghua.
The Party has approved your application.
From now on, you are not merely an ordinary soldier but a proletarian pioneer fighter.
If we can't withdraw from the battlefield,
the party members who withdrew will become the future fighting force
and fight until victory.
I've remembered all.
If we are separated by the enemy, you should hinder Nan Batian.
Well, take up the first task after joining the Communist Party.
Yes, Branch Secretary-in-chief.
Here are my first membership dues.
If we are cut off, hand them in on my behalf.
Catch them alive!
Aunt Bai, go!
This is the first baby in our women army.
Our little woman soldier.
Sister Qionghua.
The situation on the battlefield is still unknown.
Big Sister, you tell the others to check the weapons.
Collect the bullets. I will go to the front to have a look and return soon.
Be sure to take good care of Sister Honglian.
Just go.
The main force, where is the main force?
So strange and unusual.
Battalion leader.
We got two companies killed in the river by a small group of the women's army.
If without my brother Zhenshan...
Get rid of these women. Damn it!
We must annihilate the Communist Party in this district.
Though the women's army is a small group, it destroys the peace of the whole county.
Even women can shoot me.
Later everybody dares to revolt against the government.
Oh, did we come here to protect you and your house?
Report.
Our brigade was beaten by the Communist army and is in disorder.
Tomorrow in the early morning we will move to the brigade base.
Withdraw from this damn place!
Yes.
It's time to withdraw.
Master, he came round again.
Bring him to me.
I regarded you highly the first time I met you.
I haven't changed, Mr. Hong.
If you can get the women army to surrender to us,
you can have high position and great wealth.
All right, I will give you several minutes to think about it.
All right. For your communism, I will kill you.
Bring him outside. Bring him outside. Bring him outside.
Long Live China!
Down with the Nationalist Party's dominion!
Long Live the Chinese Communist Party!
-Sister Lian.
-Qionghua.
What's the situation on the battlefield? Where is Comrade Changqing?
-Sister Qionghua.
-Qionghua.
All the comrades on the battlefield have sacrificed fearlessly.
Comrade Changqing sacrificed gloriously.
Don't cry. What are you crying for?
We should avenge Comrade Changqing.
Let's go! Go! Fight against them with our lives.
Comrades, we should take revenge, but not in an impulsive way.
Then what should we do?
We left the division and the Party representative was sacrificed.
We still have you. We still have the Communist Party.
Wipe away your tears.
The enemy's fire can only burn one of our communist members to death.
It won't scare us.
Together we'll light a big fire
to burn down the enemy as well as the entire old society.
Sisters, comrades!
We should take the responsibility that the martyr left to us.
Gather round.
Forward march...
forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
There was Hua Mulan in ancient times who joined the army,
taking the place of her father.
There is a women's army using guns to protect the people nowadays.
Forward march...
forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
A'gui, we caught them!
We've caught them. They are just part of the army.
Oh, is the division commander here?
Yes.
Report.
You are back.
Yes.
Is Nan Batian planning to run away?
Yes, he is preparing to run off to Haikou.
Where is the women's army that we left there?
Nan Batian is a guerrilla in the district where Comrade Changqing was.
Good. You take off right now and find the women's army.
Tell them we have succeeded in countering encircling and suppression.
Our main force will turn back for the frontal attack tomorrow.
Ask them to try their best to encumber Nan Batian
until six o'clock tomorrow afternoon.
Yes.
Tomorrow you are required to insist upon until six p. m.
The division commander said maybe you don't have enough force,
but can drag one of Nan Batian's legs.
Yes. Insist on until six p. m. tomorrow.
-Who is that?
-I.
Dan Zhu is back.
Qionghua, Nan Batian intended to run away.
Before he ran off, he caught a great number of civilians in Coconut Grove.
What about uncle? Was he caught?
He is waiting for the slaughter.
It is a new situation.
Yes, it is.
But we only get 20 guns.
So what! We are sure to hit him,
exerting the utmost strength to fight.
Qionghua, what do you think?
We can risk our lives if you decide.
Yes, just speak out.
We won't risk our lives. We will kill Nan Batian.
If we are late, hundreds of comrades may be killed.
Just give your order.
We will follow anything you say.
Ask the team to have a meeting.
Master, we've caught all the people.
Well, let's go to meet them.
Quick!
Long live the farmers! I will offer my congratulations to you.
To prevent you from digging
my ancestral grave after I leave,
I will kill you all now.
However, whoever shouts "Down with the Communist Party" once
I will let him live.
Why, nobody wants to shout?
Down with local tyrants and evil gentry!
Down with the landlord!
Long live the farmers!
Hurry up. Move quickly
Don't move!
Quick.
Quick, come with me!
Down with the landlord!
Don't fire. Tie them up. Catch them!
Tie him up!
Don't move!
Ah, Brother Fourth!
If there is anybody who dares to move I will kill your commander-in-chief first!
Take them away!
It's the women's army!
To tell you the truth, the main force of the Red Army
has already foiled the attack of the central bandit troops.
They are matching towards this county.
Disarm and surrender right away.
I will die for a righteous cause.
I will sacrifice. I will die for my country. I, I...
Good. I will help you to fulfill your wishes.
You are cruel and unscrupulous but cowardly. When I saw you I knew you deeply.
Disarm and surrender at once.
Forget our enmity totally.
Give me a chance to live.
I will lead all my troops to withdraw.
I will leave all my property to you.
Nan Batian will retreat from military circles
and never return to this county again.
You want to stab me in the back later and choke me to death.
What a great idea. Master.
Rush ahead.
I surrender. I surrender.
I beg you not to kill me!
Long Live the Communist Party!
Now let's welcome the Party representative from Company Two of the women's army,
Comrade Qinghua, to speak.
Comrades.
From now on, you 120 persons, have become the glorious fighters of the Red Army.
Now we will learn from the excellent tradition of the women's army
and those martyrs who have sacrificed themselves.
Pick up your guns and beat down the enemy, no matter if he is Nan Batian or Bei Batian.
It's not enough just for us to do so. Our children need to fight, following us too.
We will fight until the entire proletariat is liberated.
Forward march...
forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
There was Hua Mulan in ancient times who joined the army,
taking the place of her father.
The women's army uses guns to protect the people nowadays.
Forward march...
forward march.
The fighter's responsibility is heavy; women's animosity is strong.
The End