Kim Sang-joong
Yoon Da-hoon
Lim Chang-jeong
Jin Hui-kyung
Lee Jae-eun
Kim Se-jun
Park Jun-kyu
Director Jung Cho-sin
Is the bank robbery in lately?
I sold one for 2 Grand
the other day.
Boy, It didn't come easy.
It's the latest model,
and literally a piece of art.
Money?
Put it on my tab.
Shove it up your ass, man.
I want cash for it.
no guarantee of success
Put it down and
get the hell out of here.
No money, no gun!
Is this a joke or what?
It's not a joke.
I said, "Put it on my tab."
JAKARTA
Are you ready?
All set?
Don't worry about a thing.
I'll walk into the vault
and pick up $3 mi llion.
Nobody will suspect me.
I'm not sure about this.
Can we pull this off?
I'm the VP of this bank.
Who would suspect me?
It's 9:08.
I'm going in.
Good morning, sir.
Go ahead, sir.
What?
Oh, okay.
What's going on here?
We've got a bank robber!
Get him!
He's a bank robber!
Call the cops!
Police station?
This is Okwang Investment Bank.
We've got a bank robber!
Hurry up!
I'll take him to the police,
and this bag as evidence.
He might try to run.
Freeze!
Move and die!
Didn't you hear him?
Get down on the floor!
Cops are that quick?
It hasn't even been a minute.
What timing.
Don't move!
He caught the robber.
You thief!
Not him!
He's our vice president.
this one is the thief!
Is that right?
You son of a bitch!
Let's take them down.
Let's go
- Come on!
- I'll sue you for assault.
Hey, let me go!
You're the key witness.
Come with us.
It hurts!
Don't let anybody in till
the investigation is over.
Sure!
Yes!
Everybody, back to work!
Back to work!
- Hey, come over here.
- Sure.
What are you guys doing?
Back to work!
Our van!
Money!
Where did our van go?
We've 3 bodies in it!
Doesn't matter.
We stole it anyway.
Run!
- Where are we?
- Beats me.
Are we in the interrogation room?
Interrogation room?
What a moron.
Where the hell are we?
Hey!
Get over here.
Come on!
I've got a knife in my pocket.
Get it out!
Stop yelling at me!
How old are you?
I'm the vice president!
What a stupid jerk.
Come on!
Get it out of my pocket.
I'll untie you, too.
You get it out yourself!
Gosh, you're pigheaded.
Okay, fine.
Get the knife, will you?
Where is it?
- In that pocket.
- Where?
Yeah, that pocket.
Here?
Down further.
You had to come in right then?
I was about to take off,
and you blew it!
It's my bank,
and my daddy's money!
If it's your daddy's money,
why bother protecting it?
Move your ass!
What do you mean,
I can't get my money back?
We're really sorry, ma'am.
The whole system is down.
What does that have to do
with my money?
- Any word from him?
- Nothing.
He has the key to the vault!
You told me
it was a piece of cake!
I didn't expect other rogues.
Idiot!
Can't you do better?
Practice more.
Laughing at me?
No, I'm not.
You talked back to me?
'No' my ass!
I saw you laughing at me
for not hitting the mark!
I didn't laugh at you.
You just did!
Stop!
Go easy on him.
He fainted.
Did you laughed, too?
No, I didn't.
He laughed, too.
I saw him laughing.
Not so fast!
You wouldn't go down?
Should we kill them?
Maybe.
We have no choice.
Let's erase them.
Yeah, it looks that way.
What happened to Blue?
Will he talk?
I would, if I were him.
Pigs are so merciless.
No way he can hand le it.
Last time I talked
before they beat me up.
Say something!
What are we doing now?
Let's split.
What?
If Blue talks, we're in trouble.
We'll be better off alone.
We're in the same boat.
We can't get separated!
It's safer if we split up.
Let's think!
He might not talk!
Right!
He doesn't know our names.
He only knows us by red
and White.
He knows our names.
I didn't know.
You assholes blew our plan.
And now you want us
to let you walk?
What did we do with that punk?
What punk?
Who?
the one that tried to stop us
at this bank in Suwon.
In Suwon?
What are you talking about?
That punk!
Oh, that one!
We burnt him, right?
No, did we dump him
into the river?
Didn't we send him to the hospital?
We were going to,
but he kicked in.
He was such a weak boy.
Was it that bad?
Nah, just a few broken bones
and a visceral cleft.
Right, one of his eyes
popped out, too.
Let's pop them, bro.
I'm the VP of that bank.
what you want?
I'll give you money
if that's what you want.
Just let me go.
You're the vice president?
You bet!
Didn't you hear them
sir me at the bank?
I'm really the VP.
What about you?
A bank robber.
You're not cops,
are you?
I know when... Shut up!
Get the camcorder.
It's your lucky day.
Are you nuts?
Why did you tell him?
You know ours.
That's because-
You banged him, too?
What a slut!
You fuck any...
What do you care?
I am not your girl!
Since we're at it,
let me give you another tip.
His penis is a lot longer
than yours.
Hello?
Hey, what's up?
I'm fucked, man!
Leave a message at the beep.
What happened?
Why doesn't he answer?
I've got this great plan.
I'll be right over.
Get some thugs and...
Bring a girl, too.
I've got to jet.
See you later, man.
Shit!
911?
Somebody stole my taxi!
Fi lm the VP asshole,
and kill the thief.
What?
You do it.
It'll stain my shirt in blood.
I absolutely hate it!
This isn't fair.
He gets to live?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You aren't the VP.
I'm just a thief.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
We work in the same field.
Don't kill me.
Make it quick.
What makes you think
you can kill me?
You guys are so funny.
What fami ly are you with?
Lay your fingers on me,
both of you are dead!
Now, you bastards!
Untie us.
We're dressed up as cops,
but we're bank robbers.
But, as the fate decides it,
we've become kidnappers.
Hey! Jin Dal-ho.
Want to save your son?
You have to pay us in cash.
I'd like the money
Be quiet!
We want 3mi llion.
We don't get it in 2 hours,
your son will lose his nose.
2 hours after that,
he'll lost something else.
We're not joking.
You know it from his ear.
They sent this.
Sick bastards!
Do this for 3 Grand?
In case you're confused,
we want $3 mi llion.
Show me the money.
America money, America money!
Don't do anything stupid.
Who the hell are they?
What's wrong with mine?
brother
Too much water.
Hello?
Yeah, it's me.
It'll be delivered soon.
You do the delivery.
Okay.
I'm not done yet.
5 minutes left,
and we don't have the money.
Doo-san!
It doesn't get here in 5 minutes-
Cut this off,
and send it to him.
Don't worry about it.
You can still breath
without it.
Come here, boy.
Come in.
What is it, Miss. Jo?
Sit down.
What's that?
A package from kidnappers, sir.
2 hours have passed,
so here's your son's nose.
Get us money in 2 hours.
Hello?
- It's me.
- Who?
It's me, the kidnapper.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
I don't think
he got the nose yet.
Ask him.
- Did you get the nose?
- I did.
What do you want me to do?
It's already 6!
2 hours have passed!
You didn't even tell me
where to send the money.
You didn't tell him
where to send it?
Send it to the warehouse
in Koyang by 9 tonight.
Only one person comes,
or the deal is off.
Okay.
One more thing.
It should be Miss. Jo.
She's your son's lover.
Okay.
My secretary will take you
to the warehouse.
Bastards!
Don't worry about it, sir.
Go ahead.
I'm on my way.
Sir, won't it be better
if you call the cops?
I can't trust them.
I got it all figured out.
Cool!
They're all topless!
It's time she should be here.
Hey, VP.
....
Ever been to Venice?
Any places you haven't...
That's enough!
What about Buenos Aires?
The girl's here.
She's carrying a bag.
Sa-hyun!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Don't you move.
Don't!
Doo-san!
Eun-ah!
Eun-ah!, Eun-ah!
- Let's go.
- What about Miss. Jo?
She's dead.
Home, sir?
- Let's get out of here.
- Yes, sir.
You owe me a total $ 1. 5 million.
Interest alone is half a million!
- How-
- Boss!
What did I say?
- Talking won't solve it.
- Shut up.
Boss, should I...
Where was I?
Wait...
You son of a bitch,
You're smoking before me?
You've got 15 days.
Bring me the money,
or you're dead meat.
understand?
I'm robbing the bank.
What are you talking about?
You're kidding, right?
I have a plan.
What is it?
I can't tell you now,
Don't worry
but it's very simple.
Don't do it.
There should be another way.
another way?
No, this is the only way.
My old man says he can't give me $2 million.
- No other options.
I have no other choice
- I'm worried.
Don't worry about it.
Everything will be fine.
Let's leave the country.
You and me?
You found boys?
Give me some more time.
Unti I when?
Don't worry about a thing.
I'll take care of it.
Can we talk?
- Is that it?
- Right.
Let's check inside.
No. I know the place.
Let's go.
This is our target,
Okwang Investment Bank.
There $3 million is sitting
in the vault.
And this is the sewerage
we're going in through.
We'll make a tunnel
to the bottom of the vault.
Possible, Blue?
You bet.
Digging a hole is a piece of cake.
We can get to the building
within an hour.
From there up to the target
is exactly 115 centimeters.
It takes 1 hour to dig 40cm
through concrete.
So we'll be under the vault
for 3 hours.
3 hours?
That much time?
Can't you just make a hole
and let ourselves in?
Should I get some dynamite?
This is the only way.
Do your job right.
Okay.
Good.
What about the vault, Blue?
It's Elesten 7469 from Sweden,
15.3cm thick.
It's wired with sensors
connected to SECOME.
- It looks impossible.
- We can do it.
The bottom of the vault is
only 5cm thick.
Hello?
$3 million will be wired
next Monday.
Okay.
- Are you really doing it?
- Sure.
Don't worry about it.
It'll be fine.
Okay.
Eun-ah, take a look at this.
Yeah, that's right.
Thanks.
We can't make it.
What about SECOME?
They turn it off when it opens.
Those who rob banks
in the afternoon are morons.
- You know why?
- No.
Most bank robberies take place
right before they close.
So they turn SECOME on
an hour before they close.
Nobody has robbed banks
when they're opened.
And we'll pass off as cops.
Have you seen bank robbers
dressed up as cops?
No.
So we're going to make it.
Can we really pull this off?
It's very simple.
All we need to do is dig a hole
along the sewer.
Send one of them up.
I'll walk in at 9:09
and drag that bastard out.
It will be a perfect crime.
That ass was using his head.
He was talking about making it
his own perfect crime.
We need fake bills.
What for?
We'll get money from the vault
and switch it with fake bills.
Then we leave dead bodies
in the sewage.
If we blow the gas pipe that
goes above the tunnel...
The cops will think we're dead.
Isn't that cool?
Writing a novel or what?
Let him have his fun.
I'll drag him out of there
with a bag full of bills.
I'll cut him some slack
once we leave the bank.
I bet he'll beat me up
and try to run.
I'll stay down on the street,
holding onto the bag.
When the police get there,
I'll tell them he got away.
Who could possibly imagine
this was all staged?
Unless he's God.
It'll be a perfect crime!
We're
going to Jakarta.
Why Jakarta?
You don't know what it means,
and you call yourself a robber?
Here, Jakarta is slang,
meaning the perfect crime.
I asked to see if you knew.
How could I not know it?
We're going to Jakarta!
Right?
They come to work at 7:30.
They open it at 9.
That's when SECOME gets turned off.
At 9:10,
the vault is open.
At 9:15,
we'll run into the bank.
This is our plan.
Dig it?
It sounds too easy.
Even kindergartners can do it.
Every perfect plan is simple.
That's how most scumbags
end up in jail.
You have to jinx it?
Doo san?
You never hit the mark.
Why don't I do it?
Trust me, bro.
I'm better than you are.
Did you get them?
Just one grandma's body.
That will do.
What about male bodies?
Not many men jump lately!
the news says a lot of them
jump into the river.
the media makes an issue out of it.
Now they go to the sea
or take pills, man!
I think I need a new job.
It used to be good, right?
That's what I'm saying.
2 or 3 a day jumped, man!
I miss those days,
making a few Grand a day.
Here.
Give me ten.
No way.
Give me ten!
Let me do some fishing.
I won't take long.
Not even ten?
Son of a bitch!
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
America?
Or Canada?
Switzerland.
Okay, we'll go to Switzerland.
I'll make a reservation for
two first class tickets.
When's the big day?
Tuesday, 9 A.M.
Shut up and dig with me.
Not enough space.
Keep digging.
My legs are falling asleep.
Carry the dirt then.
it's a cop
Drop it.
Drop it!
Turn off the radio.
Hello?
It's me, Eun-ah.
We just started digging.
It's 9 o'clock sharp.
Don't forget.
I'll turn off SECOME at 9.
9 o'clock sharp.
Don't worry about a thing.
It's perfect!
You got a gun?
It's a fake one that they use
for survival games.
Don't worry.
We won't be using it.
I'm worried.
What if anything goes wrong?
Plane tickets?
4:10, Wednesday afternoon.
Swiss Airlines.
That's right.
I'll bring them to the office.
I'll meet you there at 12
on Tuesday.
Hey, sis.
Want some noodles?
Reading a traveler's guide?
Aren't you worried?
Worried about what?
We're all set.
You guys are pathetic.
We got everything covered.
All we need is a gun.
What?
You haven't gotten one?
What's the matter?
Hey, look.
Leave me alone.
Do you love him?
I see.
You're in love with him.
Listen, girl.
He's a married man.
I bet he doesn't love you.
You don't know anything!
Here's what.
by any chance...
in case of...
After Doo-san stabs you,
if he carries you out...
I don't think it'll happen, though.
Then you can go with him.
What about you guys?
Nobody knows us.
We can score something else.
You're our only sister.
I want the best for you.
Hae-ryong-
Money?
Put it on my tab.
Shove it up your ass.
I want cash for it.
no guarantee of success
No money, no gun!
Is this a joke or what?
It's not a joke.
I said, "Put it on my tab!"
I told you not to play with it.
This is cool!
Give it here, bro.
It rocks!
You assholes!
I said, "No Jokes!"
5 minutes left.
Will SECOME be off at 9?
It will.
Trust me.
If it doesn't...
We'll wait until it's off.
It's 9.
Hello?
Okay.
This is...
Don't worry about a thing.
We're all set.
I'm not sure about this.
Can we pull this off?
All set?
Don't worry about it.
I'll walk into the vault
and pick up $3 million.
No one will suspect me.
Are you sure about that?
I'm the VP of the bank.
Who would suspect me?
It's 9:08.
I'm going in.
Okay, in 7 minutes.
We will.
Good morning, sir.
- Go ahead, sir.
- What?
Oh, okay.
Oh my God, it's money!
Shake a leg.
We've got 4 minutes left.
Get me the fake bills.
What for?
Aren't we leaving them outside?
Do as I say!
Time's running out!
Hurry up!
Shit!
Hello?
This is a Andong- restaurant
- Hello?
- Police station?
You got the wrong number.
This is a Chinese restaurant.
This is Okwang Investment Bank.
We've got bank robbers!
I told you, lady.
It's a Chinese restaurant!
Hurry up!
Is she nuts?
She wants me, a delivery boy,
to bust bank robbers?
Hey, you crazy bitch!
No more crank calls!
Now, you bastards!
It's so real.
Look at this blood.
Where did you get the gun?
It rules, man!
- Doesn't it?
- You bet! Here, here.
and then...
Do the other arm.
By the way...
Why did you hit me that hard?
I didn't want to, man.
Hae-ryong told me
it had to look real.
No kidding.
I bet it was personal.
It doesn't hurt now, does it?
We'll talk about it later.
Take your shirt!
- So heavy!
- No kidding, man.
Heavier than an alive one!
After I take off,
clean up the mess.
Put the bodies in the back.
Put it on later.
He's scared like a trapped rat!
Out of the vehicle, please.
Name?
White.
What are you looking at?
Name?
Kim Bong-man!
Kim Bong-man...
Occupation?
bank robber!
it's okay
Way to go, boy.
Polite, humble, honest...
That's the attitude that
criminals like you need.
Occupation....
bank robber....
What?
bank robber?
Right, sir!
Didn't he steal a taxi?
Bastards!
Don't worry about it, sir.
Go ahead.
I'm on my way.
Sir, won't it be better
if you call the cops?
I can't trust them.
I got everything figured out.
Detectives are here to see you, sir.
What?
Okay, let them in.
Yes?
Have a seat.
We're from Kangnam Station.
What's this about?
We busted a perpetrator who
tried to rob your bank.
What are you talking bout?
The attempted bank robbery
took place at 9 this morning.
Well, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
in that case
You didn't know your bank
was robbed this morning?
I talked to some people,
and they confirmed it.
I don't think so.
How could I not know
if such a thing happened?
Is that right?
I told you.
That asshole is a nutcase!
Thanks for your time.
No problem.
We're leaving.
Thanks for your concern.
It was never robbed?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Yes, sir?
Who would deposit their money
to the bank that gets robbed?
Doo-san, throw it well.
Don't kill our little sister.
Eun-ah!
Help me carry the bodies!
Hae-ryong,
sprinkle the gasoline!
Eun-ah,
didn't I tell you
he would use you?
Had I not used Red to be in it,
you would've gotten screwed.
That's enough.
Stop crying.
Let's carry the bodies.
What happened?
Where the hell were you?
You look like shit.
Is this blood?
Not mine.
It's a long story.
I didn't expect it to be
this complicated.
What about the money?
- Let me see some dollars.
- Sure.
This is all ours?
Yeah, it's all ours.
Good job, guys.
How much is this?
3 million dollars.
We've got great lives
ahead of us.
Give me a fag, bro.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Hi.
- How are you?
These are for Jakarta.
You should go over to
Indonesian Airlines.
You must be kidding.
They're for Switzerland.
Look here, mister.
It says Jakarta here.
'J, A, K, A, R, T, A'
How could this happen?
I bought them for Switzerland!
I didn't issue tickets.
Why are you yelling at me?
If you've got any complaints,
go to the information desk.
I've come to you.
You should take care of us.
I didn't issue those tickets.
- Come on.
- It's your fault!
- Let me talk to you, girl.
- Is she the right one?
Gosh, you're killing me!
I have to go to Switzerland!
No way I'm going to Jakarta.
I'm going to Switzerland!
We can go to Jakarta first
and over to Switzerland.
Where are we going
when we get there?
It's a surprise.
- That's why dad hated you!
- Give me a break, man!
Who the hell are you?
You're under arrest
for using counterfeit bills.
What counterfeit bills?
You're making a big mistake.
- Uncuff me!
- Shut up!
There must be a mix-up.
What are we doing now?
We're going to Jakarta.
- Jakarta that is!
- Let's go!
It's very simple.
We put dead bodies there
and blow up the gas pipe.
The police will think we're dead.
I'll be a perfect crime!
Then we're going to Ja...
We're going to Jamaica!