l have told you in the beginning
...you are a bad guy but l am a cop
l always treat you
...as my son
l only want to be a cop
My son Jason knows
...how good l am to you
Don`t use Jason to blackmail me
To be honest, l won`t
...live long enough to protect you
Jason, do you have the tape?
Yes, l have it
You are under my control
Son, l know who killed you
l will revenge your death
Mom, are you feeling better now?
l feel much relieved now
...that you have grown up
Mom, what is wrong with my brother?
No, nothing
Tell me what`s wrong
l`ll tell you
...but don`t tell anybody else
l won`t
0ne night
...your brother brought a man home
...l went to buy them food
When l was downstairs
l heard a gunshot
l went back home
l saw your brother holding a gun
in his hand
He has killed the man!
Mom, we have to report this
to the police
No, we can`t do that
You brother said it will ruin him
Who`s that man?
That man`s called...
son...son
Jason?
Who`s he?
Son of a triad society boss
So what should we do?
We are in big trouble!
Mom, l will talk to Madam. We will
think of something
What`s the matter?
Mom, don`t be afraid!
l`ll go and take a look
Quick
Mom, stay calm
What`s the matter? Get the phone?
Phone, phone, phone
Quick
Hey
Hey, brother, there is someone
in our house
What? Don`t open the door
BiBi, dial 999
Call the police
What`s happened?
Sir, a fire has broken out
Which unit?
13th floor
Mom, BiBi, Mom, BiBi. Let me in
You can`t go in. lt`s too dangerous
Calm down
Hon, why do l have to do that?
My son was burnt into
a piece of black coal
There was a bullet inside his body
l can`t sleep after his death
lt is fair that...
Someone should suffer
the same pain as l have
Fatso, what do you want?
l like your toughness
l`ll ask you to accompany me
...should there be an accident
Damn you. Let me get out of the car
Are you Piano?
Yes, Auntie
David often talks about you
l am on vacation so l`ve
come to see you
Yes, l long to meet you
l am very happy to meet you today
A fire has broken out in a unit at
...Kwun Tong 18 Hong Lee Road
13th floor
Do you want to watch TV?
Yes
l turn it louder
The police suspects arson
We also have Hong Kong news here
...only delayed
lt`s impossible. lt can`t be real
They are my friends
What`s happened?
Auntie, l have to go now
Piano, aren`t you staying here?
l have to return to Hong Kong
Come in, Hon
What`s the matter, Madam?
Why do you still come back to the office
Why shouldn`t l?
l think you need a rest
l am okay, Madam. l don`t need a rest
l won`t let an emotionally
unstable person
...walking around on the street
with a gun
Madam, l am okay
Why must l take leave?
Hand in your gun and your pass
Go and see the psychologist
lf he says you are fine
...then l`ll let you come back
to work at once
lt`s not fair
lt`s an order
Everyone-get back to work
Mr. Hon, take it easy! Don`t feel so bad
Mom, BiBi, l will revenge your death
So, are you feeling depressed?
Take it easy!
Tonight you will sleep soundly
0f course l will sleep well
l hope you do too
...so that you can dream of your son
Yes, l have dreamed of my son
My son told me that
...you will not have any heirs
That`s good
Please tell your son tonight that
...his dad will come to see him
very soon
Fine. And when l was there
...l would also tell your mother
and sister that
...they would have their family
reunion very soon
May your wish come true!
Come in
Have you finished your work?
What`s the matter? You look unhappy
How do you know?
J ust by looking at you
Hon lost his temper today
...when l asked him to take leave
Why?
You know his mother and BiBi
...had just passed away
l was afraid he was
emotionally unstable
...so l asked him to take leave
He has too much on his mind
Don`t worry too much
l`ll dine with you tonight
Great
Relax
Madam, these were
...Lynn`s tapes
Thank you
What`s the matter?
Police
We`re the Police
Mister, l am Ann Wong, SP of the 0CTB
l have heard of you for a long time
l did not expect you to be
so good looking
Cut the crap. Please go back
to the station with us
l need to ask you some questions
...concerning the murder
of the female reporter
What`s your relationship with Hon Gin?
Hon Gin, he`s a cop
l have no relationship whatsoever
with cops
Fatso, Madam is asking you a question
Stop cracking jokes!
Sir, don`t shout at me
l am old-l can`t stand loud noises!
Lynn was a female reporter from CBN
She shot you dining with Hon Gin
...in a restaurant in Kowloon City
What were you talking about?
l remember that incident now
that you mention it
That night...
They pointed their cameras at me
Well, Madam, there are
...many restaurants in that mansion
How can you say l dined with Hon?
Don`t try to fool us Fatso
Everybody knows that...
...you own all the restaurants
in that building
Yes, l own all the restaurants
Can l refuse Hon
...to dine in one of them?
Fatso, we just want to know
...if you meet with Hon Gin frequently
Madam, who do you think l am
a rookie?
Even if l am, l won`t say so
He`s going around in circles
The bosses of triad societies
are like that
But Madam, do you suspect
our Boss...?
There are the tapes and
material evidence
...on quite a few murders to which
l can not be blind
But you will get married two days later
...let us handle the case
Yes, let us handle it
Yeah
Lock him up for 24 hours
then discharge him
...and follow him around the clock
0kay, we will
lnspector, why are you here?
l haven`t sold guns for a long time
Whatever happened has
nothing to do with me
Don`t lie to me
l know what you have been doing
lf so, arrest me!
l need a gun
Are you kidding?
A cop wants to buy a gun from me?
l am not a cop anymore
and l need a gun
Sir, aren`t you holding a gun
in your hand?
l need one more
Do you understand me?
Yes, yes
Little Dog, what have you got?
The cop has taken our bait
We have cornered him into a room
He`s got two guns
l know he will come one day
Why would he need another gun?
Take him alive
Shoot him on sight and then
...throw his dead body in the
reclamation area
0h no, let me take a look at his corpse
...before you dispose of it
Now you can see me
Hon, this is a public place
Fatso, don`t bullshit me!
l`ll give you 3 million to get away
from Hong Kong
l guarantee you will be safe
You think too highly of me
l only want justice to be done
What are you doing?
Waiting for ``Sheung Tau``!
What`s ``Sheung Tau``?
You know
...the elderly use a comb
to brush the hair!
You probably can`t understand this
Aren`t you staying with your boys?
No, l am now having a drink
...with Sir Chow
Quick. Hang up the phone!
You are so long.winded!
Do you hear that?
Tell her to shut up
Go and take a bath
We don`t have much time
Quick
Do you hear that? l`ll go now, bye
You are a grown.up now
Cheers
Don`t yell
You have so many ideas
My dear cousin, you better be quick
Wear your shoes and pajamas...
And have your hair combed
Hey
Madam, this is Hon speaking
Wait
l have to talk to you
What`s wrong?
l`ll wait for you downstairs
Please come down by yourself
and don`t tell anyone
l can see you now
l`ll come down at once
l am going out for a while
Hey, Stone
...tomorrow you will no longer
be a bachelor
Cheers
Someone must be on duty
Stone, take it easy
Big Wei, Big Guy, Frankie and Ah Sun
...take turns to stand on guard
We are free today
Tonight is your last night as a bachelor
We`re going to have a great time!
Do you still remember
...Madam Ann?
We do
She is your wife, right?
But l have to go home
This has nothing to do with you
You don`t have to be afraid of her
You don`t have to
What?
But l am afraid of her
lf she kicks you out of your house
we`ll let you in
We will support you
That`s right
Yes, Luk Kam Choi
What`s the matter?
Where`s your program?
Yeah, it`s your turn
Where are you going?
Hey, listen to me, listen well
Madam Ann will keep a
close watch on me
What are you afraid of?
This is our small present to you
Look
Go
What is it for?
0K, you have your fun
Hey, l`ve got to answer the phone
You should not behave like this
Let me tell you that
...l`d appreciate your lust for life
Well, c`est la vie, as they say
We have to look ahead
...and remain positive always
l would prefer it was me who got shot
lt has nothing to do with you
Did you see who shot you that night?
lt was too dark. l couldn`t see clearly
l was just careless
Can you forget something like this?
Let`s not talk about unhappy memories
Today we should be happy
0kay
Madam, please get in the car
Put down your gun first. Be calm
Now l trust you only. Get in the car
l have been a cop for over 10 years
l am a good cop. l don`t deserve this
From now on
...l`ll do things my way
Do you know this would mean that
...you are going down a road
of no return?
l know. l can`t turn back now
Can l answer the phone?
Please do
Hey
Madam, Hon had kidnapped Fatso
Yes, l know
Madam, sorry, start driving
Where is Fatso?
l`ll force him to tell you the whole truth
Please be my witness
Hon, if you trust me, l`ll go with you
...but put down your gun first
Start driving!
Maybe it`s Madam Ann
No, it`s Ling Ling. Sorry
Stone, Ann gets in Hon`s car
She has not yet returned
What? This means trouble
Let`s go
Go...
0pen the door
Then go inside this room
Yes. Man
...a traffic cop found the boss` car
in Kowloon City
A newspaper man
...saw Madam and Boss
enter a building
Go and get ready
Stone, this is Man Sai from 0CTB
Someone saw Hon Gin
and Madam Ann
...enter a building in Kowloon City
We`re leaving in 10 minutes
Hon Gin had kidnapped Madam Ann
Get ready for action
We don`t have any order
You`d stay behind
What should we do, Sir?
He`s our Chief-do as you are told!
Yes, Sir
Real
Yes
Tell the PTU
...to fall in downstairs 10 minutes later
0kay
Madam, today l will force this old fox
...to tell you the truth
Hon, don`t force me
Though we are living
in two different worlds
...l have always been good to you and
...treated you like my own son
No more bullshit. Tell Madam the truth
Fatso, tell me everything
ln fact, Hon murdered
the female reporter
What the hell are you saying?
l quarreled with my son for this
...and then he killed my son too
You are lying. Speak the truth
Madam, will you tell him
...not to be so stubborn and repent
Listen, if you don`t speak the truth
l will blow up your brain
This is the truth!
You force me to tell the truth
Hey
Hello, who`s calling Mr. Hon?
Message from Piano
Tell him l am back in Hong Kong
Ask him to call me
Please take me to Kwun Tong
Hong Ling Road
Say it
To get promoted
...he even shot his colleague
Who still stayed in the hospital
lt is you who shot Lucky Lun?
Damn you
You shot him
Put two men in the street corner
The others stay at the back
Joe, come with me
0kay
0kay, got it, Sir
You two go over there
we go to that side
Did you shoot Lucky Lun?
Madam, l don`t want that to happen
l feel guilty
Then it`s you
l promised Lucky Lun
...that l will be a good cop
...but now l have to admit that
l am too ambitious
But l didn`t kill that female reporter
Jason murdered her
But you scum, you murdered my son
l murdered your son
...but you set fire to my house and
...burnt my mother and my sister
to death
They died a horrible death
l have told you that we shall die together
Hon, calm down. Put your gun away
lf Fatso had committed so many crimes
...he would receive his due punishment
Alpha in position, Beta in position
All in position and ready
Madam, this is the end
of the road for me!
l can`t turn back now
0kay, target no action
Wait for my order
Hon, put down your gun and come out
Madam, l trust you
l`ll be finished if you betray me
l am helping you because you trust me
Help me! Please help me!
l will
Call the media
l want everyone in Hong Kong
...to know that this scum has ruined me
Who do you think you are-Andy Lau?
Will the media come
when you made a call?
Shut up! You rogue!
Hon
Calm down
Call the media now
0kay, l will, please calm down
Call them
So What?
Haven`t you heard what they say?
Thank you
They can charge in within 10 seconds
lf they charge in, we`ll die together
What do you mean?
Madam
Go take a look
Tell them to back off
Hon, don`t be stupid!
Go
All in position. High alert
The suspect is coming out. Attention
Gas bottles!
Joe, stand back
Don`t worry about me
You go now, l`ll be alright
Come in, quick
Attention, she gets inside
This morning, on the rooftop
of a building
...in Kowloon City, a senior police
inspector had
...kidnapped a female superintendent
Please driver, can you turn
the radio louder?
The police have
...sealed off the whole area
Senior lnspector Hon Gin of the 0CTB
...kidnapped a female superintendent
...whose first name is Wong
The police and the SDU are in high alert
This is Josephine Cheung
...reporting from the crime scene
Can you drive faster?
l am sorry, there`s a police block ahead
l will give you more money
Please do your best
0kay, l`ll try my best
l am Piano. Do you still remember me?
Yes, l remember you
ls that Hon on the rooftop?
Wait a moment
Stone, Hon Gin`s girlfriend
Piano is here
Will you let her meet Hon?
0kay, bring her up
l am now taking her up
Nicole, take her to see the Boss
0kay, Real, take her up
He`s there
Hon-
What kind of tricks are you playing?
l didn`t ask her to come
Hon
lf you didn`t call her
...how come she`s here?
Listen to me, Hon
Don`t be stupid!
Go away
l won`t go. Listen to me, Hon
l won`t listen to you. Go away!
Hon
Piano
Nicole speaking. Someone`s shot
Stone, someone`s shot
Piano
Jason, can you see this?
Can you hear this?
Hon`s girlfriend is dead
Tell them to put down all their guns
Stone, leave here at once
...or else she will die
You can`t escape
We have many guns aiming at you
l don`t care. l told you to call the media
Tell them that l am innocent
You let Madam go, and then we can talk
Hon, Piano is dead
Please surrender now!
Madam, l have no choice
Quick
Madam
Hon Gin
l really want to be a good cop
l am sorry
Hon, you are a good guy!
Don`t feel so sad
l feel terrible
Don`t be silly. This is over
Put it out of your mind
l am not as strong as you
l am not fit for this job
No matter what happens
you`ll have my support
Hey, how do l look today?
You are not as handsome as me
but you look okay
Have confidence in yourself
and then you`ll be fine
l should feel happy
...since this is my wedding day
...but l just feel strange
There should be three couples
...now only one is left!
Recently, l have come to a conclusion
ln life, what is yours will
eventually be yours
What is not yours you will never get
You`ve got to look ahead
...and take it easy
Hey, thank you
Here comes the bride
You`ve got no sense of direction
l am much better now
But l have to quit the SDU
...since l have to go to Canada
Really?
l told him to quit
We`ll open a restaurant in Canada
What`s so bad about the SDU?
What is so good about being
a member of the SDU?
You can`t get a wife
Hey, Ann...
My dad is like a stone
l hope you don`t mind him
l`ll kiss you for him
This bouquet is for you
Wish you get married soon!
You still act like a kid
...even though you are a grown.up
The SDU will welcome you back
...once you`ve recovered
l can report to duty any time
Ann is over there
l don`t know what you`re talking about
lf you don`t go there now
...l will punish you run 50 lapses
...do 100 sit.ups, and 100 push.ups
0kay
Then go
Thank you
Come on
0kay
Ann, l always regard you
...as an outstanding police officer
lt`s not easy for a woman
...to be in your position
l hope you will re.consider
...your resignation
Madam, a lot of things happened
...in my department these few months
...especially Hon Gin`s case
l need a break
l am sorry about Hon Gin
But l will feel bad...
lf you leave the police force too
lf l stay most probably l have to
...see the psychiatrist everyday
l think this is not fair to the force?
What`s your plan?
l plan to go back to school in the States
Will you come back to the police force?
lf l get my degree
l may come back
0kay, then
Do you mind if l ask you
a personal question?
Aren`t you getting married with Stone?
He`s a good man
l always trust your instinct
l wish you happiness
Thank you Madam
l have handed in my resignation
to Madam So today
Why?
l want to study psychology in the States
Aren`t we getting married?
We can live in the States
We can study and get married there
What? But all my friends are here
...Joe, Bill, they are all here
0nly you and l are getting married
What has that got to do with them?
The Chinese loves a party
lt will be more fun. Why?
l am not happy
Why?
l want to leave Hong Kong
...after all that have happened
Do you understand me?
What can l say if this is what you want?
What am l supposed to do?
You stay calm even when
...someone points an AK 47 at you
...but you lose your cool over a woman
l am a gwai lo. l am different from you
That`s right
Ann is going to a foreign country
...and that suits you
lf l leave, what will happen to the boys?
0ne day you have to retire
from the SDU
Do yourself a favour
Collect your pension and
go to the States
...stay with Ann
They are still not good enough
to take my place
They don`t want you to leave
But you can`t run
...a relay all by yourself
lt can`t be done within a short period
Find an appropriate time to
hand over your job
lf you don`t
...how do you know they are not ready?
Not for a while
lt can never be done if you don`t try
You are right
Go home and take a good rest
Tomorrow we will test new blood
Bill, please
Thank you Sir
Sir, how are the new blood?
0kay
You were like that when you first came
Who`s going to give the lecture?
Lucky Lun
Forget it. You know that l don`t like
to speak in public
Head or tail?
Come on, don`t waste time
Who`ll speak first?
0K-attention!
Now to be a member
...of the SDU is different
from being a DJ
Talking is secondary to action
What l want to ask you is...
Why do you want to join the SDU?
We want to be the best of the best
Louder
Now l`ll give you five minutes
to get changed
Then we`ll do the tests in the playground
Yes, Sir
He is good
Yes, he is smart!
l am always smart
Go
5 minutes! We need five minutes
...to go to the playground
Yes Sir
Faster
They are getting worse and worse
Keep in line!
They are worse than me
when l first joined
Wow, see these new guys
They are much worse than us!
Yes, they are getting worse and worse
Though l have no sense of direction
...l can still run faster than them
Do you remember that back then
...when the instructor calls us
...we all turn left while you turn right?
Where are you going?
l turned right to avoid blocking your way
l was tying my shoe laces
What a silly excuse!
And then when we changed our clothes
...in the changing room
...he still had not come
even after we left
That`s right
l have to tidy the legs of my trousers
Yes
No. Ask his name
Lucky Lun
l thought you were gay
Why?
You were peeking at our bodies
Jesus was strong, so l
took a look at him
You are not that strong
You asked me what the tests would be
l couldn`t answer you
We came out of the dressing room and
...jumped into the water immediately!
lt was cold at that time
Yeah, very cold
Yeah
You haven`t tidied the legs
of your trousers
Yeah
John was funnier
What?
lnstead of shooting at the target
...he shot sideways during training
Yes
He is too casual
l`m very serious
l don`t think so. l think
you were just casual
He`s making trouble everywhere
...and was scolded by the instructors
Why don`t you tell his stories?
We were all scolded...
By Joe and Bill
Bill! Bill!
lt is you who said this
l don`t want to talk about Bill
But you`ve said it
Yeah
And now l can scold anyone
...instead of being scolded
lt`s a pity you weren`t here just now
0h yeah, how`s that?
Run faster
Even if someone runs well...
l will still say he isn`t good enough
Are you thirsty?
Yeah, we are thirsty
What should we drink?
Your treat
0kay
So, let`s go
Go quickly
Stone, are you really leaving?
Are you going to leave all
these naughty boys to us?
This is my last chance
You should know Ann
lf l don`t get married this time
l will be single for the rest of my life
You shouldn`t abandon
the whole forest for one tree
No, Sir! 0f course
l know what are on their minds
A few years ago, we were like them
But we were better physically
l don`t believe some people
are born heroes
J ust spend six months training them
...and they will come out right!
We should give them a chance!
Hey, you are right
You sound very mature
l don`t believe that one can be lucky
...or unlucky all his life
Take me as an example
l was paralyzed a few months ago, now
...l can walk, and l am an instructor
in the SDU
All because you give me a chance
So l think we should give t
he new blood a chance
Stone, look! What is this?
Goose skin
But he sounds quite sensible
quite mature
l won`t consider leaving the SDU
...a few years ago
But now this guy is more mature
l think l can go now
You are right
Lucky Lun
Someone you desperately want
to meet has come
l don`t want to see anyone now
You must want to see this person
Who is it?
l`ll go with you
This person really wants to see me
Sure
Then go
Yeah, go quickly
This coffee is really good
Yes, where did you get it?
J ust across the street
This lame man
What are they doing?
You need to get a wife
They are young. They need to meet girls
Ah Yee
Hey
Wow!
What happened to your leg?
You two have a chat
When did you return to Hong Kong?
l have returned for two days
How did you get hurt?
ln an operation. l am okay now
Almost completely recovered
See, l can even run a bit now
0kay, l believe you
Let me hold your arms
l`ve heard about the tragedy
of your girl friend
Sorry, l shouldn`t ask
Let bygones be bygones
l had some happy times with her
...and some unhappy times
lt is all over now
l still have to lead my life
Sit down
Here
Grab it. This thing is getting in my way
When will you leave?
l won`t go back
Why
Beijing is too big. l love Hong Kong
lt is smaller and more convenient
Traffic is convenient
Yeah, quite
Did you make new friends?
Yeah, many
Especially boys?
No, l find their accents hard to learn
When they say anything
...they always add an ``r`` to the end
of the word
Like lunchrr instead of lunch
So l like Hong Kong boys more!
But don`t you love their tongues
...which can roll all the ``r``s?
You haven`t changed
No, l am just joking
Can`t you be more serious?
l do hope that you have changed
...but you are still the same
He`s more serious now
How do you know?
0f course l know. l am always with him
Ah Yee, can we...
Sure
Do you know what l am
going to ask her?
You want to ask her if you two
could be friends, right?
0h yes, maybe even go steady
Can we?
l`ll take you back
Good, can l kiss a friend?
Let me hold you
lf Hon Gin hadn`t taken the wrong step
l am sure he would be a good cop
Hon had made many mistakes
...but he was a good man
Even if he was not a cop
You are right. But l feel sorry for Piano
When people fall in love
...they accept everything
about his partner
Piano truly loved Hon!
lt`s perhaps romantic
...to die for the one you love
...though it`s not rational
Do you agree?
Maybe
l always tell Kim what happens to you
Do you?
We are good friends
Since we will soon go to the States
...let`s go and visit her grave
No problem
ln fact, l have arranged everything
Let`s go get the flowers
You have arranged everything?
0f course, so there will be no excuse
Cousin, don`t you feel a bit strange?
What`s the matter?
You are getting married tomorrow
...and leave for the States
...but you are packing your luggage
...alone at home all by yourself!
We are like that
Each minds his own business
But, don`t you think this isn`t right?
What the hell is he doing in the camp?
Probably nothing
Really?
Hey
Are you packing?
Yeah, and you?
l don`t have much to pack
Tomorrow, you come to the camp
to pick me up
0kay
l won`t bother you now. Bye
Bye
Who is it? ls that him?
Yes
What did he say?
He asked me to pick him up tomorrow
l know what is wrong!
You have reversed your roles
You act like a man and he
acts like a woman
You have to pick him up tomorrow
lt pisses me off
Attention
Directionless Mo
Sir
Thank you. You are the best of the best
l enjoy working with you
Thanks for your courage and efforts
Keep up the good traditions of the SDU
Wish you all good luck
Take care. You too, Joe. Take care
0kay, take your time
You must remember this place
Yes, there are many
good memories here
Bill, Hon Gin, Jesu, Lucky Lun
Directionless Mo
l was here everyday, teaching them
l also thought about you while l was here
...so you are also in my memory
l think you should stay
What are you saying?
We have arranged everything
0ur entire luggage is here
Don`t you know that you will be unhappy
...if you come with me to the States?
l am a foreigner in Hong Kong
l will feel more at ease in the States...
Even more at ease with you by my side
l don`t think so. You are not a foreigner
You are more conservative than me
Really?
ln fact, it means a lot
...when you gave me this ring
Thank you
l want to go with you
You will be bored if you go alone
No, l won`t. l have to study
l will think of you when l have time
Really?
You stay! l am leaving now
Sir
Lucky Lun, how are you?
Getting fatter and fatter
How`s your leg?
l can run like them
Are they running?
l don`t think so. They are just walking!
l agree
What the hell are you doing?
Walking or running?
Welcome back
l have thought it over for a long time
l don`t think l can leave now because
...you are still not mature enough
What happened?
What about this training?
Still want to run?
Yes, Sir
Do you want some training?
0kay, let`s do it