Thanks.
Let's have a kiss, happy.
Ok...
Who likes to be the first customer? I'm first...
Settle among yourselves.
I'm first...
Turn around, beautiful.
It stinks!
Boss, all the flies here will be extinct.
Why?
Killing flies will be our pastime.
Our neighbour will wind-up soon.
Over a hundred dollars for a cut!
And no shaving!
No massage, no ear-cleaning.
Only pigheaded ones patrenize that salon.
It's real classy.
It's ruined! Do it again.
Ok.
Here you are, sir.
Back up 5 feet, at once!
Here is where you want.
Do as I say, 5 feet no more, no less.
Nut!
That's incredible.
Please take it back.
You are a Sage beyond this world? Yes?
Where is your consulting office? What's your title?
I need your Sage advice?
I'm puddin lai, 18th generation of soothsayer lai.
If our lines cross, they cross, if not, you loss.
When we cross again, I'll give you advice,
to get away from misfortune.
Sir, why you can't avert this.
I leaked heaven's secret for you.
I suffered for your sake.
Really? Of course.
Thank you, Sage.
- Sage lai. - Sage lai, thank you.
I can smell something evil.
Something devilish lurks this direction.
Let me charge, charge, charge.
- I cut. - Charge.
Give a hand.
- Charge. - Cut, cut, cut.
Hold it, count me out in this game.
Charge your ass.
Excuse me.
Happy
look at your hair, what gel do you use?
It's ok. The barber next door is devilish!
You know!
Luckily I got through unscathed.
To-day, I averted two misfortunes. Good luck. Oh! Heavens!
- What is it? - What?
The third misfortune.
- What date is it? - The 9th. Do my hair.
It's the third misfortune.
No on me, but on big eye boy.
Congratulations!
Grand opening, good business,
big money rolling in.
Congratulations!
Sorry, wrong blessings.
No, blessing here, oh, no. No.
No... here as well, everywhere as well.
In short, good business, big money.
Congratulations!
Skilful hands.
Don't you.
I'm not playing.
No playing! You did it purposely.
Not purposely.
That means playing.
Shave one eye-brow.
Shoot.
Come to us, big eye boy.
Papa.
Not me, he's papa,
how you become like this?
Why quarrel with these people?
Your godfather becomes one eye-brow hero.
Your papa never bows to force.
My righteous heart yearns for vengeance.
Watch my revenge.
Bravo.
That's great!
No dead!
What are you guys looking at?
Lustful eyes. Go inside, ah ying.
I'm not through with you yet.
Nothing to see!
Go inside.
So pure and fresh!
Fresh!
Her eyebrows, nose and forehead...
Are auspicious.
Ah ying, I'll marry you for sure!
Ying, let me apologize to you.
Let me say sorry for them.
What do the gods say...
Will he be alright?
Doomed!
He's really wretched.
This is my year for romance. Sure win!
You're spoiled our neighborhood.
You are the culprit,
you should be the one to settle this.
Go and apologize right now.
You know what my instinct tells me?
What?
Don't go.
Go fix it,
even if you have to pay indemnity.
Money! Why not.
May be ah ying will be moved by your sincerity.
Moved by me?
Sure.
It is my mistake; Not yours.
I should shoulder up this.
Right. Go right away.
May god be with you.
The gods look after you.
I pray to you, gods.
Hi, uncles,
What I mean is...
It's an early closure.
No, no, I don't mean that.
Uncle, I come to apologize to you.
- Uncle. - Papa.
Papa, please don't.
For 19 years, your papa never make one wrong.
Shave, not one hair,
until today. Look.
Shave two eyebrows to pay for mine.
What! Two!
Uncle, instead of eyebrow,
better shave my beard.
Or save you the trouble, I pay you money.
Thanks.
How much?
One hundred.
Five hundred, for each of you.
Not one cent less, or else...
Papa, no...
Better run.
I'll make-up for you.
Oh, it looks distorted.
No, it links better than the real one.
Excellent work.
Takes him so long, he is dome for.
Probably comes out castrated.
He has guts but no wit.
He shouldn't flirt with girls.
He should realise his weakness.
How come...
Can't believe my eyes.
Bye-bye.
Be careful!
He looks different.
Yes, what is it?
Much taller.
Ah! Taller.
How about this style for your semi-final contest?
You like this omega style?
Good, good.
It is this one then.
It's good for mummy. Go got her.
Ying, take a rest.
Have some refreshments.
Mum, don't disrupt us.
It's not up to 30 minutes yet.
You want her to die exhausted.
I say, take a rest.
Don't you want her to become miss Hong Kong.
The prize is one million dollars.
Moreover, she can marry a rich guy.
Papa, what is important for my husband is:
I love him and he loves me;
not necessarily a rich guy.
Right, greedy man! Don't you use ying to make money.
Woman's mentality.
Welcome. Yes.
Sir, please.
Smelly bean curds.
What's up?
Come! On the house.
Uncle! I'm sure you like this.
You too.
Have some chilli sauce.
Help yourself.
This is the most smelly.
Uncle, I've come to apologize...
And have shampoo. So as to hear from you.
Don't hurry.
Help yourself.
Ying, try one.
No, thank you.
Oh, you don't like it.
Shampoo, this way.
Is... she... coming...
I'm honored, you do it yourself.
Ah fu.
It's yours.
Shampoo?
Your hand!
Come align.
That way.
Ah ying.
Go, go.
Uncle,
I present you this fortune tiger.
It's will bring you big money.
Is my business bad now?
Your business is surely brisk.
But money is never too much, right?
Where shall we place this fortune tiger?
This is a vantage point.
Good for money.
Son, here is good for money, no good for sex.
Uncle, you have good sense of humor.
In fact, I come to apologise.
And have a shampoo as well.
Shampoo over there, pay here.
Shampoo?
Make-up eyebrow.
Uncle, ying, these flowers are for...
I like flowers.
Specially for you, uncle.
- Ying.. - Don't you want a shampoo?
Go.
Don't touch my thing.
I'll have a shampoo first.
Let's go.
- Are your place of work nearby? - Yes.
- Trust off-duty? - Yes.
Of course off-duty, it is so late.
Why don't you patronize grassy salon next door?
Don't mention the grassy salon, uncle.
It's a mess. They pull and pluck your hair.
You lost many hair in 1 shampoo. Really?
- Uncle, it is true. - Really?
- Many people say so. - Is it?
Bull shit.
Your friend seems quite exaggerating.
He is always like that.
Always boast and brag.
What?
But, this time he speaks the truth.
I know, I know.
Don't you move, are you a baby.
You talk foul behind you friend's back.
Not unethical, just face the facts.
Grassy, what a lousy name.
Talk of skill, can't compare with your Shanghai.
- You agree? - Of course.
Uncle when you see our hair-dresser friend.
Ask him which is better: Grassy or Shanghai?
He'll surely say: Shanghai.
Shut up! You pigs! Rats!
So, there you are! Good!
Now, be honest;
is Shanghai better than grassy?
- Is it? - Dare you say "no"!
No no... I mean yes.
You see! Uncle. You see I was right.
Sit down.
Well, since you three are so appreciative,
I myself will make the hairdo for you.
So nice, uncle.
Thank you, ying.
Hey, no entry.
You! Ungrateful pig!
You, unthankful rat.
Get lost!
Cool it! Just let us in as customers. Alright?
Don't take it so serious.
Just now we were joking.
Right. You should take jokes lightly.
Why make jokes!
What a hairdo!
Get inside.
You look grotesque.
Is the Shanghai barber misinforming you.
Not a trace of ah ying.
I gave the barber 100 bucks, he was so happy.
Is it false information.
No! I dreamed of auspicious signs last night.
I am sure of romance...
Ah ying.
- Ah ying... - What a coincidence...
- It's your Shanghai barber... - No, it is our stars.
Ying, are they your relatives?
No, they are pupils of my class.
I coach them swimming during holidays.
- Let's warm up. - Good.
Please teach us.
Let's have fun together. Good.
One, two, three...
Look, they're doing it all wrong.
They just stare at the teacher.
Who knows what they're thinking.
I know what you are thinking.
You do?
You want to "dab" ah ying.
What do you mean "dab"?
"Dab" means say hello to her.
Is that right? Yes...
Thanks, I got it.
They're cheating the teacher again. Yes.
Students...
Let's practise breathing now.
Good...
Miss, I don't know how to breathe.
Alright, I'll teach you.
Let me do it for you.
Hi, kid.
This guy doesn't know how to breathe.
That's it. It's simple.
I can hold one breath for an hour.
Just half an hour! For one breath,
I can swim across the harbour.
Liar. Don't cheat a child.
- Right. - It's all talk and no action.
Right. Can you do it?
Why not! Go ahead.
Let's test our endurance.
Let's see who will die of exhaustion.
We will have a race.
Children, you'll be our judges.
Good! Oki
ying, you be umpire.
Alright, let us watch them.
Miss, I wish to see if they break rules.
Right, go ahead.
They breathe out beautiful bubbles.
Really.
Miss. What?
They speak vulgar language.
How can you hear in water?
They growl at each other.
Miss. How is it?
They must be thirsty.
Why?
They drink at big gulps.
Really?
Teacher... yes?
They look like fish in my aquarium.
How do they like?
With protruding eyes.
How are they?
Don't press, children!
Want any drinks?
Oh, no! No! No!
Ying!
You do enjoy coaching swimming?
I love children and it is summer vacation.
I can keep fit as well.
Next month is the miss Hong Kong contest...
Miss Hong Kong.
I qualified for the semi-final.
How nice! I am an insurance agent,
I can help you to make the right decision.
You look very smart.
Just like a royalty.
Hold on, let me do it with precision...
You have used too much of your hands.
The same old trick?
Let you take a through look at ying.
You'll ruin my reputation.
Who ask you to take advantage.
He's a scum.
That's his nature.
He's always like that.
Ying, I'm ki ho yan.
I'm chan hoi sum.
You can call me big eye. Remember me.
I'm studying fashion design.
I'll be a hair stylist.
I can design an evening gown for you.
I can design the perfect hair style for you.
Let me help you.
Hey, here is five bucks for you.
Don't let me pay the bill.
Ok.
Trust me for a new hair style.
Let's go. Bill please.
Yes.
Here... thanks...
Let me...
No, I must pay.
Please don't.
Hey, don't grip so tight, I can't shuffle.
It's my turn.
Why don't you pay.
You seldom pay.
What now?
It means I pay! Why ask stupid question.
Do I have to pay you back?
Keep the change!
Yes, keep the change.
Thank you, sir.
Ah ying.
It's for you, uncle.
Next time, no flowers just cash.
I considered the whole night.
And decided...
Keep calm!
To offer you this.
Good for you?
Only two men in the world are fit for it;
one is stallon, the other one is you.
Really?
What stal...
Stallon, Rambo!
Great swordsmanship!
Yeah!
It's sharp.
He said Rambo used it.
It is highly lethal!
Touching it is disastrous!
You saw it.
Real sharp.
It's sharp. It cuts into your wallet.
I know, I've got 200 bucks only.
Even one eyebrow is worth 500.
I've got a blank check,
I'll fill in there.
It send chills to your back.
It does. I go first.
Nut!
Not so chilly now!
Daughter!
Are you fond of these three?
No, we just met a few times.
Right. Our daughter won't like common folks.
Papa, please!
Then, why did you invite them to dinner?
To manipulate them.
They flirt with ah ying.
With different excuses.
I'll make use of the three dogs.
To help ying in the beauty contest.
What, three dogs!
What do you take your daughter for?
Well,
let the dogs watch each other!
Coming!
Hi, ah ying.
You're come! Uncle!
Private collection.
You'll like it.
Oh, really.
This is for you, uncle. This is the most expensive one.
It's just a little gift. Give it to ying.
Take care of it. Ying, take care of it.
Come in and sit down.
Honey, ready for dinner. Uncle,
it's a beautiful house. Uncle, I...
Auntie. My name is puddin lai,
ying must always mention me.
Yes, you are the hair-dresser, right!
Is business good?
So so.
Auntie, it smells good.
This minced beef is good in color, smell and taste.
That's fried meatball! Go out!
Sit outside.
Auntie! Auntie!
Let me give you a hand. You don't know fried meatballs! Out!
Let me help you, auntie... Let's go.
- Have tea please. - Thank you, ying.
Puddin lai, do you excel in fung-shui,
and palmistry?
I am insurance agent, I study those
in my spare time.
Uncle, let me read your palm.
It's thick and fleshy, good palm.
You're blessed, that's why you've a pretty daughter.
A rare good palm!
Uncle, let me go with ying to her room.
To see her clothes and design a package for her.
Ying, let's go in.
No hurry, some other day.
I tried many brands of shampoo.
Can't decide the right one for my hair.
Can you help me?
Sure.
They are dry hair.
You are right, you see they split.
Quite many splits. Yes.
Split, split, split on your dead body.
Who is dead?
Oh! Your palm marks escape form death.
Which results in big riches.
That's better.
Yes.
It's all right.
Let me take good care of it.
Cut the crap.
Let's eat.
May I sit with you.
Sorry, move over.
That's my seat. Sit over here.
Auntie.
So much delicacies.
Be at home. Get started.
Cheers.
Mum.
They have longed to "dab" you for some time.
They always like to "dab" you too.
Yes "dab" your good wine.
Cheers.
Thank you for coming to "dab" our family.
Ying, watch your words!
Our pleasure!
Cheers.
Honey, drink for the occasion.
Me too! Mum, it's a happy moment, drink.
Ok, ok!
Great.
Good drinker...
Auntie, have another glass.
I can't drink much.
Doesn't matter, have another.
Drink it up.
We'll all very happy today.
I'll just drink it up.
Bravo.
Good drinker.
Please go ahead, I'll see to the fish.
Uncle, you are hospitable. Make yourselves at home.
Papa.
Mum? Auntie.
Call a crane?
Do it together.
She is real heavy.
You are useless.
Remove her, I can't breathe.
Hey, drank too much.
- Uncle, he takes too much. - Throw it back, doesn't matter.
Have some source.
Get even. Try again.
Come!
Marlboro, Marlboro.
Lemon tea, lemon tea,
no air-con, no air-con.
You lost.
The loser must drink. Drink it up.
One more time. No way!
Ok. One more chance for you.
No air-con, no air-con.
Drink?
What are you waiting for?
No drink!
You lost, you should drink.
Yes, do it.
Drink.
Silly boy.
Drink it up.
Obstinate! Come, hold him.
Open your mouth, relax.
One bit more, a little more, that's it.
Don't tease him.
That's good fun.
Dirty tricks!
Angry already? Get angry so easy?
That's not a man.
Really angry?
Not me! Uncle,
I like fun. Why angry?
What are you up to?
No angry?
It's mawkish!
So comfy, why be angry.
Can you take fun too?
Certainly.
Egg!
What for?
Stop that!
I am not angry, not at all.
Have bigger fun!
Come on, you have to do it.
Just for fun.
Go!
Second round. Be quick!
Ying!
Bravo.
Papa, that's enough.
Nobody suffocates. Continue!
Oh, damn. Uncle.
Papa!
Sorry for that, uncle.
It's you. It's sorry.
Uncle is not angry.
No problem, no problem.
Uncle's face tells he is generous and forgiving.
Ha, right, generous and forgiving.
Come, bottoms up!
Bottoms up!
Ying, let me see you home.
Good night.
You chaps can't drink. Have more.
Bye-bye.
Where is ying?
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
Uncle, we are leaving.
Main door is not there, this way.
This way.
Good-bye, uncle.
I need the toilet.
Where is the washroom?
Hold on, just press the button.
Wrong button.
Why it takes so long.
Just pull open the life door.
You first.
After you.
You don't get award for politeness.
Why hang clothes in the lift.
Who says no airing clothes in lifts?
Nonsense.
Real small lift!
So peole hang their clothes here.
Why only clothes but no trousers?
Are we there?
Push, stupid!
We arrived. Arrive where?
Repulse bay.
Caribbean sea! Mermaid!
Over there!
Let's swim there.
Breast stroke!
Freestyle.
I don't know how to swim. Give me a buoy.
A buoy!
What's happened?
My clothes?
It almost killed me.
Ying, what's the matter?
Nothing, papa, I had a bad dream.
Bad dream?
Did we...
Tell me what happened.
Are you all right?
Go!
What's now?
We'll come back for you.
Ying, don't cry.
We'll return. Yes.
Who took advantage of her?
I had no pat in anything, last right.
I slept so sound, nothing could wake me.
Can't be me. I adore her so much.
I won't do anything indecent.
We don't even know whether anything happened.
It's not you. Of course not.
And not you.
Then, it must be I.
Now that ah ying is mine, that means.
Your friend's wife.
You two should not even fancy for her.
Excuse me. I'll pay for this meal.
Now I remember.
Last night the mermaid,
and I talked very happily.
I think it was me.
Ok... l admit. It was I.
I don't want to say, but now I won't restrain.
Look, my whole body is sticky.
It is evidence of action.
You don't say. Look at my stained trousers!
Must be I.
Wait. Look here! It's all over my head.
Everyone admits quality.
Then it is gang rape!
They talk of gang rape.
What kind of youth are they?
Hi, happy!
Please, go in.
Ying, I wish...
Heavens. I've never been so faithful,
and becomes so heart-broken.
Ying paging us.
I don't like to see you again.
However I fell some changes in my body.
Take this for a test, tell me the results.
As soon as you know.
Ying.
What is this?
Perfume.
Perfume? Try it.
Very strong.
It's urine! For the test.
Why didn't you say so.
Let's go.
This is a bottle, not a barrel,
it doesn't take three to carry.
You do it tomorrow.
Me again. But, for ying, it is all right.
If the test verifies this is draft beer.
Thank heavens.
Take some urine.
Can I help you?
Urine test.
Put it on the tray.
What a coincidence! What's wrong with you?
Oh... yes... I can't urinate...
Give me a chance!
Isit v.D.?
No! See if there is precipitant in the urine.
What do you test for?
Diabetes. The usual test.
I'll do it.
Sir please.
Big eye, what really do you test for?
You're so tense.
I don't know. Whatever will be, will be.
Why so scared.
Worried for you.
Ki ho yan! Yes!
You've diabetes.
Diabetes.
Be calm. Is it serious?
Is it serious?
Ask a doctor.
Right. Go and see a doctor.
Chuk tai chung. What's the result?
Why so nosy?
Congratulations.
Congratulations! My god!
What my god! Congratulations means I...
Positive!
Positive and you congratulate me?
Be more careful from now on.
Careful? At my age?
I don't care, be it tender or not.
I'll take so far as I've got the urge.
Uncle, leave it. This laboratory may not be reliable.
Go elsewhere.
Pregnancy test?
Again!
Congratulations on diabetes. Nut!
Read the newspaper advertisements.
See who can cure diabetes.
Let's go.
What's the result?
Sugar in the urine.
Did you drink ah ying's urine,
you bastard.
What, ah ying!
How came you don't know,
I'll question them.
You three rats, who did it?
For the last time, who did it?
Torture them!
I don't want a gang rape scandal,
if you inform me of the culprit,
you'll get free,
if not, I'll break your eardrum.
Difficult choice. Break friendship or,
break eardrum.
It is your choice, who?
Yourself?
Yes or no? Did you?
Go to hell!
How is it? Sit down!
How is it? Tell us.
I am deaf!
Deaf?
Are you sure?
How did he torture you?
Can you hear?
I can't, I can't!
You can't? Never, never admit guilty!
He is ruthless.
Now what? Our turn will come.
Puddin, come in.
What's it? Who is it? Me!
Auntie asks for you.
You first. You!
No, you first.
My friend, listen to me.
Don't ever admit guilty.
Can you hear?
What? Who?
Did you do it? Talk! Did you?
Talk!
Go to hell!
Are you really so cruel?
You're more cruel.
Information or eardrum?
It is better no choice is needed.
Did you do it?
Yes or no?
Admit of not?
Thanks for not breaking my eardrum.
No break, but smack.
Now, get out.
Made foal of us.
Hey, hey uncle spared me.
What?
Tomorrow I'll register for you.
In the school for deaf & durmb.
Your foul are smells real bad.
Should have stepped asides.
You two made fool of me.
How come you know nothing?
Don't you wreck your daughter. Whatever,
abort it!
Don't!
No, I won't do it!
Hack you to pieces.
Abort or die!
Ying, run away! Quick!
Don't you run away!
You'll be prosecuted for gang rape.
Get ready for jail.
Come back.
You want her to be newspaper headline?
Quick.
Ying!
Taxi, taxi!
Follow that taxi. Quick!
Hey, stop! We are not yet in!
Step on it
driver! Be fast!
Catch up with that taxi.
Come on, faster. Alright...
Yes, it is that taxi in front.
After it...
Overtake it!
Why don't you go?
What's wrong?
Why do you stop?
Man, it is red light. My license is 11 points off.
Want my license be suspended?
We are willing to pay for any penalty.
Right. If you can catch up, we'll pay
you 100 dollars.
The license is mine, not yours.
Please!
Ok. Use you brain.
Bridy calling elephant.
What's it. Birdy?
Three passengers here request you
to wait for them.
Wait! Who are they?
Tell him, we want our baby's mother.
Please, help us.
They want their baby's mother.
Lend a hand.
She shakes her head.
Alright?
She says no.
Tell her this: Ah ying.
That night, it was not a plot.
Ying, that night, it was not a plot.
Tell her I love her till heavens rot.
He loves you till... vens rot.
What... vens rot?
Miss, this one with rotten organs.
Must be a rascal. Give him up.
The 'rotten organs' shut up! Next!
Tell her that I, puddin lai!
Smoking, no more; Gamble no more; Spindrift, no...
He says: Smoking, gambling, no... more! Spindrift...
This one is rotten too.
Unwilling to give up smoking.
Spindrift is no good husband;
next one.
Let me talk! Ying.
Hey, it's my turn.
I am no good speaker,
I feel you are unwise,
what does a woman need?
A man who loves her for life.
Now, there are 3 men who do.
You ponder that coolly.
Now you're alone,
homeless. Uncased for.
Let's find you a quiet place,
give birth to the child.
Verify the father by medical test.
One of us will care for you for life.
Let me!
Elephant, stop your car.
Let them meet.
Wait for the three rascals;
you must be out of your mind.
Not knowing how to speed, don't be driver.
Oh, no!
The three are real nice guys.
You are in luck. To hell with driving license!
Bravo!
Hey, let me alight.
No way!
For you future's sake. I won't let them get you.
Let me out!
No trace of them! Right.
What than?
Elephant, tell me your position!
I can overtake you.
I was in prince rd., when you asked.
Now I am off to lung cheong rd.
Come!
What do you want? Let me out!
Go on, hit me.
I don't allow them to catch you.
Help, help!
Bastard! Disturb my work!
Now, come out!
Come out!
Ying, don't go away!
Come, back to yourself!
Ying, you all right?
Are you all right?
Ying, you are really gorgeous!
You guys have taste; Worth risking my license.
Shut up!
Elephant!
Serve him right!
Ying, what we just said in the taxi.
Do you agree?
We do mean it. Yes!
Do you consent?
Wow! Great!
This place is a bit small.
But, for one person, I hope it is ok right?
Yes.
Ying, forget anything else.
Just concentrate on baby-making.
With whom?
Ying, I studied this place,
nothing escapes from my eyes.
This home will bring you riches,
food, clothing and many children.
Cute, isn't it?
Be careful.
What!
I'm infuriated.
Pregnancy education. Pregnancy education!
Don't you like to have a cute baby?
You call this thing cute baby?
Shame on you, queer thing!
You are cute, eh?
Look at you.
I can't pass the days in peace.
Good brothers!
Touching!
Too good to be separated!
They are a lovely couple
who want to stay together forever.
But they have to be separated.
Even gourmets.
Have never lasted such good celery with chicken.
Is this celery?
Sure. Have one good bite, ying.
For celery, we eat the stem, not the leaves.
Ignorant!
Imperial!
But, look at the green, so tempting.
That makes your mouth water.
Leave the good things for later.
Ying, it's for you.
Have a spare rib.
You guys don't know delicacies.
For good things, a little is enough.
Since it is from ah ying, I'll take it.
Happy.
Both happy!
Salty.
Vegetables in!
All charcoal!
Little bit makes it more tasty.
What is that?
Fish!
Hard like a rock.
Disgraceful!
It's fresh
the inside is edible.
See, ying says it is edible.
Eat, then?
Ah ying tells us to eat. Go ahead.
Even dog shit is good.
Don't, it is polluted.
Nowadays, sea water, everywhere is polluted.
Can't worry too much.
Don't eat it. Have vegetables.
Anything wrong with the fish? Talk!
What are you afraid of?
Can't be from the garbage bin?
Smart boy! Bang on!
You saw me eating it! Were you dumb!
Why blame me! You said just now.
That even dog shit is good. Right, ying?
Gourmet's delight!
Pig's belly and bean curd soup. Good for skin.
It tastes good.
Greed will take your life.
It's bitter!
Sour!
It's all the better; Don't waste it.
The smart man differs from an idiot.
In that the idiot feeds you with celery leave.
Making like to vomit.
What's so funny?
The smart guy makes pig's belly.
Into a delicacy.
A bonus!
That is gourmet's vomit.
Ying, don't touch that soup. Don't drink it.
Eat something else.
This is half fatty and half lean.
Ying, did I do something wrong?
Sorry. I am stupid & can't take good care of you.
No,
I am homesick.
Don't be sad. When the baby is born.
There will be a happy reunion.
You are so kind.
Kindest in the three of us?
The three of you...
No! Don't. Before the father is confirmed.
No such thing.
Ok. Ok., I'm sorry, sorry.
What's wrong?
I want tissue paper.
I have.
Yes. I...
Here...
Are you all right?
Sorry, I spoiled your shirt.
I'll clean it for you.
It's all right.
Go ahead. Breathe out!
Wait!
No more.
Then, I get nothing.
Never mind; Go on; Throw out!
Thank you.
Can I keep the clothes now?
Look at them! What are they up to.
First time here? Yes.
What's the father name?
Mr. x. Mr. x?
Oh x, anything you say.
Miss, your father!
Papa!
Uncle!
Why haven't seen you for two months.
Boarding school in the countryside.
Boarding school?
You, you, you, come here.
Get in.
Miss, better get in the shade.
Uncle!
Uncle, do we come in.
Dial 9997?
You guys shut up!
The matter is not finished.
I don't want a scandal.
Be careful! Don't let that barber know the truth.
Laugh, everybody!
Uncle, what are you up to?
Now, ying refused to abort.
That means she has to marry one of you.
The lucky man has to pay me half million U.S. dollars.
Not a cent less.
Your papa has changed.
So friendly to the three.
How about a discount of kin's.
Hold it. Money is real, kinship is shit.
60 tables in wedding banquet,
and one apartment,
only 1,300 square feet is fine.
No dry smile. Laugh.
Real funny.
Papa!
Papa, can we go home now?
Daughter, you can't go home.
You are growing bigger everyday, only 7 months more.
Try persevere it.
Let's go.
Bye, uncle.
Laugh, again, next time.
Half a million.
60 tables.
1,300 square feet.
Are you still in? Yes!
Yes!
Ying, we'll work hard for you.
Escort her home first.
Go, ah ying.
It's fate, you can't change it.
Prophet lai.
Sit please.
My friend, you have eyes like tiger's.
Prophet lai, you don't recognise me?
Oh, Mr. taxi-driver!
You escaped an accident, shout prosper afterwards.
Let me advice you how to make big fortunes.
That is fine. I take you as a living god.
Good.
You said you don't have consulting office?
But, I have a wife and a child now.
Let us go back to you.
Your brow is like the glowing sun. Yes?
But there is a tinge of black cloud.
You can't wipe it off that way.
Something may be in your way recently.
Exactly! Prophet, you're a living god.
Let me see your palm. Sure.
Work hard on the wheels...
Yes, yes!
The other one,
you'll be landlord!
Prophet lai. You work wonders!
Some mean guys want to outbid me.
Where is the property?
Connaught centre.
Good judgement! Commercial unit, good bet!
Not an unit, the whole block!
Ah..., the first time I saw you,
I knew the sky is your limit.
You're an aristocratic face.
I give you some sacred writings remember.
Put one on your chest, one on your bed,
one under the bed; Don't wet it even in bath.
When wet, it loses it's power. 3 days later.
Whoever bid against you will die.
Ah chiu! Yes!
Five thousand dollars for the prophet.
My secretary.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks, Mr. chi...
Your face is a rarity of the century.
Have a thorough look.
Ho yan, is this sausage or trousers.
Sorry, I'll do it again.
Do it right, must be finished by the morning.
You know? I know.
Why do you over-exert yourself so much?
Getting married.
Ah! Get a girl to marry you.
And a son coming soon.
A son too! Bonus for you naughty chap.
Maybe!
You nut! You are black man in black forest.
What does it mean?
All in the dark.
Is it ok? Come again. See you.
Sorry miss, we are closing up.
After finished me. Boss.
What's the matter?
Step in please.
Boss, let me do one more.
Ok.
Thank you, boss.
Fighting hard again.
Sit please.
Happy, working hard, eh?
Can't help it.
I've to shoulder up the family. Really something.
Bye-bye.
What cut you like?
A bit shorter.
Happy!
Hi, honey
so, you changed salon.
Have a kiss.
Quiet! Boss, three more jobs, please.
Ok.
We know what to do.
Sit. Ok. Let's start.
How long does it take?
Make mine first.
Why everybody looks so tried?
No. I was born healthy.
I am strong.
I've got a good heart.
We are overflowed with energy, we need a fight!
Where is the towel?
It's a nice area.
At least, the air is fresh?
- What's the matter? - Ah ying, are you alright?
Let me help you.
It kicks me. My son is so naughty.
Careful!
My dear boy,
two more months. You will come and decide our fate.
Hands off!
By that time, two fragile hearts...
Will be broken.
Don't worry, I'll give you some glue.
To mend them.
Mend your skull.
In fact, all three of you are gentlemen.
Hard-working, reliable,
and smart!
When I marry one of you.
Will you still be good friends?
We've listened to you.
We are good friends all along?
Yes, quite good.
Wow, wow your mother!
Her mother is a bitch, don't you spare her?
What kind of man are you?
Ying, you know what he is like.
Old man, I am nervous.
Feel my hand, it is like ice.
Nice to have a grandchild.
Why so tense, sit down.
You're here. Daddy, mammy.
Father-in-law, mother-in-law.
Hold it!
My grandchild doesn't have 3 fathers. Go!
Get lost! Or else I hack you to pieces,
and feed the dogs.
All right. Go home first!
Go!
Put those down. Go now.
Mammy!
What?
This is my blood type.
If it is proven that the son is mine.
I'll buy you a big present.
Mammy, if it is mine, I'll kneel and serve you tea.
- Iron proof of father and sod, mammy. - Mum.
Is that floor show? Go!
Go away, go!
How many blood types are there?
Two. Male and female.
Which are these?
This... english; What does it say?
This is odd, all are a type!
All the gods in heaven.
It must be a son.
So I expect.
Thanks for taking care of ah ying so far,
how about christening for my son.
You're dreaming.
How about plum lai.
Plum stone.
Mammy!
Mammy is here.
Son or girl?
What is it?
Does it look like me?
Of the same blood type?
Mammy, tell us.
Mammy, tell us please.
It's a son.
Wow, great. I knew it!
It's an illegitimate son. Pa sold it to godfather.
Sold my son!
Going to Canada tomorrow.
Take it back.
Godfather has money and power.
Don't fancy taking it back.
Mammy?
Go away!
Mammy!
What, now?
We must stick together for once.
Ok.
United.
Nut!
Come on...
Milk for you, son.
This way brings luck.
It's a wall. Right.
Use your brain. Climb!
Right.
You make so much trouble. Naughty dog.
Run quickly.
Where are you son?
Big eye boy. Big nose boy.
North-west.
Let's go.
Big eye boy.
Big eye boy. Big nose boy.
Go!
Are you Superman? Find ways.
South-east, impossible.
I was right.
Little puddin, here I come.
Good baby, nice baby.
You'll fly tomorrow.
They sky is smiling.
Here comes the piggy.
Morning in heavenly village is so nice.
But something big is happening.
The 4-eyed monster is causing trouble.
It was an accident.
It's a joke. Forget it.
Don't be nosy. Go to bed.
I am dying.
Boo-bee I come.
God gives me power.
Damned.
Run.
Why? He-man!
Go inside! Otherwise there will be chaos.
Dr. slump, were you struck by lightning?
'Boo-bee" "boo-bee" of course, I nearly fainted.
What's the matter?
Mirror's reflection will betray you, idiot!
Preserved plum.
Transform to Superman.
Fly, fly. Great.
Superman, fly.
Superman, you did it again.
Superman, come back here.
This way, quick. You'll get lost in the fog.
Not this way, that way.
Send him to sleep!
Doctor. Superman is sleeping!
Go on with your studies.
Save him by artificial respiration.
The phone is ringing.
Hello. Heavenly village is sleeping. Call tomorrow.
What bad timing!
I'll take it! Everyone is sleeping. Troublesome!
Baby?
No baby. Boo-bee. Superman is awake!
We can go on with the game.
Not in bed yet?
Hi, pretty, hold on a minute.
A kiss.
Kiss.
Let me do it.
Evil to evil.
Still more.
Funny!
Pass to me. Funny enough!
Hold it!
Let go!
It's my son.
I am done for. Take care of my son.
Arrest them all.
Son!
Give it back!
Ah keung. Rush the baby to hospital.
Quick.
Go to the hospital.
Miss...
Ying, come quick to baptist hospital.
Tell you everything later. Hurry!
If anything happens to my son, you...
Your son?
He is my flesh and blood.
I bought it.
Signed in lawyer's office.
You...
Your money, big deal!
Here's the doctor.
How is it?
It is suffering from concussion.
I must operate at once.
The father please sign.
I'll sign...
I am the legal father.
Even if the baby survived, it will be retarded.
Idiot! They are the real kin, sign!
Retarded child! No control of everything.
Let me sign. Probably becomes vegetable child.
I prefer a cabbage. Vegetable!
I'll sign.
Son, pa and ma will care for you.
Love you forever. Thanks doctor.
Why rush for everything.
Have you thought it over? Can't care for yourself.
Son, dead!
Son.
A doll!
If it was real, imagine going into my house?
You think they would let you in?
Back to you. Where is my son?
Ying! Son!
Son!
Good boy.
Just my replica.
You're joking.
Daddy. My part is finished now.
I must report duty, otherwise I'll be fired.
By the superintendent.
Ah, it is a plot to make fun on us.
Not fun. It's my plan to test you.
You three love ah ying the same,
and of the same blood group. All 'a' type.
Queer type!
All 'a' type. Big eye boy.
Big eye boy, you are the kindest,
so devoted to ying. Marrying you,
make me feel secure.
Woman! Hold it. Until there is the flat.
60 tables, 1/2 a million dollars,
you can meet only once a month.
Shut up! Have the wedding next month.
The number of tables doesn't matter.
Really, mother?
Any complaint?
No! Come with me.
Son, call your daddy. Call daddy.
Lost the last minute. Heaven's will!
You're lucky. Big eye.
You two cheer up. You're still good friends.
Right! Of course.
Son, this is big uncle, that is second uncle.
Who does he look like?
Such big nose, it looks...
Ah! Resembles me. It belongs to ying and me.
Ying, we shall have a squad of big eye boys.
Are you capable?
We'll see.
Ok.
Have a hair-cut. No way.
And you.
Help! Don't run.
Daddy...
Daddy, brother wants to cut my hair again.
Don't do that.
Nobody lets me to cut.
Last time, your lousy cut.
Made me the laughing stock for 3 months.
I am laughed at too.
Laugh at you, why?
My nose is big, eyes small, I don't look like you.
They say I look like uncle chan...
Don't mind what people say, you're my dear son,
daddy loves you the same.
Mammy.
Come on, granny's here.
Baby, come to granny.
Let grandma hold you.
Come, give grandma a kiss.
Ying, daddy.
Coffee please.
Come here, ying.
What's the test result?
You guess.
No need to test. Ying never disappoints you.
Wow, we have another child.
Viva mammy.
Son.
Ying is having your sixth child.
Bearing a child is real tough, you know?
I know, that's why I love ying so much.
You should, you should.
Daddy, you should be happy too;
the flat, 1/2 a million, all delivered.
I am happy. No complain at all.
But, if there is a big yacht,
we can enjoy on the sea, right?
Big yacht. No problem.
You can afford it.
How about buying a big yacht?
Good! Bravo!
You're the best son-in-law.
Thank you, dad.
Put it in my name.
Yours again? Mine again.