(Brazil)
Two years ago,
Superintendent Hong Do Heng  of CIB was murdered.
To protect his undercover agents,
he deleted their files from  his computer before he was killed.
And the Police lost contact  with the agents.
When the Police recovered the files,
they started to track down  the agents on the field
until everyone has been accounted for.
Out of the way!
Not again!
Go home!
Sorry...
Move aside!
Lunatic!
Get in!
I'm stuck!
Are you done yet?
Will you hurry up?
I can't explain this at  the roadblock up ahead.
You said the job was not dangerous.  I almost died!
I never said that.
I said it's not too dangerous.
If you can't hear,  how can you be an undercover?
If you're not happy,
we should break up.
- What did you say?  - Break up!
What?
Break up!
No need. I'll screen you out.
No need to get huffy.
Thank God!
Godfather is watching out for me.
Or I'd be dead by now.
Godfather,
I'll offer you joss sticks when I go home.
I want extra loading after this.
- Why is that?  - I'm risking my life!
You're not the only one.
Give that back!
I hurt my butt.
I deserve extra loading.
What would a crab say to a crab stick?
What?
Quit your act!
What line of work are you in?
It's part of the package.  I can't write in the report
you need loading because  you scraped your butt?
More junk mail!
Hong's code?
What is that?
(Have been looking for you)
Hong's secret code.
Find out who he is.
(Who are you?)
He said he's Blackjack,  one of Hong's agents,
and that there's no
new handler after Hong died.
Only Hong's agents
know the code?
That means someone is still missing.
(Day after tomorrow at 1900...) what's that?
(Criminal Intelligence Bureau (CIB) Control Room)
Folks,
we have an urgent operation.
We need to find someone
called Blackjack.
Age, gender, height,  nationality and race...
are unknown.
We only have a date and coordinates.
Day after tomorrow at 1900.
Luk, give me the coordinates.
Hong Kong Harbor Hotel.
Tung Yau Group's
new investment division
is hosting a cocktail party  at 1900 that day.
(Hong Kong Harbor Hotel)
I'm sorry!
Hello? It's me.
Don't you start with me!
I won't. Only you know the code.
I need your help.
I only want
to help find the missing agent.
Control calling,
Blackjack may not be a person.
Can be an object or a lead.
Don't overlook any details.
I.T. confirmed Hong had
a file called Blackjack.
But the data was corrupted beyond repair.
(Tung Yau Group's investment division)
The opening ceremony
will now begin.
Let's have our Chairman  Mr. Lam Tung Yau on stage
to say a few words.
What happened?
Don't push! I'm pregnant!
Are you OK? Can someone answer me?
The parachute is a gift.
Pick one of the two buttons.
Blue...
No, better choose red.
I picked blue.
Fine!
Call my phone. Take over the control car.
Yes, Sir!
Skiing at night?
Hey! Come on!
You didn't tell me you changed your plan.
Are you affected?
Not really.
Right down my alley.
Watch it!
The chicks will show up if I pay them.
My dad's new secretary is a knockout.
Tell her to be here or she's fired.
Park the car.
Is he your friend?
Yellow Ferrari up ahead...
Alpha Fox 3882.
Turned onto Locival Street  from Kong Hing Road.
Team C, reel it in.
You were there to pull a prank.  Did you rob someone?
Where did the cops come from?
Team D, 9 o'clock. Intercept him!
Yes, Sir!
Suspect heading west on Connaught Road.
Looks like someone wants to appeal.
What's the bet?
All in!
All in?
The cop is aggressive.
Luckily I have a contingency plan.
All in.
My money is on you to win. Pay up!
Where did you get this?
Lifted it from Lam Tung Yau.
After I sell it, I'll buy you abalones.
Not interested.
How about your favorite Ultraman toy?
I'll bid one for you online.
Only because you begged me.
This one is OK.
Thank you.
No wonder you're in management.
You had to do the job yourself.
See? You're in the spotlight.
It's included in my salary.
That reminds me...
I told you the wiring gear was not ready,
but you played with it anyway.
Luckily you gave him the parachute.
I haven't tried it myself.
You could have died.
Here's your share. Buy yourself a toy.
What's this?
Rent?
Who's counting now?
Give it back!
You really can't resist tooting  your own horn.
Don't be so petty!
Boss! Master Shiu!  Mr. Kwok called a meeting.
Let's go.
But we have to eat first.
We'll show up 2 hours later.
Grab my jacket, OK? Thanks.
Who did this?
You're busy.
Just finish it. It's a small bowl.
We're in a hurry.
Want some coffee?
Goodd idea!
Siu Ying, get us some coffee.
OK!
Who the hell are you?
Go get some coffee. I'll be right with you.
Siu Ying, call me after the meeting.
OK!
Give him a big hand for the flying trapeze.
You want an applause? There you have it.
Scoot over!
You want an applause?
Or get arrested?
Sorry I'm late.
Now that the cops are onto us,
we're making a lot less money.
Originally, I prepared a report for you.
But I guess you're not interested.
Let me give you the gist of it.
The cops never messed with us  for over 3 months.
Assume we have zero income for 3 months,
even counting all the overhead,
it comes to 2% of the profits
I made for the company in the past 3 years.
The amount is so small,  I won't bother with the details.
Any questions?
It was so fucking unnecessary.
Just kidnap Lam Tung Yau's
wife and son.
Why bother with this?
Times are different now.
We should do our part
and help the Police maintain law and order.
The key is
to shut down Lam Tung Yau's business  as soon as it opens.
He wouldn't dare tread on our turf again.
Good job, Lam.
I should get going.
Call me if you need me.
Meeting is adjourned!
Hello, Mr. Tung!
Ming,
no wonder you told me  to sell short on Tung's stocks.
The stock price plunged like the waterfall.
I gained back what he conned from me
and a few times over.
About the plan...
I know Lam was the mastermind.
He has guts and wits.
I'm impressed.
Right...
Now I know who  to send to Brazil for the deal.
Send Lam.
I have confidence in him.
I know the old fossils will give you hell.
Those who are unproductive always complain.
I have it all planned out.
But the cops showed up after just 1 minute.
You suppose we have a mole among us?
After you.
What about the mole?
Go!
Make sure you don't call me lazy.
The arm came off.
Fix it.
Inspector Q,
Lam Tung Yau wants a piece
of Tak Mou's drug business.
We think someone  wants to teach him a lesson.
OCTB brought them in for questioning.
Where were you last night  between 7 and 10p.m.?
Working out at the company gym.
At night?
No offense,
but if you're higher up on  the corporate ladder,
you'll realize
it's not that unusual.
Who can testify for you?
Fai...
This is Inspector Q from CIB.
Don't talk to him like he's a punk.
The guy in the suit wants respect
because he thinks he's educated.
Be polite.
Make him feel good about himself.  Then you make him talk.
Of course, you're the boss.
You can work out any time you like.
Yes, butter up to him.
Let it go to his head.
He's praising you?
HKU? You must be very smart.
Ask him what he did after graduation.
You dropped out, but you had good grades.
What did you do for a living?
Sightseeing.
Don't you have any say?
He's going in circles.  He's hiding something.
Keep digging.
What was your first job?
You're busy listening and asking questions.
Let him do the asking.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lam.
I've been so busy today  I haven't had lunch.
So my colleagues filled in for me.
Wow, you have an IQ of 140.
But you seem to have trouble  making conversation.
You're not answering the questions.
CIB?
A nosy bastard!
He's out of line,
doing OCTB's job.
You must be an asshole.
Bingo!
I am an asshole.
But we're just doing our jobs.
Helping each other out, like a family.
Unlike the criminals who pass the buck.
It's actually very simple.
Work with us, confess
and we all go home on time.
Are you shitting me?
Through a two-way mirror
and an earpiece, you ask a few questions
and you can crack the case?
Don't be so lazy!
You ruined the reputation of  all civil servants!
Folks, you heard the taxpayer's complaint.
Let's be more positive.
Tell everyone to get more paper.
Whenever Mr. Lam decides to cooperate,
fill up those notepads and send him home.
I'm taking off. See you tomorrow.
When you first started to question me,
and I was doing this,
did you notice
I projected a certain mood?
Never mind. Carry on.
Come over to Mui Kee.
Happy birthday to you...
Thank you...
Here's to your health and smile!
Give Uncle a kiss.
Why am I an uncle?
Go kiss the kid.
Why? Are you shy?
I knew it.
I'm going to China soon  and won't be around.
Since it's your birthday,  we should celebrate,
and you can see Mandy.
Then why didn't they bury you  when you were born?
Mandy, it's late.
You should be in bed.
Or you won't grow up to be a K-pop star.
You want to be a K-pop star?
You like kam-sa-ham-nida?
I just doggy-bagged some abalones.
Finish them before you go to bed.
- OK.  - Auntie Mui...
Yeah!
Give me a hug.
Here... have some soup.
Give me a kiss.
Why don't you let her be your godchild?
Don't you like her?
I do. I plan to marry her  when she grows up.
Guess what my birthday wish is this year.
I want to go to Brazil.
To learn the samba?
Well?
Boss!
They're coming. Run!
Why did you come back?
I'm the Boss. I can't abandon you.
Run! This massage parlor is not safe.
Without your help back then,
I think
I'm probably still working for you now.
Don't say that!
But when it comes to drugs,
I can't make any promises.
You'll hurt my feelings  if you keep talking.
Cheers!
I have a magic trick for your birthday.
Again?
Cheers!
That's it!
If only the car was slower...
Watch it again.
Yes, Sir!
Well?
Got another message from Blackjack.
What did he say?
In an hour at 1400.
I'm sending you the coordinates now.
OK!
Luke, check this out.
On Estrada Flor de Lótus, Macau.
Tak Mou Group has a hotel there.
Get over there now.
In an hour? I won't make it.
They don't want you to call backup.
Go now.
I get seasick.
I'll personally throw in a big present, OK?
I'm still shaken up from last time.
I guarantee it's huge... I mean super big.
Can you hear me?
(Macau, China)
Blackjack, I love you!
Settle down, OK?
I'm getting into my character, OK?
Break up if you can't stand me.
Your dream will come true
when we find Blackjack.
Come on, Blackjack...
show your face.
Here...
(The pool)?
What pool?
T...
What are you babbling?
...back? What is that?
Change into your T-back and go to the pool.
On the double!
Are you shitting me?
Hey... are you wearing a dress?
Where's the T-back?
I won't flash my fabulous behind for you.
It's not about doing me a favor.
You have a job to do.
Blackjack wants T-back by the pool.
He must have a reason.
Play by ear.
(Behind me)?
Tea bag?
You can't tell tea bag from T-back?
He screwed up, not me.
I know the code backwards.  Who knows who he is?
I can be so charming...
My charm is oozing out.
Madam!
Please move.
Madam, he took off. Follow him.
(See you in the casino)
They have a casino?
Chill...
Hey... get back to work!
Wait for me, I'll be back.
Morse code?
I...
M...
B...
J...
(I am Blackjack.)
It's really him.
Where did he go?
Find him! Hurry!
You've been staring at me long enough.
I like to look at good looking men.
Is that a crime?
SM look in broad daylight?
Have you tried it?
The cramps?
What are you doing?
You're molesting me.
Obviously.
Should I let you carry on?
Yes, keep it up.
Don't stop!
Yes!
I can't believe I went along with it
and let you molest me.
More Morse code?
You reek of plastic,
and you spread your legs too willingly.
You're too hard to swallow.
You're kidding!
Is your butt enjoying it so much
you didn't feel anything?
Go after him!
Not in your life!
Room 3308?
Over that way!
Listen to me, my name is not Ding  if I don't triple the loading.
Wrong room, Miss.
Inspector Q, the guy is a pervert.  He wants a threesome.
What the hell?
Why did you stick your head out?
You little bitch! I'll kill you!
Forget it!
Stop it...
Stop!
(Shenzhen, China)
Run, Boss!
Run!
Lam, Shiu is injured.
Take him back to Hong Kong.
It's been a long day.
Boss, I have something to say.
It's OK. What is it?
We're not just your bodyguards.
You saved our lives.
Next time I tell you to run,
you must listen.
Very well.
Hello?
What took you so long?
Wrong number.
Hello?
You conned me to Macau.
I thought I'd have a good time.
But I almost died.
I have yet to draft a will.
What for? You have no family.
What do you want to say?
Who'd be interested?
Nothing!
I won't tell you anything.
I'm not talking about what's on your mind.
I'm talking about funeral arrangements.
I don't care. I want more loading.
Worker's compensation and medical expenses.
No problem. Anything you want.
Seriously...
Text Blackjack
and set up a meeting tonight.
Any last words?
I still owe you a big present.
Thank you, OK?
That's better!
Where to?
Not the massage parlor. We're screwed.
We're definitely screwed.
Damn!
I just met her in Macau. What is it?
Here's her phone.
What's this?
Text Blackjack.
Set up a meeting tonight.
Promotion for my foot massage parlor.
Competition is tough.
I need ideas to keep my customers.
It's a link to a 30% off coupon.
There's nothing.
I made a typo, OK?
There's probably no signal in here.
What's going on, pal?
Let me go.
- Staying mad makes you ugly.  - I'm still mad.
Did you do this?
No...
Who ordered the hit on us?
You obviously don't know  the fate of a traitor.
Start talking or you'll bury  your family with you.
Now that you know it's a mistake,
can I go now?
I checked the CCTV.
A man was following you at the casino.
There's something fishy about you.
People follow me all the time in Yaumatei.
Is it a crime to be popular?
Please let me go.
You obviously made a mistake.
No mistake.
Put it down.
I know exactly who and what you are.
Hong Kong Police.
Undercover agent for CIB.
Ding Siu Ka.
Long time no see.
Surprise!
Miss me?
Not me.
Brother Foon Hei.
Mr. Kwok, $1B is a lot of money.
I want to know how big your appetite is.
Sorry about this.
I followed you here after our meeting.
I didn't expect to see my old acquaintance.
How careless of you!
I can't believe
I picked up a mole,
of all people.
Kwok Ming didn't suspect you.
He obviously ordered the hit.
I know.
He's a petty man. Don't be such a show-off.
Did you suspect me?
If there comes a day
I found out you betrayed me.
What do you want me to do?
If there comes a day
I found out you're a mole.
What do you want me to do?
We'll see.
Who is this Brother Foon Hei?
He used to be a major  drug dealer in Hong Kong.
Rumor has it he was dead.
Someone saw him in Myanmar  in the past 6 months.
He's tight with drug lords in SE Asia.
Be careful in Brazil.
Gotta go!
(Handler wants to meet at 0200.)
How do you know about Ding?
Hong asked me to save her before.
You didn't show up  at the Tung Yau cocktail,
and killers showed up in Macau.
If you were in my shoes,
what should I think about you?
I didn't know the Boss changed his plan.
I also didn't know about the hit in Macau.
Why was there no
new handler after Hong died?
The Police gave up on me?
Your data file was damaged beyond repair.
You can't prove anything you said.
Proving my identity is your job.
Where is Ding?
Where is she now?
Dead.
Chum Foon Hei shot her
after Kwok Ming took her.
It was my fault
she blew her cover.
I'm sorry.
What case were you on?
Tak Mou Group.
I'll be in touch with the dealers soon.
Remember these numbers. Call me.
Yes, Sir!
You suspect me?
One is texting and the other  is reading at the same time.
That's too much of a coincidence.
Even if Shiu is clean,
the girl looks suspicious.
Get rid of her.
A guided massage tour?
(Brazil)
Luke, what have you got?
Here...
At 0920,
Shiu was taken from the parking lot.
Interestingly enough...
at 0945, armed men broke into his flat.
Different parties!
What the hell?
Relax!
Just want something to drink!
OK? Thank you.
(Held hostage in Brazil.  Will meet dealer, need backup)
(Stay on the phone, we'll find you.)
Who's paying for the massage?
Whoever gets out first.
Superintendent Wong.
Any word from the Security Bureau?
Yes.
The Brazilian Police are still  locating the phone.
CIB undercover agents are often killed
not because they're not good enough,
or the baddies cheat,
but because back up couldn't  get there fast enough.
Help me out, Superintendent Wong!
Please hurry!
Show me the stuff!
Luke,
put it on the speakers.
Nice! Transfer the money.
You picked up!
Even the Brazilians can't kill you.
I really admire you.
Too bad your time is up.
Do you know your mistake?
You're too greedy.
Money is not an issue.
Take it. I can't spend it all.
But you want power.
You want to replace me.
Don't be such a bitch!
Your plan really worked.
You get the money and the goods.
That's so obvious!
With you out of the way,
I can pin everything on you.
Luckily I didn't kill you last time,
or this won't work.
In your next life, wise up.
That's how you extend your shelf life.
But this time, you're finished.
No, you are, Mr. Chairman.
A narrow mind makes life  difficult for others.
A narrow vision can get yourself killed.
Greed is normal,
but overdoing it will piss people off,
especially Mr. Tung.
He arranged this
just to see how big your appetite is,
and how much you can swallow.
I'm sure
you took the goods last time.
Ming, so it was you.
Ming, I already told you
to hire reputable hitmen.
Or at least don't be stingy.
Have fun.
Enjoy the ride.
Lam!
I have the goods.
Wrap it up!
Right!
Forget the massage parlor, go get laid.
Get out!
Who are you?
That day with Lam Tung Yau  and the chick in Macau.
It wasn't the first time  you called the cops.
Well?
You have nothing to say?
Yes, I'm a cop.
I can't choose who I am,
but I can choose who I save.
We're brothers... right here!
If you can't feel it,  anything I say is bullshit.
You want me dead?
None of this is necessary.
Shoot me!
If I hadn't taken you to Brazil,
Kwok Ming would have killed you.
You asked me if you caught  me betraying you,
what I would want you to do.
My answer is...
it has never crossed my mind.
I never intend to betray you.
Now that Kwok Ming is dead,
I can spy on the cops for you.
We'll call the shots from now on.
And be a double-crosser?
Using the cops and the triad to get ahead?
That's so typical of you!
So typical!
I am Blackjack.
Show me the stuff.
OK, Cart noodles sold out.
Copy! Closing time!
Godfather!
Thanks for bringing him back to me.
I owe you a present.
I always deliver.
Don't be silly!
You should be happy. Don't cry.
Brother Foon Hei is my senior.
I went undercover more than 10 years ago.
Then my handler was taken out.
He told me before he died the dealers  had put up a reward to find the mole.
I had no choice
but to delete my own file.
Nobody knows he's a cop.
He begged me to take him back.
No?
I saved your
ass 3 years ago.
He's bragging.  Playing dead is my strong suit.
What were you doing at the reservoir?
Q told me he had lost contact with you.
We suspect Kwok Ming took you.
Long time no see!
If it's true, he will kill you.
So I must beat him to it.
What about Blackjack?
That reminds me...
Blackjack doesn't know you're alive.
You must stay here.
Eat, sleep and recuperate.
Stay put until the whole thing  blows over, OK?
How nice of you!
- I have something for you.  - What?
This should do it for your mental  and physical needs.
What is it?
No masking for breakfast,  masking for lunch.
What do you take me for?
Quit your act!
It's boring to be alone.
You're at that wolfish age...
Wolf your ass!
What are you laughing at?
How sweet!
What about my needs?
You're on your own.
That's no fun!
Shiu and Lam both claim to be Blackjack.
Who's the real one?
Shiu's parents were doctors.
While he was in Form 1,
he studied Form 6 Maths.
At 15, he went to Europe with his parents.
They were killed in a car accident.
There was nothing on him after that
until Tak Mou.
Counting the years. He should have  started 3 years earlier than Lam
but Lam surpassed him.
Shiu knows Hong's code and saved my life.
Lam knows about Blackjack.
Where is that?
Lam's flat.
I just thought of something.
Once I met with Hong...
Showing off?
My son taught me.
He's at the center
and I can protect him.
I got something.
4 months ago,
someone hacked into  Hong's computer for 2 minutes.
He hacked into
and corrupted the Blackjack file
and the decoding table for Hong's code.
We overlooked something.
Shiu runs the online casino at Tak Mou.
He's an I.T. expert.
He hacked into the Police server.
He knew we lost contact with Blackjack
and couldn't reinstate his identity.
So he posed as him.
Why did he take such risks?
What do you think?
You said Lam surpassed him.
A gambler
hates to lose.
He wants to use our intel  on the drug dealers,
so he can beat Lam.
If he's after the biggest gain,
robbing the dealers  would have been quicker.
Lam is our guy.
The real undercover.
Shiu is only a hacker,
an imposter out to rob the baddies.
Mr. Tung wants to meet me tomorrow night.
He wants to discuss  the drug deal tomorrow night.
Allow me to introduce
my new right-hand man and new partner.
Cheers!
Know why I only do drugs
and not the other vices?
Because I like it.
You're not laughing.  You don't like my joke?
You're a college grad and you don't get it?
A college grad should have a bright future.
Why didn't you become a cop?
What for? Justice?
I need to make a living.
They use posters of the God  of Wealth for Chinese New Year.
Not a cop.
Good point!
Eat, don't let the food get cold.
Come on!
Brother Foon Hei, except for your money,
I know nothing else about you.
Kwok Ming's thugs...
NG Pak...
Wait...
good... and action!
Closer!
Look into the camera!
Smile!
Fuck!
We're eating. Get rid of the blood.
If you want a piece of the action,
I like to have the goods on you.
What do you think?
You're too old to look cute.
Brother Foon Hei,
honesfly,
I suspected you.
What?
You want to know why?
I'll tell you.
It goes back to when I first started out.
You see... someone had the goods on me,
and ordered me to kill for them.
A complete stranger.
Later on, I found out her name was...
...Karina.
How did I know?
She was on the phone when she was dying.
The person on the other end  was calling her name.
Karina! Karina!
I knew then her name was Karina.
Karina!
It was my first hit and I was scared.
When I stabbed her,
her blood splashed all over me.
I stabbed her repeatedly  until she was dead.
Guess what
I was feeling when I saw  the blood on the floor?
No different from killing a fish.
Except...
she was staring at me
and gave me the creeps.
What did I do?
I gouged out her eyes.
Brother Foon Hei,
I checked up on you.
Your ex-wife's name was Karina.
I find that too coincidental.
My wife's name was Katrina, not Karina.
If you killed my wife,
you wouldn't be here snorting drugs.
I should be grateful
your wife's name is Katrina, right?
Here's to us!
Cheers!
How could you stand that?
I should thank you.
I glanced at you when  I was about to strike.
You reminded me of who I am.
Hello?
Q
I hit a dead end.
Lam doesn't trust me anymore.
I decided to have a showdown.
No! Put that thought on hold.
For two reasons...
One, you're all we've got.  Nothing must happen to you.
Two,
we bugged Lam's flat.
We'll soon get the scoop. You should wait.
We'll contact you when we find out anything
and plan our next move.
OK?
Sure!
This international drug cartel
has a major deal in the works.
According to the intel from CIB,
Shiu intends to intercept the deal.
NB should stand by.
(Shiu ready to move. Standby for the arrest.)
Looking for me?
Here's a plane ticket to Taiwan
and a house key.
Everything is all set up.
Someone trustworthy will go with you.
You can start over.
I bought you a ticket to Malaysia.
Everything is also set up.
Enough of this madness!
No.
What's wrong with a life of  fast cars and women?
Give it a rest.
I won't let anyone stop me.
Who's that behind the door?
One of the 10 Outstanding Young Persons?
So what if you could get in?
You want me to leave?
I see.
Cart Noodles, where is my visual?
Cart Noodles...
Get up!
Get in!
- Get in!  - Go, Boss!
Let go!
Work with me!
Drive...
Ding, go!
I'm fine.
What the hell! Call it in!
While his bullet is jammed,
make a run for it.
Don't mind me.
1... 2...
Go! What are you waiting for?
Easy...
No rush...
Chill!
Do you know why
AV is free in Heaven?
Because what we do...
Heaven is watching.
Hang in there! You'll be fine.
Hang in there!
Listen to me.
I don't think I'll make it home today.
Look after Cutie for me.
There's dog food in the kitchen.
Walk her after you feed her.
No more stupid gags from me again.
This time, we're really splitting up.
No!
Not if it kills me!
No way...
Copy.
Word from NB:
they made a bust.
But Shiu didn't show up.
Tell OCTB to find him.
Siu Ying is dead.
How could you do it?
That's nice!
You want to bury your godchild too?
Go ahead!
All these years,
in order to keep Mandy out of harm's way,
you asked Auntie Mui to look after her.
You're such a wonderful father.
You want her to live?
Kill yourself.
Have a heart. You're a cop.
You've always been careful.
No other cops could put a tail on you.
We bugged Lam's flat.
We'll soon get the scoop.
You should wait.
How did Q manage?
Unless you collaborated with him.
Keep talking.
You asked me what  I want you to do if I'm the mole.
What if you're the mole?
We're brothers... right here!
If you can't feel it,  anything I say is bullshit.
You said that.
10 seconds.
Keep your word.
A blank.
Back then when you secretly let Mandy go,
I knew you're not a bad person.
What we do has nothing to do with her.
I'd love to have her as a godchild.
But I don't want people to know
she has a godfather like me.
But you're different.
You're a real cop.
You never considered seizing the drugs?
Yes.
I hired someone.
But I find something fishy  between you and Q.
So I decided against it.
I agree.
About Siu Ying...
I trust you didn't do it.
The cops
busted my goods.
I don't care who the mole is.
I want him dead.
The Brazilian captain is cool.
Who's afraid of who?
He's the back scrubber at the sauna.
Claims to know qigong.
Get rid of him and we'll go get a massage.
Hurry up!
Hang in there, buddy.
It won't be the first time.
Lam told me
everyone has a choice.
CIB in the front,
NB in the back.
Take your pick.
Can't decide?
I'll do it for you.
Keep the eyes.
No, go to hell!
Before I forget...
The CIB assault team is over there.
The NB made a move yesterday morning,
busted an international drug cartel
and arrested its mastermind Tung Pak Ho,
who was involved in money  laundering and hired hits.
The Police indicated the bust
was the result
of a deep undercover operation.
I glanced at you when  I was about to strike.
You reminded me of who I was.
I am a cop.
(Little Bok at 6 months)
(Little Bok, recital champ)
(Little Bok in Form 1)
I don't get it.
Who'd admit to being an undercover?
I'd love to be Little Bok again.