Since time immemorial,
wolves had hunted sheep for food.
The sheep community experienced great
suffering from the wolves'  constant fhreat.
One day
one wolf ancestor invented
a special method of cooking.
The Mutton Hotpot was first launched
by the wolves with much aplomb.
Just as the voracious wolves were getting smug
all the young sheep disappeared
suddenly from the grassland.
The sheep ancestors had succeeded
in cultivating white cabbage for food!
Thus,the sheep didn't need to risk their
lives foraging and grazing inthe grass land.
For a thousand years,the struggle continued
unabated between the wolves and sheep.
The wolves'  burning desire
to savor the infamous Mutton
Hotpot was kept very much alive.
Tonight,we attack the Sheep Village.
We are going to kill all the fat sheep.
To commemorate the millennial anniversary
of the Mutton Hotpot's launch!
Dip-boiled Mutton!
Honey,this is my 214th promise to you.
I will definitely capture 214
young fat sheep for you.
Capture 10,000 sheep if you can
but please return home safely.
Honey,we will surely have tasty
mutton to celebrate Valentine Day.
Daddy can Fly!!!
Daddy can Fly!!! Daddy can Fly!!!
Let's begin the celebrations!
To the accomplishment of cultivating
white cabbage for a millennium!
Wah! Ha,ha
Ha,ha,my dear little sheep,
How are you guys doing?
Watch out! It's Wolffy. Run!
Don't look so surprised.
Why don't all of you celebrate
the holidays at my house.
Ha,ha,ha,ha
Let's see where can all of you hide. He,he...
Village Chief! What should we do?
Secret weapon!!
What kind of a joke is this?
Hey,get out of my way.
Don't obstruct my plan to capture the Sheep.
Ha,ha,ha,ha
Who are you?
Heh!
Idiot,he is the super-deadly......
Super-invincible Chairman of the World
Animal Foundation for the Tiger Year.
The majestic Lord Japper.
Kung Hei Fat Choy!! Kung Hei Fat Choy!!
Demolish our houses and still want
to greet us Happy New Year???
Stop! Stop now!
It's good to demolish them
to build an amusement par.
Don't you know how much
fun it is to play in a park?
Amusement park? How big is it?
Super-humongous.
The boundary of the amusement
park will be marked by the point
Where this piece of stone hits the ground.
Wow?
Ha,ha,ha.
Cool Leopold
Great,Let's begin!.
No!
It is so wonderfull.
I want to sit in the Roller Coaster.
I want to ride the Merry-Go-Round,
where do we buy the tickets?
What tickets?
All of you are the amusement
park's working staff.
Un!
Get back to work!
Lord Japper is very kind.
The amusement park is
adopting a 2-hour shift system.
Thank goodness,we will finish our work shift soon.
Oh! You have misunderstood me.
The 2-hour shift system means all of
you only get 2 hours to eat and rest.
What? This is cruelty to animals!
This is unfair?
You want to argue with
Lord Japper abouf fairness?
Are you threatening us?
We want fairness!
Fairness! Fairness! Fairness!
Ha,ha. You want us to be fair,no problem.
Then I will treat you fairly now.
First,Let me show you what I mean by fairness.
Second,All of you listen to me.
Is there a third option?
Yes.
I am not a house,then how do I demolish it?
My friend,can you see it clearly.
Big Humphrey,you are really humpy bumpy now.
Ha,ha,Happy,you have got what you deserved.
If you don't go to hunt the sheep now,
you won't live till tomorrow.
Honey,please don't be mad
withme,I will go tonight.
How dare you disturb the home
of Wolffy,Lord of the grass land
are you tired of living?
My Lord Japper,see how
breezy and airy is this castle.
Yes,very suitable for a public toilet!
Alright.
Where should we live?
I am very sorry,I have not thought about it yet.
Guards!
Wait a second.
Are you planning to usurp my castle?
You have to first ask my relatives!
Brothers,some strangers are
trying to usurp my castle.
Would you let them?
Sure!!!!
Did you hear me?
What! Uncle Avidor,Gildot
and Boxtor and dear cousins!
Hey,are we not relatives!
We must accept sound reasoning,
and not just favor our relatives.
Honey,what should we do now?
Lord Japper had shown us how fair
he was when he visited our homes .
Show us how fair you
are,show us how fair you are.
You want me to show you how fair I am?
Huh,look like if I don't show my prowness today
all of you will not know how powerful I am.
Honey,please leave with Howie.
I don't want him to witness
any physical violence.
Goodbye,Uncle!!
Mommy!!
What is Daddy going to do?
Daddy is going to......
I shall return!
Oh,Daddy wants to fly! Daddy,fly higher!
You are late for work!
Do you want Load Japper to
talk some sense into you?
No,no,no! It's my first day of work
I don't know what to do......
He,he,you don't need to do anything
you just need to sleep!
Marvellous,this is indeed a great job
I will accept it.
It's now showtime,and we are going to
perform for the animals of the grass land.
Dear friends,it is my great
pleasure to present Lord Japper.
Welcome!! Welcome!!!
Today,we are going to present
an enchanting magic show.
I don't want to be a stage-prop! Help! Help!
Why are you yelling?
You are supposed to help me in
the perform for the audience!
Leopold!
Wow!~
Is it for real,are they really
going to saw him in two?
Help! Help!
Help! Help!Please help me!
Hey! What's going on.
I'm really upset.
A power failure now?
Everybody is enjoying the show now!
Lord Japper.
Relax. My Lord.
If only we can find the legendary
emerald power source.
Tigbot King's power will never fail again.
My Lord,you can then amuse
yourself for as long as you want.
Then where is the emerald power source?
I am using the supercomputer
to search for the power source.
We will find the source soon...
I don't want it to be soon!
I want the power source now! Leopold!
Wow!~~
Ha,ha,now we can continue the show and
continue to have fun with the animals.
My Lord.
For the sake of preserving the
grassland,please switch off Tigbot King.
Oh,but why?
If this goes on
very soon the entire grassland
will wither and turn into a desert.
Um,there is some merit in
what you say. Counselor!
Please don't be fooled by him,
My lord! This old sheep...
He is super-crafty.
If we switch off Tigbot King,you
will no longer have fun.
Right! We are having so much
fun in the amusement park!
Why are you so selfish,you old sheep.
Why don't you think of the animals'  interests?
My Lord!
In fact you are the one who is selfish
You are not being fair to others.
Being fair? Guards!
Show them the meaning of fairness!
Dinner time!
Welcome. Let me treat all of
you to some delicious food.
No additives,non-fried,super-healthy.
High-tech nanoparticle-based Lord
Japper canned cold noodles,yummy!
Oh my goodness!
We are not eating noodles
we are eating loneliness.
Is it possible to eat lonliness?
This can't be eaten!
Luckily. I have saved some food.
Big Brother ,what is this?
This,is a piece of stone.
Big Brother,my Daddy can fly.
My Daddy loves to eat stones,too.
My whole family loves to eat stones.
Alright,alright,I will share the food with you.
Thank you,Big Brother!
Look,Big Brother,the food has grown,
let's eat together.
Honey,our cub is so hungry
that he is hallucinating.
There Is No Sheep Hunting
rule in the staff handbook.
Otherwise,I would have have hunted a few-----
The village chief has fainted.
Village Chief!!   Village Chief!
Cough!cough!...
Pesticides?
Aye,if this continues
we will either work to death
or be poisoned by pesticides.
What should we do now
we are no match for the big tiger.
If only we can find the legendary Totem.
Village Chief,what Totem?
My great grandfather had told me a legend.
There is a mysterious citadel wth a golden-spire,
Which is inhabited by a generous
and kind sheep guardian saint
protecting the sheep species' Totem.
Once we can unravel the secrets of the Totem
then we will be invincible.
Village Chief,is it really true?
Then we can defeat Lord
Japper! Where is this place?
It's in ... in...
In a faraway place
there is an elderly sheep......
Your Mommy is calling you for dinner...
Is the Village Chief is going insane!!
Where is the kitchen? I am starving to death.
Who are you? Password!
Glory to Lord Japper!!
Eh,glory to Lord Japper! Salute!
I am scared,but luckily I have quick reflexes.
Oops,I manage to bluff my way through..
I am brilliant,and no one can match me.
Brilliant and no one can match me.
Am I seeing things?
Trash foods!
Evil lizard! ,we have been
eating food made from trash.
You hide here to feast on good food.
Damn it!
No,I better save this food
for my wife and cub to eat.
There should be more food.Let me check.
Kong~~
Do you want to scare me to death?
Eh? Why are you here?
Wh-what's wrong?
I have damaged the amusment
park's power supply.
Even the construction
workbots can't move now,
Hurry,run away with your whole family now!
No wonder you are called
Happy,a bagful of tricks.
Power failure again?
You are really naive
haven't you heard of a power
generator rechargeable by batteries?
This is bad news!
What should we do now?
Run for our lives!
We should make our move now! Leopold!
Wow!~~
Leopold!
Capture the wolf!
Leopold,He is there!
Stop harassing me.
No!
Wow!~~
I surrender,I surrender!
How dare you try to destroy my den!
I am not here to destroy your den.
Then what are you doing here?Stealing?
Eh,alright.I am here to destroy your den.
Lord Japper,How do we punish them?
I give you two choices.
First,reason with me...
I take the second choice!
What?
Fine,You are the first one to choose second.
Leopold.
Wow!~~
Ah! What do you want to do?
Go! Explore the great desert...
Where are we?
It is your fault! You bring me
bad luck every time we meet.
I shall return--
No water,no food.
How do we trek out of the desert?
He,he,maybe there is a way.
Wolffy,you still have the egg!
Give it back to me!
It is for my wife and cub...
Can't eat it!
I see you still have some sense
of responsibility to your family.
I have misjudged you.
You are right!
Then you should help me!
Even if you eat me now,you
will still die in the desert.
But I will die after you!
Village Chief fell sick after
he had eaten the canned food!
Then what happen next?
Because of this!
Sore throat,fever,hallucination....
H1N1! Are you infected?
If you eat me,you will be infected too.
It is really disappointing that I can't
eat you when you are at my lips..
Earlier I have warned you not to eat me!
I am hallucinating,I have got the flu!
It is not a hallucination! It is the
citadel with the golden-spire!
So Village Chief was right!
Is there roast mutton to eat in the citadel?
There is a mysterious place
with a golden-spire citadel.
The Totem is inside the citadel.
Once we possess the Totem
we can escape from the desert.
We will be invincible.
Then we can defeat Lord Japper and his sidekicks!
I can then save my wife and cub!
What are we waiting for! Let's go inside!
Hey! Wait a second...
Oh! It is just a mirage...
The batteries are discharged!
They are not the emerald power source!
Counselor,Tigbot King has stopped again...
Relax,my Lord
we have explored all nooks and corners of the
world in search of the emerald power source.
It must be here.
But,if Tigbot King can continue to deliver power
this place will turn into a desert soon?
So be it,let the whole world turn into a desert.
When that happens,the animals
will have no habitats to live in
and they will stay here to play with you.
Look! It must be here,come here everyone!
Move faster!
In order for Lord Japper to continue
having fun with the animals
in order for the amusement
park to continue operating.
Everybody must be fully dedicated to the task.
All of you must be totally committed
to excavating the emerald power source
Who is so committed to the task?
Do you want Lord Japper
to show you some fairness?
Dark clouds,it's going to rain!
Chase! Chase!
Run! Run! Run!
This,this is killing me!
Counselor,why do we excavate so much coal?
It is not the emerald power source!
Since the emerald power source is a legend
it must be well-hidden and
buried very deep underground.
It must be...,it must be...
It must be what?
Only after we have excavated all the coal,
then we can expose the emerald power source.
Continue to excavate the coal.
The emerald power source!
Is it another mirage again?
Let's have some rest.
You are still thinking of
eating mutton all the time!
Aren't you tired?
Of course I am tired! This is all fated.
If wolves do not hunt and eat sheep
then do you expect them
to eat fried rice with egg?
Do you think it is an easy
to be Lord of the grass land.
That is right. We sheep
will instinctively avoid you.
This is the law of nature.
It is easier to be a sheep than to be a wolf.
You can eat and drink all day;
frolicking and playing hide-and-seek.
You face less mental pressure than me.
You are not so bad either.
Every sheep is scared of you.
You have a wonderful family.
Then there is me,working
against you all the time.
Isn't it challenging!
Is it fun to work against me?
Of course,it is my calling.
You......Yeah,right,I got used to it!
It is meaningless to reminisce now.
We have no opportunity to
challenge each other again.
Go to hunt some sheep,and be back by dinner!
Happy,aren't you always brave and determined?
Mommy believes you can escape from the desert
Mommy will always support you...
You are always my good lad...
Mommy...Mommy...
Honey...Howie...
Mommy...
Ah? Trouble!
Stop looking; it is another mirage...
It's a sand storm!
Run!
Mr. Wolffy,I know what to do!
Wolffy! Run faster!
I should have devoured you earlier.
Golden-Spire citadel?
Ah,kind-hearted guardian saints!
This must be another mirage.
It is real,they are the guardian saints.
Who are you? What do you want?
I am the progeny of the sheep community.
May I ask whether the invincible totem is inside?
Yes,it is inside. Go in and find it yourself.
How do we know where to look for it?
What kind of attitude is that?
Hey,I will lodge a complaint against you!
What a nuisance.
According to our rules,
you must first answer our question correctly.
Ah. What for?
Our rules must be observed.
OK. Go ahead and ask.
It is simple. How many stars are there in the sky?
Are you trying to trick us?
Sorry,we are just following our orders.
Ha,ha...I have the answer.
There are as many stars in the sky
as there are particles of sands here.
Happy,you are brilliant!
Really?
Of course it is true,you can count them yourself.
One,two,three,four,five,six...
Mr Ramhead,Mr Wolface...
Hey,it is countless
Can both of you let us enter the
citadel to look for the Totem.
I have miscounted again.
What are both of you grumbling about?
Wah...
What an unpleasant sheep guardian saint?
He is worse than Lord Japper.
There is also the Wolface sphinx?
Maybe we can get out by this way....
Nonsense!
What is this! Happy,quick,think of a solution.
It is not very deep down. Let's jump together!
Hey you,don't knock onto me?
Ah! Ach! My feet are hurting!
What are you complaining?
Aren't your feet sfill intact?
Right. Ha,ha...
We have made it! The chain has snapped! Ha,ha...
Watch out!
Run,Wolffy!
These mechanical traps are deadly!
Wait for me,Happy!
Wolffy,right here!
Village Chief,the roller coaster has been modified
It should scale over the electric fence.
Shu~~quiet! Don't let them find out.
Village Chief,can we really escape?
No problem.
Based on my calculation and modification
this roller coaster can
definitely scale over the
fence of the amusement park.
Trust my calculation.
We can definitely scale over and escape!
Village Chief! Can we have another choice?
No choice!
Village Chief,do we wait for Happy?
After we have escaped,then we will look for him.
With his intelligence,he can escape unscathed.
Wait a second.
Hollie? What is she doing here?
Village Chief,please wait.
Wait. Please,please...
Please let Howie leave with you!
Don't try any tricks now!
You want to get on to the roller coaster
and wait for an opportunity
to devour us,isn't it?
Oh no! I am not planning to escape.
I just don't want my cub to stay here and suffer.
He is only a cub and he has a kind heart.
He never wishes to hurt anyone.
Mommy,I want to eat mutton!
I want to eat mutton! I want to eat mutton!
Foolish child!
He is very humorous!
Village Chief! Don't believe her story!
I am begging you!
As his mother,I wish Howie can be saved.
I don't have any other wishes.
Village Chief! Please accept her request!
Ten seats and adding two......
there are not enough seats!
He is small. He won't take up much space.
Mommy,where are we heading to?
My little sweetie,Mommy
won't be with you anymore.
You can't be childish anymore.
Listen to your older brothers
and sisters,don't be naughty.
Take good care of yourself.
Mommy...
I am so touched...Wail,wail...
They are so pitiful!
village Chief.Please agree fo fheir requesf!
OK,fine.
Both of you can come on board.
Thank you very much! I am overjoyed!
Lance,please help me to hold on to Howie.
Ten plus two...
Trouble! Overloaded!
Beauty,are you alright!
I am so scared!
Everybody watch out! Here it comes again!
Planning to escape! Leopold,Get them!
Ten plus two... What is the answer?
One,Two,Three,Four,Five......
Ten plus two. Uncle,what is ten plus two?
Wao!~~
Uncle,you can't leave
without giving me an answer?
Get them to come down.
Useless! Leopold!
Hold it...
Perfect!
Ah? Trouble!
Lord Japper,they are all down below.
Guards,tie them up!
Yes!
We can't escape now.
Let's think of another escape plan...
I have it!
We can surrender!
Sounds like a good idea....
No! If we give up
We will still be tortured by Lord Japper.
Then what should we do? My dear husband~~~
Nice rhythm,right,Sweetie?
Sweetie?
You can't even take care of your own son
you are more careless than Lance!
Err? Where is Lance?
Lance!
Howie!
I saw them flew this way and dropped down here.
Big Brother Lance,you are great!
Of course,I am brilliant
and no one can match me...
brilliant and no one can match me...
Oops...Want to uncover my secret?
For heaven's sake,I am
to get rid of both of you.
Ho~~~
My good partner will take good care of you!
Big Brother Lance!
What now?
There is a park.
Why is there is a park here?
Oh! This is ...
This is not a park! This is...
Heaven!!
Big Brother Lance,is it edible?
Yes,yes!
Wow,this fruit is really fresh!
Big Brother,taste this.
Wow~~ this is really fresh!
Eh! Well done!
Wow...
WOW~~
What is happening?
Don't bother too much,let's get over first.
It is very painful. The pain is killing me!
Stop pushing me,Happy!
You go first!
Ouch! What is this?
Pass!
Happy,you are really nasty!
Damn it,I shall return!
Wrong! I will never be come
back to this horrible place!
Before we plan to return,
we must first get out of this place.
Ha,ha,see what I've found?
Could this be the place
where the invincible Totem is hidden?
If we find the Totem,then we can go home,
and save my wife and cub.
This must definitely be
the Totem described by Village Chief
Not possible,it is just a piece of paper?
Calm down,
let's roll it up and take it back for examination.
Be careful,don't damage it.
Err,what's this smell?
It is as fragrant as roast meat.
Your fail is on fire!
Look up!
Let's jump up quickly!
Good! It is my turn now.
Watch out.!!!
We can beat Liu Xiang.
And break the world record!
Great!
Of course! Err,where is the exit?
There is no exit.
Then why do we jump up for?
To check whether there is an exit here.
What?
It looks like we are going to
be barbecued meat soon.
Hold tight!
What kind of trouble is waiting for us ahead?
479 billion 800 million and one.
It's you again?
Ah...I see you have managed to find the Totem?
Why do you pull out the stone slab?
To record the number of grains of sand.
Let's not bother them anymore
I want to head home to rescue my wife and cub..
No! You can't leave until we finish counting.
Why?
Because rules are rules.
How long do we have to wait?
I need to rush back to rescue all the sheep.
It won't take long,we have already counted......
Oh? What is the number now?
I have forgotten too,let's start all over again.
Please be patient,
as soon as we finish counting...
No need to count!
Because there are no stars at all!
If you don't believe,look up the sky now.
Really! There are no stars!
The mystery that has been
bothering us for 2000 years
is finally solved! Wail,wail...
To reward you,
we will send you home in the fastest way
Climb up and seat down.
Is this your sleeping rug?
This is really a magic rug.
The 2010 Limited Edition.
How to get it to lift off?
Is there a seat-belt?
Goodbye!
See you! Come and visit us again!
Almost the whole region has turned into a desert.
Perhaps,only our green grassland
hasn't be destroyed.
What should we be scared!
We have the Totem now.
We are invincible.
The three rogues will be
begging for mercy from us.
Ha,ha,ha,ha...
Wolffy,better sit down.
Happy,can't you be a bit gutsy?
OHHHH.... my egg...
What a fool you are! Are you
not afraid of being killed?
No,but the cooking pan is more scary!!!
It's very windy,hold tight.
I am going to adjust the balance of the rug.
Big Brother Lance,let's sing.
No,I am not in the mood!
You can nap while I sing you a lullaby.
Wake me when the monster returns.
I don't need any lullaby to sleep
I want to eat a sheep,I want to eat a sheep.
Lance,Lance
Who taught you this song?
My daddy taught me this song.
I want to eat sheep; I want to eat sheep.
Here's my Lance...
Will you come to my house,Big Brother?
To sing together?
I want to eat sheep,I want to eat sheep...
No,I won't!
Go to your house? You think I am an idiot?
How do you know that?
What?
My parents said you are foolish
and the easiest to capture......
We're back.
Hold tight!
Wah! Daddy is flying again!
Daddy is flying! Daddy is flying! Great! Great!
Shu~~Quiet!
My Daddy is a flying wolf.
Yes! Your Daddy can fly,but we will die.
Kong~~
This dark shadow is scary.
Silence! Don't move!
Big Brother Lance,you are so alert.
I have been trained by your father.
Daddy is great! Daddy is great!
It's very hot!
Hurry,run!
Didn't you ask me to keep still?
If you don't hurry up,you will get eaten!
Faster! Run faster!
I hate running! Ouch
Let's play together.
Ha,ha,ha. ha......
I am dirty and lazy! Don't eat me!
Help! Howie!
Just one push and they will all be finished.
You are back.
Eh? How do you manage to come back?
As Mr. Wolffy always says,we shall return!
Arrest these two crafty crooks..
We are crafty crooks?
Let's me deal with the leader,
and you can take on the other seven guys! Charge!
What are you yelling for? You talk too much?
Leopold
Wow!~~
I better deal with these seven guys,
you take on that one. Charge!
Ping,ping,ping...
Wow!~~
It's your turn!
Hm! We meet again!
Dear uncles and cousins,
If we are truly relatives
Then why are we killing each other...
But you are the one to start the fight!
Cousin,please let me go,
I will let you into a top secret.
What kind of secret is this?
Look at this dot
Does this look like the cave entrance?
Somewhat similar,but what does it mean?
I don't get it. What's the secret?
The secret is...
All of you are finished!
Take it easy,we did not come to capture you...
Only when I get upset,
then I realize how powerful I am.
I will block the entrance
and see you can escape from the cave!
Where are you,Honey?
You dare to trick me!
Where are you,honey-----
Honey?
Hold on,Honey!
I will come and rescue you!
We should unite and work together!
All for one and one for all!
All wolves unite!!
I can't hold on any longer.
You have to hold on,Honey-----
Don't care about me,it's too dangerous.
You can't leave!
Whatever it is,I won't leave you--
We are so touched...
Don't be foolish,either I had nagged you all day
Or hit you with a frying pan...
I have always enjoyed it.
Wolffy,unleash your power.
I love frying pans!
It is alright now,Honey,come up now!
My dear Hubby!
Are you and Howie alright?
Sweetie?
Honey! Howie is missing!
What?! Let's go and find him!
Lord Japper,come here!
Hm,as I said,we will meet again.
My Lord,they shall be punished
for destroying the amusement park.
I will give you two choices.
First,I exile you to the desert.
Second,you go there yourselves!
We will not obey you anymore!
Yes,we are united. We are not
frightened of you anymore.
Expel them from the green grassland.
What should we do now?
Who wants to reason with me?
It is safer in the pond.
We will look for our cub later.
Good idea,good idea!
Run,boy!
We must save our cub as soon as possible. Oops.
Are you OK,Honey?
Oops,my head...
But it is not painful now.
Quickly,go and save our cub!
Yeah,yeah,yeah,save our cub.
I know where is the entrance.
We are alright?
It is flour!
This,this.
They have been frightened out of their wits
why don't you surrender now!
Right,right,
see how powerful I am,surrender now!
Can you see it?
Why aren't you scared?
Hey,don't come close...
I only try to scare you
If you take another step,
I will have to reason with you!
Oops,time to scam I see.
Ha,ha,what?
Can't I reason with you with a piece of stone?
As you said,we will meet again!
It is not my fault
These two bad guys forced met to
do all the wicked things!
It's his idea to destroy
your village to build the amusement park.
I am innocent. They are responsible.
How to open it?
Ouch! Help,Lance is also down below!
My sweetie!
Where are you?
Lance!
Howie! My sweetie!
Sweetie!
Sweetie! Daddy is here to save you!
Ha,ha. This grass is good for barbecue.
Howie!
Mommy? Mommy!
Mommy! Come here to meet my adopted brother!
Adopted brother?
This is my adopted brother!
Oh?This is Big Brother!
Hi
Big Brother?
It can't be true?
What?
Any problems?
What is happening?
Get out quickly!
Ha,ha,we finally find the real
emerald power source!
Village Chief,isn't this grass similar to yours?
I am happy for the perfect ending.
Tigbot King is now perfect!
Counselor!
Counselor,I want to expand my Amusement Park.
What Amusement Park?
I want to recreate the primordial era.
Looks like they are having
some form of internal conflict?
Who is really Lord Japper?
Nonsense!
I am Lord Japper of all times!
Such a mighty fool!
Lord Japper?
You are nothing but an overgrown cat.
A cat?
Yes,because in the Tiger Year,
the tiger heads of the animal zodiac .
I only use you to obtain the demolition
and resettlement permit.
Now that I have gotten what I want
I do not need to deceive you anymore.
It is impossible!
I am a tiger!
I am head of the zodiac!
I am Lord Japper!
Destroy Tigbot King
Ridiculous!
Or someone's getting cold feet.
Wh- What's going on?
I dominate everything here!
Don't waste your time.
If you don't believe me,call out loud.
Miao
You have been lying to me since I was young?
I am a cat?
Wow!~~
Why are you rejoicing?
Wash your face and look yourself in the mirror.
And find out what are you!
Village Chief,what's this all about?
Apparently,he is a hyena.
This is a cat,this is a hyena.
Are you a fake too?
Right,I am not a gecko
But a noble dinosaur! Check this out.
Are you a dwarf?
Hm,because of this environment
I have become what I am now! Ha,ha.
After destroying all existing vegetation
I can recreate the environment of a long-gone era
which is most suitable for me.
At that time,our species
were huge noble dinosaurs.
I can evolve to be like them!
Destroy this place,Tigbot King!
I want to recreate the primordial era!
Let's scatter!
What can we do to stop him,Honey?
Isn't it nonsensical! No!!
OK,we know what to do now!
We want to be on your side again.
Why make this choice now...
I won't allow all of you to defect.
I am exiling all of you to the desert!
He doesn't look like he
is going to fight any more.
Being soft-hearted again?
I hope he is not unleashing his secret weapon.
Look out for my super Tigbot King!!
Hold tight,Honey!
Wah,not again?
All of you are exiled.
Who have any weapons,hurl them at him!
Come on,Hollie,use your frying pan!
Charge!
How come you were so accurate
when you hitting meHow c,Honey?
Aren't you the only one that I have ever hit?
He,he. Hollie,just aim at Wolffy!
Happy! How can you suggest that!
Trust me!
Wolffy,you didn't tell your wife
that you had had an egg,right?
What? You ate it all by yourself,
leaving your wife and child starving?
No ...I didn't...
Where is the egg?
Good Shot.
Happy!,You set me up again.
Wolffy,jump up and dodge!
Wolffy cooked the egg
in eight different ways.
Oh,there goes my family!
Eight different ways to cook the egg?
Take this!
Oh dear,the controller is damaged!
If you didn't eat the egg,why are you hiding?
Happy,I hate you.
Eight different ways of cooking the egg,
take this and this!
Wah,help!
Oh,this is the Tiger Year's
first miscarriage of justice.
You dare to claim you are innocent!
No one can defeat a two-pan strike!
Wah~~~
Ouch!!
Mission accomplished.
I am now the one
and only Lord of the grassland!
What else did you eat?
Honey! No,I didn't,honey!
Cousin,bite them to death!
Cousin?
Bite them to death!
Get out of my way!
I will deal with him!
Good,let's go and play somewhere else!
Cousin,when did you become a vegetarian?
Dinosaurs evolved to be vegetarians
because of environmental changes...
Don't you know that?
Evolution can't be retrogressive
It is impossible to return to the Jurassic period.
Regretfully I have to admit defeat,
what is on your mind?
Let me have your address.
I want to convert your house into
a public toilet.
I give you two choices
First,spare us.
Second,release us.
All of you are civilized
please let us go and release us?
Wang!~~
Gecko! Your days are numbered!
I want a way out too,and not to learn math!
How dare you make fun of what my wife said!
Wait!
Listen,I have deciphered
the secret of the Totem.
Hey,old chap,are you invincible now?
Village Chief,share the secret with them!
I have been experimenting with it for sometime.
Finally I have unraveled the mystery.
Looks like a family photo..
Yes,the family tree of life on Earth,look...
See,this is the wolf,tiger,elephant,
cat,canines,and sheep.
All of them are mammals
they evolved from reptiles
What? This gecko is our ancestor?
Don't interrupt!
And their ancestors were amphibians,
then fishes,then...
Village chief,can you be more direct,
what's this?
This is a single-cell organism.
Old Sheeep,what exactly is your point?
Ha,ha,we are actually related to each other.
Yesterday they came here
to tear down our houses
And today we are making them suffered,
Isn't it ridiculous?
Ridiculous,ridiculous!
What kind Totem is this,
and how can it be invincible?
As long as we are not enemies
Aren't we invincible. Can you figure this out!
Ha,ha,ha,ha...
Dear friends,smile...
Wolffy,can you promise that
we will remain friends in the future.
If we are friends,then you should
not let your friends be hungry.
Happy is missing!
Happy,you deserved to be eaten.
Come out to face me.
OK!
Is everyone alright?
I have modified Tigbot King
to serve us now.
Relax,my friend!
Happy New Year. I am returning the egg to you!
Honey,I saved the egg
for you and Howie!
One is not enough,I want more!
Honey...
I shall return!
Daddy is flying again!
Ha,ha,ha,ha!
SubToSrt:Song