Let's go play.
I'll look out for you.
I can't swim.
The water's not deep.
We'll stay near the bank and play in the mud.
I'll protect you.
Don't be scared, OK?
I'm leaving you behind then.
I'll go first.
Here I come!
- I'm home.
- Xingxing's back.
Wash up for dinner.
Use soap.
Lots of it.
Time to eat.
Want some fried eggs?
I've made five.
- You want some?
- No, I'll drink this first.
How was school today?
Not bad.
Here are some peanuts.
You can have three.
Xingxing.
Xingxing!
Take him to the hospital!
Careful!
Haohao.
Out of the way!
SILENCE
Watch out!
Move aside!
Where's the kid?
Upstairs.
I've asked him to come but he won't.
Playing that game again, huh?
Why don't you go get him?
Let's eat.
Let's drop by the school tomorrow.
If this goes on,
we'll have to find him a new school.
Your son is a little closed off.
He keeps things to himself.
We want the best for him, too.
That's why we should discuss
how to handle it.
I can't believe that.
Can you look further into the case?
As you wish.
But it could escalate the problem
and have an adverse effect on Liu Xing.
Take my advice.
Sit him down
and have a proper chat with him.
Convince him to give it back.
There should be no hard feelings.
Make him see the error of his ways.
It'll be fine
as long as he never does it again.
Yaojun...
Explain this to me.
I want to get back at them
for bullying me.
Who bullied you?
They did.
So you did steal it?
What a good-for-nothing!
I didn't steal it.
It wasn't me.
Then what's it doing here?
I hate this place.
I hate them.
I hate you.
Oh Xingxing!
- Xingxing!
- Stop!
Think you're a big boy now?
Fine, we'll deal with this like adults.
I won't hit you.
You have two options.
Either...
give this back
and apologize to your classmate.
Or...
we hand you over to the police.
Take me to the police station then.
As you wish.
Now apologize to your mother.
Let go of me.
Yaojun, let go.
Xingxing.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good enough for you.
Why are you doing this?
Where in the world
could he be?
Consider him dead.
How could you say such a thing?
We've raised him all these years.
What do you want me to say?
You've fed and clothed him.
You've spoiled him rotten.
Don't tell me
he'll care for you when you're old.
He's an ungrateful bastard!
He may look like Xingxing
but he's not our son.
Our Xingxing is dead!
Gone forever.
Today is Xing and Hao's birthday!
You're making a celery dish, too?
It's Xing and Hao's birthday.
What's for dinner?
It still isn't done cooking?
Here's your birthday present.
White Rabbit candy from Shanghai!
All for you!
Rock, paper, scissors!
The winner gets the jar.
Happy Birthday, boys!
Cut the cake now.
Weren't you dreaming of a birthday cake?
Here it comes.
Decorated with flowers.
Where are the candles?
Right here.
Hurry, blow them out.
Together!
Ready, set...
go!
Happy Birthday!
These boys have the exact same birthday.
If they were boy and girl
they'd make a nice couple.
Yes, that's a pity.
But this is great, too.
They're brothers now.
Like us.
Brothers now, brothers forever.
What a heaven-sent blessing.
I propose a toast to the little brothers!
- Yaojun, I'll get going.
- OK, I have two more holes to drill.
Are you OK, Liyun?
I'm fine.
Can you take over for a minute?
Come here. Turn around. Go to sleep.
Stay out of Haiyan's sight.
I can't hide this from her forever.
We'll think of something.
There must be a way.
What way?
I'm about to show.
I almost fainted in the factory today.
Is it that bad already?
How about this?
Let's take a few days off
and stay with my aunt in the countryside.
We'll pay the fine, no big deal.
The baby's nickname can be "Penalty".
That's not funny.
It's not just the fine.
We could both lose our jobs.
Didn't you hear Haiyan?
Things are even worse in the countryside.
(Men speaking in Fujian Dialect)
Mr Liu.
Come have some tea with us.
You've been working hard.
Come have a seat.
Say, is your child back?
What kind of tea is this?
Why bring that up?
Kids his age are most difficult.
Particularly boys.
Boys or girls.
They're all only children
and hence a treasure.
We shouldn't have brought that up.
- Pour him some tea.
- Cut it out. Cut it out.
Oh, there's Liyun.
- Liyun, come have some tea.
- I'm good, thanks.
- Come have some tea.
Yaojun, it's time for lunch.
Next time.
- Come back later.
- Sure.
See you.
You put your foot in your mouth just now.
What a strange family.
Everyone's flocking
to modern cities to get rich.
But they came to this godforsaken place.
I heard even the kid is not their own.
Seriously? No wonder.
I'll go to the police station later today.
There's no point in going there so often.
They'll call us if they hear something.
We can't let them just sit on the case.
The orphanage called me.
He can only register his ID and permits
under our family's name.
I've talked to my sister.
She'll help out.
As long as he comes back,
I don't care where he's registered.
Can you hear me?
Who is it?
I'm gonna stock up in town tomorrow.
And put up a search notice
in the newspaper.
Do you want anything from town?
No, I'm good.
You look like you've aged.
Are you here on business?
I didn't want to take this trip at first.
But then I remembered
that you and Liyun live here.
It might be a chance to see you before I
leave.
How did you find out where we live?
You think you could just vanish?
Everyone knew what you were up to.
First you went down to Hainan.
Soon afterwards you moved here.
We all wondered where you'd go next.
Unexpectedly you just stayed here.
There's nowhere else for us to go.
We like it here.
We don't know anyone.
In fact, we know nothing here.
Not even their dialect.
Like living in a foreign country.
I suppose so.
How is Liyun?
She's OK.
Just like she once said:
"Time stopped for us long ago.
"Now we're just waiting to grow old."
How's your brother's family?
Well...
Haohao is a sophomore at university.
Yingming is
always busy with his business.
Haiyan took early retirement
and just passes her time.
When they heard I might see you,
they told me to send you their regards.
Did you say you're going abroad?
Yes.
What I learned at university is getting
outdated.
So I decided to take the TOEFL.
Somehow, I passed.
As soon as I get back, I'll resign.
- And your...
- We divorced.
You read my mind.
You were always such a smart kid.
Well, you were my teacher.
A few days' training in the factory don't count.
Anyway,
I owe it to you that I got into university.
You didn't even take my training seriously.
Correct.
Don't worry.
Hold still.
Stay calm.
It won't bite.
Your other hand.
Hold that pose!
Both of you.
You know that pose right there?
It's like the rumba dancers
pressed this tight against each other.
How's that?
Yaojun, now you've got yourself
an apprentice.
Moli, I'm telling you:
He knows all about machines.
But about fashion, you have to ask me.
What do you think of my outfit?
Don't I look like a Hong Kong movie star?
Sure.
Your pants are sweeping the floor for us.
Sweeping?
I don't mind.
It's fashion!
Strange romance!
On a bus!
Looks nice!
Yaojun, come here.
There's a fabulous dance party tonight.
A lights-out party!
Lights-out, my ass! Get lost!
You're so out.
So come with me, Moli!
How dare you!
You're really hitting me!
It's the new dance moves.
Jitterbug.
Who is it?
It's me.
Haiyan?
Open the door.
Sister-in-law.
Hurry in.
Come in, brother.
Shut the door!
It's the new dance, named Jitterbug.
Stop that.
Why?
Turn off this trashy music.
Now you're a leader
and you want to meddle with everything.
- Stop it.
- Don't pretend!
- Stop it, stop it...
- No!
Don't wreck the tape!
I brought it all the way from Guangzhou!
Well, Meiyu.
How about we play something quiet?
Don't be so serious.
How could old friends forget
the good times of the past.
What song is this?
It's beautiful.
"Everlasting Friendship."
Liyun, have you heard it before?
When we were sent to the countryside.
No way you could hear such songs
during the cultural revolution.
You just don't know.
Meiyu, you've picked a great song.
Perfect for the occasion.
Was it '77 or 78?
The end of 78.
All the students were trying
to go back to the cities.
Some got to leave, others didn't.
Every time it was a farewell for life.
When it was our turn to leave,
someone started to sing this song.
We all burst into tears.
Nobody had ever heard such a moving song.
Right, Yingming?
Yes.
Unforgettable.
Comrade Deng clearly asserted at Beidaihe
in a discussion with Police Chief Liu,
"The steep rise in serious crime
"is highly detrimental to society.
"The people are very dissatisfied.
"Why not wage a war
against criminal activities,
"once, twice, even three times?"
Yaojun?
Brother?
- Yaojun!
- Yaojun. My brother is calling you.
On 25th August, the patty central
government announced
they will heavily crack down on crime.
You'd better pick up your son
from his grandparents.
He's fine.
I'll stay here.
You're back.
- He's sleeping.
- He just fell asleep.
There's a rum our in the factory.
What happened?
Xinjian got himself arrested
at a lights-out party.
For dancing?
They're cracking down
and branding it "debauchery."
Some have been executed for it.
How about Meiyu?
We don't know.
We can't find her.
Have you seen her?
No, we haven't.
She didn't go to work today?
No.
Where could she be?
What a mess.
Meiyu just came back.
- She's back?
- I saw her walk in.
We should check on her.
Let's go and see.
Stop it.
Hello?
Yes.
The truck broke down
in the middle of the road.
I got someone to fix it.
I'll pick up the stuff and then drive back.
Don't wait for me.
Bye.
You didn't tell her I'm in town?
There you are.
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
Go to bed.
I have to unload the truck first.
Dear comrades of the communist petty
and youth league,
to meet our goal by the end of this century
of limiting the population to 1.2 billion,
the State Council has called upon couples
to have only one child.
ONE COUPLE, ONE CHILD
ACHIEVING ECONOMIC REFORM
This is a major measure that concerns the
speed and future of the Four Modernizations
as well as the health and well-being
of future generations.
This policy impacts national interests
in the long and shalt term.
The central government
requires party members,
especially cadres of various ranks,
to actively can)! this policy out,
to set an example,
and to responsibly take on the duty
of propaganda and education of the masses.
What's wrong?
Look what you've done!
Stop playing dumb.
Liyun's told me everything.
She's several months along.
How dare you hide this from me for so long!
Well.
You know the rules.
I've called the hospital already.
A car is coming to pick us up.
What the hell are you doing?
We're going home.
Yaojun!
Do you really think you can run forever?
Liyun,
don't be a fool.
You've been foolish enough to let this happen.
What if word gets out in the factory?
Consider the consequences for me.
Can't you see my point?
Director.
Come in.
Let's go.
Yaojun!
Calm down! Restrain him!
Stop it!
You're out of your mind.
Yaojun, how could you?
Quickly, get in the car.
Get in.
- Liu Yaojun!
- It's OK!
I'll come with you.
OK, let's go.
Director Li.
Dr Yang.
This is Wang Liyun
from the Sorting Department.
She has agreed.
I see. Let's start with a blood test.
Liyun,
don't worry.
It'll be over in no time.
I've taken care of everything.
You'll be fine.
I'm here for you.
Go on.
Follow us.
Doctor Yang?
- Doctor Yang?
- Here.
Something's wrong. She's haemorrhaging.
What's going on?
Please take a look.
- Who are you?
- I'm family.
Please wait outside.
You can't be in here.
What's happening to her?
We are the future of communism.
Following the path of revolutionary forebears.
We love the motherland,
we love the people.
We proudly call ourselves
the young pioneers.
Salute!
At ease!
Dismissed!
It's time to present the final award of the day.
The Annual Award for Family Planning
by Outstanding Individuals.
Let's welcome Director Li
from the Family Planning Office
on stage to present the award.
This year,
our factory did well in family planning.
Among couples of child-bearing age,
we achieved zero unplanned births.
We're setting a positive example
for the locals.
Besides that,
the party members are excellent,
and the workers have shown
higher ideological awareness.
Some comrades had to face personal hurdles.
However, with our counseling,
they've overcome them.
I hereby announce
the 1986 Award for Family Planning:
The honored couple is...
Wang Liyun of the Sorting Department
and Liu Yaojun of the Assembling Workshop!
Congratulations.
There's money in it. Why the frown?
Give us a smile.
Has Meiyu made up her mind
to go to Guangzhou?
What's so unusual about that?
Nowadays everyone with ambition
is going south.
I admire her gumption.
What about you?
Want to get an IUD?
I don't think I need one.
The doctor said my uterus wall is too thin.
And then the surgery went wrong.
I'm unlikely to get pregnant again.
Yaojun should take the blame.
He agreed to get a vasectomy,
but then sent someone in his stead to fool me.
He looks like such an honest guy.
Seriously?
He's an idiot.
There you are, Yaojun.
- What brought you back?
- I was sent home for field practice.
You're here, too?
Where's Mama?
Over there.
Teach me how to waltz, would you?
Your brother is a better dancer.
Look, he's dancing with Meiyu.
Kiddo? Here.
Go have fun.
You're about to graduate, right?
Times flies, doesn't it?
Yes.
You're so tall,
I didn't recognize you anymore.
You got a boyfriend?
Do you want me to?
Do I want you to?
Just catching up with my apprentice.
None of my classmates are my cup of tea.
You don't want to end up like Meiyu, though.
She's different, she's waiting for someone.
For who? Xinjian?
Of course.
That makes her a fool.
All women are fools in love.
You're right. Look at her:
all meat and no brains.
Is he still mad at me?
No, he isn't.
He's just mad at himself.
He's frustrated he could do nothing.
How I wish you wouldn't go.
So you could stay with me.
Why won't you stay
Leave me here alone.
Every meeting is too short.
You always keep silent.
Every time wave farewell.
I'm always extremely sorrowful.
How should I spend the long night alone.
Please don't confuse me anymore.
We are young now.
We are full of energy.
Even if there are ups and downs in life,
never mind.
Do not sigh.
Do not abandon yourself.
Only you can decide your success or failure.
Time flies.
It'll be too late
if you don't cherish it.
You're all here.
I'm fine.
The government has been easy on me.
It's not so bad in here.
How is everyone?
We're fine.
Yingming joined the party.
Haiyan got promoted to Director.
Deputy Director only.
Liyun and Yaojun
were named Outstanding Individuals.
Not by choice.
I'm going down south to try my luck.
That's good to hear.
Go out and see the world.
Make the most of it once you get there.
Don't let me hold you back.
Xinjian, stop talking nonsense.
Why does a grown man like you
have such a long face?
They've fattened you up.
This new haircut suits you.
Makes you look decent.
Alright, alright.
We wanted to see if you are doing alright.
We'll get going now.
See you next time.
Take care, OK?
Say something.
Don't worry.
I shall obey the government
and reform myself.
Cut it out.
Be serious.
Can you give me your word?
Go get them!
Run! Run!
Do you surrender?
- Surrender or we'll keep shooting!
- No, we won't!
Shoot! Shoot!
Stop, we surrender!
We Win!
Let's go!
Let's go home.
Let's play more.
Let's go.
Let's go somewhere else.
Shall we go in?
No way.
I'll go and see.
Xingxing, come in.
It's too dark. I don't want to.
It's fun inside. Come on in.
No.
Haohao.
Haohao?
I'm coming in.
- You scared me!
- What a pussy-cat!
It's too dark in here.
Come on, this way!
So what's the latest news about the lay-offs?
Everyone is worried.
Nobody knows who's really in charge.
I've asked the manager several times.
All he did was give me attitude.
Said I should set an example
as an outstanding individual.
As though that was my idea.
And that was years ago already.
It's so upsetting.
To hell with him!
Yingming was smart to start his own business.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Haiyan, you're here.
- You're here.
- Yup.
Have you had dinner?
I'll heat up some leftovers for you.
- Right.
- I'm fine. I'm taking Haohao to his grandma.
- Haohao, time to go.
- Let me finish this.
- Hurry up!
- Let me finish, please.
- Where's your coat? They can't stop playing.
- Here's his coat.
Liyun, listen.
Today they caught a family
hiding out in the village.
The mother was seven months along.
What were these folks thinking?
Putting themselves through such torture.
- Say goodbye.
- Goodbye, Uncle and Auntie.
- Goodbye, Haohao.
- See you.
Watch your steps.
Let's go.
Comrades!
Today, we have a new agenda
for our meeting.
This is neither an award ceremony
nor an annual review.
It concerns key decisions on livelihood.
Every crisis harbors an opportunity.
I know full well
that each worker's welfare is at stake.
And their ripple effect
on the whole organization.
Patriotism knows neither latitude
nor longitude.
When you're feeling low,
forget not our nation's plight.
"Serve your country
before sewing your own interests."
You're the one who forgets it!
- Comrades!
- Get to the point!
We Chinese have along history
of selfless patriotism.
Let me give you an example.
The country is in jeopardy, comrades!
- What jeopardy?
- Spit it out!
If the enemy is at your doorstep,
What shall soldiers do, comrades?
- What shall soldiers do?
- What do you want to say?
They sacrifice themselves without hesitation.
They'll lay down their lives for the homeland.
Comrades, please.
Now let's come back to us, OK?
Our factory is in financial doldrums.
Our workforce is too large to sustain
so many workers.
So what can we do?
- It's your fault! No lay-offs!
- To relieve...
To relieve the factory's burden,
we must sacrifice our state-guaranteed jobs.
There's no shame in redundancy, comrades,
and even higher honor in re-employment.
Therefore,
some of you must make the sacrifice
and seek employment elsewhere.
Listen to me, comrades.
We're in a market economy now.
Our industry has undergone reform, too.
Understand?
No more iron rice bowls!
- You can't just fire us.
- You should get sacked first!
Comrades!
There's no shame in redundancy.
- And even higher honor in reemployment.
- You can't lay us off like this!
As long as you work hard...
As long as you work hard
with your own hands,
you can still help
to build our great socialist country.
- We want our job!
Comrades, think about it.
Listen to your own conscience:
"The country is in jeopardy.
If I don't step down, who will?"
You step down first!
- Silence!
- You step down first!
Enough, comrades.
I'll announce the names
on the redundancy list.
"The phoenix that dies in flames
will rise again from the ashes."
I'll read out the lay-off list now.
Be quiet! Please!
From the Sorting Department,
Zhang Yan.
- Will you accept this?!
- No!
- Huo Jianguo.
- No, we won't!
Quiet! Quiet!
Feng Xiaobo.
- Give us our jobs back!
- Yu Yonggang.
Wang Tianquan.
Wang Liyun.
Give us our jobs back!
Hello?
I really couldn't make a decision on my own.
Like I said over the phone.
From...
From that one time...
I found out on the day
I got my U.S. visa.
Man plans, God laughs.
Does your brother know?
What am I to tell him?
That I'm pregnant
and you're the father?
Don't worry. It's still early.
Don't beat yourself up.
We're adults.
Go talk to Liyun about this.
I'm staying for a few more days.
I know how much it means to both of you.
If you want to keep the child,
I won't go to the U.S.
until after the birth.
But what about yourself?
Don't worry about me.
I've thought it through.
Maybe this is karma.
- Payback for my brother and sister-in-law.
- Payback?
This isn't about paybacks.
This is...
Think about the child.
Growing up with... without a mother.
Liyun will make a better mother than me.
Don't drag Liyun into this.
That's not the point, not at all.
Don't tell her it's my child.
I'll return to Beijing after your decision.
Tell Liyun it's someone else's.
This is my own doing.
It's me who came to you.
I can't pretend I didn't want it myself.
When you left, I wanted to go after you.
But I was too young then.
I just couldn't bear to see you two suffer.
This time,
I knew exactly what I was doing.
After I leave,
I don't think we'll see each other again.
I'm not young anymore.
I didn't expect this.
I thought I'd be happy.
But...
now that I'm here,
I'm suddenly scared.
I wanted to tell Liyun the truth myself,
and ask her for forgiveness.
I'm sorry, Yaojun.
Am I being immature?
MISSING PERSON: LIU XING
Something strange happened today.
What was it?
On my way out,
I saw a woman on an incoming ferry.
She was obviously not a local.
She seemed so familiar,
but I couldn't recall who she was.
That happens sometimes.
Just like
the moment we arrived here.
It felt as if we'd been here in a past life.
That's true.
I was thinking.
When I...
die,
will it be here
or in our hometown?
We agreed not to bring this up again.
If I lose you, too,
how could I go on?
What's with you today?
Yaojun,
if you want a divorce,
I'll accept it.
I don't know
if it was a woman's sixth sense.
It's true.
I also felt
someone watching me across the water.
I didn't dare to look.
Liyun and I only have each other to live for.
Especially Liyun.
She won't survive another blow.
But you've wanted a child for so long.
Only if the child is our own.
If we do this,
I'll be hurting three people.
Liyun.
The child.
And you.
I understand.
Maybe this is my fate.
I'm resigned to it.
Xingxing!
Take him to the hospital!
Whose idea was it?
Tell me!
How many times have I told you?
Don't go down to the reservoir.
Why don't you listen?
Why don't you?
Was it your idea or Xingxing's?
Say something!
Say something.
Just tell me!
You won't be eating anything until you tell me.
I'll let you starve.
How many times have I told you?
Don't go down to the reservoir!
Tell me what we should do now!
Don't you dare cry.
Don't raise your voice.
The neighbors can hear you.
If you yell like this,
you'll scare the boy.
What shall we do?
Tell me.
The boy's scared to death.
He won't say anything.
We've sent him to his grandparents
and asked the school for some time off.
Let's not tell him what happened yet.
If he asks about Xingxing,
just say he's with his grandma.
It's Haohao's fault.
I've cautioned him so many times.
- Do not take Xingxing to the reservoir.
- Enough.
They're just kids.
You can't blame them.
Blame me, please.
I've spoiled Haohao too much.
I'll give him a good beating at home.
Cut it out.
I'm tired.
Get some rest.
We'll head back now.
Chairman Wang is here, too.
Take care.
Sis...
How shameless they are.
Enough.
How can we make up for this?
Xingxing was their only child.
He didn't have to be their only one.
Pardon?
You know what I mean.
I dare you to say that again.
That's enough.
Moli, Why dredge it up again?
I feel sorry for Yaojun and Liyun.
What are you insinuating?
That this was my fault?
Don't you blame this on me.
What did I do wrong?
Spell it out.
Please.
Give it a rest.
Haohao can hear us.
Do you want to eat something?
What's wrong? Is it your tummy?
It's OK. We're going home.
Don't cry.
The fever made him talk nonsense, right?
What he said couldn't be true.
He was probably really shaken up.
That's right.
And probably under too much stress.
What should we do now?
What to do?
Go to bed.
Don't cry.
Listen to me.
Never mention this to Haohao.
But what about Yaojun and Liyun?
This is unforgivable.
Out of my way!
No, don't you dare!
Drive faster!
Give it a rest.
- Let's have another round!
- OK.
Thank you, Auntie.
Help yourselves.
Liu Xing,
come over for a second.
Come on.
Help yourselves.
Xingxing,
are they from your school?
No.
Then who are they?
Friends.
Friends?
They don't go to school?
No.
Just like me.
Xingxing,
do you know how hard we tried to find you?
Can't you see you're letting everyone down?
What do I care?
The missing person notice said
I have an ID card now.
Leave it.
If it's come to this,
What else do we have to evade?
Since you've made up your mind,
we won't force you to stay here.
Here's your ID card as we promised,
and some money.
It's not a lot, so be careful with it.
This ID card
makes you an adult
and grants you legal status.
Go and get a job.
Don't make us worry about you anymore.
Mom and Dad are very grateful to you.
We turned you into a stand-in for Xingxing.
And you played along.
To make us happy.
Tod ay,
we give you back your true identity.
Zhou Yongfu.
One more thing.
If you get into trouble out there,
remember how I used to beat you up.
Moli?
Yaojun.
It's you.
Come on in, it's cold outside.
Liyun?
Moli is here.
Sis.
Have a seat.
I've brought you some dumplings.
Haiyan and my brother made them.
Have a seat.
It's been a long time.
- Hot water.
- Thanks.
It's cold outside.
Have you eaten yet?
- I'll boil some dumplings for you.
- No, I'm good.
Have some water.
Meiyu and Xinjian are back.
They dropped by earlier.
They suggested getting together
tomorrow night.
So I wanted to come and invite you.
You all have a good time.
We'll pass.
So Xinjian made Meiyu his wife after all.
When he followed her to Hainan,
I knew it'd work out.
It's the little Chinese New Year.
Liyun, those dumplings are stuffed with fennel.
My brother said you like them.
Let me pour you more water.
Thanks.
Careful, it's hot.
So you've been well?
And you?
We get by.
Everything is fine.
Oh, Haiyan!
Happy New Year!
It's your auntie!
Or rather "Godmother!"
- What's the baby's name?
- Just call it "Baby."
Little sweetie!
Say "Auntie!"
It's "Godmother!"
- How are you, Xinjian?
- Fine.
You look good.
Meiyu, your face is red.
- How about you?
- We're very well.
The flame's too big.
Is everything OK with Haiyan?
She has problems sleeping,
and she babbles.
She's paranoid that others
talk behind her back.
You better keep a closer eye on her.
Let her get some time off.
I already told her to quit her job.
We're getting by better now.
We don't need her measly salary.
So you haven't caught up
with them for years?
I have visited them.
They were very polite to me.
But we had nothing to say to each other.
We used to
be so close.
Liyun and Yaojun don't blame you at all.
So much time has passed since the accident.
Don't think about it anymore, OK?
You have to move on.
You don't get it. Cut it out.
I know, I understand.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You were just doing your job.
You didn't have a choice.
Stop, stop, Haiyan.
OK,OK.
Liyun!
Help!
Doctor!
Dr Shen, I'll be direct.
Her condition isn't looking good.
I'm afraid the diagnosis is final.
I see.
If you want her to remain hospitalized,
I can make arrangements accordingly.
That won't be necessary.
Don't tell the patient yet.
Is it that serious?
It could be anytime,
if something
like this happens again.
What about surgery?
Not recommended.
The tumor is too big now,
pressing against the nerves.
It's been diagnosed as malignant.
You haven't told your mom, have you?
Not yet.
How could you let her do all the cooking?
Mom, let me help you.
No, no, no.
I can handle it. Relax.
- Mom, let us do it.
- Don't worry.
- Are you still feeling dizzy?
- Not anymore.
After a whole day's sleeping, I'm well now.
Hurry.
My little baby!
Go sit down.
Take it easy.
Here, here, here.
Thanks, Mom.
Something strange is going on.
Guess who I dreamed about recently.
Who?
Liyun and Yaojun.
You don't know them.
My godparents when I was young.
Really?
You've never mentioned them before.
I dreamed of them too, some time ago.
What do you think this means?
It means nothing, just a dream.
More than that.
I was thinking...
If I were to die all of a sudden,
my biggest regret
would be not seeing them again.
You're talking nonsense again.
It's been so many years.
Maybe they've forgotten us already.
They couldn't have.
Mom,
I have to go to work.
Listen to the doctor.
No dancing or strenuous activity.
Be sure to get some rest, OK?
Take your medicine.
You've kept in touch with them, right?
Moli paid them a visit
before she left
and gave me their number.
But I never called them.
Give them a call.
Invite them over for my birthday.
We'll pay for the trip.
Do we have to?
Just tell them
I'm dying.
Before I go,
I want to see them.
What's this nonsense?
I want them to know
that over the past 20 years,
for me, Li Haiyan,
not a day has passed
without me thinking of them.
Dear passengers, please return
to your seat due to the turbulence.
Or sit tight and wear a seat belt.
Please don't move around the cabin.
Please take care of your children.
Thank you.
Isn't it funny
we're still afraid of dying?
Dear passengers,
Flight CA272 to Beijing
is ready for boarding.
Please bring your belongings to Gate 5.
Aren't you cold?
It's alright.
It's good to feel cold.
We haven't felt this cold for years.
Have you heard from the boy?
Who?
No.
He has to renew his ID card.
Right.
Every citizen's card
will get a new chip installed.
Sister,
- have you told our old man I'm here?
- Not yet.
He might get overexcited.
I barely recognize this place.
The streets are wider now.
The old building opposite was demolished?
All these are new.
Let me take the bags.
Everything looks so different.
Wait for me, please.
Thank you.
Our old block hasn't changed.
All that talk about demolishing it
was just talk.
Do people still live here?
Some moved out,
others sublet their units.
But your building has been left alone.
Natural gas and broadband are installed,
except in yours.
With so few residents left,
nobody cares anymore.
Every winter when the heat com es on,
I come by to drain the radiators.
The heating is no good.
I wanted to clean up the apartment
and buy some winter bedding for you.
MASSAGE
Then I thought it's best to leave it up to you.
If it's too uncomfortable here,
come stay with us.
OK, thank you.
Son...
Excuse me, Where is Li Haiyan's room?
Li Haiyan? She's in number 11.
Down the hallway.
- I see. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Have we made it in time?
Yes.
Xinjian.
Yingming.
Haohao, come here.
Greet your godparents.
Look, you're a big boy now.
Godfather.
Haohao.
Godmother.
You're taller than me.
Haiyan.
Liyun and Yaojun are here for you.
It's me, Liyun.
Yaojun and I have come to see you.
What do you want to say?
I'm listening.
We are
rich now.
No need to be afraid.
We can help you
pay the fine for a new baby.
I've missed you so much.
- We're leaving.
- OK, OK.
Thank you.
- My condolences.
- Thank you.
Take care. Watch your step.
- Take care of yourself.
- OK, thank you.
Watch your step.
Farewell. Thank you.
- How's everybody doing?
- Everyone's well.
See my old buddies from the factory?
They're in great shape.
They don't even have any gray hair.
Why don't you and Liyun
stay here a bit longer?
The city has really changed.
Yes, don't leave again.
At our age, we should be spending time
together. Just like old times.
I'm afraid that's not gonna happen.
Why not?
Yingming could get you an apartment.
What are we talking about?
Yaojun says he can't move back here.
Why don't you put them up
in one of the condos you're building.
I'd be more than happy.
Haiyan never stopped nagging me to do it.
Let me take you around
my housing developments.
If one catches your eye, it's yours.
And what if we can't afford it?
Where's Haohao?
He was here a minute ago.
He must've gone to the restroom.
I'll check.
Stay here.
I'll go.
Help yourselves.
When's your due date?
Very soon.
It's a shame Haiyan won't see the baby.
So you've made up your mind?
This has tortured us
for far too long.
I don't want to be like Mom.
Burdened with guilt until the end.
It was neither your fault, nor your mother's.
I know. No one's blaming Mom.
She was just doing her job.
But I know how she really felt deep down.
So...
- should I get them over here?
- No.
I'll drive them home.
Shall I join you?
No.
So much has changed, right?
Where are we now?
This used to be Wuyi Square.
Qingnian Road is over there.
We just drove past
where the auditorium used to be.
Gosh!
- They tore that down too?
- They sure did.
Most of the old factory dormitories are gone.
Ours is one of the few still around.
Right.
There's almost no trace of our past.
We're here.
Thank you, Haohao.
Godfather, Godmother...
may I come up for a second?
- Yes.
- Of course, of course!
Just park the car here.
Come on.
We could've stayed with Yaojun's sister.
But we wanted
to be back here again.
We've been away for too long.
Does anything look familiar to you?
Come in.
Please.
Come on in.
Let me give you some water.
- Put on some tea leaves.
- OK.
You still remember this place, right?
Nothing has changed here.
It's exactly as we left it.
We're only here for a few days.
No point in rearranging things.
Same old furniture.
Appliances are old, too.
We were tidying up and somehow
the photo ended up there.
Haohao, sit down.
Have some tea.
Put more tea leaves in.
No, that's plenty already.
Godfather.
Godmother.
Please sit down so I can tell you something.
We're listening.
This has been weighing on me all these years.
Now Mother's funeral has brought us
back together.
I think
it's time to share it with you.
That day,
when we decided to go to the reservoir,
we agreed
to stay near the shore.
But Xingxing
wouldn't go.
I was annoyed,
so I left him there.
Then the other kids started making fun of him.
This embarrassed me.
So I told him,
if he didn't get down to the reservoir
I'd stop being his friend.
So he came down.
A while later,
the other kids
started swimming towards deeper water.
I told him to join them,
but he was too timid.
Sol
dragged him towards the reservoir.
Xingxing was so scared, he screamed,
and grabbed onto me.
The other boys kept teasing us.
I got really angry.
Then I...
Then I nudged him into the water.
I gave him a push.
What did your
parents say about this?
You didn't ask me,
because you wanted to protect me.
My parents kept silent for the same reasons.
They hoped
that with time, I'd forget it all.
However,
from that day on,
I've felt this thing inside me.
It was like a tree, growing bigger as I grew.
It feels like it's going to explode from my body.
I can't stand it anymore.
I have to tell you the truth.
Let it out, Son.
You'll feel better.
Take this and chop that little bastard in half.
An eye for an eye.
You're crazy!
Shen Yingming, I'm telling you.
Never bring this up with Haohao.
Not one word.
You hear me?
You and Haiyan,
stop blaming your child.
For as long as you live,
don't say a word.
Xingxing is gone.
We must take good care of Haohao.
He's just a child.
If you never mention it,
he'll put it behind him.
Put it down.
Let's clear away the grass first.
Son,
Mom and Dad have come to visit you.
Yes?
Haohao?
OK!
OK,OK, OK.
I'm hanging up.
The baby?
The baby.
Boy or girl?
Boy,
a big boy!
How wonderful.
- Godfather, Godmother, come in!
- Congrats.
Thank you, come in.
Wow, look who's here.
Congratulations, Yingming.
Come meet your grandson.
You really didn't need to bring anything.
You're a granddad now.
We should celebrate.
This is Grandpa.
This is Grandma.
He's smiling!
Let Grandma hold you.
Give us a smile.
Any name yet?
The names I came up with all got rejected.
Have a seat.
Let's call him Dudu.
That's cute!
Auntie Moli, can you see us?
Look Who's here.
Moli!
It's been an eternity!
Don't I look young after all these years?
Liyun, you're back.
Moli, you haven't changed at all.
You still look so young.
You can't be serious.
- Are you well?
- Yes.
Moli, where is Sunny? Go fetch him.
Wait a second.
Sunny? Who is that?
- Moli's son.
- Who would've thought?
She never wanted a family.
And now she has a big boy already.
Well, she changed her mind.
He's coming.
Do you rem ember me?
Hello, even/body!
Hello! How do you do?
Sunny, hello!
Look who we have here.
You're an uncle. Meet your nephew, Dudu.
She must be the great-aunt...
Call her great-auntie.
Moli, we are all great-aunts now.
XING REPAIR SHOP
Hey, who are you looking for?
If you miss any snacks from home, tell me.
I'll have them sent over.
Hello?
Hello, is this Liu Yaojun?
Dad?
It's me, Xingxing.
Xingxing.
Mom is right here, too.
She wants to hear your voice.
Xingxing is back.
Hello?
Xingxing!
You're home.
We came back to visit friends
in our hometown.
We'll be back soon.
Xingxing,
Mom and Dad miss you very much.
Son?
Take care of my business.
No doubt, you're also the boss!
Hold on, "Boss Liu."
Xingxing, how long will you stay this time?
That's great.
You've brought your girlfriend with you?
Xingxing has a girlfriend!
That's even better!
Great!
We're very well, don't worry about us.
We'll be back soon.
Wait for us, Son.
We miss you so much!