I was always wondering...
what my future would be like.
Good morning, Truly.
Morning.
Graduate from my dream school,
fully develop my potential,
realize my dreams.
Bravo!
The lucrative deal in Shenzhen
is finally signed to us.
Listen,
you should learn more from Truly.
Do everything you can for the company.
Fight for more good deals!
Cheers!
Thank you boss.
Thank you.
Wow!
What is this, Truly?
So shiny!
My life will shine...
like a diamond.
Hurray!
Shall we got for spicy hot pot?
Sure.
Which restaurant? I'll make a reservation.
Hello?
What time do you think it is?
Why are you still in the office?
I've been waiting for 5 minutes.
Sorry.
I'll go to the restaurant now.
If you're not here in 5 minutes, I'll leave.
That's not enough time!
It'll take me half an hour to get there.
Hello?
Shit.
Conference call with Edinburgh at midnight.
Your team will stay to prepare for it.
But I have...
I'll do it now.
Look at Truly.
What a role model!
Yes, sir.
Everyone.
Let's stay a little longer to work on it.
Go! Go! Go!
Earlier done, earlier home.
No one ever told me,
the truth is...when you grow up,
it's likely you'll have a not-so-good job,
be in a not-so-good relationship,
and live a not-so-good life.
...dunno what he wants to eat.
It seems like Hsin is on a diet...
Go! Go !Go! Early done, early home.
She's the one who told us to stay.
I won't get her bonus anyway.
The manager told us to learn from Truly.
Fuck! Who wants to learn from her?
Working overtime for little salary.
She treats the company as her family.
The company treats her as animal.
To be honest,
I feel bad for people like her.
I hope I won't be like her when I get old.
Who wants to be like her! Miserable.
I think...
if I ran into this woman
when I was 18,
I would have definitely laughed at her
like them, without mercy.
Yabiyabi. Good evening everyone.
This is Guangyu.
Do you like who you are now?
When we grow up,
we become sophisticated
and tend to compromise
in order to survive.
We become someone we don't recognize.
Would you sometimes
miss the time when you
were rather naive and dared to dream?
Is that part of you still there?
Do you still remember those people
who played an important role in your life?
(My dream: Go to Andy Lau's concert...)
Tonight,
we'll start our program with
this song from me to you all.
A song we haven't heard for a long time.
"Forget Love Water" by Andy Lau.
Good morning. Here is the latest news...
yesterday Alec Su of The Little Tigers
said he dropped out of Taiwan University.
The whole entertainment world is in shock.
Are you giving birth? Are you done or not?
I'm done!
Back then, I was turning 18
and truly understood something important:
History has proven that, there are mainly
two types of young girls in the world.
Hey, here she comes.
Wow! How elegant.
Oh my God! She's gorgeous!
So cute!
Pretty girls who are popular...
Don't go!
Wait for me! -Tao Minmin!
and
those who are not pretty.
My name is Lin Truly.
Sorry!
I'm the one who just fell on the street.
If you're a guy,
let me tell you a story of an ordinary girl
who you've never bothered to care about
and her ordinary life.
Back then, the most important decision
we had to make every day
was what to eat for breakfast.
Can you please hurry up?
Is it that tough to decide?
was on the day of exam,
we'd say...
I didn't prepare for it.
Neither did I.
I thought we were having math exam.
The most luxurious thing to do,
was to go shopping in the bookstore.
Back then,
that was our department store.
The biggest dream we had
was to meet our idols
one day.
The shame of being shameless
is shameless
Somehow young girls of that time
had some kind of fantasy.
We believed whoever collected most photos
would be the most qualified person
to marry him.
This is Small.
Although large in size,
she is a super romantic teenage girl.
Kaneshiro Takeshi is her ex,
and now
Aaron Kwok is her fiance.
Even I am not married yet,
how come you already have a husband?
Boss Lau...
However hard you try, he'll never reply.
What you do is called shameless.
This is Meimei.
Very cheerful,
but...almost too cheerful.
Girls, where are you going?
Back in our teenage life, we were always
doing silly things apart from studying.
And this is the silliest
among all.
Ouyang is coming. He's so handsome.
Hey, be quiet. Come on.
He has a style. He's here.
There is always a boy like this,
in every teenage girl's life.
Thank you.
It's on me.
60 please. -60.
Somehow they're always basketball players,
secret crush for every girl in the school.
I feel Ouyang is looking at me.
I think he's looking at me.
We can giggle for the whole day
just because of a look from him.
Dear all, can you please stop helping
those idiots send love letters
to our Minmin?
Especially this kind of idiot,
who misused "disney" for "destiny".
This kind of ordinary, simple life
was turned upside down by that very letter.
(to Lin Truly)
This is a chain letter from South African
missionary Anthony DE Croud.
Now the good luck is bestowed on you.
Send 5 copies to your friends,
and the good luck is yours.
Otherwise disasters will be waiting for you.
In 1979, Mr. Chen from Taiwan did not
take the letter seriously and tore it apart.
...he died in a car accident the next day.
In 1963, Flayre from Holland burnt it...
3 days later, his mother started to...
suffer an incurable disease.
(You still have three days. Good luck.)
The person I want to send chain letter to
the most, is Lin Sincere.
5 places in this exam.
Last time he got the lowest score. Besides,
he's spent 7 years on a 5-year program...
Don't you talk back!
Only if you could get half of the grade
30 points.
You even tried to alter it
with a different color.
How stupid!
My red pen ran out of ink.
Take it.
Thank you mom.
Take one more.
Thank you dad!
Many of you probably
had the same thought,
"Am I'm really my parents' child?"
But if my brother's family is really ruined,
I might suffer as well.
So I dismissed that idea.
I gave the first letter
to him.
Lin Truly.
Question 1:
If the balls are put in the order of red,
blue, green, what's the color of ball 555?
It's ok if you don't know the answer,
but why drawing it like this?
Don't you dodge!
There must be a psycho teacher like this
in everyone's school years.
"Wang Baidan"
Our home room teacher and math teacher.
We all call him
"Wang Badan" (asshole)
I haven't even started!
Come back.
You're even louder than me.
I gave the second letter
to Tao Minmin.
It's definitely not because I envy her
Not even because
she's that girl who could
get his attention.
It's simply because she lives next door.
Right on my way home.
What? A good student?
Do the recycling.
Hey you.
Kick it back.
Ouyang Extraordinary.
I might've seen this disgusting name before.
As there is a "God" in every school,
there is also a "boss".
Stand up.
Hsu Taiyu.
Last number of the last class in 3rd grade.
He's the boss who leads our school in
turf wars and charge others protection fee.
Rumor has it that
he fights, runs away from home,
he's on drug
has killed people, set fire...
So notorious that no school wants him,
except for First High School...
How daring are you to be here.
You despise us
the 12 Masters of First High?
What about Ten Brothers
from Chuoshui River?
Kill them.
He's even appointed as school patrol
Indecent clothing.
Eating while walking.
Studying too hard.
Too matured body.
First High...
has since been trapped
in the devil's clutches.
Recycle it!
Hey, what are you doing?
Why bully others like this?
What the hell are you guys doing?
Here comes the director,
let's go.
Come on! Go, go.
Chicken.
Therefore...
I decided to send him the third letter.
Guile.
G your mother.
Sorry
(to Hsu Taiyu)
It's pink
with fragrance.
Love letter?
Aren't you over the moon, boss?
Over what! Get lost.
Who has the guts to write him a love letter?
Oh, he was even blushing.
Blushing! Hahahaha
He must be over the moon now.
Not just over the moon...
Over the whole world!
Boss.
Did you hear about it already?
Hsu Taiyu had a car accident yesterday.
Lin Truly...
If I find out who cursed boss,
I'll make sure to break his arms and legs.
Sorry, she needs to take her medicine.
Lin Truly, let's go.
Why are you so heavy!
Go.
Boss, watch your step.
Someone is spreading the rumor,
saying this year's school anniversary
will be suspended due to track renovation.
Let me clarify it here.
This year, school anniversary festival
will be held as scheduled.
Since I'm retiring from First High soon.
The new director will take over
the responsibility as the organizer.
Last but not least, do not leave yet.
School patrol is now conducting
a surprise safety inspection.
Dahe.
Breast baring.
That's too nasty.
Make a note.
Confiscate it.
Hey you.
We need to talk.
Where are we going?
Just follow us.
No!
Enjoy, boss.
In 1979,
Mr. Chen from Taiwan...
did not take the letter seriously
and tore it apart.
The next day he died in a car accident.
So it's you.
Whose films do you like?
What?
Who?
S...Stephen Chow.
Which film do you like best?
All..."All's Well, Ends Well".
How many "all"s?
One.
Your birthday?
Good, you're honest.
What don't you like about me?
Nothing.
I...think...you're
tall...
and cute...
and if I look closely...
You even look a bit like Andy Lau?
I know you sent the chain letter to me
because of him.
No!
What no?
I can't change the film?
Would you like to change the film?
Yes, to...
All..."All's Well, Ends Well".
Sure, just a moment.
Let's...
be friends.
What?
You just introduced yourself.
In Taiyu's dictionary, friend means
unconditional devotion.
In order to protect Ouyang,
I'm willing to listen to Hsu Taiyu.
Be his slave.
Auntie.
One sesame noodle.
Don't put sesame dressing and noodles
together. They need to be separated.
No fatty no lean for braised pork rice
but half half.
And veggie tofu soup without spring onion.
Two eggs in it but don't beat it.
Thank you.
If no spring onion in veggie tofu soup,
why have it on sesame noodles?
Get a new one!
Wait.
This is your reward.
Autographed photo of Andy Lau.
It's Andy Low from the TV show.
Here.
I thought you forgot your book for math
excursion, where are the other people?
Idiot.
What kind of excursion for math class?
Hurry up.
The movie starts at 2.
Ah...
The bell rang already, I'm going back.
Then who'll get food for me?
Who'll collect my trash?
Who'll fan for me?
I can't climb the wall.
So...
I really can't do this.
You wanna die?
What if the teacher finds out?
I've never skipped class in my life...
If you've never done that in your uniform,
you'll regret in the future.
You're so heavy.
Hurry up.
Don't goof off.
Can I go back for tutorial class?
Attach yourself to the end of the line.
Hsu Taiyu, I had enough!
Are you ok?
Are you alright?
I'm ok...
Then go get squid balls for me!
Hsu Taiyu!
Thank you.
Go away! What are you looking at?
Sit down.
Quickly!
Sit!
Sit tight!
Hsu Taiyu.
Don't you dare touch my gal...
What's wrong!
Holding hands when roller skating?
How can you do it without holding hands?
Shut up!
What?
Kill him.
Sakuraki.
Hsu Taiyu!
Boss, are you ok?
It's ok.
Hsu Taiyu!
If I didn't have final exam this afternoon,
I'll never let you get away with it!
Let's go back to study!
I'll get you, you motherfucker!
(No distinction of classes in teaching.)
Miss Lin.
I know you're innocent.
If you to tell me
what happened at the skating rink,
you won't be punished.
I...
I don't...remember
what happened when where who at all.
Right. You went to indecent place
during school hours. Your punishment is
10 hours of pool cleaning.
Go back to your class.
What were you doing?
Hey, school patrol!
Lin Truly!
How come you were in the office with Taiyu?
Shhhh...for what?
We can't what?
I see! How many words?
Ouyang!
Ouyang what?
See...
...your face
We can't let Ouyang see you.
Yes!
Lin Truly?
I didn't know you're actually pretty good.
I also like roller skating too.
Next time we can go together.
Lin Truly.
Ouyang knows your name!
And even asked you out...
Praised by Ouyang for skipping class...
Strangely amazing.
Look, love fire is burning.
Love fire is bouncing.
Warmly, our hearts
embrace each other.
I told my mom...
Did she give her approval?
Yes.
But...
What if the teacher finds out
about us...?
This is not allowed by the school.
Don't worry.
I am the father.
I'll take the responsibility.
So glad you're here.
You should go now!
Others can come here anytime.
They'll find us suspicious.
Was someone here?
What should we do?
Will people find out about us?
We'll be fine.
Let's get out of here now.
What the fuck are you looking at!
Did you just try to drown yourself?
Just for that prick?
Then what on earth are you crying for?
You're the silly one...
Do you have it with you all the time?
If you never had beer in your uniform...
I'll regret in the future.
I got it.
You wrote this?
You like Tao Minmin?
Dear Tao Minmin:
When you were trying the hairpin yesterday,
I really longed to touch...
the beautiful black hair of yours!
You're so sick.
Because...
It's so nice to meet you
do you know that?
Quoting lyrics...you really suck.
Now we're both kind of...
Association of the Dumped members.
For the first time I think you're clever.
What?
Let's help them break up.
If you help me chase Tao Minmin...
wouldn't that make your Ouyang
single again?
Sorry! Sorry!
Excuse me!
Did you bring powdered milk and bottle?
Yeah.
Hsu Taiyu!
Sorry...
Mommy's late.
You must be starving.
Slowly... slowly.
Look at the eyes...
So adorable.
Just like you.
Should we take it to the vet for shots?
Yeah. Let's do it after school soon.
OK.
We misunderstood them.
There is nothing between them.
Just a puppy.
Having a dog now together means
they'll walk the dog together. Get closer.
Then the dog will have more puppies.
We can't let this happen.
Say that again. What do you think of me?
You're tall...
and cute...
If I look closely...
You even look a bit like Andy Lau.
Tao Minmin!
The campus belle!
So pretty!
Our boss is hot!
Tao Minmin.
Wanna be my gal?
Say yes Say yes\\(U VUL I NIMNIM OAT)
If you dare to tell others what happened,
you are dead.
Don't you tell others boss is dumped.
Let me repeat.
What the fuck!
Get out of there!
Hsu Taiyu...
I think...we should give up.
Tao Minmin...will not be attracted by you.
There is no such word like "give up".
(Report stray dogs to have them caught.)
As long as the dog is gone,
they won't have excuse to meet each other.
Don't do silly things.
I got it!
Hurry up.
Puppy...they'll think you ran away...
you're not stolen.
Hurry up!
Someone's coming.
Such a stupid idea.
Where can he go?
Who's gonna take care of him?
I thought you were really that cruel,
that you wouldn't care if he dies.
Before you can find him a new owner,
he's staying with you.
Why the fuck do you pee...
Quick!
Alright, alright.
What should we call him?
What about...
Andy?
You like it?
No way.
How can you humiliate my idol like this!
Besides...
It's a she.
ND the alphabets.
Anything wrong?
ND...ND...
See! She doesn't like it!
Why not?
Because you can't humiliate my idol!
Besides, she's a girl! -ND!
I'm gonna rub some dog pee on your head.
ND... -Hsu Taiyu!
(Report stray dogs to have them caught.)
It seems like he's really caught...
I looked for her everywhere...
Maybe she's just taken back by her owner.
Who's on duty today?
Clean it up!
You have no respect for your teacher...
Stand up.
No need.
Who did this?
Cursing others with this silly stuff!
Come to my office and turn yourself in.
Excuse me.
You should at least take exams.
You don't remember what I said?
I got an anonymous letter saying you did it.
You know.
I remain unmarried for so many years,
devoting myself to you...
I mean...
to the school.
Can't you just do me a favor?
It's ok.
Tell me the truth...
I'm very understanding.
Listen...
If I find out that you're lying to me later,
I'll have no choice but to punish you.
I know who wrote it.
Wrote what?
Hsu Taiyu.
You...
I wrote it.
Very good.
Miss Lin.
You can go now.
Thank you.
I knew it!
Hsu Taiyu.
I really wish it's not you again.
How can you leave in the middle of my talk?
Ms. Chen
Let me punish him first.
Mr. Wang, I haven't finished yet.
Let me scold him first.
It's not a matter of...
No, I was in the middle of scolding him.
One thing at one time.
Don't rush.
You first.
OK.
Hsu Taiyu.
Why do you think the school still took you in
even though it's your last year
in high school?
Because you were in science honors class.
Even attended
Science Olympiad competition.
What happened to you?
Have you heard of
"The Tortoise and the Hare"?
And "Eradicating the Three Scourges"
Do you know who's "Zhou Chu"?
Yeah.
It's pronounced "Chu" not "Choo"...
Thank you.
You...
really didn't have to do that.
That's what a friend is for.
It does me no harm anyway.
One chain letter to me...
One to "Asshole"...
Two others taken away by me...
Who got the last one?
Tao Minmin...
I really regret for it.
That's why...
You should work hard to get her!
Girls like her must have had
enough of compliments.
Why not write bad things about her
to get her attention?
For example...
Thick waist...
Huge butt...
So fake when she talks...
You sure?
Yeah.
And conclude it with...
But still...
I like you a lot.
Hey.
Don't quote lyrics if you have no good idea.
You can quote foreign poets' work.
Who's gonna understand it?
That's why it'll make you look mysterious.
You sure?
Sure.
Let me tell you.
Girls are so difficult to understand.
When we say nothing's wrong...
it means something's wrong.
When we say it's ok,
it means it's not ok.
If we say...
I am fat...
That means we hope you can tell us...
You're not fat at all.
That's the way...
Tao Minmin thinks.
(Chongde Junior High Yearbook)
(Hsu Taiyu)
I'll do this.
You pick that one.
(Ouyang Extraordinary)
Don't stop.
Watch out.
Ouyang Extraordinary...
You actually...
know Hsu Taiyu quite well.
Right?
What?
Did you watch the Bulls vs. Lakers game?
Of course.
Shit, what a dramatic victory.
Jordan is God!
So dramatic!
One-on-one if you dare.
3 minutes.
Whoever swims farther wins.
Bring it on.
C'mon.
A-yuan.
A-yuan...
Hsu Taiyu, don't go further.
Ma Suyuan.
Hsu Taiyu
Taiyu thought the accident wouldn't have
A-yuan.
Happened, if he didn't take the challenge.
That was the last time
I saw Hsu Taiyu,
before he transferred to First High.
He became someone I don't know.
Why don't we meet at Ice Palace,
but here?
You feel embarrassed?
Hsu Taiyu.
Let's have a race.
The winner can make a request.
Whoever crosses that line first wins.
You can never beat me.
Stop or you'll kill yourself.
What's wrong with you?
When you saw me in the pool the other day,
were you afraid that I'd die like Su-yuan,
in front of your eyes.
Ouyang told me everything.
None of your business.
Who are you to shout at me?
Who are you to hurt yourself like this?
It's also not easy for Ouyang, ok?
Ma Suyuan must be pissed off
to see the way you are now.
Don't make me beat you!
Hsu Taiyu.
If I could do it over again,
I'd still have a race with you.
If A-yuan could do it over again,
he'd still go into the sea.
But it's our own decision.
Not your responsibility.
Hsu Taiyu.
You agreed that
the winner can make a request.
What do you want?
Can you...
be that Hsu Taiyu again?
Stand up!
A...attention.
Good morning, sir.
Shut up!
Hsu Taiyu.
Do you...
have any question?
Yes.
Which page are we at today?
Chapter 7 on page 125.
World War 2.
Hsu...
You have
geography textbook in your hand.
Chapter 7.
Page 125.
Take your textbook out!
Those who don't have it...
go and sit next to those who do.
Am I cute?
Wow!
Miss.
You look familiar...
You are my high school...
teacher.
What's wrong with you today?
Going to temple festival?
Not really.
I...
Hurry up!
We need to secure our seats at McDonald's!
Temple festival is this way...
Look at that guy...
So cute... -Look, it's him...
so tall.
So cute...
You idiot.
Look where you're going.
You got a hole in your brain?
It's fine.
Let's look for a seat first
and order later.
You're gonna help me.
OK.
Here's what you ordered.
Thanks.
Have a nice meal.
Hello! Welcome!
What would you like to order?
Hsu Taiyu.
He's studying there.
It seems like he really changed.
Maybe he's here...
because you come here often.
Let's go... -what?
Hey, she wants to talk to you.
I'll find us a table.
That seat is...
Hsu...
I heard you were in science honors class...
If that's the case,
you should never give up.
If there's something you don't understand,
I can help you with it.
Thanks.
You asked me to give you my personal info.
You'll have it.
But...
Don't mistake "Disney" for "Destiny" again.
Why "Destiny"?
Disney is my pseudonym.
What...were you...talking about?
Nothing. They wanted to share the table.
Study.
Hsu Taiyu started to study hard.
Very hard.
Although I think it's because I woke him up,
the truth is...
he did it for Minmin.
He wants to get into top 10
in the coming mock exam.
Hsu Taiyu.
Did he come to see you?
Back then...
if a girl
was willing to give you her personal info,
that means...
she didn't dislike you at all.
(The person I like:)
Latest version of sample exams, good luck.
Thank you.
Ah.
It's my hubby.
When I grow up.
I will go to Taipei for your concert...
A piece of cake.
One day I'll ask Andy Lau
to sing for you.
Really?
Yeah right.
Hey! Don't touch it!
Let's go.
If we add the two together...
Idiot.
sin^2(x) + cos^2(x) = 1
No exception.
What?
Look behind you.
Wow...when did Truly become so serious?
Something's wrong with Boss...hehe.
I live just down there.
It's quite late.
You should go home now.
Oh...
It's ok.
If I linger a bit,
I might run into Tao Minmin.
Oh...
By the way.
ND already learned to pee at the same spot.
Thank God...
she didn't grow into an idiot like you.
For me?
I planned to give it to Tao Minmin.
But it's so ugly and it's Andy Lau...
better give it to you.
Hey...
tell me, for guys...
what's the definition of pretty girls?
You mean what kind of girls Ouyang likes?
Whatever.
Anything.
He was crazy about Vivian Chow before.
What about you?
Uchida Yuki is not bad.
Sakai Noriko also.
Both Japanese?
Yes.
I want to learn roller skating.
Why so sudden?
Because...
Ouyang says he likes roller skating.
You're pretty good...can you teach me?
Sure.
I want this.
Hello, Mr. Tang.
Should I ask my bro to come down?
Where can I get the same look as yours?
Go to hell and get reborn will be easier.
Lin Truly, are you hitting puberty?
Don't be so mean.
It's normal for girls to care their looks.
Let me help you.
Thank you sis.
Are you alright?
Yeah, sprained my ankle, that's all.
Just need to ice it a bit.
Ouyang got injured. Does Truly know?
I don't know...
Let's tell her when she's here.
Hey hey.
Are you close friends of Ouyang's?
Ouyang!
Chiayi, you... -Calm down.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Wow it swells so much.
No way, we must heat it.
Ice it.
Heat it! Were you there in health class?
Hey...
I always ice with this when I'm injured.
Convenient and tasty.
Thanks.
Guess I don't have to visit health center.
I'll go back to class now.
You look cute today.
The hairstyle suits you.
Good luck with your exam.
Wow!
So cute.
Lin Truly, you are so pretty.
I want to look like you!
He said you're cute!
Did you put on makeup?
Hsu Taiyu got 10th place in the mock exam
among all 3rd year students.
While the whole school was still in shock,
the new director arrived.
Littering.
Which eye of yours saw that I littered?
You are the litter.
Director Chuan said...
Everyone in class 317...
is a piece of shit.
Fuck! What the hell!
School regulation says "no hair coloring".
The new director hates people
who break the rules.
Excuse me.
Hsu Taiyu from class 317.
Finally.
You'd better be good until you graduate.
Otherwise I'll kick you out of the school
once you're cited with 3 serious demerits.
As you wish.
I'll do my best.
Because people like you
do not deserve education at all.
Stand up.
Who got first place in the exam this time?
Please stand up.
Let's give him a big hand.
Good job.
So good that I have to ask Hsu...
how did you cheat in the exam?
I asked people to give you a big hand
to see if you know what is shame!
You just talked, stand up!
Sir.
I didn't talk.
I have eyes to judge that.
Did you help him...
in the exam?
Can someone come forward and testify that
Hsu Taiyu cheated.
No one wants to tell the truth, huh?
Now...
All of you, go to the running track.
Stand up!
I know you dislike me...
but it has nothing to do with them!
Leave them alone.
Fine.
Want to play the hero?
I'll leave all 50 rounds to you.
Run to your heart's content.
Director Chuan must be sick. So strict.
Demerit for skirts above the knees.
A lap is 400 meters!
I heard that Hsu already finished 35 rounds.
I heard that he cheated in the exam
and started a battle with the director.
He's punished to run 50 rounds.
He's not that kind of person.
Minmin, Chiayi is bullshiting.
Lin Truly...
Hsu Taiyu.
Why don't you tell the truth?
Hsu Taiyu!
Excuse me.
Director.
Hsu Taiyu really didn't cheat.
I can testify for him.
He really studied very hard.
You should stay away from people like him.
Tell him,
if he can't finish, 1 more demerit for him.
Plus one-week suspension from school.
Let him reflect on himself at home.
How's your boss doing?
Dunno...
He doesn't answer on his pager.
I heard that the school festival next week
might be cancelled by the director.
He said we students don't study enough.
What the fuck is he thinking!
Students also deserve human rights!
The authority shouldn't let him bully us!
Of course not!
We'll let the authority hear our voice
at the school festival next week.
Let him know he can't do whatever he likes.
Let's do it!
Sorry.
Please stand up for our rights -Please.
Please, the revolt needs your support.
The revolt needs your support.
Please have a look...
Please, please have a look.
Please support First High's revolt.
We really really
need your support.
Don't take it.
You're done if the director knows.
Leave it to me.
Hand it out over there. You, there.
You're openly instigating others to revolt,
violating the regulations,
humiliating your teachers.
Everyone who helped you
now has a demerit.
Do your parents know what you're doing?
You brought disgrace on your parents.
You brought shame on them.
The teacher said Hsu is a gangster.
He's not even allowed to go to school!
You completely destroyed my reputation.
You...go upstairs and write your confession.
You're grounded for two days.
Now!
How embarrassing.
I was scolded by the teacher on the phone.
I...
Hello? -This is Truly's cram school.
Lin Truly is busy now.
Hey...
It's a guy...
Hello?
It's you again!
Never call again!
You are so rude.
If he calls again, let me pick it up.
Must be him.
Pretending to be cram school staff.
Lin Truly.
Don't call me these two days.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Nothing's wrong. Bye.
Are you ok?
It's so late...you must be going to bed?
I'm just stopping by.
Well...
I'm leaving then.
Hold on.
ND.
Are you alright?
Never knew I can be suspended
from school.
Feels awesome.
I mean...you passed out at school...
It's just heat stroke.
Nothing fatal.
Why are you suddenly grounded?
Anyone can be grounded for knowing you,
ok?
What brought you here?
Because you said...
When a girl says "I'm ok", she's not ok.
Nothing's wrong means something's wrong.
Do you want to come to a place with me?
What?
Wait here.
Since I discovered this place,
I've been coming here at midnight a lot.
You want to learn roller skating, right?
Let me tell you how not to fall.
What's the tip?
Don't...
be afraid of falling.
It can't get worse than falling.
The important thing is...
why are you here.
Thank you.
What?
On the day of school festival,
let's give out awards to the top 10 students
of the mock exam of 3rd grade.
1st place.
Class 301, Ouyang Extraordinary.
2nd place.
Class 301, Li Chiming.
3rd place.
Class 302, Yang Chiaying.
4th place.
Class 303, Liao Chide.
10th place.
5th place.Class 304, Tao Minmin.
6th place.
Class 301, Lin Bingsheng.
7th place.
Class 309, Chen Yuting.
8th place.
Class 306, Li Chengfu.
It's coming...
9th place.
Class 303, Wang Aiwei.
Get ready. Get ready.
Up to the stage, now!
Please come up to the stage.
You might be wondering...
why there are only 9 of them.
Because...
the school denounces cheating in exams.
We human beings
must have a sense of shame.
You should never think those sneaky,
shameful behavior of yours
will not be found out.
Hsu of Class 317, I'm talking about YOU.
What rubbish?
Mind your own business!
Sir.
We're giving out awards now,
if you want to talk, we'll...
Director.
I have something serious to report now.
My skirt is 3cm higher than my knee.
My socks are not 100% white.
My jacket's zipper never pulled high enough.
Please punish me, sir.
All these are not important now.
We'll take our time to punish her later.
If none of these rules is important,
why should we follow them?
Therefore,
please cite me with an admonition
according to school regulations.
Director.
I cheated in exams.
Please cite me with a major demerit
according to school regulations.
Ouyang.
Don't play with your future.
You're applying for Taiwan University,
Your discipline record can't be affected.
Besides, we know very well. You're smart.
It's not possible that you...
Why not?
If Director Chuan can say that Hsu Taiyu
of Class 317 cheated on the exam,
I can say I did it.
And what I say counts.
Alright.
Since Ouyang confessed his crime bravely,
I'll make sure he gets a major demerit.
Director Chuan...
We need further discussion.
Principal, Ouyang just...
Director.
I'm in shorts while it's not a P.E. class.
Please cite me with an admonition.
Director.
You're my chocolate.
I'm disrespectful to teachers.
Please cite me with an admonition.
Director.
I spread obscene ideas.
Please cite me with a minor demerit.
Director.
Eat shit!
Sorry I humiliated teachers.
Please cite me with a major demerit.
Director.
I... I have a girlfriend.
Bullshit.
Director.
I brought my pager to school.
Please cite me with an admonition.
Director.
I didn't flush the toilet.
I'm not wearing underpants.
I play Game Boy in class.
I sleep in class...
I have a boyfriend...
Director.
You said students should be like students.
But neither exams nor school regulations
can define us.
Those with good scores can make mistakes.
Those who made a mistake can improve.
Whether we're good or bad is not up to you.
Only we know who we are.
Only we can decide the way we are.
Alright. Alright.
Calm down everyone.
Today is the 54th anniversary of our school.
First High is always a liberal school.
I'm here to promise you that, we'll discuss,
improve ourselves and proceed accordingly.
The long-waited water balloon fight
officially starts now.
We didn't know until years later...
the first person you throw your balloon at,
is not someone you dislike,
but someone you can't take your eyes off.
Hey! You meant it.
That's not true.
Just to wait for Dahe and Small.
Are you tired?
Just to keep your hands warm.
I picked your key.
We must be meant for each other, right?
Meant for hell.
You're going so slow on purpose...
is it because you want us to be alone?
Boss...
Sakuraki...wait for me!
Follow the beat!
Truth or Dare.
Ouyang...
Are you seeing someone?
Is she here?
Yes, she's here.
Wow! Mr. Straight-A confessed his love.
Boss, boss.
So...are you seeing someone? ls she here?
Is she here?
Yes, she's here.
Who's that?
Boss, tell me...please.
Hurry up...
Oh...Lin Truly.
Are you seeing someone?
Is he here?
Hold on.
Is this bottle...
pointing closer to Tao Minmin?
Boss.
Ask again. Ask again.
Tao Minmin.
Minmin, Minmin.
Have you ever sent out chain letters?
What the hell is that?
Drink it.
How did you know that Minmin sent me
the chain letter and reported me?
Who knows that
you're sending chain letters?
Must be the person who sent it to you.
Tao Minmin received exactly the same letter
she sent out. That's why she knows
one of the classmates who received
her letter sent it to the teacher.
I guess you're the only one who knows
Wang Baidan among the 5 receivers.
I never thought
she would do something like this.
I thought she was perfect.
Now I think your personality is better.
And if I look closely...
she's not that much prettier than you.
Maybe just this much prettier.
Which university do you want to go to?
Taiwan University, I guess.
And you?
Same for me.
But...I don't think I can get in.
Hsu Taiyu.
If...
we end up going to different universities,
can you promise me?
That...
you'll continue to study hard and graduate.
That you'll never fight again...
That you'll never...
worry people who care about you.
Ok.
I promise you.
What about you?
Yes?
If I go to somewhere very far from you,
can you promise me?
That sesame dressing and noodles
will never be mixed together.
Not funny.
I'm serious.
Hsu Taiyu.
Shooting star!
Make a wish.
Chain letters can never bring good luck.
But on that night,
I felt...
I found my luck.
Welcome to the
"Superstitious Show".
Mom! It's starting!
Let's have a look at this weird picture.
A group of high school students went
camping last month and took this photo.
Let's hear what the expert has to say.
The student in the photo
became translucent.
If we look at the supernatural aspect of it,
it's obvious that
this photo
is full of supernatural energy.
I suggest the student
visit temples guarding land and underworld
to remove ill fortune. -Go home soon.
Take care.
Thanks.
Hsu Taiyu.
I finally...
got you.
The bell has rung.
Hand in your paper.
Sakuraki said that
Hsu hasn't come to school for a week.
He's even absent from the mock exam.
Did you watch the TV show last week?
Maybe something really happened to him?
I don't think so.
Hsu Taiyu.
Why didn't you take the mock exam?
None of your business.
Why did you...fight again?
For no reason.
They wanted to fight.
So I fought with them.
Hsu Taiyu.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
When a girl says
"nothing's wrong",
something must be wrong.
"I'm ok" means "I'm not ok."
We didn't know until
long after that:
when a girl says
"I don't want to talk to you anymore."
She doesn't really hate you.
Instead she cares about you...
very
very much.
Happy birthday!
Thank you...
This is...
Boss brought it back himself.
We don't know what he's been busy with,
but he still remembers your birthday.
And this!
Boss said that you shouldn't listen to it
before the university entrance exam.
There must be something special in it.
When you see boss in school tomorrow,
don't forget to thank him.
Bye bye.
Lin Truly.
Today's your birthday, let's go to...
Chicken House...
Great! Hand-shredded chicken set for me.
I'm gonna have two.
Look! It's Hsu Taiyu.
Who is he looking for?
Hsu Taiyu.
Lin Truly...
go go go.
He came to see you, Lin Truly.
Happy birthday...
So romantic!
Last night...
Thank you.
Oh. You're welcome.
Did you like it?
Of course!
Happy birthday.
What did you want to say?
Small and Meimei are waiting for me.
We're discussing where to go for dinner.
Do you want to join us?
By the way.
Please write this for me.
Make sure you...
fill in your personal info
like the sample on page 1.
What's wrong?
Taiyu...
Were you looking for me?
For what?
Wait for me here.
So you came for Minmin?
You should've told me...
you came for Minmin to...
She told me she likes me.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Hmmm...congratulations.
What a surprise!
I even helped you chase her for so long.
Congratulations.
Finally.
Thank you.
It'll definitely work out
between Ouyang and you.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I'm...really happy for you.
It's pouring rain...
Goodbye.
Come with us...
It's ok. Thanks.
Look! It says that
Andy Lau has a girlfriend!
What? It must be rumor.
Andy Lau will never get married.
We all dreamed of marrying our idols,
That must be a rumor.
But in reality...
Of course
Andy Lau belongs to someone else.
Same for our first love.
Of course we can't beat girls like Minmin.
Morning.
Don't cry.
Going abroad as soon as he got you.
He was just fooling you.
In the end...
we shouldn't have trusted a freak who
separates sesame dressing from noodles.
I heard that Director Chuan
caught him fighting with others
and wanted to kick him out of the school.
That's why his dad sent him abroad.
What? Really?
Shhh...
Quiet. Here she comes.
What are you talking about?
We are here to study.
Yes -Right.
Back then, there was no facebook.
12,000km means
parting for good.
But sometimes
there were some moments,
I felt he would appear
the next second.
Are you ok?
Be careful.
This is the ultimate note.
Let's go roller skating
after you finish the exam.
Or...
do you want to go to the movies?
Ah! Stephen Chow's
Monkey King is on again.
I want to watch it again.
Last time...
I didn't quite get it.
Hsu Taiyu left.
My life
seemed to be back to the same old.
But I know
because of him
I am...
who I am now.
(To: Lin Truly)
OK.
(You're pretty. Can I be your friend?)
Congratulations.
Finally done with the entrance exam.
Thanks.
I think...
I did pretty well in math.
Thanks for the ultimate note.
Did you...
listen to the tape?
The one Taiyu gave you.
I promised him
to remind you of this.
It's a shame that
the ending
isn't like what he thought.
Hsu Taiyu! Shooting star!
Make a wish!
You know that I heard it, right?
The person you like...
is here.
In the beginning,
I thought whoever believed in chain letters
was either an idiot
or an idiot.
But later I realized that
she's simply a very kind person.
To whoever received this:
I am really really sorry.
I was forced to send it...
You might be hit by a car,
get cancer...
or...lose your family.
But...
I'm sure you'll turn ill luck into good,
have a successful life,
become wealthy.
That's why I wanted to know her.
Let's be friends.
I was serious.
What?
I thought chasing girls...
was that simple.
Tao Minmin.
Wanna be my gal?
Say yes! Say yes!
Later I realized...
if you really like someone...
you might not even notice it.
I was actually super nervous that day.
I have to thank that car.
The moment I held her in my arm...
I realized that I never knew...
my heart...can beat so fast.
What...were you...talking about?
I didn't want her to misunderstand.
But somehow...
at the end of that day
she didn't seem happy.
When you like someone
and see her walk to someone she likes,
you'd suddenly realize that
you treat her badly just because
you want to get a bit closer to her.
For me?
You'll keep every word she said
in mind.
Nothing's wrong.
Bye.
When we say nothing's wrong...
it means something's wrong.
When we say it's ok,
it means it's not ok.
Are you ok?
I didn't know that when I'm in love,
I actually have no courage to tell her.
On that night,
I made a wish upon a shooting star.
I wish I was also
in her wish.
Even if I know it's someone else
who could make her happy...
Sometimes...she still pretends to be ok
even when she feels very sad.
Spending 5 minutes deciding what to have,
before choosing the same old raddish cake.
She doesn't watch where she's going.
Please watch her at all times.
Are you ok?
She wants to go to Taiwan University,
but she's really bad at math.
She likes roller skating,
loves Stephen Chow's films...
Let's go roller skating
after you finish the exam.
She...
likes you very much.
I didn't know that
he disappeared for so long
was because he had a surgery.
Do you see that?
You have a blood clot here.
This is why you passed out when running.
It might be caused by the car accident.
That sounds really bad!
Should've charged the driver more.
You really should.
You'll need a surgery
and stay in the hospital.
Your family has to come to look after you.
He wanted me to keep the secret.
I guess...
he didn't want you to blame yourself.
His family told the school long time ago
that they wanted to take him to the U.S..
Hsu Taiyu.
I hope you can start over again
after arriving in the U.S..
Director.
Thank you.
Sakuraki said that
Hsu hasn't come to school for a week.
He's even absent from the mock exam.
Aren't you moving to the U.S. soon?
Why are you still studying this?
Because...
I made a promise.
Can you...
be that Hsu Taiyu again?
Why did you...fight again?
For no reason.
They wanted to fight.
So I fought with them.
Sorry for coming here so late
and asking that standee for free.
Sorry.
Hsu Taiyu.
I finally
got you.
It's Andy Lau!
Don't you motherfucker dodge!
You want me to invite your gal for tea?
She always goes to
that teashop to study.
Class...
304...
Lin...Tru...ly...
Don't you ever touch her!
It depends on whether you're a good boy...
whether you let me beat you...up...
Lin Truly.
Now you're with the person you like, right?
I won Tao Minmin's heart.
You won Ouyang's.
We fulfilled the promise
we made in the beginning.
I guess...
this is the only
and the last thing I could do for you.
Lin Truly.
Although you're short
and stupid.
And you even like someone else.
Even so...
I still...
like you a lot.
Lin Truly.
If you already listened to the whole tape,
just look up at the sky.
Then I will know
I'm looking at the same starry sky
as the girl I like.
I Love You
(The person I like: Hsu Taiyu)
You were always wondering...
what your future would be like.
Now... I can give you the answer.
Give me the salary
and the holidays I deserve,
or let me quit.
I don't need to waste my life
in a place where no one cares who I am.
Truly! Truly!
What the fuck!
Handwritten resignation letter...so ancient.
We'd probably just send emails.
Who dares to
do this.
You're so cool.
Sometimes...
it's still way cooler to
do it our way.
By the way.
All of you have a share
of my performance bonus.
Yay!
So you quit?
How can you be so immature?
Why can't you just be flexible?
Everyone can stick to it, why can't you?
Do you remember that
once I asked you to pay card bill for me?
It's true I gave you the bill quite late.
But it doesn't mean you could...
In the future...
you won't really become someone amazing.
You still make mistakes.
You still get confused.
You still regret for not having more ice,
or not experiencing more relationships.
...that's what I don't like about you.
Same here.
Let's break up.
...and being too kind to people you dislike.
And cherishing people you like more.
But...
the way you are is good.
You're still very brave,
very naive.
You still...
scream for your idol.
Ah!
How can you stay so popular for 30 years?
How come I still can't get a single ticket!
Come on. Come on.
Truly glow stick!
See, I finally got the ticket.
Where?
I've queued for a long time!
I'm in the first row at the mosh pit.
Come on. Come on. Have a look.
Truly glow stick!
Come have a look.
Hello.
May I help you?
Kumquat lemonade, please.
No problem.
30 dollars.
Hello.
Bubble milk tea.
Bubble milk tea? Sure.
It's gonna take some time.
You dropped something.
I'm taking a break.
Just treat me as an ordinary person.
Don't worry.
I think you're so ordinary.
I don't like you at all.
I'm not your fan.
This is...what my colleague...
helped me...
download earlier today.
So good.
I...don't know who's the singer...
I agree.
It's good.
Let me play another song.
Can I take a photo with you?
Although you think I'm ordinary,
and you're not my fan.
Can we...take a photo?
Yes...
Ok.
Sorry, I'm a bit...
nervous.
Good?
Thanks.
Ok.
By the way...
Can you sign for me?
Sure.
Thanks.
Oh!
Can you please write...
To Lin Truly
L.l.N.
Truly as in "Truly Madly Deeply".
Lin Truly
You're going to the concert tonight,
right?
How do you know?
Because
my concert is called "Truly Love You".
So...
you really have to go.
But I couldn't get any ticket.
All your concerts
are sold out.
Call this person.
He's our staff.
You have to come.
OK.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Don't forget.
Hello?
Hi...
hmmm...
Andy Lau gave me this number.
I guess he told you about it, right?
My name is
Lin Truly.
Is sesame dressing...
still separated from noodles?
The concert will start soon.
Are you excited?
I am.
Because one of my friends made his efforts
to make the concert happen.
He wanted to fulfill a promise he made
to his first love.
I like their story very much.
I want to dedicate this concert
to everyone who has truly loved someone.
Thank you.
Truly love you.
Is that you...
come up with this title?
Otherwise?
The concert is starting soon.
But...
I didn't get any ticket.
I'll ask...
Andy Lau
to sing for you.
Yeah right.
Sure.
It's been a long time.