Go, go soon
Knock if off, go
Disgust, you old bastard
Enough of that, go
Don't forget to bring some wine
I need a wipe, Mom
Now
Good morning, uncle
Let's have a bite
There are some vegetable for you
What are you doing here? Go back home
Or I'm going to tell your sister
Good morning, uncle
I want to go with you, uncle
Please, uncle
The story began from my first sight at uncle
I was only two months
old like a piece of garbage
And dropped on the sidewalk
Nobody could tell me why
When he's holding me in his arms
I felt that I'd never leave it
because he made me feel so cozy and warm
Just like any father to his children
Her name is Ah-mei
The gods will protect whoever adopts her
From a pitiful person
Uncle's got a baby
That's me my clothes
It's all-right, just a loan for your sister
Take her hands, now give it to me
Tit it up this way
Men are usually all thumbs
I wonder how you could take care of a child
She's hungry, give her some porridge first
Good baby, whose child is it?
let me see...Don't cry, good baby
You'll never come home till you lose your money
She's stopped crying
That hand's dirty
Look how you made her cry
Kids mustn't talk loudly
Does she have a name, Mute?
Precious
Precious?
That's no class, just give her another name
Don't pretend you know it
If you know it, then read it
You take it at a wrong way, she's Ah-mei
An-mei!
An-mei...
What's wrong with this woman?
Don't give me any gesture
Okay, don't give me any of your gestures
Uncle
You need an extra can today?
You need some milk? For your health?
Wait a minute
Want to get rough? I'll show you
How do you believe we can afford this baby?
I wash and cook for you everyday
And I satisfy your desire at night
But you still forget our rice wine instead
What kind of life is this?
You tired of me? Want to chase me off?
Ever since the day I moved in
I hate to live with a mute like you
I hate to live with a garbage man like you
You got clobbered, didn't you?
Somebody gave him a fix
Good morning, uncle
Let me see your glasses, uncle
Need something for your health? Rice wine?
It stands to reason
Take care, Chih-lan, bye-bye
Uncle
But when I walked into this family
Our life changed all of a sudden
I got a man I could depend on all my life
But uncle lost his company who is his partner
Auntie Chi-Ian
I think it was my fault, wasn't it?
Because Auntie Chi-Ian tried her best...
Just to love me and take care of me
But I was such a naughty child
I made Auntie couldn't get any love from him
Because uncle's given me almost everything
Thanks for the applause
Now it's the time for audience to perform
Who wants to come up and perform?
Come on...
Him! He can play a trumpet
Let me hold the baby
Right...go ahead
He's damn good
I once thought of that many times
Me and my uncle actually had the same fate
We both had been deserted
I was deserted by who gave birth to me
And the whole strenuous time deserted him
He'd once owned his parents and his family
And Auntie Chi-Ian
But all of a sudden
Nothing existed but his heart
He might take me as his continuity of life
Just like that chaos of my heart
Took it as something couldn't take place
Just like a supreme being in the days gone
But we couldn't talk to each other with words
Worshipping your ancestors!
Ah-mei
Come to my house for New Year's dinner
Be my guest
Let's have a good drink today
You aren't doing me favor, are you?
Take a look at Ah-mei, uncle
Go tell Dad, Ah-mei
Ah-mei, hurry up, go and tell Dad
I wonder if she's mute too
What are you talking about?
Ah-man's always a big mouth, don't be mad
Let's go home
Be sure to come over later, uncle
Until that day, it might be Ah-ming's hint
Or it might be help from heaven
My first word in my life is...
Dad
This way, sit down please
What happened? What did he say?
Ah-mei can say Daddy
A phoenix raised by a crow can talk
Ah-mei knows how to say Daddy
Now, say daddy
Daddy
Ah-mei, you're wonderful
Mute
Uncle
Improving your mind!
Come on
It's winter beginning, let's have extra natty
There's one dish my wife can't make
Can you help with it?
Dog meat!
Sorry, doggie, I'll help you be reincarnated
You'll belong to a foreign family
That'll make your next life better
There's a dog barking, whose dog is it?
None of your business, go back your homework
Just put it into the pan
By the way...
Where's the dog? Where did you put it?
Dad
How pitiful, there's blood all over its head
Let's keep it, okay?
No, we want to eat it
Ah-mei
Ah-ming, we've got a dog
What a cute dog
Why is its head all bloody?
I don't know, somebody hit it, I guess
Let's put some medicine on it
Okay
Easy, be careful
Does it hurt when a dog's bleeding, Daddy?
Nuts, of course it hurts
I'm not asking you
Yeah, she's not asking you
You shut up
What do you think you're doing?
Meet me after school is over, okay?
Any bottle for sell?
I want to get off
Come on, Ah-mei
Just tell me what the matter is
Any bottle for sell?
How dare you push and bite me,
I'll show you back
Look, Ah-ming
What're you doing, Liu Chun-chieh? Stop
Come back, Liu Chun-chieh
Ah-ming, don't let him get away
Ah-ming
Ah-ming, look
Ah-mei
Go, go, Lau-fu
Lai-fu
Bite hime to death
Lai-fu, kill him
You're great, Lai-fu
Good boy, Lai-fu
Is it dead?
I don't know
Is it dead anyway?
It's dead
Mom
Just drop it
What's wrong?
Come on, it's a kid
Don't do that again
Okay
Good, over two catties
Come on, take it easy
It scared you, so you can eat it
No, I don't
Is it poisonous? Isn't it?
Don't know till we eat it, have some, mute
Eat
What's the matter with you? Dad
What's the matter, Dad?
Dad
You never know when to come
in once you come out
Like a rag in a stream
What are you sneaking around for?
Fooling around all day long
It's okay, just tell me about it
I brought this to Ah-mei
Thank you!
Shame on you, a man loves a woman
What about mine?
No more
Stingy
No, you're stingy
Why don't you give me a present?
I've got no money to buy toys for you
He is an adult, he should buy me something
Shame on you
No, you're shameless
Stop it, just listen to me
Ah-ming, Ah-kun, one car for each
A doll for Ah-mei
A wool hat for mute
A necklace for Mom
Money... money
What are you doing now?
Nothing, I think I've got some luck today
I'm taking it
That money belongs to somebody else
Give it to me
I'll be back soon tonight
I'll give it back twice as much as this amount
Why must you gamble? It's dangerous
Go to hell
Take it all
Bets...or you're a coward
I've lost so much, I should win once
Everything depends on this
You always rant at my gambling
I'll stop your mouth with a gold necklace
And I'll make you call me darling tonight
Go home, you've read that a hundred times
None of your business
I'm not going back
You keep out of this
Pretty, dolly, you've run away?
Went swimming
Come back...
You won't get away, come back
Auntie, come on, oh, my God
He's by the gutter, Ah-man
Ah-man...
Auntie...
Sister...
Ah-man...
Must you torture me this way?
That makes you happy, doesn't it?
I didn't really mean to scold you
You know that?
I didn't really want you to die
Auntie's house is on fire
I didn't want you to die...
Auntie, come on and go home
House will burn down if you still stay here
The house will burn down if you still stay here
You silly brother still sleeps in it
What will you do if he's burned?
Ah-mei
Ah-mei, wait a minute
Dad...
Mom, let me go, I want to find my Mom
Mom...
My little baby, don't cry, Mon's here
Dad...
Hat hot and fierce light, shadow of death
Helpless crying and miserable look from Auntie
Seems like it became a memory of my childhood
Though terrible fire burned everything up
It couldn't burn our hope
People have to go on living anyway
Misery makes a man forget about yesterday
It makes people live in today's fatigue
No matter how fast time would pass
Everyday to us is the same
The same neighbors and friends, the same work
Until one day...
Suddenly I found something
white in my father's head
Then I found that I'm grown up
And a strange now world has tied us together
So secretly and so tightly
Come on, little mouse
It's not a marriage with Ah-mei
Shut up or I'll fix you
You bought that much food for a feast?
To celebrate her first day at work
Ah-ming's more anxious than she is
Look, uncle
Uncle
It's okay, I've made some extra money today
Don't get mad, Uncle
You'd run into another rich window, didn't you?
Don't talk nonsense,
I've got nothing to do with her
I only say that she's beautiful
Is she beautiful
Sure she is, beautiful as you
When does Ah-mei finish her work?
Let me make some dishes for our snack
Give me a ray of warming light
Don't maintain that you're in a stupor
Dance with me to our heart's desire
How much loneliness does a stranger have
Listen again-ding dong, ding dong
How the distant notes pierce my heart
Sing again - do be do wa
Feeling of sorrow if you'd like to stimulate
I'll take you home, okay?
I didn't mean it just now
But it's true you don't sing well
Don't be angry, act like a lady
You want me to lie about your singing?
Wouldn't that be pretty vain?
Okay, you sing very well, better than anybody
Even better than Teresa Teng, satisfy?
You have no right to criticize me
True, I have no right
But I can tell if you sing well or not
I'm a composer, I can give you some advice
You car
It's okay, too bad for the owner, though
Get in
Later on the song became a hit
I'm home, Dad
Dad, he's Shin Chun-mai, a song writer
My Dad
Don't be so rude, Dai-fu
Want to come to my house and sit for a while
No...there'll be opportunities later
Good-bye
Let's go home, Lai-fu
Let's go, Dad
That Shin Chun-mai I just mentioned, Dad
He said he's got some new songs
Which fits me and he
wants to teach me personally
I'm so happy
Dad, you know something
I like singing very much
Here it is
Go ahead, Dad
Drinking so early, you are not driving, are you?
Leave me alone, Mom
What do you think you are?
Much of us have lived here for thirty years
Where did you have us move to?
Please give a fin comment, you guys
Where did you want us move to?
To Green Island?
What's the matter, Auntie?
The illegal building must be torn down
The government will make up for you
What a joke
Money is only enough
to buy two pieces of candy
What do you take me for, a child?
You have preference for government housing
Preference? It'll still take a year or more
Stand still
Listen, I just work for the government
I live here too the same as you guys
Just like us
The government preference and have priority
The government will protect only those
who are the same
How can you tell other people to move
Such a man like him needs a good lesson
A bunch of mad dogs, I'm telling you...
If you don't move out, I'll get rough with you
What do you mean by that? get rough with us
Don't run away
Beat him
Why me? I want to beat somebody too
I wanted to beat somebody last night
Come back
Wait a minute...
I told you to come in, let' go
Don't be unhappy, Dad
Our house isn't the only one to be torn down
Anyway, we'll have to move
Don't worry about the money, Dad
I'll make a lot of money for you to buy a house
I walk with unvarying footsteps
Waiting for your coming
When you have anxiety and doubt
Please come with me
I carry a dreamlike hope
A feeling that can't be repressed
When you are distracted
Please come with me
It's world you cannot foresee
You don't have to say anything
Your eyes have already told me
When spring showers are drifting down
And dripping endlessly from your hair
Wear your crystal pearl necklace
Please come with me
It's world you cannot foresee
You don't have to say anything
Your eyes have already told me
When spring showers are drifting down
And dripping endlessly from your hair
Wear your crystal pearl necklace
Please come with me
I hope you could
The Manager Yu of Kuang Tail wants to see you
Don't be afraid, he has no interest in you
He has interest only in men
Let me introduce...
I know her, she's the famous singer star, Shen-ni
I like your singing very much
Thank you!
This is my friend Shin Chun-mai
I knew each other before, I'm her manager
I just heard you sang, you'll have a good future
Here's my name card
I'd like to talk to you tomorrow
When will my next record be released?
Your last record didn't sell well
I think you'd better offer some shows nowadays
Manager, Miss Shen's here
I've got something to discuss with you
You leave for a while, okay?
Sister Shen
I hope you could take Shen-ni's place
Why?
The audience needs some
new excitements, new faces
They tired of Shen-ni now
Your qualifications are better
Do you think I'm qualified?
Do you think she's qualified?
She was a dancer, she couldn't speak Chinese
The qualifications depend on me, not you
You just do whatever I tell you...
And you'll be bigger than she is
Okay, I agree
But I have a requirement
What's that?
I want him to compose for me
Mr. Shin, I'm sorry, I have 10 tell you the true
What we need are commercial songs
Not those folk songs, like yours
That's what I insist, Miss Sun
I hope you'll think it over
What does he think he is?
Gay, a shark, vulgar
None of Shen-ni's songs has class
Would I write those stupid songs?
I don't care these money he earned
If you like him, go with him
I just want to make more money
and buy my father a house
That'll make him a better life
Am I doing wrong?
I you don't like it,
I'll give him a call right now
Maybe you should go along with him
Okay, thanks for your trouble, Miss Yuen
It's nothing, nothing
Now we've finished the first step
And the second is to change your name
Change my name?
Yes, just like making a new person
From now on your name is Sun Jui-chi
Sun Jui-chi
By the way, I've rent
a very comfortable room for you
You can move in tomorrow
Why?
Because I want to make you a star of all stars
I'll inform the mass media
You grow up from a wealthy and cultured family
And make you full of the manner of a fine lady
Something the audience can see, not touched
You're allowing Ah-mei to move out
It's dangerous to be a singer these days
Rich men are always after them
It won't do, you say it, mouse
Okay
You collect newspaper everyday
Don't you read what's in them?
Bad guys like to abduct singers
Take their clothes off and photograph them
Like that Spin-up Girl case
It's really
An-ming, I said what you wanted
What's wrong to be a star?
Get famous and find a rich man
You'll have more money than rice
Uncle will have everything then
That's right
Then she won't recognize her own father
I don't think Ah-mei's like that
Don't be silly, Ah-ming
She just wants to make some money
Dad, I'm back
My stuff is there
Your father is waiting so long,
for having dinner with you
I can't eat at home, Dad
The company's arranged a party
With reporters and the record company boss
I have to practice singing after dinner
But I'll come and see you often, Dad
Good-bye
When did the frog croaks become memory
When did the land become so crowded
With tall buildings towering all around
And neon signs making the night so harsh
Who can tell me? Who can tell?
Did we change the world
Or did the world change you and me?
The same moonlight
Shines on the same Hsintien River
The same winter
Brings the same cold rains
The same dust
Is blown by the same wind
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
Ah-ming's really beautiful
Sounds really good
You don't have to worry now, do you?
See? Ah-ming's really wonderful
She'll be a very popular singer
Thank you, thank you
I hear you grew up on a wealthy family
What business is your father in?
My father...
Her father's a big contractor
He's emigrated to America now
Only Miss Sun is left here
How do you make a living here, Miss Sun
It depends on my manager's arrangement
She stars a Southeast Asian tour tomorrow
She'll be back in a month
The she'll have the biggest concert here
Let me ask an irrelevant question?
Do you have a close boy friend?
Well? Do you?
Yes, a lot of them, my listeners
My listeners are my closest friends
You aren't well, shouldn't come out
Ah-mei's gone too far
Only coming back so rarely to see you
Not asking you to her press conference
When I see her, I'll ask her about that
What's the matter with you?
Aren't you that great singer, Shen-ni?
Yes, I'm that great singer
Why? You want my antograph
Give me a pen
I'm not your friend, I came to see Ah-mei
Who's Ah-mei?
Ah-mei's Sun Jui-chi
Sun Jui-chi
What's so great about her?
How can her singing compare with mine?
She's just younger and prettier, that's all
Nobody's young and pretty forever
Anyway one day she'll fall
Then she'll never come up again
Be careful about what you say
So what? What's she to you?
I'm her neighbor, that's all
He's her father
He's her father? That's laugh
It's true, he's really her father
Attention, everybody, quiet, please
I have some good news for you
He's Sun Jui-chi's father
Her father, just back from America
The big contractor, back from America
See? That's the way it is
He isn't her father, folks
Does he look like him?
They're just enthusiastic fans
What? He's really her father
You're trying to pull a fast one?
You're the fraud
Tell them, Ah-mei
Isn't he your father? Speak up
See? Even he doesn't say it
If they're not frauds, what are they?
Ah-mei, come here
Tel them he's your father
Why don't you speak up?
No, Ah-mei, please
Listen to me, just this once
Dad, I'm sorry
It's too late to say that now
You're popular and you despite us now
Who despite you?
Don't say silly things, Ah-ming
Me said silly things? Dame you
Don't be that way
Over 20 years and this is what I get
I really don't despise you
You're star, we're not on the level as high as you
No...
Ah-ming, don't talk so much
You can go now
You don't belong here
We can get along without you
You're just a foundling, anyway
Are you finished, Ah-ming?
Ah-mei
I watched Ah-mei grow up
She isn't like that, I believe in her...
Stop drinking, your high blood pressure
Ah-mei, we may have loved once
But love and friendship are different
You know what I mean
Sorry, I'm leaving, Shi Chun-mai
Think how the earth shook when we met
And then the changes, like passing mists
As the seasons change in he heavens
You wander without end
Under the sky with its traveling orbs People
will entertainment you in Singapore and Hong Kong
I can't leave here
I can take care of myself
Okay, good luck on your tour
Don't forget, give Dad two hundred thousand
He needs it to buy a house
Okay, I'll send it to him
Thanks, good-bye
I'll cast aside unwanted memories
Far away, they lose their mystery
Think how the earth shook when we met
And then the changes, like passing mists
As the seasons change in the heavens
You wander without end
Under the sky with its traveling orbs
In a gauss like haze
I was careless, lost my love
Much to my regret
I'll cast aside unwanted memories
Far away, they lose their mystery
Think how the earth shook when we met
And then the changes, like passing mists
When thunder-like applause came
I knew it was all mine
I should be moved and excited
But nobody knows that...
I felt so lonely at that moment
Nobody down there is who I wanted to see
They're all thousand miles away
It's hopeless, humanity is dead
He's pitiful, his head's all bloody
Let's go home, Lai-fu
Mr Sun
I'm sorry about that night, Mr. Sun
She wants you to have
this two hundred thousand
It's to buy a house with
She misses you very much
She'll visit you when she comes back
There's something I want to tell you
She's lucky, she's got popular fast
A lot of girls dream about...
Being the way she is now
I hope you'll give her your help
Ah-ming
Call an ambulance
Taxi driving is the job he owned
Killed in tearing an illegal building
Totally joining his funeral with our respect
His soul will live with us forever
God bless him
Bow to him with utmost heartiness
First bow
Second bow
Third bow
I own you my thanks
Ceremony concluded
Mouse and I are going back to Tai-tung
We'll come to see you when we have time
Ah-ming
First to my home on Hsinyi Road
No, to Yangmingshan first
Didn't you agree to let me see Dad first
Your concert will begin in two days
Concentrate on your practice
Trust me to take care of your father
This concert is important to us
The best singer of the year Miss Sun Jui-chi
She's returned by taking CAL
Beef noodles and a beer, Mamasan
Right away
She accepted the invitation
from Singapore Television
It was a very successful tour
Now she's come back to Taiwan
The invitation of the Deal-Mute
For a charity concert on Aug 15
Her talent and charitable generosity
Really impress on the Taiwan entertainmet
Do you know Ah-mei?
Where did the people here move to?
Don't know, you're looking for somebody?
An old friend I haven't seen for 20 years
I want to see him
But this place has changed so much
Good-bye
Ah-mei, I've been looking
for you all day already
Finally, I guess you came here
What have you to say about this?
I don't when this happened
I want to find my father
I gave him the money, like you said
He can take care of himself
We have to prepare for the concert
You have a press conference too
We've got too many things to do
You can't destroy yourself this way
I'm begging
It's luck Ah-mei left that money
It covered Ah-ming's funeral, the noodle store
We can get by
Uncle thinks of Ah-mei all day
He doesn't say so, but I can tell
So I live with him
His health isn't good lately
I can't take care of him, living there
I'm too old to care what people say
Uncle's blowing again
He used to soothe Ah-mei that way
That would make her laugh, so cute
Since Ah-mei went abroad
Uncle blows all the time
There something
Say hello to uncle for me
Ah-mei's come back
I'll go see her in a couple of days
Want to sell wine bottles?
President
Ah-mei, try the song I wrote for you
I hope
You can sing it for those who need love
Especially for your father
Shin Chun-mai
Want.. to...sell...wine...bottle
The same moonlight
Shines on the same Hsintien River
The same winter
Brings the same cold rains
The same dust
Is blown by the same wind
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
When did the frog croaks become memory
When did the land become so crowded
With tall buildings towering all around
And neon signs making the night so harsh
Who can tell me? Who can tell?
Did we change the world
Or did the world change you and me?
Who can tell me? Who can tell?
Did we change the world
Or did the world change you and me?
The same moonlight
Shines on the same Hsintien River
The same winter
Brings the same cold rains
The same dust
Is blown by the same wind
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
The same smiles
The same tears
The same days
The same you and me
Ah-mei
Hurry up, hurry up
What's the matter?
Hurry
I'm sorry, ladies and gentlemen
There is something happened
in Sun Jui-chi's family
So now we ask Miss Shen to sing for you
Dad...
Do you have wine bottles to sell?
What a familiar sound that is
It's been with me day in and day out
I never need to think about it
It's something I can never forget
Without heaven, where would earth be?
Without earth, where would home be?
Without home, where would you be?
Without you, where would I be?
Without you to raise me
To give me warmth and life
Without you to protect me
What would my fate be?
It was you who raised me
Accompany me from my first word saying
It was you who gave me a home
To share with you, together
You cannot open your mouth and speak
But you know black and white, right and wrong
You cannot express how you feel
You contribute your precious life, though
Your familiar sound, from afar
Reminds me of your loving soul
When will you return to my side
And let us sing together
Do you have wine bottles to sell?
What a familiar sound that is
It's been with me day in and day out
I never need to think about it
It's something I can never forget
Without heaven, where would earth be?
Without earth, where would home be?
Without home, where would you be?
Without you, where would I be?
What a familiar sound that is
It's been with me day in and day out
I never need to think about it
It's something I can never forget
Do you have wine bottles to sell?