Do you believe in God?
No, but I enjoy the tranquility here
Want to check the gun?
I trust you
Don't move
I can't see
Your corneas have been badly damaged
Will I recover?
There is hope, but your sight
will never be perfect
My sight is so blurred
We can do an operation, a transplant
Will I be blind?
Jennie, I'm Sergeant Chang
Do you remember the murderer's face?
Please leave me alone, I'm so afraid
Calm down
Help! Help!
Please help!
Bastards!
Just go away,
They have gone already, don't be afraid
I'll take you home
Jennie!
How do you know my name?
I listen to you singing every night
Who are you?
I feel as if I know you
I know you can't see too well
I've wanted to help,
but I didn't have the chance
In this world
not everybody is untrustworthy
Will you let me help you this time?
Is it alright for me to leave?
Keep calm, let me check it out
It's only a cat
It often sneaks in and scratches my furniture
Such a nuisance!
Why did you turn off the light?
You can see?
I only see shadows
Last month it was better
I could see images
Turn on the light it makes me feel safer
What are you doing now?
I'm looking at this scarf
It's got my blood
stains on it
The man who shot me wrapped it round my eyes
I will never forget
Would you like some tea?
No thanks
It won't take a minute. Sit down please
I'll put some music on
Hey relax, you look exactly like
what you are an undercover agent
Lighten up or it'll be an open secret
Come on
Smile!
Now you look like something out of a nut house
Chang, this guy Eddy's a lunatic. Be careful
Same to you pal,
watch your ass!
Eddy, sorry to keep you waiting
Who the hell's that?
He's a good buddy. Say hello to Eddy
Eddy
Search him!
Eddy, what's with the security?
It's not our first deal
Maybe I've seen him before
$200,000 We'll check the guns first
What are you guys doing?
Nothing special, officer. A reunion
Open the trunk
Open it!
Now!
Damn you! You set me up, didn't you?
Are you a cop?
Talk!
I'm no cop! I didn't betray you
If you ain't, how come he's here?
He's not! I stake my life on it Eddy!
He's not a cop!
Lying bastard, I shouldn't have trusted you!
- The guy's a cop, I recognise him! - You've got it wrong
Chang, I'll get him
That shithead!
Shit
Keep back
Don't move!
Goddamn! Ass Assho
Finish your sentence
Assassh
Inspector Li, the suspect Eddy Wong held a hostage
in a crowded tram
Could you see him clearly?
Could you?
Yes
Why did you shoot?
By instinct
Did you consider the safety of the passengers?
Did you sound any warning before you shot?
There was no time for that
The hostage had a coronary thrombosis
She died of a heart attack
Her family have made an official complaint
You're responsible for her death
That's crazy, how could I know she had a heart condition?
I've been on Eddy Hung's case for seven months
The guy was a maniac
He'd shoot anybody for any reason
Should I have waited till he killed her?
You forget I'd just seen him kill a cop
Who's responsible for that cop's death?
Fine! Do whatever you want
I'm used to all sorts of complaints
One more doesn't make any difference
Catch it!
How is the action hand?
Pretty useless
Better use it more
It won't help
A one handed killer's out of the action
I've had my day
His name is Tong Weng
He works with a drug ring in Central America
Who wants him dead?
No questions. Take it or leave it?
1.5 million
Seems high
This is my last hatchet job
Alright it's a deal
Money's no object
These guns are clean. No serial numbers
Untraceable
Explosive head bullets, your favourite
It's easy to pick it up, hard to put it down
Want to change your mind?
Why take this job?
This one's for Jennie
If you doesn't have a cornea transplant soon
She might lose her sight forever
There is a cornea bank in Hong Kong
But it's always empty
When a donation does come in
Someone else gets it first
So we're going to try abroad
I have to leave you for a few days
On my return, I'll take you overseas for surgery
You will come back
I promise
Thanks!
Today is the Dragon Boat Festival
Many VIPs and government officials
will attend the opening ceremony
You are assigned to protect them
Their information is in your files
Make sure you do a professional job
Yes sir!
Tony Weng, protecting that scum
Attention please! Will all competitors please
assemble before the floating platform for the dotting the dragon's eye ceremony
It is our pleasure to welcome the president of
Tung Yuan Financial Corp, Mr Weng
The chairman of Rotary Club, Mr Peter Chu
Mr Weng
Faster
Good luck
Mr Weng, please
Cover him up, keep everything under control
Red alert, red alert!
Tony Weng's been shot on the floating platform
The shot came from around the fishing junks
The murderer must still be nearby
All units prepare to seal off the area
Mr Weng fainted.
Everything's alright
Please enjoy your day
Chang!
Chang, look over there! An explosion
Right, let's check it out!
Chang, we can't lose him now!
Freeze!
Don't be afraid
You'll be alright
Don't cry
He's down there Step on it!
Ok!
Any hospital's nearby?
Think he's got a conscience?
He won't let the little girl die
Nurse, where's casualty?
This way
What happened?
She got shot
Quickly! Put her down
Nurse, check her blood pressure
Prepare her for surgery
Oxygen mask
How is she?
Blood pressure unstable
Weak pulse
Blood pressure low
Have you seen a man carrying a wounded child?
He went to casualty
Detain anyone suspicious
Yes sir!
Are you related to the patient?
How was she wounded?
Sir, you can't leave now
I have to register your name
Where is he?
I'm an Inspector, just carry on
Right, nurses, ignore them
Yes
Don't mind them, save the girl
Don't disturb the doctor
Put your guns down
What happened?
There was a gunshot
- Where? - Over there!
- Get everybody out - Yes sir!
I'll call HQ
Any progress on Weng's case?
No, none at all
I nearly got the suspect
But he escaped
I thought you had razor sharp intuition?
I'm being made to look a fool
so this case is real important to me
I don't need you letting me down
You always were a pain in the ass
Do me a favour and prove me wrong
Sir, I do nothing for nobody
I'll get the murderer
I won't let you lose face
I hope you don't forget who helped you reach the top
I want you to draw the suspect
Try, To bring him to life
He's over 30
He looks determined
without being ruthless
Something heroic in his manner
Doesn't look like a killer in any way
Comes across so calm
Acts like he has a dream
Eyes full of passion
Hello
It's me, Jeff
Jeff?
Why haven't you left town?
I want my money now
I want it tonight
Tonight!
Sure, I'll bring it over tonight
Mr Weng!
You should let me handle Jeff,
he's my side of things
- What if he squeals on me? - He's not that kind of guy
I don't trust anyone
Including you!
I know the rules of the game
I'll do what I promised
I'm not interested in rules, I want him dead
because he exposed his identity
I'm the boss now
and you do things my way
Ok, you kill him for me
If you blow it, you're dead meat
After all, you got paid for it
Eagle, this could be a lead
Six months ago, Weng's partner, Lim
was cut down by a professional hitman
The killer
was never caught
but he accidentally blinded a singer
What was her name?
Jennie!
She hasn't recovered yet
Life's cheap, it only takes one bullet
He's no ordinary assassin
I hope we're just looking for one man
If I'm not mistaken
This man is not a cold-blooded murderer
It only takes one bullet
cold blooded or not
He risked his life to save the little girl
And if he did hurt the singer by accident
He must have contacted her
Jeff?
I'm not Jeff
I'm sorry, I can't see clearly
I thought you were my friend
This is a beautiful song
Could you sing it again?
I only sing for one person
Jeff?
Your singing is so full of emotion
After listening to it, I feel like I know your friend already
I wish he was here now
Wherever he may be, you are in his thoughts
But a part of him will always be here
Don't you trust me anymore?
You know why
Of course
People in our profession
are not supposed to trust anyone
How did they know I'd go to that beach?
I might have been followed
when I drove the car there
That's my fault
Who wants me dead?
Why do you ask?
You know the rules
Why didn't you flee, after the job?
I haven't got my money yet
Who wants to kill me?
If you hadn't exposed your identity
he wouldn't want you dead
Answer me, who wants to kill me?
Answer me first, do you have any bullets left?
I always save the last bullet
Either for myself, or my enemy
It's Johnny Weng, Tony Weng's nephew, he wants you dead
He hired you to kill his uncle
Do you really have one last bullet?
Jeff, thank you for sparing me
We are in the same boat now
There's no way out for us
I never want to see you again
Inspector Li!
Inspector Li, five dead witnesses
It was him
Are you sure?
Show his picture to the neighbors and ask if he was here
Ok
Inspector Li, you hit it on the nail
The neighbors say he lives here
Are you nuts?
Jennie!
Jeff, it's you?
Why don't you come back?
I'll be back this morning
We're moving to a new home
Why?
I thought you loved
to live by the sea
do
Beautiful sea breezes
I can imagine the view of the deep blue sea
and the clear blue sky
Great, pack your things and wait for me
I'll be here
You didn't leave Hong Kong when you had the chance
What stopped you?
Are you the new janitor?
Yes lady
You're not doing your job properly
This is a fire-escape
Look, there's garbage everywhere
What happens if there's a fire?
I can't fly away like a phoenix
I pay my maintenance fee every month
If I find you lazy again
I'll file a complaint against you
Don't leave...
- any garbage here - You bet lady
Move it all away
Shit
Jeff, you're back
Yes, Jennie
Are you with a friend?
Yes, he used to play football with me
We grew up in the same squatter area
Yes He's
I'm Dumbo, he's Mickey Mouse
You called each other that?
It's good to see you again
I don't share that feeling
You're not pleased to see your friend?
We're not that close
He's been causing me a lot of trouble
I'm here to sort it out
Have a seat
Let me make you some tea
Don't bother
No need
Please be careful
Take care, Jennie
I know how to do it, I won't hurt myself
Jeff, take care of Dumbo while I make the tea
Dumbo, make yourself at home
I am, Mickey Mouse
Ma'am, why're you so concerned about the garbage?
He paid me 1,000 bucks
to keep you talking
Don't walk out on me now!
I haven't had this much fun
in twenty years!
You're going to lose this game
Am I? Let's wait and see
You're always the loser
Not this time, I'm well prepared
Let's put your preparations to the test
Are you always so determined?
Yes, that's my style
Mine too!
So we have something in common
Is that what you think?
For sure
Have some tea, whilst you catch up on old times
Thanks Jennie,
be careful
Jennie, this is Dumbo's hand
Here's your tea
- Thank you - Pleasure
Is he another friend of yours?
No, he's the janitor
We don't have a janitor in this building
Oh, he's the plumber
There's a burst water pipe outside
Dumbo, your voice is so familiar
Have we met somewhere before?
I met you in the nightclub
I loved your singing,
but you didn't want to sing without Jeff there
Oh, I remember
What a coincidence!
Dumbo, take care of Jennie for a while
I'm going to the bathroom
Me too
There's another bathroom in the bedroom
Jennie, there's a rat
Rat?
In the kitchen, I'll catch it
Hey, don't shoot! It's me!
Don't shoot!
Somebody down there's aiming at my ass!
Jennie!
What happened?
Where's Jeff?
I know you and Jeff lied to me
Tell me the truth!
Who the hell are you?
I'm a cop
Jeff is a professional killer
He murdered somebody
I've been after him for months
I don't believe you
Jennie!
Listen to me, Jennie
No I won't
Jennie, it's true
Chang!
Jennie, calm down
Listen please!
Sit down
Six months ago
Jeff shot your face up by accident
Now, his employer wants him dead
I don't believe it
I'd like to help but I can't in my position
I hope you'll cooperate with us
Jennie, we're using you as bait
If I can get Jeff in this time
I'll be able to help save his life,
otherwise the guy who hired him will kill him
Name your price, I just want him dead!
He was seen on the job
I want him wasted, the sooner the better
Deposit US$100,000 into my account now
another US$200,000 on completion
No money no action Mr Weng
Not even if I see someone's finger on the trigger,
ready to blow your head off
Get the hundred grand into his account
I could have got him
What do you want?
You should pay Jeff,
or he could be a real danger to you
That's bullshit! I'm safe
Look at these guys, they're killers
You're the boss, you should keep your word
Don't talk crap
I ain't going to pay him,
even if you beg
Mr Weng, let me keep my word,
and pay him what I promised
Then I'll bring him to you
Mr Weng, if it pleases you,
I will beg
Go to hell, you jerk!
If you hadn't worked for my father for so long
I'd have kicked the shit out of you
Who is he? He doesn't deserve your sympathy
Why are you doing all this for Jeff?
He's my best friend
Cut the crap!
Come here now! Mr Weng's been shot
Kill him!
Kill him!! Don't let him go!
Mr Weng!
Mr Weng, you've been hurt!
Just kill him!
Let's go! You're in danger
Get after him!
If you consider me your friend,
kill me now
I loathe seeing you demean yourself
by begging
Though I didn't succeed
I risked my life to get your money
I could have just killed you
I didn't have to beg Weng for your money
I'm not completely without honour, am I?
Our world is changing so fast
It never used to be like this
Perhaps we are too nostalgic
Nostalgia is one of our saving graces
At least, when I die,
I'll know I was remembered by a friend
Let's settle our dues in the next life
Think we can cancel them right now,
that's what friend are for
Right?
A drink?
Thank you
Jennie always wanted to live by the sea
You've done so much for her
I wonder how she feels about you?
Hello?
Jennie!
Jeff, why did you leave me?
You didn't say goodbye
I'm sorry I had something to do
We've got to leave tonight
Tonight?
Dr Ho called this afternoon
He's reserved a pair of corneas,
but they're in Singapore
We have to be there by midnight,
or they automatically to go someone else
Alright, I'll take you
Ok, be at the airport at 7:30 tonight
I'll meet you near Information, you must come
Of course, bye-bye
Do you think he'll come?
Will you go?
I trust her
Everybody's here, let's go
How's it going?
Right, full alert now
I want you to check,
every inch of this place
Everything's ready
If he dares to come,
he will never escape
Jeff!
Get away from here, run!
She's crazy!
Jeff!
Jeff, the cops are everywhere, run away!
Jeff, the cops want you,
don't come near me
Jeff, are you there?
Run
Don't let them catch you
Are you alone?
Run, Jeff!
The cops are after you
Freeze!
Jeff, the cops are all over the place
Jeff, the cops are everywhere!
Escape! Please get away!
Jeff, run!
It's me, Jennie!
Don't move
Let's go
What is it, officer?
Flirting is not a crime
Arrest him!
Keep clear everyone!
Let me through!
Don't move
Stop!
Stop! We have to check that luggage
We're sorry
Open those suitcases
What were you doing at the airport?
Chasing tail!
What is your job?
I'm a casting agent for movie companies
Why did you run and resist arrest?
I was drunk
Stand up and walk a straight line
Where is your friend?
What friend?
I'm sure you know who I mean
He's in grave danger
Help him, tell me where he is
I want to help him solve his problem
I have some questions to ask him
That's none of my business
But if the guy you're talking about is my friend
He sure doesn't need your help
From now on, you're off Weng's case
Inspector Chan will take over
I'm assigning you a new case
I want an explanation
I don't trust you
Siding with the suspect,
is not the way to catch him
Sir, you don't understand how I work
You said it! That's why you're off the case
I won't give up the investigation
Bullshit!
Chang, you're now Chan's assistant
Yes Sir!
Release the man you arrested at the airport
Give him a twenty hour surveillance
He'll lead us to Weng's assassin
Have you got that?
Yes Sir!
Will you kill again?
I thought the people I killed deserved to die
Now, I believe everybody has the right to live
No, I won't kill again
I hope I can keep my promise
I've been followed!
Weng's men, and the cops too
Don't worry, I took care of them
Weng's hired Paul Yau to waste you
Don't worry, you can use my guns and ammo
Where are you going?
To get your money off Weng
I'll meet you in the church
Are you going alone?
Yes, of course
I have to keep my promise
Weng is not going to hurt me,
I still deserve some respect
Sidney, I don't need the money
I do need your friendship
Chang! Chang!
I followed him to, 6 Horizon Drive
I almost got him
I know
Yes sir! Mr Weng!
Don't worry, I'll find him
Chang, don't worry
Eagle
You can't win all the time
But you can't lose forever either
Chang! Chang!
Inspector Li, did he give us anything?
Go ask him yourself!
Jeff!
Jennie, what is it?
Why's it so dark this morning?
It's just a cloudy day
Relax, it'll be alright?
Are we leaving today?
Yes
Freeze!
Who is it?
It's Dumbo!
What does he want?
He's come to say goodbye
What're you waiting for?
I'm a cop, I don't shoot people in the back
Another way we're the same
No we're not the same!
I uphold the law and you break it!
Chang died because of you
I swore I'd get you this time
I'm sorry
But I won't let you put me in prison
If you must take revenge for your friend
Shoot me now
Don't force me to kill you
So you really would kill me?
I won't let you go this time
Ok let's see it
You can't win all the time
Jeff, where are you?
Jeff!
Where's Dumbo? Where is he?
Right in front of you
Don't take him away
Jennie!
Jeff's promised me he'll never kill again
Put that gun down
Jennie, put that gun down
Not unless he leaves us alone
I beg you, please, let us go
- Jennie! - I'll never let you arrest him
Did I kill him? Is he dead?
I didn't mean to kill him, I didn't mean it
He's alright
I didn't mean to
Calm down, be brave
You stay there!
Jeff...Jeff
Let's get out of here, then you can arrest me
Let's get Jennie out of here
The car's outside
Come on!
I won't let you put me behind bars
Throw the gun down
I know you won't kill a cop
Thank you
You could have killed me with one shot
I don't kill anybody
until I know they are the real enemy
Do you really know me?
Sometimes fate controls everything
The only person who really knows me turns out to be a cop
But you could always give up
No, I've made a promise,
I keep my word
Sometimes, I really envy your freedom
I just don't have it
I believe in justice
but nobody trusts me
I have the same problem
You're an unusual cop
And you're an unusual killer too
I'm sorry to drag you into this mess
Tell me, who is behind all this?
That's not my game, I play by the rules
I knew you'd never tell me
Take care of Jennie
Weng won't stop untill he kills you
You'd better let me arrest you
We'll stay here tonight
Then Sidney will bring me my money,
and we'll leave tomorrow
I'm scared those gangsters will find us here
Don't worry
This is an out of the way place
Why is it so dark?
I can hardly see anything
Jeff, turn on the lights, please
Why don't you turn on the lights?
Jeff!
Jeff, turn on the lights!
There has been a power cut
Will your friend come back with the money?
I'm sure he will
Boss
Here's the US$100,000. Please check it
Do you think Paul Yau will be able to kill Jeff?
Boss, Sidney Fung's here
If he betrays you again, then what?
I'd still treat him as my friend
He was so good to me
Where is Jeff's money?
Where the hell is he?
I wish I could have a friend like you
You will, one of these days
Drop your guns!
Your right hand still works?
Yes, well enough
It still fires a gun, fast and accurate
You've got no way out,
why're you doing all this?
You tell me, what's the alternative?
Where's the money?
Give it!
I'm one step ahead
Why didn't you shoot me in the head?
Right
Maybe I'm just not a professional anymore
I wish I could start all over again
It's a pity
Give me the cash
Where is Jeff?
Give me the money first
We owe it to him
Hypocrite!
Do all killers have a sense of honor?
Our world is changing so fast, honor's
Sidney, sometimes I think you're not human
You're more like a dog
At least we have one thing in common
We both use guns for our living
Just our motivation's different
Right?
In some ways dogs are superior to men
If you don't tell me where Jeff is
This is your funeral
Throw this garbage away
Give me the money
Are you sure you still got bullets?
You want a bet?
Jeff said, always save one last slug
Either for yourself, or your enemy
Quick!
Turn around!
Godamnit!
Get him!
I want you to promise me one thing
if I don't make it
Take me to a hospital
Get the doctors to operate, my corneas are for Jennie
If you can't do that, organize my money
and send her abroad for surgery
Don't think like that
It's the first decent thing I've ever done
Will you help me?
What's that noise?
Who is it Jeff?
It's Sidney Fung
Sidney
Here's your money I fought for it like a man
This is my last tribute to a friend
Sidney, you didn't have to do this
He said I was a dog
Now I'm not sure if I'm human,
or a dog?
Sidney, nobody can call you a dog
Sidney, Sidney!
Sidney!
Sidney, Sidney, are you alright?
Am I a dog?
No, you're not a dog. You're a great man!
We're outmoded characters, outcasts of our community
I don't want to die like a dog
But you see, I didn't keep one last bullet
I have one
Jeff!
Jennie, stay where you are
Don't leave me alone!
What are you going to do?
Storm my way out!
Don't kill anymore, please?
Give up your guns and come with me
What? You say me kill Sidney
He was my best friend
And you dare to tell me to give up?
When Chang died
I swore I'd kill you
But now I don't want you to get killed
Get out of here with Jennie
How?
They'll chase me to the ends of the earth
I have nowhere to go
Get out there and tell them you're cop,
see if they give up their guns
- Jennie! - Jeff!
Jeff!
Dumbo!
Thanks, Mickey Mouse!
Dumbo, I owe you
You don't owe me nothing
This is the gift of friendship
Good luck!
Jennie, take cover!
Don't move!
Jennie!
Dumbo!
Give me gun!
Mickey Mouse, here!
How good a shot are you?
I'm a cop, I've got to be good!
We've been through so much together,
I don't even know your name
Is it important?
Whether we win or lose,
you ain't going to be around
I'd like to have a name to remember you by forever
Would you rather see me dead or set free?
If fate spares us, I don't want either
You're a helluva good friend!
Remember me as Mickey Mouse, why not?
Come back!
I must find my friend
Leave her alone, she's innocent!
Move!
Drop your gun!
Drop your gun
Godamnit! You heard me? Hurry up!
Jeff, where are you, Jeff?
Jennie, don't be afraid, I'm in front of you
Drop your gun
Jennie, don't move an inch
Don't hurt her
No, I won't hurt her
I'll just kill her
Release her!
Stop
Let her go
No way!
What if I don't?
Drop your guns!
Dumbo!
Will you do what you've promised?
No problem
Don't forget, there's always a friend to back you up!
Drop the guns, or I'll kill her
Drop your guns, idiots!
Mickey Mouse
Jeff!
Jennie!
Jeff, where are you?
Jeff!
Don't move!
Ok! Ok! I surrender,
I'll cooperate, arrest me please!
You're an unusual cop
And you're an unusual killer too
I believe in justice
but nobody trusts me
I have the same problem
Arrest him
I'll do it!
Arrest me, arrest me
Arrest me! I'm asking for police custody!
I'm a criminal, arrest me!
Mickey Mouse...