It's an heirloom, pay up if you scratch it.
Nonsense, I remember that suitcase.
You discovered it abandoned by someone...
At the airport,
and you brought it home.
It stinks like an old fish now.
Uncle kin, I was only joking.
Joking?
You have nothing to gain if you fire me.
Business is bad after the June the 4th crackdown.
Don't laugh. Traffic light.
They've all emigrated.
If I leave you too, you're going to be bored.
I'm even more bored having to pay you each month.
Why don't you give me any face then?
Stop it.
Sorry.
Your crab.
- It's yours. - Sorry.
Am I interrupting?
Oh, no. What can I do for you?
There's a Jim kee garage at 2 pok ching street.
You know where?
Miss, here it is, 2 pok ching street.
Oh yes.
I'm the president and general manager of this garage,
and concurrently chief mechanic. I'm Dr. lau ting kin.
I'm his boss.
Don't listen to him, he's out of his mind.
I'm you client,
ain't I your boss?
- Have you got a car? - Sure!
Please make it run.
It's so humble here, let's go for tea, come on.
Ching, man, tack.
Auntie man.
Man, you're so early.
Brother-in-law.
This four eyes looks familiar.
- Auntie man. - Brother-in-law.
Auntie man have you seen my new shop?
No.
Look, it's here.
Well, I remember now.
Aren't you lau ting kin's god brother?
You're bloody bluffer Jim.
You haven't changed after all these years.
Poor fellow, now you're sunk to a repairer.
What, what do you then?
I'm the boss of the garage next to you.
Why aren't you repairing a car then?
I have three daughters who can help me.
Uncle.
They're all so beautiful.
They can't be yours.
My wife is dead, don't use her name in vain.
Oh, ting ting was my flame...
But she died after marrying you.
She was always in love with me.
You entangled her and she died as a result.
Outrageous. First you took away my love,
and made me a life long bachelor,
and now you're my competitor in the garage business.
Sure, I'll make you go broke.
We'll see which of us will go broke first.
Let me help you compete against him.
I don't need your help.
I'll bring in a few wolves to ruin your daughters.
The romancing star III
lo kar ling, lo kar ling.
Hey, lo kar ling.
What's the matter? Boss.
I'll give you the lead role.
Don't ruin my show!
Or I'll fire you.
Boss,
I'm nervous, I've forgotten my lines.
Let me read the script again.
Crazy. It's too late now.
Go and ad-lib.
Are you alright?
Yes. Oh, no.
You're in trouble, you hit me hard.
If I get nasty.
Your pants are finished.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't repent now, at worst I'll let you hug me.
You be the godmother I'll be the baby.
You're crazy, you're crazy, you've got aids.
You're head's bigger than Kenny b, but your mind's like a baby's.
You've made me lose face.
I'll shoot you till you're finished.
- Boss, I... - Well, don't expect to go on anymore.
Oh no, I've been fired.
Darling, darling.
Bad, my husband's returning.
No? Darling.
Get dressed quickly.
Oh, darling.
Just now I saw a set of excellent furniture.
Darling, this bed is not bad.
No.
I'm just slept on it, mr.Chu.
Oh, yes.
Hey, this double bed matches in color and suits you best.
Damn fatty, you're seducing my wife.
What... what did you say? Have you got any proof?
Proof? You're the 2nd man after Superman who
wears the underpants inside out.
The tribunal for crasing the membership of the triad society.
Don't stare. Have you never been chopped? Damn your whole family.
Fill in the form now.
Nonsense.
I'm here to have my criminal records removed.
Now do it for me or I'll chop all your family.
Okay, okay.
Don't state or I'll chop you dead.
"Please open"
please put your beautiful face in.
Angel, you're an angel in my eyes.
Guess who I am?
Stallune?
No.
Jackie?
I'm your faithful servant, weakling chen.
May I kiss you?
Excuse me.
Don't!
I beat you
help!
Sit down. Have some tea.
Hello, guys.
Have some tea...
How have you been getting on?
So-so.
Frankly, I'm now out of a job.
Me too.
Who'll pay for this meal then?
Cousin, the elder should pay.
This should be your treat.
Have you no sympathy.
I've already decided to go straight.
I can't chop or frame anyone anymore.
I can't charge high interest either.
I've no more means of making a living.
Please, for heaven's sake,
pay for this.
You may drive me to desperation,
if you insist I pay for this.
Keep cool, keep cool.
I've offended big sister, anymore.
I have no standing in the cantonese opera world anymore.
Cousina, with a good voice like mine,
what other acting can I do?
Mime.
Cousin, of us four
you look the richest.
No way.
I look like chin han but I have no lover like liu ching hsia.
I look like Erin tung shung.
But I have no lover like cheung man yuk.
I look like lau tack wah, but...
Who is it? Who is it?
And why doesn't Madonna like me?
All bloody nonsense.
I've been muttering nothing but nonsense.
Well, let's not argue anymore. Yo.
You be the host in respect of the three elders, okay?
Why?
Because your name is frailty and you can't complain.
Oh, on the crossroads.
I don't know which way to go.
If I were a girl, I'd become a taxi dancer.
With looks like yours you'd be done for.
Damn you.
Oh, look, over there.
What is it?
What does it say?
Jesus saves. Uncle kin saves Hong Kong.
Have your car fixed by kin, you need fear no tanks.
He helps you emigrate and be free.
So many benefits. You could buy a house if you worked here.
Of course.
Aren't you uncle kin?
Well, if you hadn't told me,
I would have known you were looking for work.
Although I've had 2000 applicants,
for only 4 vacancies.
I'll give you young men a chance,
by giving you an interview. Come in.
Hey, you promised to help me emigrate.
You'd have to choose countries other than the Soviet union and China, first.
Even if it's the last one I'll follow.
Can you afford an investment of us$1 million?
What about half a million?
What about $200,000?
Are you a university graduate and have you special skills?
Forget it then.
You can only emigrate to two places,
the north pole,
or aricutta in Africa.
The hottest temperatures in summer
is 110 below at north pole zero.
Aricutta.
It's like spring the four seasons,
the girls are all beautiful like flowers,
fruits are abundant everywhere and you don't have to work.
I want to go to aricutta.
But the aids rate is 90%.
That means 9 aids sufferers out of 10 people.
Well you'd better go then.
But don't worry,
if you sign this contract with us,
you'll not only get benefits,
but assurances of
immigration to a paradise.
- What do you say? - Let's accept it for the time being.
You young men have no legal common sense.
You signed it,
without asking about the working hours
and the terms.
Luckily you came upon me.
Listen, you work 18 hours per day,
17 hours on Sundays,
and get 11 months pay each year.
Your pay on the month of my birthday is deducted for my gift.
Your monthly wages are $1300 each.
$700 is deducted for one day's leave and $500 for late arrival.
Your first six months pay will be deducted as security.
Besides fixing cars,
you're got to do household work for me,
like cooking and doing the laundry. Understand?
Before you worked with horses, now you're a menial worker.
You're well served.
Beautiful, four beautiful girls.
Beautiful, but are they meant for us?
I don't mind coming up
to hang clothes everyday now.
Young ladies our grettings to you
louder.
Can you do it? Let me help you.
Hey beautiful, want to go to cheung kwok wing's concert?
I've got tickets, it's free.
Why no response?
Could they be fans of Alan tam?
What a stinking month.
Hey, they could be acting?
No, no. Go and test them out.
I first
I am willing to follow you.
Only three ropes left, I'll be counted out for sure.
Someone is going to shoot themselves over.
I'll do you a favor and let you go.
Okay, you go.
How touching
you really are nice cousin.
Go on bitch.
I'll count up to three and fly over.
1, 2,
2 and a half,
3, go
Hey, dried pork why aren't we moving?
What are you up to?
It's stuck.
Come on, pull me up now.
Oh no, all three ropes are stuck.
Let me get someone to help you.
Hurry up.
I will.
Damn, he's still not back.
I'll mince him.
Oh, on the rope's going to...
Shut your stinking mouth.
- Help! - Help!
- Taking a bath? - Sex fiends, sex fiends.
Sex fiends.
One more sex maniac.
One more ugly sex maniac.
What? I'm a member of the flying tiger squad.
Flying tiger squad?
He asked for it.
He really is coming up. Let's stand by.
Okay, wait till he gets close,
1, 2, 3...
Oh my god! Look at that!
Help!
Oh, it's you! How dare you?
I didn't want to.
You bastard.
You play a young man, a bad man.
It's so exciting.
You're treating us to tea?
Are there burglars in here?
You would scare them off.
Oh, it hurts.
Boss, headquarters wants you back.
Hurry up.
Get me in first.
You don't have to.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Today is the official opening of Jim kee garage.
We offer 31% off all services.
Mr. kwan is here.
It's that bore again.
Let's get going.
Uncle Jim have you got a new employee?
My sister-in-low man.
Mr. kwan, ching, tack, mun.
Come here, let me introduce you to Mr. kwan.
My three daughters Mr. kwan.
Hi.
Hello, don't come round when you have time.
Sorry, my two sisters are cranky,
please don't blame them.
I won't, anyway you're different.
Not any different.
Damn, he's taken away my customers.
Hello... come here.
Go and tout for customers.
Hi father, want to have your car fixed?
Yes, but...
Don't hesitate, we can fix anything.
I tell you,
don't ever patronize them,
their service is lousy.
And they don't believe in gods. Patromize us.
You get free barbecue port buns from us too.
Mine's a bicycle.
We can fix it all the same.
Hey, come here.
Hey, lau ting kin.
You've gone too far.
Is this any of your business?
God has sent a priest to patronize us.
Complain to god if you'd prefer.
- You talk too much. - He's my customer.
I'm a Christian, I pray every day.
- You should pafronize a Christian. - Father patronize me
and you'll get free barbecue port buns.
Don't argue with each other.
You have a wheel, you have a wheel too.
- No. - No. They are both mine.
Is mine.
You've damaged my wheels,
I can't use it anymore.
- It's alright. - Alright?
Yes, get him.
Aren't you members of the flying tigers squad?
Flying tiger squad?
Well, can't I do that?
Bite my head, it's hard.
Bite my chest, it has bones.
Bite my potbelly, it's tough.
Bite me.
I don't want to say that.
Don't bite that.
You're damned.
I have no more wheels.
What happened?
Lau ting-kin
and those four bastards came to snatch my business.
Don't waste your time on these ignorant people.
This is the property of my property company.
Tomorrow I'll announce a rent rise of 30 times.
What, did I offend your mother?
There's no point in getting excited.
Hey, what's up?
Don't try anything foolish.
Don't worry I'm here.
Watch out.
It stinks,
it scared all the customers off.
And my sister's in a coma too. Go now.
- Go now. - Go now.
You did it.
Ridiculous!
How dare you lay hands on my boss.
Hey, what's the idea?
I'll get you too, damn you.
Hey, come and give me a hand.
We will for some money.
I'll give all my money to you.
That's different.
If you hadn't had got away, I would have castrated you.
Hey, pay up.
Don't worry, I'll keep my promise.
What? 80 cents?
I only keep up to $10 in my pocket.
I'd rather borrow then lend to others.
Are you alright daddy?
How are you brother-in-law?
Lau ting kin took me unawares.
How dare they beat my daddy.
Get a spanner to hit them.
Don't use a spanner to fight.
Don't be nice to those kind of people.
Men can't be killed with spanners.
- Use a softball bat. - Okay.
How can this be?
- It hurts. - It hurts, I won't do it again.
I promise I won't resist anymore.
Don't hit me, please.
At worse I'll let you do anything you like.
So, daddy has beaten them up.
If they die daddy might get jailed.
Man, get plasters to dress their wounds.
Go and see to them
are you alright?
You howl like a dog. Come on.
What are you doing?
You're not as badly hurt as I am.
I'm badly hurt, pity me.
Wait four the ambulance then.
Okay.
You don't care about how I suffer.
So poor.
I'll get some plasters for him in a minute.
In fact I'm suffering even more internally.
- Is that so? - A mental illness requires mental treatment.
You mean that
if we go out with you for a meal
and a movie you'll recover.
Right, right, right.
It's too expensive.
Buy back stalls, $30 is too much for loge.
I'm lucky.
Don't laugh, if could be a trick.
Let me go out and see.
Man man, man man.
Yes?
You look like your bigger sister ting.
I think of her when I see you.
Don't.
I wish I had...
A chance to chat to you alone
to show my feelings for your bigger sister.
You mustn't.
My sister died years ago.
Isn't it boring talking about her now?
Don't be loutish.
Wait for me in the street
at 7:30 if you want to date me.
Oh, I'm lucky.
My methods of seducing girls are great.
I'm sending if to janpan to see if any garage will buy it.
What's so special?
Once a girl gets in,
the seat belt, once fastened, can't be undone.
It gets tigher and tigher.
To avoid seducing the wrong girl,
once turned on,
any dentures, false lashes, wigs, padded bras
are removed.
After the check up one push will
turn the seat into a bed.
And there's soft music and laser lights.
Another device is the automatic safety system.
It serves as a reminder to you.
So you can mix with any girls in the world.
I love it.
Such a fantastic car may cause vandalism.
The two sides of the bonnet...
Can spray red paint
and plastic bullets.
Anyone seratching if will get hit.
And the rear of their car
can emit a stinking smell.
It can shoot at anyone trying to beep you,
besides.
There are two loudspeakers on the top
so you can guarrel with anyone.
They'll definifely drown out any other sounds.
I like that.
Hold on...
Well, what if she smelt bad
or exposed her defects?
Right.
Don't worry, pushing this button
will catapult the person beside you out of the car.
Hey, why have you taken away my design?
If this car should fall into your sex in end hands
any innocent girl in Hong Kong would be finished.
Let me try.
I give you three days to turn one out.
This car costs at least $300,000.
Hell, $30.000, $3,000 will fix it.
$3,000?
Sorry, no way.
How can we buy spare pats with only $3,000?
There's nothing I can do.
The trouble is your name is frailty.
Won't you join us?
Yes, yes.
Come in and take him to the roof to do an opera.
Buddy.
I told you not to call me buddy.
It's underworld slang only.
They take the law into their own hands.
And call me big brother.
Big brother, we'll castrate anyone who joins us.
There's no point in adopting small brothers.
You're crazy, 1997 is approaching fast.
Without money how can we emigrate?
We're members of the underworld, no worries.
Those old fellows are members of the underworld as well.
But they destroy anyone who goes against them.
They'll frame anyone for any crime.
They talk black into white and kill many innocents.
Yet they say none have been killed.
Aren't they worse than us?
Well, take it as bargaining over terms then.
There number is one billion.
What have we got? To talk with a hair, idiot?
No, look.
500 dollars.
Right, right.
Make a counter offer if you prefer. Come in.
Please.
A guest.
Yo, let's come back later.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
What, are you trying to make trouble?
Once inside you must buy.
Buy, buy, buy.
Leave your thumbprint and bring $500,000 tomorrow.
It said $500, why half a million now?
$500 for the windscreen only,
the car costs $500,000.
How can we have half a million?
How much have you got?
Only $3,000
well, we'll take this money
as a visiting fee.
You don't have to buy. Go now.
Big brother why don't you bring them in?
One weights less than 100 pounds
and the other's less than 5' 2".
Even the police station won't take them, let alone us.
Tell them to leave thumbprints.
They've voluntarily paid us this for the visit.
Take off their clothes and throw them out.
Go now.
Ontrageous. What a frame up.
Why don't you let me frame you instead?
Those thugs are tough.
I've never seen any tough guys in my life.
Keep cool, firsts can't fight 4 hands.
What then? Are we to call it quits?
Now yo has more money for spare parts.
We should get a car to fool around.
My friend's got a Van. Let's borrow from him.
What about the spare parts?
Let's try to get them from the market.
Where is it?
In the street.
We to go out at midnight.
Pick any piece you like.
The four really lazy. They've already closing.
Bad man!
Uncle kin, a bad man car.
A bad man car?
A bad man car plus a bad man robe.
That's quite smart!
Well, I'll let you leave 15 minutes earlier tonight.
Bad man robe.
Mammy, a vampire!
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid!
They say "vampire".
Bye!
Your car's funny, let me drive it.
You can't!
Let me drive it or I won't heed you.
Okay, you win.
Man man, I feel you're more beautiful then your sister.
When you first stepped into the entrance of my garage,
I knew you were a consolation prize from heaven.
Turn on the music, it's so boring.
Push the button, please.
How come?
You may unfasten your seat belt.
Try this, I want some music.
- Sun ma tsai. - Yes?
It's so jarring!
Switch to another station.
Break through hour compered by rev. Dulles.
Woe betide those who commit adultery.
Don't, god forbid...
Woe betide those who adulterate.
Ladies, don't be misled by so-called love,
and don't get involved in sexual complications.
So you're a love crook!
Don't listen to this nonsense.
Come back - go away!
Hello, don't go away!
He's only muttering nonsense.
Don't believe in it!
Damn this car, let me pull it down.
What now?
Keep clam!
Listen, don't move, all of you!
Don't be threatened by them!
We'll pull down your car.
Don't!
You're lucky, I used plastic bullets.
Had I used real bullets like they did, you'd have died.
Let's attack from behind.
Oh, it's stinkier than manure.
Well, I already warned you extras.
Now get out, or I'll kill you.
Let me push the button to see if it works.
Don't
don't do it at random!
Don't!
Please, don't - beat him.
Help!
Does it hurt badly?
Damn you, damn you!
An invention? What invention?
Oh, uncle kin.
You really got beaten up like that?
I should've introduced you to take out and insurance.
Then you'll be getting compensation now.
What?
Insurance against assanlt aricing from,
libel, sex harassment or bad looks,
if only you can prove either one, you'll get 25%
I'm lucky, I can prove all of them.
Sometimes ago,
chan pai-cheung was assaulted in Australia,
and he got a 100% compensation.
Would I get the benefit if it was through your medium?
Well, let me go out for a rest.
Hello, uncle kin.
I've only just opened. Buy some.
In return, I'll help you wso that girl next-door.
Hello... do help us.
Okay.
Take out an insurance.
Is it true you're a love bug?
Sure.
As your friend, let me show you something.
If it works, take out an insurance from me.
We dated the 4 girls next-door for a show tomorrow night.
Good, good, we can woo them there.
This is the rudiment of 13 ways to woo a girl.
Put the chair.
There are girls and girls.
Many are the ways to woo them.
You come here.
He wants you to go over.
Go over.
Come one, sit down.
Brave men like me do it this way.
Put your hand on her shoulder.
Then attack like an awalande.
Paw her all over like a hurricame.
You make it or part with $30 to get off the hook.
This suits me best.
What about he second way?
Sure, play small and it suits you best.
Take her to the seat inside the cinema house.
Take off your coat like a gentleman.
"Miss, it's cold here, keep covered."
"Thank you."
Not bad.
Remember, don't play tough.
Wait patiently till the show's over.
Play "cold", the airconditioning is so cold."
"Oh, it's so cold."
"It's so cold, I'm trembling."
The more you shake, the more you get closer.
The more you shake, the closer...
It's so cold, so cold...
Seeing you tremlding which cold.
She won't stop you, will she?
You get closer and closer.
Then you get warm and it words.
This is called "dramatic", understand?
What if you should come up on a tough girl.
And you want to cool her off?
What have you got then?
That's a good question.
Here's a gimmick of "touching the elbow."
What good is it in touching the elbow?
Touching the elbow?
As I said, you're not yet up to the scratch.
The elbow is an important strategic position.
A girl won't resist this strongly.
Now, listen, you sit next to her.
And stretch out your hand slowly to touch her elbow.
Attack if the opportunity arises.
Touch, touch, or retreat if needs be,
attack openly,
or attack secretly.
If you won't attack,
just touch her hand.
Or attach by putting your hand on her other hand.
Thank you
nothing you can do
in fact, you're still touching her.
Be flexible.
Right.
One thing ou must remember is,
girls of the 90's have a strange mentality.
They want to be wooed but,
don't want to show they can easily be wooed.
So take a low-key stance.
Make believe you're wooing her when you've already won her heart.
Make believe you've gained nothing.
Then she'll keep her pride,
and love you from the down of her heart. Right?
Yes, ok.
Good, remember it well.
Now take out some insurance from me, ok?
Yes, but do me a favor.
Man man, tack, ching, mun.
Beautiful, where's bluffer Jim?
In the toilet. What for?
So much the better.
I'm bringing you tickets from those boys next-door.
Don't let daddy hear it. Show me.
Look, the back of it shows wher to wait.
Hello.
Why no toilet paper?
Oh, Jim.
Jim, it has been a long time.
Hello... oh, no.
Are you after my sister-in-law or my daughters?
I have something important to talk to you.
Do come in.
Hey... what is the up to?
No idea.
Look.
You know what a brinkman is?
Yes, I saw him in a show.
I'm a brinkman.
Oh.
Your neighbor lau ting-kin is none,
other than an underworld boss.
I imagined it.
I'm an undercover agent.
Recently he's suspicions, so I've to quit.
He's cold-blooded.
Those 4 boys of different sizes are,
killers.
They even finished off some cops.
And they killed cops at the vietham came too.
He's perverted. He peeped when I was taking a bath.
He sure is.
They are suspected of being involved in the sodomy case.
What shall I do then?
Don't worry, if you co-operate with the police,
pretemed to be nice to them.
If they date your daughters,
let hem go out with them to awoid suspicions.
Remember, watch lam ting-kin
call me if anything happens.
I'm in a dangerous situation them.
If you are afraid
well, I'll gind someone else.
There's a $1 million reward for the arrest of lau ting-kin.
I'm a model citizen.
None can do the job better than I.
Here it is.
Brother-in-law, what happened?
Nothing, nothing.
Well, if the boys next-door date you,
don't turn them down.
Remember.
"See you at theatre."
Oh, it's you.
We'd better go in.
Go in? Okay.
One packet each of cuttle fish and dried beef, please.
Okay.
Oh, it's you!
Sure, am I a disgrace to you?
I don't mean that.
What are you staring at?
I'll kill your whole family, set five to your house.
Popcorns, please.
Let's go in.
Okay. Buy something to eat.
Hey, one whole bag of popcorns, bigger.
Well, I forgive you.
Let's go in. Please follow me.
- Not yet up to 18 years of age - I've got a ticket.
Sorry, go now.
Show me your l.D. Card.
What?
People under 18 are not allowed to see this 3 grade movie.
I'm already 28.
Sow me your l.D. Card.
I forgot to bring it.
Go home and get it or you'll be barced.
I really an 28 years old.
Tell him how old I am.
Sixteen.
You go in now. I'll go home to get it.
Oh, it's you. Where's mun mun?
You dated mun mun. I must leave.
I've dated you.
You're crafty, you'br brought me to a horror picture.
Don't just stand there, get going.
Oh.
"See you inside the theatre"
excuse me.
Hi, come and sit down.
Oh, it's you, dried port.
It's youl!
Advance or retreat...
What?
A dimensional movie.
The fists come right on your face.
Wear eyeglasses first.
Advance or retreat...
Keep your eyes on the screen.
Are you cold?
Let me take off my coat to cover you up.
No, keep it for yourself.
Oh, it doesn't work.
Let me try the other gimmick.
One girl ever day, don't touch my girl.
I've wooed her for 3 years but have never touched her leg.
Now you've stolen a march.
Sorry, sorry.
Next time don't do it.
I know you'd cry, but not the way you do.
Look, she's crying with such god presentation.
Not as bad as you did.
Pretend not to know me, sit over there, please.
I'm scared to sit alone.
I'll take the seat then.
L... 1 will.
If I knew who's the director of this movie,
I'd chop him to over 90 pieces.
Look, everyone's working like hell.
He must be new in filming, look.
Everybody's wearing a stone face.
They're all black men.
Please slow down the voice!
Damn you.
I booed it because it's disgusting, damn you.
Why, why no bedroom. Scene and no stripping?
She's a nun.
Does a nun have to take a bath?
No smoking here, pal.
Which of your eyes saw me smoking?
This.
Hell with you.
- You can't see it now, can you? - No...
Can't see it now.
What was that line?
I don't know, I don't know.
If I knew who the director was,
I'd chop that bastard.
He's a French director.
He died a long time ago.
I see.
My brothers in France must've finished him off.
Hey, pal, quiet, pleas.
Why don't you blame the other?
Do you enjoy staring at me?
Don't see it anymore as penalty.
Don't stare elsewhere, grasp your ear.
Advance or retreat...
Don't you know what I did before?
Dairy farm. Open attack, secret attack.
Hello, I.D. Card.
So you've already 18.
Yes.
- What's it? - Are you out of your mind?
Does the hk govt say anyone with an l.D. Card can see movies?
Tickets?
Dropped.
Don't worry, I'll buy another one
"full house"
oh, no!
What about me? You saw me holding a ticket just now.
My girlfriend is watching the show inside.
Only our manager can decide on this.
Where's your manager?
In the toilet. What for?
Manager, manager.
Yes?
Wait, give me a ticket first.
I can't, I have internal discorder.
Give me a ticket first.
Wait till I've done it.
No, sell me a ticket first.
What kind of a show is that?
Red bean puree lovers, part 29.
It's not a good show. I must go in.
Don't, sell me a ticket first.
This grade lll film poisons youngsters.
You may lose your mind seeing it.
I'll give you a ticket after I finish.
No, the show will be over then. Don't go.
Oh!
No, I can't hold on anymore.
Please help!
I beg you to sell me a ticket.
Don't see such a boring show any more.
If you want, watch a wong Jim show. Understand?
Got it
hold it.
Say ' goodbye ' to me.
Goodbye.
Get and throw it.
Look, we've got much face, right?
Yes.
We may go in.
The show's over, little friend.
Wait for them, okay?
Whom were you seeing the show with?
Lo kr-ling.
Why ask?
What does he do?
He was much scared by that scene.
Well, your sister's here.
Sister, let's go.
Hello, let's have snacks at temple street. I'll be the host.
Don't be formal.
Go in and see your friends.
Friend.
Friend pork.
Hey, dried pork, it's over.
Dried port - are you alright?
Hey, what's wrong? Why's the show so long?
The moment it starts it ends.
It seems 3D.
One puch knocks me unconscious.
Next time don't count me in.
Oh!
Okay! Okay!
Why are you sighing?
Now tienanmen knows your four are frustrated in love.
Oh!
It was all the fault of lau pei.
He mixed up all the ticket. He's damned.
I'm bringing you the insurance policies.
Damn you!
I should've chopped you.
I know you've been in a mess,
I'm here to bring you news.
What's it?
The people from darkie garage opposite
are surrounding bluffer Jim's shop.
Your garage affects our business,
I'm now persuading, you to change your business
to avoid unnecessary competition.
That sounds like a threat!
We can talk it over.
We're all for democracy and freedom.
We don't interfere in each other's business.
As of now, anything happens to you:
Fire, car crash, assault,
burglaty, burst of
the waterpipes, etc.
These are none of my business.
I didn't want to expose my identity, but now I must.
I'm a royal Hong Kong policeman
and a brinkman assigued to watch gang bosses.
Brinkman?
Daddy, what's a brinkman?
Big brother, it could be a hoax,
wish it wasn't true.
Let's go over to ask lau ting-kin,
good, big brother.
You're smart!
Thank you. Let's have some tea first.
Scared? If you leave late, I'll fire at you.
Hey, stand there, none of you shalll leave,
don't take sides of bluffer Jim.
Anyway, we have nothing to do.
Nothing? I'll give you some work to do.
My shoes are torn. Glue them for me,
and you fix that fan in the room.
And you, get a pole to hit that rat in the toilet.
Okay.
Next time it will be your turn tho' you're big brother.
- I don't mind. - Oh, here he is.
Who's it? Lau ting kin?
It's him.
What's up? Who's looking for my boss?
Come in.
Well, question him.
Hello, any staff here?
See for it yourself.
Oh, kun sin-hai is here.
Big brother, test out his poems.
It won't work.
Watch fireworks from 99th floor,
and lose a big melon,
peace benefits everybody,
I want your mammy, if not your daddy.
Please enlighten me.
Lo kar-ling, you fix him.
Dried pork is more educated, let him fix it.
Right, right.
- Go on, go on. - Go on.
To see a show, see chou jun-fat.
To wear a watch, wear enigar,
use insecticide spray for cockroach and drink Carlsberg.
Damn you, you're advertising.
So, he's good for nothing.
And he claims to be a brinkman, a big brother...
Get the men to pull down that shop opposite.
Yes.
Let's pull this down.
Okay.
Who dares to do it?
What now?
I only want to know why!
Big brother, don't! Just say what you want?
Don't call me big brother to expose myself.
As of tomorrow, don't do garage business.
You can do anything else.
Otherwise, I'll pull your shop down.
Well, if I see you running the garage tomorrow. I'll be nasty.
Let's go!
What? To play a brinkman?
Damn bluffer Jim, you're finished once & for all.
Daddy, what now?
Don't laugh, it was all your fault.
You lied to me about a brinkman.
I hate your guts.
Never mind them, let's go!
Are you okay?
Are you alright, daddy?
Uncle kin, what shall we do?
At worst we'll switch to another business. Anyhow we have no business now.
What line of business?
I'll make you a recommendation.
I know a seafood hot pot restaurant is closing down.
Let's take over their business and run it.
Okay, okay, anything will do.
But remember, it should be fixed with up to $300 only.
Here you are.
What's wrong? Why are you all lying idle?
There's no customer.
The shop next-door is opening today.
And doing a roaring business.
Welcome, welcome.
Ladies & gentlemen, thank you for coming.
Today's the opening of Jim Jim bbq poultry.
Well, lau ting-kin, no business?
Close your shop and work for me.
I'll pay you $8 an hour-better than McDonald's.
Who financed you in such beautiful decorations?
Money is no problem.
Mr kwan gave me the capital. He's now my partner.
Lau ting-kin, your lease expires in 3 months.
I'll increase your rent 20 times then.
Outrageous, he's playing chicken and duck.
Free balloons and this attracts business.
They are so much promotion, so it is hard to compete.
Hello... they play chickens and ducks to sell chickens and ducks.
- Let's play seafood... - To sell seafood.
Hell with you.
Ladies & gentlemen, come in please.
Kin-ke's seafood hot-pot restaurant's fine.
- Very good - Kin-ke's hot-pot restaurant.
Ladies & gentlemen, you're welcome.
Hello, come in to eat.
Hi... kin ke's hot pot is the best.
Hi, hi, hi.
Miss oyster's glamorous and bewitching.
Free flats and $100,000 gifts.
Why are you hitting me?
Are you crazy? $100,000 for every one?
Why?
Let's count the number generously.
$100,000 for everyone.
Hey, hey, no soup, hey.
Buddy - no soup
bring the soup.
Be quick!
Hurry up!
Be quick! Be quick!
Hey, didn't you say there would be miss oyster?
Where's she?
She's making up and will appear soon.
Eat the hot pot first. How won't be long.
No way, she won't appear. She wants to raise the price.
Call for uncle kin at once.
Hey, sister, why are you so naughty?
You didn't tell me there are so many males outside.
They may swallow me if I go out.
Well, pay me $3,000 more for this special mission.
What? You'd better kill me.
Oh, miss oyster appears.
Miss oyster, miss oyster, miss oyster.
Ladies & gentlement, before her performance,
let's draw a lucky live audience first.
He is...
Yiu siu hung.
Mr yuan, only by turning our lucky wheel,
to this section, you'll get a flat.
Yes
a flat, a flat, a flat.
Over, over, over.
Congratulation to mr yiu siu hung on winning...
One onion.
What's wrong?
- The onion. - Never mind.
Only if you answer a simple question correctly,
you'll get our special prize.
That is, to spend one night with miss oyster in kowloon tong
for the weekend.
Great.
It simple, take it easy.
Which singer has recently held 38 performances of concert?
Alan tam.
His father,
tam pak Kong.
Not yet finished, his uncle,
tam shang king.
Not yet, an auntie's auntie's grandnephew's grandauntie's
auntie's cousin's son. Who's it?
Tips, please.
Not Anita mui.
You can't answer it.
"Alan tam."
Alan tam.
He's real smart to have answered it.
I'm not, I turned over paper and see it written on it.
Miss oyster, miss oyster, miss oyster.
Don't stare, it's mine.
Please keep calm, keep calm.
Let's go - let's go
it's a set-up.
Pay... hello.
Hello, trying to sponge?
- Hello, pay up. - Pay up now.
What's it, creep?
You can't compete with me, lau ting-kin, close down.
Damn you bastard, bet I'll kill you.
I'm not afraid of your stinking shrimps and crabs.
- Fish, shrimps, crabs, bet, bet. - Bet!
It's crab.
- Crab, banker takes all. - Banker takes all.
Chicken, banker takes again, pays one.
Hey, stop that!
Uncle kin, a game over there.
I'll bet on crab. I've $3,000 ready.
Bet, bet...
$5,000 on shrimp.
Medium shrimp. I win
cops, cops, let's run.
Hey!
Hey, why are you getting out of hand?
They're even more unruly.
I don't care, anyway, it's over between us.
Creep.
Go back in.
Oh, I forgot the detergent.
Deraxol, deraxol.
It's for children only, not for you.
Sorry.
All four villains are here.
Let's divert.
They're leaving now. What shall we do?
Get someone to say something nice.
Good idea.
I can't do it.
I'll stab you.
Don't be such a bore?
I'm not a bore.
I'm serious.
I'm fond of you.
Shit!
I love your body more.
Buddy, don't bully my sister.
Tall sister, he's jilting your sister.
Talk it over if you have the nerve.
Who cares? A man using vidence is no good.
Right, a girl should be kissed, not beaten.
Let's talk it over.
Go away, go away.
Why?
Don't be a stumbling block.
Be smart.
They all want to woo you like I do.
Love is not a crime.
Why did you help lau to beat my daddy?
Well, I won't talk sides from now on.
What?
I'll try to make them reconcile.
Are you sure?
Oh, what's wrong?
Coming to a party?
We're going to a disco with 4 girls tonight.
We're taking part in a hot dancing contest.
Congratulations!
Well, for old times sake, let me show you something good.
- What's it? - A discount card for
men's beauty parlor.
One man each, keep it.
Why are you dancing to and fro?
Dress up as a gigolo.
They've going to a disco with 4 girls.
You creeps, you're counting me out.
No way, we're not as smart as you're.
You're modest.
Let's go together tonight.
I'll woo all your girls unless I have another one.
How come?
"20% discount off"
thank you very much, gentlemen.
Are you satisfied with our service?
Yes, very much.
As a token of thanks,
we offer 20% and free gifts too.
Well, don't even give us the dhrinking mixture.
I tried it before and feel the pinch.
No, it's the rejuvenation pills.
What's the use?
One pill will remove the wrinkles.
Your skill will be tenderer and you'll look 5 years younger.
Thank you. Let me give it to them for you.
Let me put it aside.
Take a rest, sir.
Dried pork, what would you drink?
Are you alright, sir?
Oh, no, uncle kin, look.
Oh, I'm blind.
Uncle kin.
One's blind and the other's dumb.
Hey, are you alright?
Give me a bbq pork bun, please.
What? Bbq pork bun?
What did you say?
Are you dumb?
Alas...
Oh, no, one's blind, one's dumb and one's mute.
What shall we do then?
Damn it.
"In tears the Princess offers to the shrine."
What would you drink, sir?
Alas!
What would you drink?
Cheers!
Damn it, why's lau ting kin still not here?
I'll chop him dead.
Cousin, she's lighting the fire for you.
No.
What's wrong?
She wants to make a glass of Mike for you.
Go and get it from your mammy.
Cousin.
Play cool, come what may.
If you talk, I'll talk likewise.
Cousin.
Don't run around!
Oh!
Cousin.
Just remind me with desticulation.
Are you possessed?
Nonsense, I'm taking part in the dancing competition.
I might win prizes up to thousands.
I'll go and beautify myself.
Damn you, bloody lau ting-kin.
She's beautiful.
Sorry, uncle.
This old man's quite presentable.
Yes.
Uncle? Who's uncle?
Ain't I looking so old?
Luckily I've taken away theirs too.
Let me take a few pills.
Ha, coming, coming.
- Hi! - Over there.
Hi!
Chou sze-pok, let's dance, the music's hot.
I've only just arrived, a little later.
I'm in the mood now.
You're in the mood.
I went out with a friend,
passed through a Lane at the junction of kormu street,
saw a cassette stand and
bought a cassette on hus lau-sin's pavillion Willow.
It was newly recorded and of high standard.
Have you got a good voice. Teach me how to sing.
I've already eaten, I've already eaten.
We don't seem to speak the same language.
Whose cock it is, whose hen it is?
- Oh, no. - What's wrong?
Go and dance.
Go on.
Hey, where shall we go after dancing?
Why are you quiet? Playing cool?
Well, go on, go on.
It's fixed.
May I borrow your boyfriend?
Let's go.
Where to?
You've offended her, go and say "sorry".
Go and soothe her, go now.
Oh, a blind man at the disco!
We're here to listen to the music.
Anyone taking me to the toilet?
Chow sze pok, help him.
Me? The toilet's over there.
It's opposite the dance floor. Go now.
- Get going. - Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Toilet, toilet,
- toilet. - Cousin, don't worry.
Move forward 10 steps and push the door.
When the music dies down, just piss.
Oh.
Move forward 10 steps, the toilet.
10,9, 8,7,6, 5,4, 3, 2,1.
No more music, must be here.
I'll do it here.
Oh, what flashers!
- Well, hold it. - Thank you
keep it.
Thank you.
Have you got a mentally retarded your brother?
No, he's my bigger brother.
He's much younger than you.
Me, old? Let me take a few pills more.
Thank you for your participation tonight.
We'd like to thank those famous dancers
for acting as our panel too.
Well, the competition begins.
- Ready. - Hello... ready, ready.
Now the first participant Mr. kwan.
- Oh, not bad. - Yes
are you alright, uncle kin?
I'm alright.
- Great. - Great, great.
Yes. Now the second participant Mr. lau ting-kin.
Great, great.
- Your turn. - Damn, I'm shrinking again.
What are you doing?
How can you dance then?
Why not?
Oh, it really is him.
Even a moron is participating.
Get up, get up, I'll back you up.
Get up.
Ladies & gentlemen, Mr. lau ting-kin is a moron.
He took part in this competition
to raise funds for the mental retards.
Please contribute in cash or in kind to support him.
Money.
Pennies from heaven!
- Great, great... - You've won, you've won.
You've won, you've won.
I really admire your perseverance, sister.
Here's a prize of $10,000.
Thank you, sister.
Sister, you've a nice gold watch.
It's a ladies' watch, it's not for you.
Sister, sister.
Well, don't cry, don't cry.
Take this $10,000 and buy one yourself.
Thank you, thank you, sister.
Brother-in-law, have you thought in over?
It's now the vogue for every company to relocate.
Once Mr. kwan acquires Jim bbq poultry restaurant
and the company is listed in mannis with stacks insured,
we're going to be rich.
And you may even process emigration.
Right.
Where's mannis?
In Africa, it's a men's paradise.
Woman ore subordinate to men and men may lawfully take a dozen wives.
When shall we go then?
Soon. The contract stipulates that you, your 3 daughters
and your sister-in-law, man man,
can get passport once you're worked there for 3 years.
Boss, what's your idea of hiring them all to mannis?
They confront us and I must beat them.
All the cops in mannis are my men
and money makes the mare run.
I want all his daughters to marry me.
After I get fed up with, I'll sell them to negroes.
There must be something wrong.
Of course, he's craftier than sze kin.
Right, who knows where mannis is?
It is worth taking the trip?
We'd better send someone to make a survey.
But the man be wise, sagacions and a good fighter.
He must also be smart and brave.
Chow sze pok.
I overheard your compliment on me in the toilet,
but if will never go there.
Don't pick on me.
You can't change your mind.
Hey, dried pork, where are you now?
Hello, uncle kin, I'm now in mannis.
I'm calling from the peak.
Well, how's it over there?
It has picturesque landscape like a paradise.
Believe, it or hot, there are only girls here.
I haven't seen one man for a whole month.
Oh, we're lucky.
No need to bring so much money here.
Us$10 has lasted me for one whole month.
Sounds like our friends. Hold on.
Barbarians! I'm finished.
Help!
You must go now, you've already signed the contract.
Oh, there are barbarians over there.
Are we to go there to be cooked for food?
It's by mutual consent.
Tramp.
Beautiful, don't mutter nonsense!
I've got a witness here.
When you're in mannis, you'll feel grateful.
Brother-in-law, what shall we do now?
How do I know?
Listen, though you're bad to me,
I won't let you be eaten by barbarians.
Let me try something to fix it for you.
Oh, Jim.
Don't come here any more!
I've already opened a paultry restaurant to avoid you.
Thank you for your help, but help me once more.
I want to open a kei kee poultry and fishball shop
to sell chickens and fishballs.
I'll pay you $50,000 for your shop.
Don't bully us, we have protection.
We have a protector.
Who's your protector?
Mr. kwan.
That cissy man who has just left.
Our big brother is such, powerful and regal.
He claims he'll settle through legal channels.
Well, let me how powerful he is.
Let's talk terms with him at noon tomorrow.
No, to talk only.
What did you say just now?
Don't be silly. One of them goes by law,
the other depents on the underworld influence.
Let's use our brains to fight them.
Uncle Jim, tell Mr. kwan we're protected by darkie fung.
Tell him to come here to talk terms at noon tomorrow.
Aren't you darkie fung?
Yes, you must be Mr. kwan.
Sounds like that show several months ago.
I copied it from chi Yung's lu ting chi.
Be punish, don't talk.
Up to the ears in debt all the life,
it can't be redeemed even by flesh and blood,
it could be fatal,
if the collector pursues too hard.
No repayment left and right, no repayment left and right.
Dragged on indefinitely, indefinitely.
I didn't want to expose my identity,
but at this crucial moment I need your help, buddy.
What's so special with money? Even you ingratiate yourself.
I fear no underworld, I have lots of money.
You only have one unit.
I could pay to hire 10 units to gang against you.
He's rich and powerful, don't get involved.
Boss, you're a notable, don't quarrel with the underworld.
It's not worthwhile.
Anything can be talked over.
Big brother, don't compromise!
Finish him off. Our men are coming.
Act now, boss, before his men arrive.
Get him!
Peace berefits. Don't act on impulse!
Keep cool, keep cool.
Well, darkie fung.
We tried to persuade our big brother.
He'll pay you $100,000 once & for all.
From now on, don't get men to cope with him.
Okay?
Mr. kwan, we'll persuade him to pay you $100,000
and you have the contract cancelled.
Otherwise, we'll fight to the end. Okay?
Ok. $100,000.
Oki
boss, take this now, don't stand to suffer.
Take it, and forget it. They seem to be after something
okay.
Hey, uncle kin, we've come to terms. Give me $200,000 first.
Come on, quick.
This time it's like a grand sale.
Lau ting-kin, I was bad to you
and now you help me.
I really don't know how to thank you.
Glad you understand.
But remember, I charge 5% interest for my loan.
Stand there, don't move around.
Where's the contract?
Give it to him.
- The money? - No problem.
Leave through the back door,
or they may misunderstand when they meet you.
How hilarious with 2 groups of people here?
Stop that nonsense!
Didn't you say darkie fung forced you to move?
And you said Mr. kwan forced bluffer Jim to move to mannis.
Why are you no good terms now?
Why?
Make it straight now.
Darkie fung, are you his big brother?
I thought you were his big brother.
What? You fooled me?
Get back the contract.
Catch.
Darkie fung, give a hand, $300,000, if you get it.
$300,000 if you get it. Come on!
Oh, you really are tough.
Hey, do you need help?
Of course. Come on.
$5,000, if help you.
Hell with you.
Call the police, $500 only for calling the police.
I'll pay you, I'll pay you.
Don't touch my glue!
Get hold of him.
We help you!
Beat him.
You deserve it.
Are you okay?
What shall we do now?
Just let me go.
If the police arrive,
I'll accuse you of conspiracy with the underworld
to blackmail and you may get jailed.
Nonsense, I'll glue your mouth.
See if anyone dares to talk anymore.
I have an idea.
Hurry up!
Hey, wait till I open the gate.
A gang boss?
An underworld clerk?
Kun au-ting having a gay affair?
Underworld membership ceremony.
What are they murmuring about, sir?
They're mute.
Can a mute man join the underworld?
Why not?
- Help! - Help us!
Luckily, you've come fast, sir,
or they'd have forced us into their membership.
Yes
take them away too.
- Take them all away... - Take them all away...
Why are they all out of their mind?
No idea, we've all been tied up.
Take them all to the police station.
Yes, sir.
Come up, come up...
Hello, come up quickly.
Shut the gate quickly.
Dismissed, dismissed. Go.
You've taken them away, sir.
Do we have to testify in court then?
If we can't convict them the way they are,
we can't be called policemen.
No need to go to court.
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
So nuch the worse, we can't get fees as witnesses.
Don't covet this.
We're enemies, but it's the 1st time we've had a pleasant co-operation.
Let's continue with our co-operation.
Well, we can open a kin-Jim poultry hot pot restaurant.
We'll make money for sure and when we do, we may emigrate.
What do you say?
Good idea.
"Year 1999 Hong Kong"
big-pan rice, big-pan rice, hk's big-pan rice.
Hk's big-pan rice is in hk people's canteen.
We've got steamed, fried, cold, burnt,
soup and dumpling rice.
When in the hk people's canteen, you want nothing but rice,
because there's nothing else available.
Big-pan rice, big-pan rice.
$100 comsumption is impossible
"Africa"
You want brothers or gold?
Gold, gold.
Brothers or gold?
And you? You want brothers or gold?
Gold, gold.
Cousin, why are you keeping so many blacks?
They're all so dark.
What else can they do, if not an underworld member?
You must choose gold, not brothers.
Gold, gold.
"San Francisco"
excuse me.
May I wait a show time?
Show time is coming.
Look, look!
What's wrong? What's there to see?
Gentleman and gentleman.
Show time.
Oh, great.
Why get emigrated? Why fuss?
I'd rather be a dish-washer in usa,
than to serve the pla.
No need to wait for democrancy and freedom,
no guts to face the tanks.
Why get emigrated?