Starring: Connie mak, lam kau
lung ming-yan, sit chi-lun, Jeffrey lam
tien feng, pau hon-lam, Kenneth tsang
Kelvin wong, koo jing-kwong, karel wong
lin kang, jing ri long, Robert zajac
cameo role
theme song: "Shifting sand revolving in the air"
composer: Lo tayu, Richard lo
lyricist: Richard lam, lo tayu
singer: Chow yun-fat, lo tayu
- Daddy. - Joe.
- Are you a good boy today? - Yes.
- Did you listen to your mom? - Yes.
Dear, let him answer.
- Hello, grandpa. - Good boy.
Grandpa, are you looking for daddy?
Ask your daddy to answer the phone.
Daddy... your call.
Don't know what you're talking to grandpa.
Hello?
Dad, happy birthday and many happy returns.
Today is your birthday.
I've been calling you all day but couldn't reach you.
I've gone to lamma island.
You must have gone to play mahjong with uncle ha.
Dad, I've recently started an estate company with friends.
The business is good.
When are you coming back?
Wait till Joe has holiday.
I miss you.
Dad, please don't work so hard.
Take some rest.
Come and visit us when you have time.
How are uncle ping and the rest?
Send them my regards.
Dad, I must hang up now. We're eating.
- That's all, bye bye. - Bye.
What... what are you doing?
You shouldn't play with these.
They're for emergency use.
- Put it away. - Yes...
I've told you not to play with it.
Listen.
- Today, our boss uncle kwan will lead us. - Yes.
Be smart and alert.
Got it...
Flying eagle hall
Hung hing
good weather, happy new year, peace
- Congratulations... - Congratulations...
Same to you.
- Keung. - Uncle kwan.
Give these red packets to everyone.
- One for everybody, don't miss out. - Yes.
- Thanks, uncle kwan, let's go inside. - Okay.
Here are some red packets,
please distribute for me.
Thank you so much.
It's too much.
I think it's okay.
It's bad if I miss out anyone.
Nephew, let's cut to the chase.
Uncle ha and I fought hard to get this territory.
You shouldn't incite your men
to grab my clients.
Moreover, I do give you a share every month.
You can ask for more if it's not enough.
It's unreasonable that you did all that.
Uncle kwan, have you checked?
Why would my men do that?
We're giving you face...
By saying your men did it.
And you are still faking?
Keung, don't be impulsive.
Uncle kwan.
When uncle ha and you were at lamma island,
you agreed on the share.
But uncle ha is sick and can't take care of it.
So he got a sum from you and retired.
But you didn't even say a word about it.
You give us only a small share. Who do you think I am?
You make big money from all fields.
But we can only sit and watch.
New year is around the corner, and you said we grabbed your clients?
How can you say that?
You must have evidence to back up your accusation.
This is the evidence.
Uncle kwan.
Such ledgers...
I can make dozens of them for you.
Little ha.
Have you seen these ledgers?
What's your intention of showing these ledgers?
Who do you think you are? Are you in any position to talk?
What are you then?
We're in the same position, are you scaring me?
- You think I'm scared? - Neither am I scared of you.
Keung, sit down.
It's good if you didn't do so, let's forget about it.
But I don't want this to happen again.
Okay, uncle kwan, I respect you.
But what am I going to say to my men?
Please tell me.
As I wounded your men, I'll compensate them.
Satisfied?
Of course, since uncle kwan has said so,
it must be okay.
But...
How can I keep the reputation of "flying eagle"?
I taught him a lesson for you.
I would have killed him if it hadn't been for you.
Please remember who you are.
- This is lamma island. - So?
- So? - Don't quarrel.
Why quarrel during new year?
We should be happy.
Okay, uncle kwan, let me make it clear.
From now on, you run your own business.
And I'll do ours, but...
You must give my men a red packet of 100,000 dollars.
What?
It's my boss who gives you a chance.
Since when you have the rights to make decisions?
We'll see who gives chance.
Beat that old man.
Uncle kwan.
Uncle kwan, let's go.
Scum.
Go to hell.
Attack...
Get the weapons...
Uncle kwan, escape through the window.
Be careful, uncle kwan.
Uncle kwan, be careful.
Uncle kwan, jump.
- Uncle kwan, you'll be all right... - Shing, you don't have to say.
- You'll be all right, hang on. - Don't have to console me.
When ho is back, ask him not to join our gang.
And not to take revenge for me.
I will, uncle kwan, I'll do as you say.
Ask him to go back to the states.
Be careful.
Careful.
- Uncle kwan. - Uncle kwan.
- Set sail... - Uncle kwan...
Uncle kwan.
Uncle kwan...
- Dry your hair. - Yes.
Hello?
- May I speak to Lee man ho? - Who's speaking?
- I'm shing's wife. - What's up?
Shing has something to tell you, please hold on.
Daddy, who's calling?
Who's calling?
- Ho, this is shing. - Don't disturb your dad.
Uncle kwan met an accident and died.
I think you should come back to Hong Kong for his funeral.
I'll tell you everything when you are back.
- Brother Kong. - Brother Kong.
I've collected the debt from creasy, please count.
He paid?
He paid promptly once I mentioned your name.
Well done, take it.
Thanks, brother Kong.
You know what to do next time?
- Yes. - Good.
- Hey, you two. - Boss.
What are you two doing?
It's our leader's funeral today.
Why are you wearing bright colors?
Brother shing, don't be angry.
Go and change your clothes. Yes...
Claypot, you're looking smart.
Where have you been recently?
Don't be rude.
How dare you address him as claypot?
Brother claypot is now the head of kwong hiong hall.
Know your place.
Just ignore him, let's go.
Darn it.
- Brother Kong, who is he? - A scum.
We used to work together.
Now that he becomes successful, he thinks he's better.
I'll see how far you can go.
- What a jerk. - Kong.
- What's the matter? - Nothing, I've collected the balance amount.
Don't make trouble today.
Got it.
Dad, take it and buy some food to eat.
- Keep an eye out, got it? - Got it.
Funeral at Lee's
I'm sorry, brother bi...
We're held up by traffic.
Boss.
The guy opposite is taking photos of us.
Are you scared?
I've got many records at the police station.
Don't be afraid, just ignore them.
Righteousness
First bow.
Second bow.
Last bow.
Gratitude from the family.
Ping.
Is he brother kwan's son?
Don't you recognize him?
Brother biu, he's man ho.
He's just returned from the states.
This is uncle biu, he's known you since you were small.
- Uncle biu. - My condolences.
Wait, brother bi...
He's only a child, he knows nothing.
Your hair's still wet, let's sit over there, okay?
Come on.
First bow.
Second bow...
- Boss, uncle kwan's son seem incompetent. - Third bow.
- Gratitude from the family. - It's hard to say.
He might be pretending.
That's simple.
Send our men to test him and we'll know.
Right?
- Send some men to follow him tomorrow. - Yes.
- Test him if there's a chance. - Sure.
First bow.
Second bow.
Last bow.
Gratitude from the family.
Mom, when can we leave? I'm tired.
Stay a little longer.
No.
Don't misbehave.
- Joe, what are you doing? - Put it on.
Put it on.
It's uncomfortable with this tied on.
- Put it on. - Be good.
Put it on!
Why are you shouting at him?
- He's just a kid. - It's almost done, don't cry.
Ho, don't be like this, he's just a kid.
Don't cry.
Forget it.
I think we must elect ho.
If everyone thinks ho is capable, we'll do just that.
But it's uncle kwan's will to ask man ho to go back to the states.
Yes, uncle kwan said that before.
But if hung hing has no leader,
it'll soon split up.
Right, if it's not ho,
who will it be then? Tell me.
Let's not argue, we shall ask ho.
Yeah...
Ho, we want you to be our leader.
What do you think?
Uncle ping.
You've always known I didn't approve of my father working for the society.
That's why I went to study in the states.
Anything related to the society,
don't count me in, I'll never lay an eye on it.
I'll return to the states after the funeral.
Ho, how about the estates...
Your dad left behind?
Moreover, if a society has no leader,
it'll soon collapse.
Brother shing.
You've been taking care of my dad's properties.
I think it's better that you take charge of them.
But...
Uncle ping, don't say anymore, I'm tired.
Please get me a car and send me home.
Good night.
- Good night. - Good night.
Uncle ping, what shall we do now?
Let's talk about it later since he refused.
Uncle ping, why not let shing do?
Me? No way.
Why not?
Uncle ping, this cannot be delayed.
Bad breath chuen, who are you to speak?
- What? - We'll do as uncle ping says.
You shut up.
Don't argue...
- Don't argue... - Forget it...
Come on...
Forget it.
Yeung Kong, claypot, coffin rope.
Fear not.
If the information is correct,
I fear Lee man ho the most.
He's skilled at organizing and is well educated.
If he controls the triad society,
and make it an enterprise...
We can't deal with him by then, instead we may be ruined by him.
Then you'll be in great trouble.
Confidential
Dad should've seen this coming.
I fear something might happen to him when I was in the us.
But I promise you, we'll go back to the states after the funeral.
Hong Kong is actually good, we don't need to leave so soon.
Hong Kong is good?
Then why did you study and even naturalize in the us?
I never said the us is bad. If it's bad,
I wouldn't have married a good wife like you.
That's so sweet of you.
Let's go.
Dear, I wish to stay a few more days.
What do you think?
Sure, as long as you like.
Why? You have no money for a room?
Ignore him. He's just a boy.
So silly and boring.
In order to accompany them to see night view,
I can't go to dance tonight.
We just do as uncle ping said.
By the way, brother Kong,
you've been working for uncle ping for 20 years.
Why is he still treating you like a boy?
Shut up, uncle ping is my brother.
He brought me up and gave me a chance.
But I was right.
Don't you ever say such things to me.
I mean it.
Got it.
Silly, watch closer.
Mr Lee man ho.
I'm chan tin lok, from anti-triad section.
Mr chan, how can I be of any help?
I came to protect you as I fear you might be in danger.
I'm not a triad member, no protection is needed.
You must be careful, someone wants to attack you.
How do you know?
Of course I know. I'm from anti-triad section.
Mr chan, are you trying to mislead me?
It's our duty to protect the people.
Officer chan, what's the matter?
Brother ho, you leave first.
Mr chan, I'll make a move.
Yeung Kong, we've got news...
Me too.
Coffin rope right? I can handle it.
No need for police.
There's nothing concerning you, you may leave now.
Get in the car.
Lee man ho.
What do you want? Don't act rashly.
Jenny...
- Jenny, lock the door. - Yes.
Help!
Kong.
Have some water.
Thanks.
What do you want me to say?
You know I'm not eloquent.
He likes you better, go.
Ho.
As you know, hung hing is now in a chaos.
No one can make decisions.
Can you come and help?
Uncle ping, I prefer not.
If I had wanted, I would have followed my father long ago.
Take this.
Ho.
Do you know someone came and checked on you just now?
Seeing that we didn't respond,
they'll soon join other societies to seize our areas.
Facing such critical situation, you still refuse to help?
No!
Don't force me to be a triad member please.
Get me the phone.
Brother keung.
Page 123, 678.
Ask him to gather all our men to keep an eye on the factory.
It's factory, not battery.
- Watch closely. - That's all.
Okay... that's all...
Stop calling.
Tell me how many of them are eyeing us.
About six, seven or eight.
In fact, every one of them wants us down.
But people of coffin rope are the most ambitious.
He's just got some territories in Europe.
Made some money and came back to Hong Kong.
He had some vietnamese to help him.
Try renting your territories to other societies.
Ask them to pay you rental every month.
If it turns out well, you will cooperate.
They will do it for their benefits.
You'll too, won't you?
What? Let out our territories to others?
We fought very hard to get those territories.
What if they seize them?
- There's a place called police station. - Shut up...
Report to the police if they dare.
How can we report to the police as we're the triads?
How are we going to face people?
You are but I'm not.
Superintendent chan tin lok.
Officer chan, this is Lee man ho.
I want to tell you that hung hing has...
How many territories do you have?
Eight.
They have eight territories.
Someone will get them into trouble these few days.
Thanks for your information.
We'll watch closely for you.
That's great, thanks.
I want to meet you.
- Sure, let's find a day. - Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
Brother Kong, I have bad news for you.
What's that?
Uncle ping said you'll be promoted this time.
Really?
Water...
This is hot water.
You want me to have no offspring?
Help me up.
You're lucky.
My hand.
The uncles said you did well to protect the master.
The ceremony is done.
- Kong, congratulations. - Thanks.
I should thank you.
If it wasn't for you that night at tst east,
I would have been killed.
That's nothing. We're used to it.
Hung hing gang
write it again.
Hello?
Brother chuen?
Looking for shing?
He's gone out, yes...
What now? Why did you tell everyone I'm out?
Don't go.
Hello?
Shing's speaking, my wife thought I was out.
Is it? Okay, I'll be right there.
Please page 174.
Also 274, 374, 537 and 22.
Tell them shing asks them to get the stuff ready.
Then wait for him at regal ballroom on Shanghai street.
Yes, thanks.
- Be careful. - Sure.
- Bye, dad. - Bye.
God, please Grant shing safety.
That he can overcome all difficulties.
Coffin rope, adding up the three areas in yau tsim mong,
we have four nightclubs in total,
three mahjong shops and two domino shops.
We get one and a half million a month.
Give us three months of down payment.
We'll oversee the security and management.
What? You will oversee?
What about my men? They do nothing?
What about I rent it to you with such conditions?
Coffin rope, this is the condition.
I assure you'll benefit from it.
I can show you the ledgers.
No need, you created the ledgers.
You can make it any way you like.
What about carrying this out for a week?
We shall continue if you think it's doable.
Of course I want to rent, brother shing.
But is there really free meal in the world?
Coffin rope, you know about my boss.
We're now being closely watched by the police.
If not, we won't rent either.
Many people want our business.
Forget it then, let's go.
Brother shing, don't get angry.
Sit down and we shall talk it over.
Okay.
We'll rent for a week and see how it goes.
Bring me the ledger.
Excuse me.
- Let's not talk about it. - Lunatic.
Mad keung, why are you here?
Nothing, I'd like to talk to your boss.
What is there to discuss?
What if we want to rent you our territories?
Rent your territories?
Mad keung, what plan do you have in mind?
I don't think you can decide.
- Ask your boss out. - Just a moment.
Boss, mad keung wants to see you.
Mad keung, what does hung hing have for us?
Come, let's talk about it.
Have a look.
- Brother biu, call me if there's anything. - Okay.
That's it.
Boss, is there such a good bargain?
Don't believe everything a triad member says.
- Right? - Yes.
Stop running.
Take them.
Don't move...
Stop, don't run.
Okay...
What's going on...
What's going on?
Go to hell...
Stand still.
- Where are you from? - Why?
Don't you know I'm the boss here?
Nothing to see, go away.
What's so cocky about?
Still here? Go away.
Kid, let me know if there's anything, okay?
Call him brother Kong.
Say.
Brother Kong.
We are brothers now.
Come on.
You did a good job last time, continue to find me some kids.
I need smart ones.
Brother Kong.
- Take it. - Thanks, brother Kong.
Sister, are things manageable?
Yes. Uncle ping, why don't you sit down and have some tea?
Steaming fish can be troublesome.
You're right.
Keung. “What?
Why didn't Kong come?
I've called him all day but got no reply from him.
I called his mobile phone.
But a foreign lady answered.
He's getting more successful.
Having many men working for him,
and collecting money everywhere.
Come... here is something good...
- It's good. - Uncle ping, you shouldn't do this.
Let the women do this.
You're wrong. They can't cook as well as I do.
Got it?
You're right.
Talk no more, let's eat.
Sister.
Enjoy the food. There're many more dishes.
- Fine, if you don't want to. - Have some rice, try this.
You can't always eat burgers.
- Let me take for you. - Okay.
This is delicious, try some.
Hello? Speaking... oh, it's shui.
What is it?
Alright. I'm eating now.
This chicken tastes good, have some more.
- Is it tasty? - Yes.
Keung, it's chaos out there.
People from all sides are showing up.
Ho, your method works.
You must stay and help.
Save that and eat more.
Get a newspaper tomorrow and see how many are arrested.
Right? Dear, is the fish good?
Yes.
Get the contract ready as soon as possible.
I can sign anytime.
No.
Business is business.
We must be serious.
We should be fair in doing business.
Mad keung, come over, my boss wants to see you.
What is it?
Lunatic, what is it?
Mad keung, don't be so loud.
My boss has something to talk to you.
Are you blind? Can't you see I'm busy?
- Talk later if you must. - Mad keung.
Why is it just after you'd rented me the place,
that people came giving me trouble?
Then police came...
And arrested my men. What do you say?
Brother biu, we agreed on the business.
Now you come to me when things go wrong, won't I be busy?
Now you're really in trouble.
How dare you fool me?
- How can you compensate? - Are you kidding, brother biu?
Who has no rivals as a triad member?
Why would I let it to you if it was easy?
That's your business, but you mustn't trick me.
Some were even admitted.
Who's going to pay for the legal and medical fees?
I've an idea.
You'll pay the rent for the next six months.
What? What do you think hung hing is?
You frame me?
- Mad keung. - What?
Be polite to my boss.
Darn it.
Don't move...
Keung.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
How can you be so rude to uncle biu's men?
Uncle biu, we can discuss.
Brother, who are you to talk to my boss?
I'm the head.
Uncle biu, we're of the same kind.
Let's sit down and discuss.
Is ho officially the head now?
Why didn't I know?
This is our new head.
It's your problem if you didn't know about it.
You think this is yamakuchi or Italian triad?
Do we have to advertise?
Or maybe a press conference? What I say counts.
Okay... stop that.
But this is truth.
Okay, I believe you are, but how do you explain?
Brother biu, everyone has rivals.
We've rented you the place.
You should hold the responsibility if things go wrong.
How can you say we trick you?
Brother, you mean I...
Okay, let's sit down and talk.
You go out.
Keung, I'm worried.
Don't worry, he'll fix it, let's go out.
Uncle bi...
You know I was forced to.
My men need a living.
We must try and solve any problem.
Yes, you're right.
But we must make money the right way.
Especially leaders like us, we should be reasonable.
Uncle biu, let bygones be bygones.
I'll take care of all your charges.
What do you think?
Great, it's a deal.
Thank you.
It's not easy to be leaders.
Right, it's easier to be the followers.
So we must be on good terms.
We can make money together, right?
It's good that your dad has a son like you.
Thanks to you too, uncle bi...
Please look out for me.
Let's have some tea.
We'll make a move.
- See you later, you two go over there. - I'll leave first.
- I'll follow their car. - Bye.
Let's go.
I wonder what's wrong with bi...
Shing, be careful.
Knock him down.
Run after him...
Quick...
Keung, protect ho, quick.
Run, quick, start the car.
What's going on?
Didn't we make it clear to uncle biu?
Yeah, uncle biu won't be so cunning.
It must be coffin rope.
What shall we do, uncle ping?
Beat him.
Quick...
Stop the car.
Be careful. Take it easy.
Ho, let's go.
Quick...
Protect brother ho.
Brother shing, take him to the hospital.
You can't just treat him with herbal medicine.
It works, I always treat my men with this.
Just a minor injury, it's okay.
It's okay? He's seriously wounded and you think it's okay?
Shing.
Ho, don't do that.
We'll be in trouble if this spreads.
He'll die if you don't send him to the hospital.
Ho, you know what we do.
We can only heal ourselves if we get injured.
Take him to the hospital? Can we say he hurt himself?
Tell me how serious he is now.
He's sure to be disabled.
All his limbs are broken.
Uncle ping.
Have you found Kong?
I've sent my men to locate him.
- Tell me if you find him. - Sure.
Daddy, mommy, I'm back from school.
Good, put down your school bag first.
Now that he's seriously injured,
how am I going to tell his family?
Take some money from our account as compensation.
If he's surely disabled,
what's the use of money?
Alright, we'll hunt coffin rope down.
I just can't understand.
Do fighting and killing solve problems?
Ho, don't forget.
If we hadn't fought for your dad,
where would you have been now? You would've been just like us.
You caused all this.
How can you blame us?
Right, you're lucky.
When you were small and fought with others,
we took care of it for you.
And now you're murmuring.
Talking about the past, huh?
If I hadn't begged my father for you,
what would you have become today?
Always put me in a dilemma.
Luckily uncle biu did us a favor.
Otherwise, we would've all been killed.
What did you say? “What?
You said we put you in dilemma?
You insisted to do so and now you're blaming us?
- 1'd kill you if you weren't our boss' son. - What do you want?
- Don't behave like that. - Okay...
Stop arguing, please?
Dear.
Daddy.
Your son is calling you. Why don't you go over?
Stupid.
I know.
- Daddy. - Good boy.
What's going on?
Let's go out.
Ho, what happened?
Why do you have blood all over?
Why are they here?
I don't know how to tell you.
No need, we shall leave tomorrow.
It's too dangerous here.
That guy got injured because of me.
How can I leave now?
They are doomed to end up like this.
What? They are also humans.
If it hadn't been for him, I would've been killed.
If you must leave, take Joe with you.
Don't cry, Joe.
Go to mommy and apologize for me.
Go.
Mommy, daddy says sorry to you.
I've told you this cannot be solved.
Take me to Kong.
- Hong. - Boss.
Keep an eye on dirt for me.
- Call me at mahjong shop if there's anything. - Yes.
Look, put the tape on the arm with weapon.
Then you won't kill the wrong person.
We've been waiting for you for an hour.
- There was a traffic jam. - Quick.
Kneel down...
Uncle ping, brother ho.
- Where's Kong? - He's inside.
You want brothers or gold?
Say.
Kong.
- Why are you here? - I'm asking you why you're here.
Finding a man to be scapegoat.
It's okay, I'll settle it.
You? How?
Kong, listen to ho.
Boss, you know there's no way to solve it.
We must kill coffin rope.
Brother ho, leave it to me.
Kong, that boy is still studying.
Don't ruin him.
Brother ho, uncle kwan used to teach us like that.
To find kids who are underage to be scapegoats.
I used to be like this too.
- Uncle ping, I'm taking a walk at lascar row. - Okay.
Sing, keep brother ho company.
It's okay, I want him to go with me, thanks.
No worries.
Come on.
What's your name?
Tak.
- Do you know what you're doing here? - Fighting.
- Are you afraid? - Yes.
Crazy to, he's out.
Get him...
Get in the car.
Start the car.
Police, run...
Don't run.
Stop.
Don't move, stand still...
Don't run...
Get down.
- It's me... I did it. - Don't move.
I won't mislead you.
You needn't cheat me.
I might as well go to jail.
He answered as if everything was rehearsed.
Watch and you'll know.
There's evidence? Are you joking, sir?
Who instructed you to do this?
How much have you taken?
- Officer chan. - Mr Lee.
It'll ruin you forever.
Mr Lee, sorry to bother you.
No worries, it's my responsibility as a citizen.
Have a seat.
Is it? Tell us.
The hk governor, her majesty,
icac, the complaints unit, how's that?
Fooling me? You want me to beat you?
- Kid, don't say I don't care for you. - Do you know this kid?
No, I don't.
Is there anything to do with me?
Who is your boss?
- Tell me. - Did you know that two hours ago,
there was an assault in kowloon tong?
- I don't know. - For real?
We've got information saying that you planned it.
Sir, if you talk to me like this,
I'll call for my lawyer.
Okay, mr Lee.
Are you now the head of hung hing?
No.
It's good that you're not.
I'd arrest you if you were.
Sir, I'll leave if there's nothing else.
- Give me a call if you need me. - Sure.
Mr Lee.
Do you know him?
Yes.
- Lee ka shing. - You fool with sir?
- Don't do that. - Let's go.
Mr Lee, mind giving me a cigarette?
- Thanks. - Go.
Mad keung, kill me if you dare.
Come on, kill me.
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Go to hell, scum.
This is not heroic.
Come on, kill me.
Don't act rashly.
- Stop, you've killed one. - Don't stop me.
Ho is coming back soon.
- I want to kill him. - No.
Brother shing.
- Kong, what are you doing? - Kong.
Kong.
Sit down.
Ho, this is yours, come on.
Take revenge for dirt.
Kid, just kill.
Don't hesitate.
Kill you, huh?
You fooling me? Go to hell.
Brother ho, do you need my help?
Wait.
Ho, this is our society's affair, leave it to me.
Brother shing.
Shave off his eyebrows and let him think over.
What to think about? Just kill me.
You're not a hero if you shave my eyebrows.
- Shut up. - Dare you say anymore?
Brother ho, we can't do that.
It'll be problematic if you let him go.
Ho, Kong is right.
This won't work.
What are you still waiting for?
I would've killed you if it hadn't been ho.
You're lucky. Shaving your eyebrows...
Matches your baldness.
Go.
Now brother ho is letting you go as a lesson.
Thank brother ho.
Let's go.
Be smarter.
Watch out.
Come on...
Boss, hung hing got the top today.
Yeah...
Good...
Uncle ping, we rely on you from now on.
Brother shing, don't reject to be the head.
- Ho, I... - Brother shing, I'll leave one day.
It's okay, let me talk to him.
We'll get ready at the restaurant.
Kong, why are you so angry?
I'll ask brother shing to let you be the head if you like.
It's not about if I like it.
If the seniors are always in power,
hung hing will soon collapse.
You don't want to ruin your dad's business, do you?
You're still young, find a proper job.
Brother ho, I've followed your dad since young.
I can't even read, what can I do?
Work at 7-11 or McDonald's?
There's no turning back for triad members.
I'm not you, who could study abroad.
Brother ho, this is not your place, you'd better go back to the states.
This way.
- Move faster, you fool. - Uncle wu, make yourself at home.
How can you take these out so late?
I've friends who do renovation.
- Help them if you can. - Sure.
This is brother hung.
- Brother hung. - Brother Kong.
- Why are you so late? - Please go inside.
- Brother hung. - Yes?
- I've business at the pier. - I see.
Let's talk about it sometime.
- Sure. - Great.
Come on, cheers...
- Cheers... - Cheers to you.
This way please.
- Hello, mr Lee... - Hello, mr Mario.
Hello, just arrived today?
Tell him I'll treat him to dinner tomorrow.
My boss would like to invite you for dinner.
- Thank you... - He says thank you.
Kong, what are you doing here?
Help to serve the guests, come on...
You...
Ho, uncle ping, why are you so late?
We had something urgent.
You're late. I thought you weren't coming.
Don't talk nonsense.
Young man.
- Uncle biu. - So late.
You've been here long? Sit...
Uncle biu, this antique watch is nice.
It's rolex of 1920.
- Is it? - It's porcelain and Rose gold.
May I have a look?
What do you think?
It's rare.
What are you doing here? You fool.
- Testing... - Remember.
A leader must be fair.
You mustn't be biased.
My fellow men and guests.
We thank you for coming tonight.
Now our host has something to tell you.
Then we'll start the auction.
Let's welcome mr Lee man ho.
It's you.
Please.
Dear all.
I'm honored to be here to talk to you all.
I just want to talk about...
The future development of hung hing.
As I'll be leaving for the us soon,
uncle ping will be responsible for all the businesses concerning the society.
And mr tse shing will be the head.
On behalf of hung hing society,
I thank you for coming to the celebration of tin hau's birthday.
Enjoy yourselves.
Let the auction begin.
You may bid while eating.
First, it's a fortune mouse at 500 dollars.
Five thousand.
Mafia company from us offers 5,000 dollars.
Anyone offers more than that?
Ten thousand.
Solicitor lam offers 10,000 dollars.
I'm sorry.
Solicitor lam, they're triad members from the us.
You'd better bid other items, sorry.
Anymore?
Twenty thousand.
Mafia from us offers 20,000 dollars.
- Anyone more than 20,000 dollars? - They're really giving us face.
- Anyone? - Don't panic.
- Anyone? - Thanks.
One, two, three, it's a deal, thanks.
All, both hands...
Now it's a piece of red scarf at 10,000 dollars.
Original price at 10,000 dollars. Any offers?
- Boss, bid now. - Original price 10,000 dollars.
Twenty thousand.
Kwong heung hall offers 20,000 dollars, anyone more than that?
- Call Joe. - Twenty thousand dollars.
- Thirty thousand dollars. - Anyone more than 20,000 dollars?
- Thirty thousand dollars. - It's 30,000 dollars now.
Anyone more than 30,000 dollars?
- Anyone... 30,000 dollars. - 100,000 dollars.
- 100,000 dollars, anyone more than that? - Fight with me?
One hundred and fifty thousand dollars.
Uncle ping, he insists on getting it.
- Forget it. - What can we do?
Two hundred thousand dollars.
Two hundred and fifty thousand dollars.
Trying to fool me?
It'll be troublesome if this goes on.
Stop him.
- Don't stop me, I must teach him a lesson. - Uncle ping, what are you trying to do?
Kong, what are you doing? They are our guests.
You'll be doomed if you get in my way.
Three hundred thousand dollars.
- Brother Bo. - Yes, brother shing?
I'm sorry, my boy is drunk.
He's drunk?
Five hundred thousand dollars.
Now you see.
I came to support you and wanted to buy this.
- He's now getting in my way. - He didn't mean it.
Let's go.
Brother Bo... please.
Sigh.
- Scum. Don't stop me. - Don't...
- Let me teach him a lesson. - Don't...
- Go away. - Don't be like this.
Kong, have you played enough?
Are you happy that you made this mess?
Shut up. Who are you?
Why must I listen to you? Save it.
- Have you fooled enough? - You beat me?
- Kong, don't be like that. - Shing, stop, shing.
Scum.
- Shing, what are you doing? Don't do that. - None of your business, go away.
- Brother shing, sit down... - Sit down.
- What's wrong with you? - Don't do that.
- Tse shing, I'll remember this. - Calm down.
Say no more.
- Drag him out. - Go.
- Why are you so rash? - Sit down first.
How could he do such a shameful thing?
Brother shing, your wife's just left.
Go and find her.
- Yeah, quick. - Go.
Come on, quick, go now.
- Scum. - Come on...
It's all right, he's just drunk and lost his temper.
Nephew.
This is obviously a rebel. It'll bring us trouble.
Honey.
I am going back to U.S.A.
Mong kok night club
boss, yeung Kong is mad over there.
Where?
There.
What's so difficult...
I don't care about the regulations.
What? Are you new? You know nothing.
- Let me... - Be smart.
Take it easy.
Kong, I know you're in a bad mood.
Being followers is hard, but being leaders is not easy either.
I know, but slapping me in public,
how am I going to face my men?
Frankly speaking,
you were at fault first.
You can't blame shing solely.
You made a mess tonight.
Have you spared a thought for ho?
I didn't bring ho trouble, I just can't stand tse shing.
If you can't stand shing, you can challenge him one-on-one.
If you make a mess in public,
you'll only be laughed by others, right?
We can discuss things over.
Every time I ask you to quit, you'll say later.
Do you know every time you walk out of this door,
I fear I can't see you anymore?
If they hadn't stopped you,
you would've got injured again.
Is this the first day you know me?
Before you married me,
you'd known about my job.
Shing, the world has changed.
Young people nowadays are crazy.
They don't care about righteousness.
I didn't ask for a rich life when I married you.
I only want a peaceful life.
Kuen, I know you're good to me.
But there are times when I can't control.
Have you thought of me and our daughter?
Selfish.
Daddy, mommy won't get angry if you listen to her.
Good girl, go back to sleep.
Go to sleep.
You should sleep too, don't bark.
Who's there?
Kong, what are you doing here?
- It's late, what's it? - I came to teach you a lesson.
You're drunk, wait till tomorrow.
Why wait?
Scum.
This is my revenge.
Go away, I don't want to see you again.
Mommy, it's me.
What's it?
Mommy, daddy is fighting with uncle Kong outside.
- Shing... - Daddy...
One for each of us.
- Shing, how are you? - Daddy.
Kong, why did you do this?
This is our own affair.
Now it's settled.
Don't cry, I'm all right.
I told you not to worry.
You're all right? Your face is seriously injured.
Let's go to uncle wah.
I've told you not to worry.
Can you listen to me just once?
Daddy, please listen to mommy.
Maybe there's broken glass in the face.
No need.
No need? Fine, I'll get ho to take you to the hospital.
- Honey. - How are you? Let me help you.
It's late, don't bother him.
Okay... I'll go with you.
I've told you but you never listen.
You can never improve.
It's not my fault.
I don't want it either, honey.
Why don't you quit then?
I'm worried every time you go out.
Fine, I promise you I'll quit, okay?
You said it yourself that you'll quit.
- Yes. - Our daughter is our witness.
- Yes. - You'll die, no, I'll die if you regret it.
Don't talk nonsense.
- Shing, your bone is injured. - Hello?
- You'd better take an X-ray. - Hello?
Who is this?
- Is it ho? - Yes.
Shing is willing to quit the society.
Is it?
He said it personally?
Yes, he promised me personally.
Tell brother shing I'm happy for him.
And sister...
Soon I'll arrange for you to move to the us.
Shing, ho says he'll arrange for us to go to the us.
Us?
We can't speak english, how can we make a living?
True.
But we can't speak english.
My wife can teach you, it's easy.
Ho's wife will teach us.
Who's that?
Who are you?
Shing.
Honey, how are you?
Shing, take care of our daughter...
I will, honey.
- Shing... - Mister.
Are you all right?
Shing, are you okay?
Don't disturb the patient.
Uncle ping, who tried to kill shing?
It's hard to say.
Put out the cigarette.
Please put out the cigarette.
This is hospital, not police station.
Annoying.
Mr Lee.
Officer chan, how's shing?
The tendon in his ankle was broken and his wife died on the spot.
Keep calm.
Officer chan, which ward is he in?
- Is it possible that yueng Kong did it? - Scum.
How dare he tried to kill shing?
I'm not mad keung if I don't kill you.
Go away, scum, go away.
Keung.
It's impossible that Kong did that.
Mr Lee...
Brother shing.
How are you?
Ho.
Why did you elect me to be the head?
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
From the day I became a triad member,
I've seen this coming.
Brother keung, no...
Don't stop me.
Don't do that.
What do you want?
You should know.
- What do you want? - What have I done?
Scum, you killed shing and his wife.
I must kill you, scum, don't run.
Don't run.
Go away.
Don't go.
Get out of my way.
I must kill you, scum.
You run?
I didn't do it, are you crazy?
I must kill you.
I merely fought with him, why did you accuse me?
Go away.
Bastard.
What do you want?
Mad keung, stop or I'll fight back.
Fight back? Come on.
Go to hell.
Be careful, boss.
Scum, go to hell.
Are you all right?
Shall I take you to the hospital?
I didn't kill shing. Do you hear that?
Do you understand...
Are you retarded?
Don't ever accuse me, I don't fear you.
Go.
Dad, now hung hing has no leader.
It'll be easily taken over by others.
I can't just hide here.
Even if I believe you didn't kill shing,
do you think keung's men will let you go?
I'm not scared of them.
Why did you create so much trouble?
Now hung hing is in a chaos.
We should find a way.
I'll try to talk to uncle wu.
No, he's a cunning old man.
You know him well.
He'll only bring hung hing down.
Dad, we have to take the risk.
You don't want me to be like this forever, do you?
I'm not comfortable to do that.
Dad, what are you afraid of? I'm no longer a kid.
Let me decide this time.
Mr chow, he...
What's it, young man?
Is it time to talk about the business at the pier?
Uncle wu, I want to talk to you privately.
Sure.
- Little ha. - Yes.
Just do as I told you.
Got it.
- You may leave first. - Okay.
You must follow up and do it by yourself.
- Got it. - That's it.
I'll leave first.
Little ha? The one who killed my boss?
Let bygones be bygones.
Now coffin rope, little ha and kwong heung hall...
Are working with me, only left hung hing.
So?
Can you give me kwai chung pier?
Uncle wu, I can't give you the pier.
Any other is all right.
But I'm not interested in others.
I only want the pier.
Uncle wu, I hope you could help me get hung hing in order.
Sure, as long as I get the pier.
Okay, no problem.
But you need to pay one million every month.
I'll give you two million.
At midnight on the first day of next month,
send some men from hung hing,
and wait for me at gate 3.
Help me draw the guard's attention.
It's easy, I'll send two men there.
No, I want you to drive a car,
and exchange another car from the pier.
It must be you as I don't trust others.
- Why? - I'll give you half a share after that.
Uncle wu, you want me to be a scapegoat?
Silly.
What's good to me if you're arrested?
My stuff is worth several millions.
What do you think?
Okay, but I must take a million as deposit.
And I'll only do one thing which is this.
Okay, it's decided.
Uncle wu, I thank you on behalf of hung hing.
Since we're working together,
I want to ask you something.
- Sure. - The case of tse shing couple...
And the current state of hung hing, did you plan it all?
Not me, it's him.
Yes, I did it all.
Hung hing made me do so.
You shaved off my eyebrows.
It's your fault that you didn't kill me.
I did that for my men.
Don't be like this...
Take it easy.
We're up for big business.
Come on, go home and rest.
Come, go home...
Go...
Rope, guns shouldn't be used this way.
Isn't it too easy for him to die this way?
Listen to me, soon I'll show him my true color.
I was just fooling him, uncle wu.
Okay, but don't ruin our business.
I know.
Ho, can you...
Uncle ping, I don't want to be involved.
Let us go back to the us.
Ho.
You know chow sai lun well.
If Kong works with him, he'll surely die.
Why don't you talk to him?
He might let Kong off for the sake of your father.
Ho, please do me a favor.
I know nothing, how can I help?
You can't get your car in, park aside.
Is uncle wu in?
In the office.
Thanks.
Uncle wu.
- Can I ask a favor for Kong? - Go away.
No, Kong is willing to do so.
Take him back if you can.
- Uncle wu. - Don't come near.
Uncle wu... for the sake of my father,
please let Kong go.
Your father? He had never let me go.
He was the one who killed your father.
I don't want him to kill you too.
Uncle wu.
Nephew, this is not your game.
You're not up to it.
Go in... quick.
- It's exploded... - It's on fire...
Quick...
Put out the fire, quick...
Hey.
Stop, don't run...
Block him from that way.
- Don't move, stop... - Don't move...
What are you charging me with?
I was just fighting.
Kid, don't be too calm.
I was informed that there's drug in your car.
You'll surely go to jail this time.
Silly, I knew that old man would be trapping me.
I've thrown it away.
Pull him over.
Go.
Stop.
Don't move.
Sir, I found this in the car.
Sir.
This isn't glucose, is it?
You frame me?
Get in.
- Let's retreat... quick. - Retreat.
Turn back... quick.
What kind of driving is this?
What do you want? “What's it...
Sir, Kong is innocent, you arrested the wrong person.
I saw the men of chow sai lun...
Put it in Kong's car.
You think I'll believe you?
I received the news and indeed there's drug in the car.
You're the head of hung hing, of course you'll side him.
Sir...
The stuff has to be taken for test.
- Kong. - Why are you always helping them?
I know he's thief when I first met him.
Are you a police or triad member?
Of course he is a triad member.
Have you ever seen him arresting triad members?
What are you doing?
Why did you frame Kong?
What? Sir, you heard that.
Do you need my help in the investigation?
Mr chow, thanks for your cooperation
that led us to arrest this man.
No worries, we as businessmen...
Fear triads the most. I should thank you.
You trash.
Sit down.
Don't ever come again, we're equal now.
Don't let me see you again.
Don't do that.
Scum.
Quick... go after him.
Get in the car and chase.
Go, quick, come on.
Get in the car.
Kong.
Coffin rope is in front, don't let him run away.
Move backwards...
Coffin rope is in front.
How can you drive like this?
Go away, man.
Kong, get in the car.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Knock him, knock him to death.
He killed your father.
Kong, how are you?
Kong.
My leg...
Something's not right, let's go.
Kill him.
Forget about the stuff.
Brother ho, let's go... quick.
Police are almost here.
Don't move...
Get up.
Quick, get up.
Go.
I'm the head of hung hing, I was the driver.
I killed them.
Sir, not him, it was me.
- Officer chan, I was the driver. - Arrest me please.
- Arrest me. - I killed them both.
Don't arrest him, arrest me please.
I did that.
- What should I charge you of? - I killed them.
- Driving without license? - Sir, the two men...
- Arrest me please. - Towing truck...
Sir, may I have a cigarette?
Brother ho, you're a kind leader,
but not a good triad member.
Get in, let's go.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I hope you'll understand why I did this.
I'll go back with you to the states.
The end