Kit!
US $2
Yes!
Come!
Coming!
The plate
Sir!
Taste good?
Are you alright?
Take it and go to see the doctor
Thanks
Can you read it?
What?
Don't pretend
How are you!
Hi, Russ
Thanks
That's it!
That's great, first class
Why don't we go out for a drink sometimes
It's pleasure doing business with you
Good!
Your English is improved
Even know of course
Of course!
- Good morning. Mark
- Good morning, Mr Sung
Good morning
Good morning, Mr Sung
Good morning, Mark
That's good
Mr Yiu
Ho, you are back! Everything OK?
I counted already
Clever
Those foreigners are easy going
Not all of them are as good as they are
Your weakness is too easy to believe someone
Thanks!
You are Shing? Sit…
No, thanks. It's better for me to stand
Good morning. Linda!
Rose!
There's a lot, you can learn from Ho
He's excellent
But I'll never be as good as him
Though mark is frivolous
But he is loyal
Yes, he takes good care of me
What are you talking about?
Nothing. Just talking about you!
Really?
Your brother, Kit, graduates today
Oh! Yes. I forgot to buy him a present
I've got to go now
Ho. Take Shing with you tomorrow to Taiwan
Give the kid a chance
Taiwan. Don't mistake it with Chai Wan?
Though I've been in this field for years
I'm still afraid to go
Do you know why?
Too much fighting
and drink
Don't fool him
OK
Give Kit a hooker for a graduation present
I'm no good, but I want him to be a good citizen
But it's better to have a whore
I want to see him to be a PhD
Getting married
And having his own baby
Then you'll be as busy as a buffalo
People say, one will step on shit
with a big mouth
You go in first
You first
I won't
We will go in together
Hold it. We are police
- Search!
- Sir
Freeze
That's not funny
Don't turn around
Both of us have guns If you don't respect me…
I won't
See who doesn't respecting the others
So ticklish
Don't…
Please…
Are you sure?
I have good news
You'll surprise
I am an Inspector, surprise!
You have to work hard
At least you've got to be a superintendent
Jackie!
She is my girlfriend
She takes care of dad when she has time
My brother
Hi!
Taking care of dad in this way!
Thanks a lot
Don't mention it
I've got to sit for an exam
Are you going steady
Don't know yet!
You said you'll go with me! Hurry up!
I really want to stay… But…
No need to explain.
- I go first
- Go!
Sorry
Let's go!
Quick!
Bye!
Ho!
Dad!
You should quit
Your brother doesn't know
what you have been doing
Still remember
You two played cop & thief when you were kids
He almost lost
But he still wanted to be a cop
I don't want you to play
the same game again
For your brother
Promise!
Yes!
That's better
Excuse me… Traffic is so bad
Yes. Traffic jam
I am Jackie
Sir, Traffic jam
Give me a chance
Please give her a chance
Are you alright?
I'm fine
Sir, the traffic is really bad
Give her a chance please?
OK…
Go!
So pity
Listen. Judges
Sorry
It's you… You made me so embarrassed
You spoiled everything
How can I help you,
if you don't have confidence yourself?
They didn't say you are out
How do you know you'll fail?
Give it back to me
I will really fail this time
Are you sure?
This will be my last time
Because of Kit?
Don't come with me to Taiwan tomorrow
Any goes wrong, you here to handle it
Then they will follow you
I can't do it
Then Shing will do it
He resembles Al Pacino
Please don't fool me, Mark
Ho, we can't do without you
I'm not mature yet
Don't expect too much
Don't think you can be the Big Brother
by reading the books about underworld
Anyone ever point a gun at you?
No!
12 years ago…
12 years,
Ho and I went to Indonesia the first time
We had a dinner at a club with their Big Brother
I said something wrong
Suddenly 2 guns were pointing at my head
and I was ordered to drink a bottle of whisky
I was so scared
Ho is really great
He drank it for me
But there was even worse
4 guns were pointing at me then…
Do you know what they asked me to drink?
Urine!
Drank urine in the club
Learning! That's what you call learning
That's our first deal
That's history Don't talk about it anymore
No!
Never cried since I was a kid
That's the first time I cried
I swore that
no one would ever point a gun at me again
That's good!
Be careful
Hitting a sand bag more often
I've to go tomorrow
Regular disappearance
I'll be back soon
When I'm away, take care of dad
I will
Take care!
Yes!
They're coming
Be careful, there's something wrong here
How do you know?
Intuition
Mr Sung, how are you!
Where is Mr Wang?
He's not feeling well I'm his nephew
He asked me to replace him
How are you!
What kind of illness he has got?
Mr Sung, let's go in and talk
Nothing serious
Just hiding out
for a while
Have a cup of tea
Thanks!
Mr Sung, this way please!
Scared of everything when you are getting old
Please sit
Don't waste time!
Attention, head quarters
Please check a car
Taipei 1086379
It's a bit suspicious
We know you're reliable
I respected you when I was a kid
Do you believe that?
Someone paid me double to kill you
He's crazy, who do they think I am?
I give you money
Police!
Hello!
Uncle
We'll be miles away
Sung kill some of our men in Taiwan
He is wanted by the Police
Big brother is worried that
Ho might talk his secret
Please come with me
I don't want to be rude
You son of a bitch
If you hurt my son
I won't let you off
Run!
What are you doing?
No!
Don't push me!
Wrong number
Go. Uncle!
Uncle!
Jackie, what's happening?
Be careful, Kit?
Dad, don't come out
Dad, please don't
Dad!
Kit, you have to forgive your brother!
Who betrayed me?
You?
Ho, if I did
I wouldn't be here with you now
I don't know if I can escape this time
Ho, what are you doing?
I'm going to surrender
You can't
Please don't
Please don't go
No
No!…
Run!
Ho…
Go away
I don't want to implicate another friend
There's gun shots in the cavern
You go
No
I insist you go
Stand and don't move
Put down the gun
Did you hear me? Put down the gun
There's no more rules in the world
You can't trust any one today
Even my nephew, Wang
betrayed me
He joined up with a new HK gang
to try to take over my business
As a result, we've lost Ho
We respect a faithful man
but not a traitor
Hello!
Yes!
He will be in Fung Lim Restaurant tonight
What are you gong to do?
Do you need any help?
Do you need my men?
Take care!
Thanks!
Chief
What's this?
Inside here
I'm not scared
My boss will post bail for me
If you've the gut,
fight with me without a gun
See who is stronger?
Sir, what's happening?
Nothing!
Sung, what's the charge?
Drug trafficking, attacking the police
How dare you insult Inspector Sung
Take down his statement
Thanks!
How's that? Feeling different!
Can I give you a lift?
No, thanks We are not going the same way
I admire you
Because of your friends
You kept quiet
That's ridiculous. You were behind bars
The counterfeiting racket is still strong
Thanks!
I'm not involved anymore
Tell your friends
The case is still open
I won't let him off
A bad guy for a day
Will never be a good guy again
Bye!
I'll never come back again
Stop!
Kit, cool down
Stop fighting
Kit, stop
Don't let me see you again
Manager!
There's no manager here
I'm Ken, are you looking for me?
Uncle Chung, asked me to come see you
When I was doing business in Taiwan…
Doing business? You were in jail!
Mr Chung asked me to give you this letter
Chung, he never does anything good
But we are friends
It's so difficult to get a job for an ex-con
No one will hire an ex-con
Don't feel depressed
All these guys were prisoner before
Some people like to adopt orphans,
I like to take care of ex-cons
Because I was in prison too
Everybody, here's a new man
Take care of him
He is… you are…
Sung Tse Ho
Ho brother!
Just call me Ho
Social gathering?
Back to work
I'm not paying you for doing nothing
Do you have a driving license?
No
Whether you pass the exam or not…
You can stay
Thanks, Ken
Don't mention it. There's no Boss here
- Take it for lunch
- Thanks
Mark!
That's not what you told me in your letter
Even I break my legs,
I can't pay you back
It's not your fault
I'm so glad to see you again
Haven't seen you for so long
You're still looking the same
Mark. This isn't our world anymore
Why are you still here?
I've waited for you for 3 years
Let's start all over again
Don't bother me Pay attention to your brother
He's following Shing everyday
That's very dangerous
You're brothers
Kit, we all know you are good at your work
I recommended your promotion,
but it's rejected
Why?
This guy, you know him very well
He disappeared 3 years ago
He's back after being released
from prison in Taiwan
and got back with his old partners again
It's none of my business
We're investigating
underworld activities
and none of their family members
would be related
Understand?
When I carry out my order
I've never thought of my brother
Kit!
You're not in Shing's case anymore
Or you'll spoil the whole matter
Sung, Shing will meet those Thai tonight…
Nam!
Bottom up
Mark
Tell us about your stories
Let Ho say it
My boss says
$18,000,000 maximum
OK
Boss, Ho is outside
Draught beer, please
This way please
Ho!
How come you didn't inform us you're back
You shouldn't do that
We were good brothers once
Is that right, Mark?
Ho, if you didn't take care of me
I would never have what I have now
Oh no
You deserve it
I don't have the ability
It's Mark who gave me the chance
Mark, if you need my help in the future
Just say so
Don't bullshit. Let's drink
You have to take care of our brothers
Cheers!
This is for my leg
Happy
Come to see me when you're free
There's a lot we can talk
I'm not interested
You will be
I have to go
Sung Tse Ho!
Follow me
What are you doing?
What did Shing tell you?
Bullshit!
Don't fool me!
Business or bullshit?
Bullshit, really
Is there something arriving the day after?
Don't know
Where to load and when?
How can you be a Big Brother knowing nothing?
Kit!
Don't call me Kit, call me inspector!
I'm not a Big Brother anymore
Where do you work?
United Taxi Co
Decent business
Robbing with a taxi?
Where do you live?
United Taxi Co
Someone still accepted you thief
Thief… Doesn't he have a name?
Don't think you are great to have a gun
I'll shoot you down, cripple
Don't point at my head with a gun
If you've got the guts,
then shoot me…
Kit!
Sir, I know I owe you too much
Give me a chance!
Give you a chance?
I beg you to give me one!
Do you know because of you
I lost my chance of promotion
Because you are a member of the triad
Don't leave HK
I'll be back to get you
Do you need an invitation for a cup of tea
Thanks!
I will deduct it from your salary
You are mean
Otherwise How can I support my family?
You're right
There's a beautiful girl staring at you
Your girlfriend?
Please come in!
No!
I want your help
Can you leave HK for a while?
I don't want to see Kit getting mad
He can't take this pressure, neither can I
So I think it's better for you
to be away for a while
I won't leave!
I want Kit to see that I'm in my new life
Can you give me a chance
to show it to him?
Don't you see I want to skate
Riding bicycle with him too?
I don't want to lose this brother
Ho!
Don't stay here, go in!
There's no use just staying here
Ho can handle his own matter, go in!
Who are they?
They're not good
Ho, Big Brother wants to see you
I'm busy
Give me some face
Just come with me
Hello!
Ho, Mark is with us
Come over too
No, thanks I am not interested…
You may not interested in business
How about your brother?
Doesn't it raise your interest?
I'll wait for you!
OK!
Ken, I want to go out for a while
You have to have principle, don't be afraid
Be straight!
Ho, please!
You'll never be cleaned once
you belong to the underworld
Ho!
Ho, so glad you're back
How are you, Mr Yiu?
Fine, thanks
Come, talk to Shing!
Not you?
It's the same as talking to Shing
I'm too old to make decisions
Ho, sit please
We can make big money
I really hope to cooperate with you again
How?
You're still our Big Brother
Mark handles the trafficking of money
I'll take care of the drugs,
make money for our company
We need you to contact the old clients
You haven't got to the point yet
With your brother's assistance
That would be perfect!
What else to have your
own man in the police!
Come, I have something to tell you
How about if I don't accept?
Ho
I kept Mark because of you
Your brother is following everything
If it wasn't you, he's dead already!
Shing, one is my brother the other is my friend
How would I walk out this door
if I said yes?
It doesn't matter for you to insult me
But not my friend
If you hurt my brother
You won't live long
We've wanted Mark Lee
for 3 years
But we can't take him back legally
Otherwise,
we can control the syndicate
The Roc Police Dept is willing
to give information
to the Interpol to the Hong Kong Government
The US Government has also taken action
I see!
We've some information recently
in 2 days there'll be counterfeit
shipped to Taiwan
and 500 kg heroin!
Though I can't do this case myself
I hope to see
Mark and his men being charged
Boss, Ho is too much
Let's kill him
Not necessary
Do as we plan
I gave you the money already
Where do we load the thing?
I'll give you the address
Get in!
Come back!
Did you have dinner yet?
What are you doing?
Mr Mok, it's Kit, I've got hints
That Thai will deal with Shing tomorrow
Time and location should be…
OK, you hand in the hints tomorrow
and there will be no concern of yours
Why?
You are not involved
I'm afraid that you'll spoil the whole thing
Give me a chance?
I have told you that
There is no hero in the police
What are you doing now?
Do you know that today is my birthday?
Can you look at me?
You'll look
at vase
This is your home, not the police barrack
You even forget my birthday
Jackie
Happy birthday
I didn't forget
Blow out the candles
What wish did you make?
You really want to know?
What is it?
Promise not to lose your temper
Say it
The reunion of the two of you
Don't be angry
Nothing
Don't get angry on my birthday
I don't let you get angry
Otherwise I will get angry
Smile
Let me open it
Anything happens?
I want to speak to Kit
Who is?
Don't be mad
Keep your promise
Sit
Thanks
Today is your birthday?
Yes
Have a piece of cake
Why do you treat him that nice?
Don't do that
I don't care how you treat me
I'm here to tell you that
Shing tries to trap you
Be careful
Thank you!
Don't trust those crummy
It's always a trap if you
have it too easy
Do you think I am as dumb as before?
I only want to help you
Help me or trick me?
Do you know
You are my burden
Can you trust me one more time?
Trust you?
Jackie!
Ho!
His impression of me didn't change a bit
Don't give up
Don't let the other look down upon you
Why can't you forgive him?
Let him start a new life?
He killed dad indirectly?
Why do you force me to accept him
He can't blame anymore for
choosing the wrong way?
I'm the cop, he's the thief
We're going opposite
I'm a cop
What's happening? Ken!
Your brother is having an operation
He's now at Queen Margaret's
Hurry up!
OK
What happened to my brother?
He was trapped by Shing
He purposely did it
How is he?
You can't get in
I tried to stop him alone
But he insisted
I hope you can cooperate with the police
and let us know your location
It's easy to be a hero. Jump
It's not the same now, you don't have any choice
Get along with us
And don't tell the police
We know each other well
What's happening?
Don't use Sung ever again
Stop!
Fight with them
Stop it!
Can we make a deal
It's not worthwhile
breaking the law again
Stop fighting
Stop
Run!
You idiot, don't go!
Stay if you have guts!
You, son of bitch!
Ken. That's my fault
I don't want you to be involved
You've no principle
They fight because they are scared
If you hit them back then they win
Why do you want to change?
Why?
Who's he?
Ken! Ho!
Come and have a look
Come over
Mark…
Emergency box
Quick!
Ken, what are we going to do?
Let's go!
Police. Stop for searching
That's too much
I'll send the quotation to the Station
Smart
I didn't notice HK is so beautiful at night
But it doesn't last
It's not worthwhile
Ho!
Let's start all over again
After this last time
then leave HK gloriously
Mark!
We've never been scared before
Why are we scared of Shing…
Don't push me, I'll never get involved again
That was the past
I'm still alive
Even you do 10 times, 100 times
Then what?
Even you kill Shing?
I lost my brother already
I don't want to lose you too
Mark, can you wake up?
I don't want sympathy
You didn't owe me anything?
I never force my friend's
doing things unwillingly
I've my principle
I don't want to be a loser for my whole life
Do you think I like begging?
I've waited for a chance for 3 years
I've to show them
that I'm not the best
but I just want to say that
what I've lost, I will take back
What do you look like?
We were scared when we were bad
Felt as if we were being
followed when we are good
Did you fight for a chance?
You didn't
No!
I don't want to be like you
Mark!
What happened to you?
I just want to take back something
Stand over that side
Go and get the plate
You'll be in big trouble
Think twice before you do it
Stop for a moment
Run!
Open the door!
Thanks. Mr Chan!
Go after them
You idiot!
I told you that's too much
Idiot
If Ho hands the plate to the police
Not only you will die but
even the syndicate will collapse
That's enough
Don't call me idiot
What did you call me when I made money for you?
I regret to have you
I'll kill you if you
don't bring me back the plate
You kill me then
I betrayed Ho 3 years ago
Would I be scared of him now?
You have to pay him back
We've to share
the problem together!
Hello!
Ho, why did you give me such a problem?
Mr Yiu. I want to speak to Shing
Shing? Wait a minute
Beg him to give
us back the plate
Ho, don't fool me
We can compromise
10 p.m. tonight. Go to Temple with US $2,000,000
For the exchange of the plate
and have a boat ready for you at The Bay
That's simple?
I want cash
You yourself!
I will be there
What did Ho say?
What did he say?
What?
He said he wants to have dinner with you
OK, I'll wait for him
Sir!
Come in!
Mr Mok, I've information
Ho, Mark and Shing have a quarrel
They blackmailed Shing
and they're having a deal tonight
Did you know the time and place?
Later
Hello. I'm…
Thanks!
2 minutes ago
Shing debited US $2,000,000 from the bank
Everyone get ready
for order
Yes, Sir!
Mr Mok. Let me in
You should be in the hospital
What are you doing here?
I'm fine
You've a paid leave for a few days
See, I can lift the chair easily
You're not included
My brother is the thief. Not me
Why do you
give me pressure?
If you still remember the rules
You shouldn't get involved
My dad died 3 years ago
I allow Shing
But you two are brothers
I know this case most thoroughly
Don't pressure me
would you lock him up?
I want to lock him up myself
I'll lock him up
Kit. Be practical
Jackie
I'm leaving HK tonight
You are giving up
Can you give
this packet
to Kit tonight at 9
It's very important to him
Will you come back?
Kit, your brother is leaving tonight
He asked me to give this packet to you
Kit. The plate I gave you
is the proof to charge Shing
We're having a dealing tonight at The Bay
You can put me in prison if you like to
I decided not to stay in HK
What are you doing?
I have to grab him
No. You can't
No
Go away!
Kit…
Ho. They are late
Do you know what to say?
Do you believe in god?
I'm the god
God is a human
Anyone will be god, if he can control his fate
But sometimes you couldn't
You'll either gain or loose
Hold it!
Money?
Plate?
Hand it to the police
Don't
There's a bomb
I'm not a dummy
You scared?
Don't trick me?
Shit!
After Ho arrived, he had a quarrel with Master
He asked for $2,000,000
He'll be at sea tonight
Then I heard a shot
That's him
Are you sure?
Yes!
Do you want to be the witness?
I know you'll do that already
You'll lose
Get out!
Get out…
Let him go if you're smart!
Come over
Go!
Ho, on board
You go first
You said we'll go together
I've something to do
I'll meet you
Mark. Go!
I'll wait for you
Release him
Otherwise, I'll kill your brother
Don't do it
One for one
Go!
I won't let you off
I know!
Kit!
Come over
You
Look at your brother
Look!
No matter how he wronged you before
He paid you back now
He has the guts to change
What can't you forgive him?
Why?
For a brother…
Shing!
You can't get over, Miss
Ho, you're being surrounded
In 3 minutes
Come out unarmed
No more bullets
I'm going to surrender
I'll be alright
You'll not
I will have money, 3 days later
I'll be released
I've money, can change black to white
I learned it from you
But your brother,
because of you, he's from white to black
You've dragged him down
Kit. You didn't do it wrong
We are on different routes
Yours is right
I was wrong before
I want to be back on the right one now