[Script Info]
Titlet: Zoo.S03E13END
Original Script: Orange字幕组
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FDFEFE,&H000000FF,&H00010200,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: LOGO,微软雅黑,21,&H00EBEBEB,&HF0101010,&H00713B0B,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,0,0,0,1341
Style: 片头,微软雅黑,100,&H32005F89,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00132121,-1,0,0,0,100,100,10,0,1,1,1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 人员,微软雅黑,21,&H32C9D6E3,&H000000FF,&H4B1C2123,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,3,1,1,8,10,10,10,1
Style: 硬字幕,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H0003050A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,45,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.05,0:00:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十年前 动物种群发生变异
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.93,0:00:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威胁着地球上的人类生命
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.96,0:00:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的队伍成功治愈了动物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.70,0:00:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但代价惨重
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.40,0:00:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让动物回归地球
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫牧人联盟的秘密组织
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.77,0:00:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,释放了一种绝育人类的气体
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.44,0:00:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后 实验室制造的物种 混种
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.41,0:00:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摧毁了西海岸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.91,0:00:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一座巨型围墙拔地而起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.12,0:00:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用以保护北美其他地区
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.28,0:00:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但新的物种已经开始出现
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.32,0:00:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我们重新召集队伍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.02,0:00:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在不同的前线上战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找治疗不孕的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.56,0:00:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抢占先机 阻止那些混种
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.09,0:00:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一名创造混种 计划终结人类的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.36,0:00:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧人联盟成员
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.53,0:00:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类生存之战刚刚拉开序幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困兽 前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.60,0:00:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们降落在围墙的另一侧 混种区
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.43,0:00:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们 听好了 无论要做什么 速度要快
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.38,0:01:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在加里森下令用导弹消灭信标和巢穴之前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.17,0:01:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只剩不到两个小时了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.09,0:01:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把死亡开关
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.42,0:01:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交到指挥中心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.59,0:01:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还有很多混种挡着我们的路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.76,0:01:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们造一个费洛蒙扩散器
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.29,0:01:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引开混种 为大家打开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.99,0:01:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前往指挥中心的路
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.66,0:01:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.09,0:01:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将孩子送入围墙内
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.90,0:01:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能结束这场不育之战
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.60,0:01:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经也有过家庭 有老婆有儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.80,0:01:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 克莱姆和孩子会安然无事的 - 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.17,0:01:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉 杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.74,0:01:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的世界正在崩塌
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.84,0:01:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.92,0:01:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚推下山崖的那个男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.42,0:01:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字不是山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.88,0:01:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫康纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.18,0:01:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.73,0:01:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡开关应该能够关闭信标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.33,0:01:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望这个世界能撑到那会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.43,0:01:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 报告情况- 利马无应答
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.87,0:01:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香港已失守 军队正在撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.14,0:01:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柏林有大批百姓伤亡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.81,0:02:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已请求支援
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.04,0:02:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被激活的信标有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.31,0:02:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12个 还剩一个尚未激活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.88,0:02:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在美国位于圣路易的信标
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.55,0:02:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围墙东面有混种巢穴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.55,0:02:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 我们已经清除了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.88,0:02:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围墙外有大量混种
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.45,0:02:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦圣路易的信标被激活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.63,0:02:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有混种都会奋不顾身地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.99,0:02:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲向围墙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.39,0:02:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北美暂时安全
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.96,0:02:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果超出巢穴临界值 这话当白说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.49,0:02:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部人都完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.93,0:02:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和那块疯狂的科学玩意儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.98,0:02:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最后的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.53,0:02:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咳咳 真是小菜一碟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.62,0:02:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加里森说我能在这里找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.19,0:02:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不让我去围墙外找他
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.36,0:02:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们这儿有优秀的医生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.76,0:02:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和更好的药物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.46,0:02:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有杰克逊和山姆的活动迹象吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:02:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 也没有混种的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.90,0:03:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们肯定用山姆的费洛蒙扩散器成功引开了它们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.50,0:03:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你联系过他们了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.07,0:03:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人应答
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.31,0:03:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的电话肯定是被电磁脉冲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.61,0:03:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,影响了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.25,0:03:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这影响很快会消退
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.38,0:03:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会一直给他们打电话的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.59,0:03:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官 我输入了新数据 但操作系统
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.99,0:03:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 毫无反应 - 我也是 没有关闭窗口
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.46,0:03:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你知道这么操作这个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.81,0:03:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不知名堂的死亡开关 - 它激活了信标
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.25,0:03:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它理应也能关闭信标
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.37,0:03:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切断电力或许是个办法
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.82,0:03:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不能这么做 当我们切断东京的电力时
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.64,0:03:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触发了一场大爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.61,0:03:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.11,0:03:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能切断电力 或许试试转移电力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.65,0:03:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.91,0:03:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官 距离巢穴临界值
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.53,0:03:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 尚余30分钟 - 召集各位将军
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.53,0:03:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候讨论应急预案了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.06,0:03:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这应急预案到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.43,0:03:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用多国联盟
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.93,0:03:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组成的海军舰队
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.47,0:03:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消灭信标和混种巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.04,0:04:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能用远程导弹来处理这事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.63,0:04:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会造成无数伤亡的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.16,0:04:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已与将军们连好线了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.57,0:04:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢 - 你不能这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.41,0:04:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.91,0:04:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾萨克在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.94,0:04:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 - 他在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.65,0:04:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在印第安纳州的朋友家 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.28,0:04:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他打电话 让他抓紧上路 一路朝北
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.85,0:04:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没到尽头别停下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.45,0:04:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇 你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.49,0:04:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澳大利亚的信标刚刚变暗了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.03,0:04:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.96,0:04:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香港的也关闭了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.50,0:04:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俄罗斯也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.64,0:04:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼亚也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.86,0:05:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们正在关闭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.20,0:05:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.48,0:05:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥伦比亚的也关闭了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.36,0:05:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣路易斯的信标激活了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.31,0:05:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣路易斯的激活了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.53,0:05:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇 你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.97,0:05:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.05,0:05:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 那边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.49,0:06:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和山姆在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.90,0:06:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得开门
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.57,0:06:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺住 山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.09,0:06:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.93,0:06:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这张小脸脸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.36,0:06:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的外婆 她喜欢给我洗手和洗脸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.47,0:06:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小就是病秧子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.60,0:06:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她视细菌为敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.17,0:06:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望你能见到她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.14,0:06:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 我们奉令
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.78,0:06:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真敬业 但我要见我女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.28,0:06:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 爸爸 - 这是我女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.22,0:06:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他过来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.80,0:07:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.21,0:07:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 去哪儿 - 哪儿都行 除了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.65,0:07:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不走
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.05,0:07:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你告诉要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.72,0:07:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混种要来了 所有的混种
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.99,0:07:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.03,0:07:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣路易斯的信标激活了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.51,0:07:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如我们所说 吸引了更多的混种力量
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.05,0:07:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法关闭信标 无法切断电力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.63,0:07:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你引它们来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.80,0:07:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 总得去某个地方的 - 我应该把你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.60,0:07:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔到禁闭室
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.44,0:07:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有围墙好吗 我们比其他地区的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.12,0:07:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更好一些
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.16,0:07:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能处理这个事的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.87,0:07:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里需要帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.53,0:07:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.73,0:07:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么救我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.86,0:07:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会没事的 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.80,0:07:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.70,0:07:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.65,0:07:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.28,0:07:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别乱动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.68,0:08:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 你没事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.32,0:08:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些混种都是从哪来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.19,0:08:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇刚刚关闭了全球的信标
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.76,0:08:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代价是把北美的所有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.19,0:08:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信标能量转移到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说在屏障西侧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.74,0:08:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的混种都会冲我们来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.41,0:08:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.29,0:08:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就祈祷这屏障能有作用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.38,0:09:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人员注意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.51,0:09:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上向长官报道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.97,0:09:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受调度命令
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.42,0:09:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我们没多少时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.29,0:09:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱姆 我只希望你和孩子能逃出去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.69,0:09:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我们走 - 不 我不会丢下山姆的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.26,0:09:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不走 我也不走
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.70,0:09:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面的墙是水泥砌成的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.88,0:09:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,15尺厚 40尺高 虽然我们的确身处险境
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.90,0:09:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这里对她来说是最安全的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.06,0:09:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死去的士兵都是你的责任 摩根博士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.08,0:09:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你操作的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.24,0:09:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道就没想一想激活标的后果吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.01,0:09:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的作为救了全世界几百万条人命 懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.74,0:09:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好 那现在怎么办呢 米奇 - 别吵了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.28,0:09:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他的计划 - 我们根本就不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.91,0:09:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 怎么关了这玩意 - 就是炸掉几个城市
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.22,0:09:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吵啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.68,0:09:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪也不去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.22,0:10:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是要在这里陪着山姆 直到他好过来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.77,0:10:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了你别担心我了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.73,0:10:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想一下信标的事情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.23,0:10:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只需要再争取一点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.73,0:10:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.97,0:10:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研究这个信标到底是怎么设计的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.11,0:10:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行么 如果你们能搞到所有的情报
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.64,0:10:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不定可以把它重新设置一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.84,0:10:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要调取东京的监控录像了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.37,0:10:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得知道还有哪些信标在发射信号
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.32,0:10:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你说的这些都不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.64,0:10:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有一个信号控制站
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.32,0:10:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在墙另一侧往北走500米
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.82,0:10:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带一队过去 把它的方向调整到对准信标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.97,0:10:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你失败了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.48,0:10:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就要强制关掉这个信标
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.99,0:10:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 千万不能那样做
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.89,0:10:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经疏散了整个圣路易和半个密苏里州的居民
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.39,0:10:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些居民
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.93,0:10:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定来不及在爆炸之前逃生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.59,0:10:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也束手无策 这是上级命令
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.06,0:10:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你有能耐 那你来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.02,0:11:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.69,0:11:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想个能一招制敌的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.49,0:11:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转换器有三重保护
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.63,0:11:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信号无法获取
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.30,0:11:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定搞不出来个能救所有人的完美系统
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.77,0:11:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为完美系统根本就不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.56,0:11:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 而且信标也不是你设计的 是邓肯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.61,0:11:32.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用我的脑子设计的 有什么区别么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.61,0:11:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解铃还需系铃人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.25,0:11:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 随你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.29,0:11:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.98,0:11:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就呆在这陪你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.18,0:11:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇 摩根
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.45,0:11:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起想办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.41,0:12:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种血清可以促进你的宝宝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.91,0:12:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生成CLM蛋白质的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.36,0:12:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重塑人类生育能力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.24,0:12:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 没什么副作用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.94,0:12:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需要三针
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.51,0:12:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是第一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.58,0:12:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12小时后再打一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.75,0:12:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,24小时候打最后一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.78,0:12:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 准备好了吗 小宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.42,0:12:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他就是全世界的救星的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.22,0:12:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得给他起个响当当的名字的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.19,0:12:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还没给他取名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.75,0:12:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想了几个 都是家族里的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.79,0:12:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦好啦 没事啦 宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.61,0:12:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为人父母真的不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.41,0:12:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆和我一直没想好名字
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.48,0:13:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能我们永远都没机会了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.82,0:13:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.55,0:13:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.75,0:13:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的行为 是需要勇气和善心的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.32,0:13:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道山姆和阿比盖尔是一伙的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.66,0:13:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你还是舍身救他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.43,0:13:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我是做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.36,0:13:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 亚伯 你也会这样做的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.07,0:13:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你救了他的命 杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.84,0:13:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你救了一个孩子的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.42,0:14:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是为了孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.02,0:14:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.92,0:14:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.33,0:14:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.16,0:14:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆就是康纳 奥兹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.71,0:14:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆是我儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.95,0:14:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是阿比盖尔计划中的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.28,0:14:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们这样见面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.85,0:14:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔因为我夺走了她的父亲 她要报仇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.62,0:14:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她让我又一次看着康纳死去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.96,0:14:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果是阿比盖尔告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.16,0:14:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆就是康纳 你为什么这么相信她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.20,0:14:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为她有证据
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.14,0:15:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.44,0:15:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼娅给康纳织的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.41,0:15:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是裹他的小毯子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.09,0:15:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.43,0:15:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20年前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.20,0:15:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亲眼目睹我的儿子死去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.16,0:15:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他在这
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.98,0:15:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我当父亲的时候还要成熟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.33,0:15:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个大人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.49,0:15:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.31,0:16:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信标还没关掉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.71,0:16:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论米奇怎么弄 信标一直都亮着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报告情况
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.97,0:16:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联合军守住了伊斯坦布尔和香港的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.12,0:16:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分居民所在中心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.55,0:16:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平民伤亡人数在减少
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.39,0:16:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德国空军正在消灭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.99,0:16:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柏林外的混种
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.46,0:16:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根教授还在想办法解决
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.03,0:16:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣路易斯的信标
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.34,0:16:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我点好消息
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.14,0:16:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 毫无进展
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.45,0:16:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有信标活跃迹象吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.98,0:16:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.55,0:16:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我们占上风了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有 摩根教授
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.12,0:16:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还在混种包围圈里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.26,0:16:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且数量悬殊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.83,0:17:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.09,0:17:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监测站被攻下了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.66,0:17:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已被混种占领
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.26,0:17:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没法复位天线阵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.27,0:17:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但守住了圣路易信标的信号数据
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.44,0:17:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快到医务室去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.57,0:17:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是威尔森的话 我现在得去停尸房了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.24,0:17:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我们去给你包扎一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.95,0:17:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 威尔森 我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.32,0:17:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖狗狗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.82,0:17:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意最好是值得这么折腾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.96,0:17:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的人还能撑多久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.38,0:17:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道对你的解决方案没信心吗  因为如果
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.07,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他们还能撑多久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.90,0:17:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你心里有数吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.87,0:17:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 我要你现在把我女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.17,0:17:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和她的宝宝弄出去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 她们两个现在是全世界最重要的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.51,0:17:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会冒险让她俩待在这的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.52,0:18:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你其他的队员同意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.75,0:18:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事比队伍还重要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.32,0:18:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我们任何一个人都重要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.91,0:18:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让欧洲人道主义救援队转移你女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.89,0:18:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有她的孩子到东边去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.75,0:18:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的就靠你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.36,0:18:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H区已经陷落
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.93,0:18:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混种已经快攻到发电机了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.18,0:18:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,E F和N区持续损失惨重
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.37,0:18:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,C区检测到火情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.10,0:18:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封闭C区
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.21,0:18:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面还有我们的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.01,0:18:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着的人都撤出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.71,0:18:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的作战范围太大了 我们得开始划重点了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.99,0:18:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先保护好发电机
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.67,0:18:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一但停电 我们就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.95,0:18:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安排剩余部队守卫指挥中心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.02,0:18:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把三角小队调去发电机那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.05,0:19:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后立刻下令疏散所有非战斗人员
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.26,0:19:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤离
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.10,0:19:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把命令传下去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.60,0:19:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场仗我们赢不了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.85,0:19:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能尽量守住阵线
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.76,0:19:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈祷我们有办法在那些怪兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.59,0:19:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲进来之前关掉信标吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.26,0:19:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医务室全体人员
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.26,0:19:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请马上将病人转移到西南角走廊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.69,0:19:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医务室全体人员
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.19,0:19:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请马上将病人转移到西南角走廊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.40,0:19:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱曼婷 我们得
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.66,0:19:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.06,0:19:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有两种不同的频率
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.28,0:19:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是从圣路易斯信标传来的信号吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.58,0:19:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把它分离出来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.72,0:20:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我认得这个频率
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.09,0:20:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是阿比盖尔从我脑电波里录下的频率
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.53,0:20:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说我就是靠这个控制动物们的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.27,0:20:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信标是用来吸引混种的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.14,0:20:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 她为什么要用你的频率 - 我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.17,0:20:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 这频率没有吸引来动物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.41,0:20:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是我的频率
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.98,0:20:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你打赌这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.64,0:20:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.11,0:20:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 她就是这样控制混种的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.22,0:20:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我猜测
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.79,0:20:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两种频率
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.03,0:20:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被信标放大以后 就会创造一个声垒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.82,0:20:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 就像东京的那个 - 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.09,0:20:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是你的频率的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.60,0:20:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能是唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.89,0:20:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以穿过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.06,0:20:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信标堡垒的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.76,0:20:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.57,0:20:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我搞清楚我是怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.63,0:20:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说邓肯是怎么设计这个信标的了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.11,0:20:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我发现了一个漏洞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.68,0:20:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是用来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.02,0:20:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,防止人类接近的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.14,0:21:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把这个想象成两把完全相同的音叉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.35,0:21:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同一个频率上产生共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.35,0:21:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和信标频率一致
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.95,0:21:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但地球上其他人的频率都不同
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.59,0:21:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是说我不会受到这个信号影响
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.43,0:21:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是这么猜的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.50,0:21:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是鉴于发生在东京的士兵身上的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.00,0:21:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得靠近信标还是会疼成狗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.64,0:21:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 即使你是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.50,0:21:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近信标对我们有什么用
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.61,0:21:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以做一个装置
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.15,0:21:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接连到信标上 这样我们就能远程控制它了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.79,0:21:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你做得到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.18,0:21:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也许就能把信标彻底关上了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.22,0:21:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把包裹准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.22,0:21:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会保证它被顺利送达
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.69,0:21:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你想这么做吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.42,0:21:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确定
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.89,0:21:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果这法子行不通
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.13,0:21:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次解决一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.93,0:21:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇 你怎么敢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.23,0:21:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱姆的宝宝对解决不育问题来说至关重要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.80,0:21:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没和我们商量就把他送走了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.89,0:22:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.01,0:22:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别着急 慢点说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.51,0:22:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱姆和宝宝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.14,0:22:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得待在安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.17,0:22:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你知道这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.61,0:22:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮我们解决了一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.25,0:22:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你那么确信你做了对的事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.48,0:22:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么还瞒着我们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.09,0:22:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本应要给他注射血清的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.59,0:22:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他没有继续注射 解药就毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.56,0:22:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的家人 我做决定
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.38,0:22:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 米奇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.69,0:22:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们队伍不是这样处理事情的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.23,0:22:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这是我处理事情的方式 杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.52,0:22:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承担个人风险的人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.08,0:22:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.30,0:22:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把那个装置做出来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.68,0:22:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好祈祷克莱姆和宝宝都没事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.44,0:22:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.95,0:22:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆的真名是康纳 奥兹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.36,0:22:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是杰克逊的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.41,0:23:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边走 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.48,0:23:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中央指挥部认为 你们已经找到
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.48,0:23:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒这玩意的方法了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.62,0:23:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 至少我们已经有思路了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.37,0:23:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们能将这装置连上信标
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.56,0:23:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围墙里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.06,0:23:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可能关掉这玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.63,0:23:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人就不用上西天了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.29,0:23:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会发出一种镜脉冲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.80,0:23:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让混种们远离围墙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.82,0:23:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意发出的声波
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.40,0:23:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放倒了我六个手下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.53,0:23:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医疗兵说他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.83,0:23:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,器官都被震散架了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.84,0:23:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个大家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.45,0:23:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前怎么会没有人注意到这玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.58,0:23:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文件说是在建造先进的无线电塔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.93,0:23:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来便利巨墙之外的通讯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.52,0:23:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.42,0:23:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少有一半是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.86,0:23:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.53,0:23:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光说不练瞪着看没有用
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.90,0:23:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.73,0:23:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 泰莎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.23,0:23:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 呵呵 - 听到他说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.63,0:23:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能靠近那玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.80,0:23:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就走到最远的那一步
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.20,0:24:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.90,0:24:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你救过我不计其数
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.74,0:24:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这次
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.24,0:24:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须独自前行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.52,0:24:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.93,0:24:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.84,0:24:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 杰克逊 - 不可以过去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.07,0:24:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.25,0:24:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 快回去 - 我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.78,0:24:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 快回去 - 我不要丢下你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.59,0:24:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求你了 退回去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.36,0:24:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.27,0:25:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.93,0:25:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嗯 我没事 - 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.30,0:25:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.96,0:25:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他比任何人都走得更近
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.67,0:25:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括穿着全密封装备的海豹突击队
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.97,0:25:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只需走到足够近的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.44,0:25:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连接上逆变器
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.64,0:25:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.53,0:25:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角洲 报告情况
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.96,0:25:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在H区遇到尖背狼袭击
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.94,0:25:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们已经突破了防线
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.21,0:25:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.59,0:25:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校 不能撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.66,0:25:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须保持发电机正常运行\N少校
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.50,0:25:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指挥中心 我们弹药不够了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.03,0:25:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人手也不够了 混种数量太多
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.37,0:25:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们断电 
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.27,0:25:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算杰克逊连上信标 都没有用了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.24,0:26:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角洲特种部队需要增援
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.21,0:26:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是仅剩的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.13,0:26:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个身体强壮的人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.21,0:26:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我一起来 守护发电机
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.70,0:26:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人 现在行动
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.29,0:26:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会尽可能长时间的保持电力供应
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.00,0:26:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊快成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.84,0:26:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一次在混种袭击中 我丢下你一人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.36,0:26:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果一别十年
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.91,0:26:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.82,0:26:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊 回话
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.15,0:26:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.76,0:26:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交换位置吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.23,0:26:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 你必须快点
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.46,0:26:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的发电机正在遭受攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.21,0:26:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们断电了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.36,0:26:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就没法发动指令关掉信标
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.60,0:26:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.50,0:27:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.74,0:27:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四号发电机需要增援
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.61,0:27:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尖背狼一定是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.85,0:27:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻破了西南通道隧道
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.41,0:27:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果攻击他们
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.55,0:27:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有可能阻止他们进一步靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.79,0:27:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.83,0:27:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会前往变电站 走吧 威尔逊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.27,0:27:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威尔逊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.01,0:27:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.47,0:28:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚肚还真软
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.33,0:28:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你一样
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.27,0:28:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过这里后
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.65,0:28:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要半小时就能到布伦南堡
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.12,0:28:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里找到婴儿座椅的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.42,0:28:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我听说你跟一个新生儿一起返回
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.69,0:28:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的第一件事就是联系物流团队
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.93,0:28:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到过去十年中从来没有出生过新生儿
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.18,0:28:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找婴儿用品可不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.83,0:28:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直对我照顾有加
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.97,0:28:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从我跟你还有杰米一起生活的开始
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.84,0:28:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.31,0:28:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有两个人需要我照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.68,0:28:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给这个小家伙起名字了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.21,0:28:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说我们继续叫它巨墙宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.72,0:28:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是这么喊他的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.74,0:28:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.01,0:28:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他提出抗议之前
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.81,0:29:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须想出个好名字
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.33,0:29:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞缪尔
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.13,0:29:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者山姆也行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.80,0:29:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证山姆醒来的时候 会喜欢这个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.77,0:29:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他醒得来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.47,0:29:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱姆 他会醒来的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.11,0:29:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.02,0:29:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过山姆会跟在我们后面的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.52,0:29:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有看到救护车
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.02,0:29:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛根 山姆在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.46,0:29:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.64,0:29:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 调头 - 他身体不够好 没法转移
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.62,0:29:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.59,0:29:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓稳了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.77,0:29:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论发生什么 不要下车
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.75,0:30:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛根
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.43,0:30:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给点力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.89,0:30:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没子弹了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.19,0:30:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达瑞拉 我不知道我们还能不能
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.43,0:30:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了 我们马上就能再见到艾萨克了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.60,0:30:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会给我们生很多孙子孙女
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.67,0:30:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们来宠着他们
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.40,0:30:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是他爸爸合成了解药
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.97,0:30:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你绝对不能放弃 亚伯
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.07,0:30:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见我的话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.96,0:31:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊 杰克逊 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.33,0:31:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安装完成
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.04,0:32:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.11,0:32:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.31,0:32:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不动了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.96,0:32:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 让我去看看
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.16,0:32:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 你不能去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.89,0:32:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.69,0:32:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们上线了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.83,0:32:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电源重启
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.33,0:32:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在发送指令
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.70,0:32:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.07,0:32:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这起作用了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.74,0:32:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.94,0:32:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 杰克逊 - 别去
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.17,0:33:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混种开始撤退了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.67,0:33:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是他们关掉了信标
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.60,0:33:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.60,0:33:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住机会
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.91,0:33:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.92,0:33:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.38,0:33:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.42,0:33:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.93,0:33:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.33,0:33:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的 你成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.31,0:33:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 睁开眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.00,0:33:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.84,0:33:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成功了 亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.27,0:33:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的 你成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.51,0:33:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 睁开眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.08,0:33:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说句话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.51,0:33:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.35,0:33:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.89,0:34:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起把这些混种赶回老家去
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.93,0:34:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.17,0:34:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成功了 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.47,0:34:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们痛揍了那些
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.25,0:34:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的混种
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.21,0:34:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拯救了世界
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.42,0:35:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有你 我不可能完成这些的 
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.42,0:35:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.47,0:35:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会还真悬呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.88,0:35:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不都喜欢戏剧化的吗  
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.45,0:35:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.38,0:35:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们一起完成的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.58,0:35:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.19,0:35:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.54,0:36:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次袭击里我们守住了医务室
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.97,0:36:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我们关闭了信标 赶跑了混种
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.36,0:36:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们守住边界
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.73,0:36:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加里森就召回应急小队
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.26,0:36:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就可以把克莱姆和孩子接回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.03,0:36:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.23,0:36:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国际动物保护组织和当地军队
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.73,0:36:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有关押混种的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.33,0:36:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们正在清除游荡的混种
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.20,0:36:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们关闭了信标
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.77,0:36:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止了混种 还治愈了人类的不孕症
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.23,0:36:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功近在眼前啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.67,0:36:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想一起喝一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.24,0:36:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.55,0:36:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根博士
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.25,0:36:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加里森要求你马上回到指挥中心
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.55,0:36:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.86,0:36:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特洛伊的狗出事了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.42,0:36:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们刚刚发现
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.79,0:36:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特洛伊在诊室里被撕成碎片了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.26,0:36:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,士兵们不得不把那只狗困住射杀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.59,0:36:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它已经死了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.93,0:36:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 然而它又活过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.39,0:36:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了一只混种
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.60,0:36:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 - 这
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.79,0:36:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不可能 - 无论这到底是什么鬼东西
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.59,0:36:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在必须马上去那看看
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.57,0:36:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 什么情况 这些还有传染性了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.90,0:36:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果混种能转化别的动物
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.07,0:36:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论我们关闭信标还是摧毁它们巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.00,0:36:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都变得毫无意义了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.28,0:36:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么阿比盖尔就可以把所有动物都变成她的军队
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.11,0:37:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们还有隔离墙
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.88,0:37:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们能守住围墙 就还能阻止混种扩散
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.25,0:37:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱姆
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.29,0:37:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.46,0:37:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了 你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.72,0:37:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子 孩子没了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.73,0:37:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 孩子去哪了 什么 - 外面到处都是混种
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.63,0:37:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔出现了 然后
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.33,0:37:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 孩子怎么了 - 孩子被抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.79,0:37:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你确定那是阿比盖尔吗 - 对 我很确定
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.97,0:37:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔出现了 然后抢走了孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.94,0:37:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混种追上来 杀了洛根
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.37,0:37:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.34,0:37:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.86,0:37:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天哪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.00,0:37:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应急小队途中遇袭
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.28,0:37:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子被抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.49,0:37:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们从空中搜索
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.12,0:37:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.29,0:37:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你当初一有机会
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.21,0:37:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了阿比盖尔
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.24,0:37:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都不会发生
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.51,0:37:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能洛根还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.30,0:37:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们一样都尽力了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.65,0:37:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛根在外面的唯一原因
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.99,0:37:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你和米奇想要转移克莱姆和孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.34,0:37:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们把他留在这里 这个安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.51,0:38:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加里森正在召集所有能派遣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.78,0:38:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但转移额外资源需要更多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.18,0:38:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.78,0:38:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不在四个小时之内用药
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.52,0:38:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就没有机会治愈不孕症了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.35,0:38:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你以为阿比盖尔会让我们轻易找到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.01,0:38:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全球的所有政府机关都在找她
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.81,0:38:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那我们应该开始想想其他方案
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.09,0:38:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.53,0:38:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.20,0:38:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你伤害他
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.60,0:38:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔 我发誓 我会杀了你的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.37,0:38:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子很好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.50,0:38:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.34,0:38:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 洛根就没这么幸运了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.01,0:38:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.38,0:38:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的一直没变过
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.22,0:38:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我的混种们在任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.78,0:38:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受自由
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.85,0:38:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做到这个 我就把他还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.30,0:38:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.20,0:38:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 不可能让那些混种
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.45,0:39:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过巨墙的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.97,0:39:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你朋友们一直很有门路
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.04,0:39:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你们能找到办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.86,0:39:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我们
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.43,0:39:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联系下牧人联盟的朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.31,0:39:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们可以帮帮我们
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.12,0:39:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿比盖尔可是带着一个
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.24,0:39:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这十年间世界上才出现的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.47,0:39:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不可能完全消失
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.90,0:39:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能把孩子找回来
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.76,0:39:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚是阿比盖尔打来的 她想做个交易
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.22,0:39:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 宝宝还好吗 - 她说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.22,0:39:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子没事
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.32,0:39:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她准备把他还给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.62,0:39:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 她想用什么来交换
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.43,0:40:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.51,0:40:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想要什么来交换
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.28,0:40:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想让她的混种们通过隔离墙
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.95,0:40:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么 - 你想用
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.55,0:40:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞机导航板干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.11,0:40:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.15,0:40:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不不不不不 - 不 嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.45,0:40:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你疯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.35,0:40:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嘿 - 这是唯一的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.79,0:40:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是阻止混种扩散
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.62,0:40:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感染所有动物的的最后防线了 杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.07,0:40:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须把孩子要回来
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.53,0:40:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你这么做 你就成了和你父亲一样的罪人了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.47,0:40:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 或者像你妹妹那样 - 杰克逊和他们不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.34,0:40:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个孩子就是解药 而且他是
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.51,0:40:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,防止人类灭绝的唯一办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.98,0:40:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他现在在一个疯子手里
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.25,0:40:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能和她谈条件
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.18,0:40:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们不按她说的做 阿比盖尔会毫不犹豫地
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.58,0:40:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了那孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.82,0:41:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能相信她
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.89,0:41:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有别的选择吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.99,0:41:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛根为了保护孩子而死
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.10,0:41:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把孩子抢回来 杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.57,0:41:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰克逊 你好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.08,0:41:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北美洲的每一只动物
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.78,0:41:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会成为混种大军的一员
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.02,0:41:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.22,0:41:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次只关注一个问题 米奇
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.63,0:41:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次只关注一个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\pos(20.267,27.447)}m 65 187.5 b 69.625 185 73.75 182.875 77.75 180.75 82.875 178 87.75 175 92.875 172.25 95.75 170.625 98.875 169.25 101.75 167.625 105.75 165.375 109.75 163.125 113.75 161 116.5 159.375 119.5 158 122.25 156.5 125.25 154.875 128.125 153.125 131.125 151.5 133.125 150.5 135.125 149.5 137 148.5 140.125 146.875 143.125 145 146.25 143.375 149 141.875 151.75 140.625 154.5 139.125 157.375 137.5 160.25 135.875 163.125 134.25 164.75 133.375 166.375 132.5 167.875 131.625 172.25 129.25 176.625 126.875 181 124.5 184.125 122.875 187.375 121.375 190.5 119.625 194.5 117.5 198.375 115.125 202.375 113 202.75 112.75 203.25 112.375 203.625 112.25 203.625 117.375 203.875 122.75 203.5 127.625 203.125 131.75 202.375 135.875 201.375 140 200.25 144.5 199 149.125 196.75 153.25 195 156.625 193.75 160.375 191.75 163.625 190 166.75 187.75 169.5 185.75 172.375 184.75 173.875 183.75 175.375 182.5 176.625 181 178.25 179.375 179.75 177.875 181.25 176.125 182.875 174.5 184.625 172.75 186.125 171.375 187.25 169.875 188.375 168.375 189.375 165 191.5 161.625 193.75 158.125 195.875 156.375 197 154.25 197.75 152.25 198.5 149.75 199.625 147.125 200.75 144.5 201.75 143.875 202 143 202 142.25 202.25 136.625 204.125 130.875 205 124.875 205.25 121.125 205.375 117.375 206 113.75 205.75 108.5 205.375 103.25 204.625 98 203.625 94.375 202.875 90.75 201.625 87.25 200.25 83.75 198.875 80.25 197 77 195.25 74.125 193.75 71.5 192.125 68.75 190.375 67.5 189.625 66.5 188.625 65 187.5 m 58 189.125 b 53.875 185.125 49.625 180.875 45.25 176.625 48.5 174.25 51.25 172.375 54 170.25 58 167.25 61.875 164.125 65.875 161.125 68 159.5 70.375 158.125 72.5 156.5 75.375 154.25 78.125 152 81 149.75 83.75 147.625 86.625 145.625 89.375 143.5 91.75 141.625 94.25 139.875 96.625 138 98.5 136.625 100.5 135.25 102.375 133.75 106.25 130.875 110 127.875 113.875 125 116 123.375 118.125 121.875 120.25 120.25 123.375 118 126.375 115.625 129.5 113.25 131.625 111.75 133.75 110.25 135.875 108.75 138.125 107 140.25 105.25 142.5 103.5 144.125 102.375 145.75 101.25 147 99.75 143.625 102.125 140.25 104.5 136.75 106.875 134.5 108.375 132.25 109.625 130 111.125 126.625 113.375 123.375 115.75 120 118 117.625 119.625 115.125 121 112.625 122.625 110.375 124.25 108.125 126 105.75 127.5 103.75 129 101.625 130.375 99.625 131.75 96.875 133.5 94.125 135.25 91.375 137.125 89 138.625 86.5 140.125 84.125 141.75 81.625 143.375 79.375 145.125 77 146.75 75.125 148 73.25 149.375 71.25 150.625 68.125 152.75 65 154.875 61.75 156.875 60.5 157.625 59.375 158.5 58.125 159.125 57.5 159.5 58.875 158.625 58.375 159 45.25 168.25 47.5 167 54.625 161.5 51.5 163.875 41.375 171.125 38.25 173.625 35.625 175.75 38.375 173.25 35.5 175.625 34.125 173.625 32.625 171.75 31.5 169.625 29.5 166.125 27.75 162.5 26 158.875 25.25 157.375 24.625 155.875 24.125 154.375 23.375 152 22.625 149.625 22 147.375 21.5 145.125 22 144.375 23.875 143.375 26.875 141.875 29.75 140 32.625 138.375 35.25 136.875 37.875 135.375 40.375 133.875 44.375 131.5 48.375 129.125 52.375 126.75 54.75 125.375 57.25 124 59.625 122.625 62.5 120.875 65.5 119.125 68.375 117.375 70.625 116 73 114.75 75.25 113.375 78.625 111.375 81.875 109.5 85.125 107.625 87.875 106 90.75 104.5 93.375 102.875 95.875 101.375 98.375 99.75 100.75 98.375 102.75 97.25 104.75 96.25 106.625 95.125 109.25 93.625 111.75 92 114.375 90.5 116.5 89.25 118.625 88 120.75 86.75 124.25 84.625 127.75 82.625 131.25 80.625 133.875 79.125 136.625 77.625 139.25 76.125 140.125 75.625 140.875 75.125 141.625 74.375 139.625 75.375 137.5 76.375 135.5 77.5 134.25 78.125 133.25 79.125 132 79.75 126.75 82.75 121.375 85.5 116.125 88.5 111.5 91 106.75 93.625 102.125 96.25 97.5 98.875 93 101.625 88.375 104.25 86.875 105.25 85.25 105.875 83.625 106.75 80.375 108.625 77.125 110.5 73.75 112.375 71.25 113.875 68.625 115.125 66 116.625 62.875 118.375 59.75 120.125 56.625 122 53.25 123.875 49.875 125.75 46.5 127.625 43.625 129.25 40.625 130.75 37.75 132.375 35.875 133.375 34 134.375 32 135.625 31.625 132.5 31.125 129.75 30.875 126.875 30.5 123.25 30 119.625 30.125 116 30.375 110.75 31 105.5 31.875 100.25 32.75 95.875 34.125 91.5 35.625 87.25 37.125 83 39 79 41.25 75.25 43.75 70.875 46.75 66.875 49.75 63 52.125 59.875 54.875 57.125 57.625 54.375 60 52.125 62.5 49.875 65.25 48 69.25 45.25 73.375 42.5 77.75 40.25 81.625 38.25 85.75 37.125 89.75 35.5 95 33.25 100.625 32.625 106.25 31.75 111.75 30.75 117.375 31 123 31.25 127.25 31.375 131.5 32.125 135.625 33.125 139.5 34 143.25 35.25 147 36.625 150.25 38 153.375 39.75 156.625 41.25 158.25 42.125 160 42.875 161.625 44 164.25 45.75 166.75 47.625 169.375 49.5 171.125 50.75 172.75 52.125 174.5 53.625 174.875 54 175.125 54.5 175.75 55.375 171.75 57.5 168 59.625 164.125 61.75 165.625 63.375 167.25 65 168.75 66.625 169.5 67.375 170.125 68.125 170.625 69 170.75 69.25 170.5 70 170.25 70.125 166.375 73.125 162.5 75.875 158.75 78.875 156.875 80.25 155.375 82 153.5 83.375 151.625 85 149.5 86.375 147.625 87.875 145.5 89.5 143.375 91 141.375 92.625 139 94.375 136.75 96.25 134.5 98.125 132.625 99.625 130.75 101.125 128.875 102.625 128.25 103.125 127.625 103.375 127 103.75 127.125 104 127.25 104.125 127.25 104.25 131.25 101.5 135.125 98.75 139 96 141.375 94.5 143.75 93.125 146.125 91.5 148.75 89.875 151.25 88 153.875 86.375 158.375 83.25 163 80.125 167.625 77 169.75 75.625 172 74.25 174.25 72.875 177 71 179.625 69.125 182.25 67.25 184.25 65.875 186.375 64.625 188.375 63.25 190.375 61.875 192.25 60.625 194.25 59.25 195.25 58.625 196 58.5 196.75 59.75 197.375 61 198.375 62 199.125 63.25 199.375 63.75 199.25 64.75 198.875 65 197 66.5 195 67.75 193 69 190.375 70.875 187.75 72.625 185.125 74.5 184.875 74.75 184.875 75.75 185.125 76.25 186.875 79.875 189 83.375 190.625 87.125 192.375 91.625 193.75 96.125 194.875 100.75 195.875 104.875 196.375 109 197 113.125 197 113.625 196.375 114.5 195.875 114.75 192.125 116.875 188.375 118.875 184.5 120.875 179.625 123.5 174.625 126 169.875 128.625 164.5 131.5 159.375 134.5 154.125 137.375 150.375 139.5 146.5 141.375 142.75 143.5 139.875 145.125 137 146.75 134.125 148.375 132.125 149.5 130.125 150.375 128.125 151.5 124.125 153.625 120.125 155.875 116 158.125 113.125 159.625 110.25 161.125 107.5 162.625 104.375 164.25 101.375 166 98.25 167.75 96.875 168.5 95.375 169.25 93.875 170 89.75 172.125 85.625 174.375 81.5 176.5 79 177.875 76.375 179.125 73.875 180.5 69.875 182.75 66 185 62 187.25 60.875 187.875 59.625 188.375 58 189.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}m 26.375 141.5 b 83.75 110.625 144.125 78.125 202.25 46.875 203.875 54.125 206.875 60.875 206.875 67.875 206.875 72.375 205.375 72.25 204.125 72.875 189.875 79.25 175.75 83.75 161.375 90 120.75 107.75 80.125 125.5 39.5 143.25 30.75 147.125 32.125 150.5 26.375 141.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H37BA71&\p1}m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&HFFFFFF&\p1}m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0)\fade(1000,1000)\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp-0.853\fs21.333\fn微软雅黑\b0\pos(66.003,22.858)}O{\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&}range
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.19,0:00:15.19,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0\\fade(1000,1000))\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp2.133\fs19.2\b0\pos(66.203,47.524)}字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\pos(20.267,27.447)}m 65 187.5 b 69.625 185 73.75 182.875 77.75 180.75 82.875 178 87.75 175 92.875 172.25 95.75 170.625 98.875 169.25 101.75 167.625 105.75 165.375 109.75 163.125 113.75 161 116.5 159.375 119.5 158 122.25 156.5 125.25 154.875 128.125 153.125 131.125 151.5 133.125 150.5 135.125 149.5 137 148.5 140.125 146.875 143.125 145 146.25 143.375 149 141.875 151.75 140.625 154.5 139.125 157.375 137.5 160.25 135.875 163.125 134.25 164.75 133.375 166.375 132.5 167.875 131.625 172.25 129.25 176.625 126.875 181 124.5 184.125 122.875 187.375 121.375 190.5 119.625 194.5 117.5 198.375 115.125 202.375 113 202.75 112.75 203.25 112.375 203.625 112.25 203.625 117.375 203.875 122.75 203.5 127.625 203.125 131.75 202.375 135.875 201.375 140 200.25 144.5 199 149.125 196.75 153.25 195 156.625 193.75 160.375 191.75 163.625 190 166.75 187.75 169.5 185.75 172.375 184.75 173.875 183.75 175.375 182.5 176.625 181 178.25 179.375 179.75 177.875 181.25 176.125 182.875 174.5 184.625 172.75 186.125 171.375 187.25 169.875 188.375 168.375 189.375 165 191.5 161.625 193.75 158.125 195.875 156.375 197 154.25 197.75 152.25 198.5 149.75 199.625 147.125 200.75 144.5 201.75 143.875 202 143 202 142.25 202.25 136.625 204.125 130.875 205 124.875 205.25 121.125 205.375 117.375 206 113.75 205.75 108.5 205.375 103.25 204.625 98 203.625 94.375 202.875 90.75 201.625 87.25 200.25 83.75 198.875 80.25 197 77 195.25 74.125 193.75 71.5 192.125 68.75 190.375 67.5 189.625 66.5 188.625 65 187.5 m 58 189.125 b 53.875 185.125 49.625 180.875 45.25 176.625 48.5 174.25 51.25 172.375 54 170.25 58 167.25 61.875 164.125 65.875 161.125 68 159.5 70.375 158.125 72.5 156.5 75.375 154.25 78.125 152 81 149.75 83.75 147.625 86.625 145.625 89.375 143.5 91.75 141.625 94.25 139.875 96.625 138 98.5 136.625 100.5 135.25 102.375 133.75 106.25 130.875 110 127.875 113.875 125 116 123.375 118.125 121.875 120.25 120.25 123.375 118 126.375 115.625 129.5 113.25 131.625 111.75 133.75 110.25 135.875 108.75 138.125 107 140.25 105.25 142.5 103.5 144.125 102.375 145.75 101.25 147 99.75 143.625 102.125 140.25 104.5 136.75 106.875 134.5 108.375 132.25 109.625 130 111.125 126.625 113.375 123.375 115.75 120 118 117.625 119.625 115.125 121 112.625 122.625 110.375 124.25 108.125 126 105.75 127.5 103.75 129 101.625 130.375 99.625 131.75 96.875 133.5 94.125 135.25 91.375 137.125 89 138.625 86.5 140.125 84.125 141.75 81.625 143.375 79.375 145.125 77 146.75 75.125 148 73.25 149.375 71.25 150.625 68.125 152.75 65 154.875 61.75 156.875 60.5 157.625 59.375 158.5 58.125 159.125 57.5 159.5 58.875 158.625 58.375 159 45.25 168.25 47.5 167 54.625 161.5 51.5 163.875 41.375 171.125 38.25 173.625 35.625 175.75 38.375 173.25 35.5 175.625 34.125 173.625 32.625 171.75 31.5 169.625 29.5 166.125 27.75 162.5 26 158.875 25.25 157.375 24.625 155.875 24.125 154.375 23.375 152 22.625 149.625 22 147.375 21.5 145.125 22 144.375 23.875 143.375 26.875 141.875 29.75 140 32.625 138.375 35.25 136.875 37.875 135.375 40.375 133.875 44.375 131.5 48.375 129.125 52.375 126.75 54.75 125.375 57.25 124 59.625 122.625 62.5 120.875 65.5 119.125 68.375 117.375 70.625 116 73 114.75 75.25 113.375 78.625 111.375 81.875 109.5 85.125 107.625 87.875 106 90.75 104.5 93.375 102.875 95.875 101.375 98.375 99.75 100.75 98.375 102.75 97.25 104.75 96.25 106.625 95.125 109.25 93.625 111.75 92 114.375 90.5 116.5 89.25 118.625 88 120.75 86.75 124.25 84.625 127.75 82.625 131.25 80.625 133.875 79.125 136.625 77.625 139.25 76.125 140.125 75.625 140.875 75.125 141.625 74.375 139.625 75.375 137.5 76.375 135.5 77.5 134.25 78.125 133.25 79.125 132 79.75 126.75 82.75 121.375 85.5 116.125 88.5 111.5 91 106.75 93.625 102.125 96.25 97.5 98.875 93 101.625 88.375 104.25 86.875 105.25 85.25 105.875 83.625 106.75 80.375 108.625 77.125 110.5 73.75 112.375 71.25 113.875 68.625 115.125 66 116.625 62.875 118.375 59.75 120.125 56.625 122 53.25 123.875 49.875 125.75 46.5 127.625 43.625 129.25 40.625 130.75 37.75 132.375 35.875 133.375 34 134.375 32 135.625 31.625 132.5 31.125 129.75 30.875 126.875 30.5 123.25 30 119.625 30.125 116 30.375 110.75 31 105.5 31.875 100.25 32.75 95.875 34.125 91.5 35.625 87.25 37.125 83 39 79 41.25 75.25 43.75 70.875 46.75 66.875 49.75 63 52.125 59.875 54.875 57.125 57.625 54.375 60 52.125 62.5 49.875 65.25 48 69.25 45.25 73.375 42.5 77.75 40.25 81.625 38.25 85.75 37.125 89.75 35.5 95 33.25 100.625 32.625 106.25 31.75 111.75 30.75 117.375 31 123 31.25 127.25 31.375 131.5 32.125 135.625 33.125 139.5 34 143.25 35.25 147 36.625 150.25 38 153.375 39.75 156.625 41.25 158.25 42.125 160 42.875 161.625 44 164.25 45.75 166.75 47.625 169.375 49.5 171.125 50.75 172.75 52.125 174.5 53.625 174.875 54 175.125 54.5 175.75 55.375 171.75 57.5 168 59.625 164.125 61.75 165.625 63.375 167.25 65 168.75 66.625 169.5 67.375 170.125 68.125 170.625 69 170.75 69.25 170.5 70 170.25 70.125 166.375 73.125 162.5 75.875 158.75 78.875 156.875 80.25 155.375 82 153.5 83.375 151.625 85 149.5 86.375 147.625 87.875 145.5 89.5 143.375 91 141.375 92.625 139 94.375 136.75 96.25 134.5 98.125 132.625 99.625 130.75 101.125 128.875 102.625 128.25 103.125 127.625 103.375 127 103.75 127.125 104 127.25 104.125 127.25 104.25 131.25 101.5 135.125 98.75 139 96 141.375 94.5 143.75 93.125 146.125 91.5 148.75 89.875 151.25 88 153.875 86.375 158.375 83.25 163 80.125 167.625 77 169.75 75.625 172 74.25 174.25 72.875 177 71 179.625 69.125 182.25 67.25 184.25 65.875 186.375 64.625 188.375 63.25 190.375 61.875 192.25 60.625 194.25 59.25 195.25 58.625 196 58.5 196.75 59.75 197.375 61 198.375 62 199.125 63.25 199.375 63.75 199.25 64.75 198.875 65 197 66.5 195 67.75 193 69 190.375 70.875 187.75 72.625 185.125 74.5 184.875 74.75 184.875 75.75 185.125 76.25 186.875 79.875 189 83.375 190.625 87.125 192.375 91.625 193.75 96.125 194.875 100.75 195.875 104.875 196.375 109 197 113.125 197 113.625 196.375 114.5 195.875 114.75 192.125 116.875 188.375 118.875 184.5 120.875 179.625 123.5 174.625 126 169.875 128.625 164.5 131.5 159.375 134.5 154.125 137.375 150.375 139.5 146.5 141.375 142.75 143.5 139.875 145.125 137 146.75 134.125 148.375 132.125 149.5 130.125 150.375 128.125 151.5 124.125 153.625 120.125 155.875 116 158.125 113.125 159.625 110.25 161.125 107.5 162.625 104.375 164.25 101.375 166 98.25 167.75 96.875 168.5 95.375 169.25 93.875 170 89.75 172.125 85.625 174.375 81.5 176.5 79 177.875 76.375 179.125 73.875 180.5 69.875 182.75 66 185 62 187.25 60.875 187.875 59.625 188.375 58 189.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}m 26.375 141.5 b 83.75 110.625 144.125 78.125 202.25 46.875 203.875 54.125 206.875 60.875 206.875 67.875 206.875 72.375 205.375 72.25 204.125 72.875 189.875 79.25 175.75 83.75 161.375 90 120.75 107.75 80.125 125.5 39.5 143.25 30.75 147.125 32.125 150.5 26.375 141.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H37BA71&\p1}m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&HFFFFFF&\p1}m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0)\fade(1000,1000)\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp-0.853\fs21.333\fn微软雅黑\b0\pos(66.003,22.858)}O{\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&}range
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.62,0:20:35.62,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0\\fade(1000,1000))\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp2.133\fs19.2\b0\pos(66.203,47.524)}字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\pos(20.267,27.447)}m 65 187.5 b 69.625 185 73.75 182.875 77.75 180.75 82.875 178 87.75 175 92.875 172.25 95.75 170.625 98.875 169.25 101.75 167.625 105.75 165.375 109.75 163.125 113.75 161 116.5 159.375 119.5 158 122.25 156.5 125.25 154.875 128.125 153.125 131.125 151.5 133.125 150.5 135.125 149.5 137 148.5 140.125 146.875 143.125 145 146.25 143.375 149 141.875 151.75 140.625 154.5 139.125 157.375 137.5 160.25 135.875 163.125 134.25 164.75 133.375 166.375 132.5 167.875 131.625 172.25 129.25 176.625 126.875 181 124.5 184.125 122.875 187.375 121.375 190.5 119.625 194.5 117.5 198.375 115.125 202.375 113 202.75 112.75 203.25 112.375 203.625 112.25 203.625 117.375 203.875 122.75 203.5 127.625 203.125 131.75 202.375 135.875 201.375 140 200.25 144.5 199 149.125 196.75 153.25 195 156.625 193.75 160.375 191.75 163.625 190 166.75 187.75 169.5 185.75 172.375 184.75 173.875 183.75 175.375 182.5 176.625 181 178.25 179.375 179.75 177.875 181.25 176.125 182.875 174.5 184.625 172.75 186.125 171.375 187.25 169.875 188.375 168.375 189.375 165 191.5 161.625 193.75 158.125 195.875 156.375 197 154.25 197.75 152.25 198.5 149.75 199.625 147.125 200.75 144.5 201.75 143.875 202 143 202 142.25 202.25 136.625 204.125 130.875 205 124.875 205.25 121.125 205.375 117.375 206 113.75 205.75 108.5 205.375 103.25 204.625 98 203.625 94.375 202.875 90.75 201.625 87.25 200.25 83.75 198.875 80.25 197 77 195.25 74.125 193.75 71.5 192.125 68.75 190.375 67.5 189.625 66.5 188.625 65 187.5 m 58 189.125 b 53.875 185.125 49.625 180.875 45.25 176.625 48.5 174.25 51.25 172.375 54 170.25 58 167.25 61.875 164.125 65.875 161.125 68 159.5 70.375 158.125 72.5 156.5 75.375 154.25 78.125 152 81 149.75 83.75 147.625 86.625 145.625 89.375 143.5 91.75 141.625 94.25 139.875 96.625 138 98.5 136.625 100.5 135.25 102.375 133.75 106.25 130.875 110 127.875 113.875 125 116 123.375 118.125 121.875 120.25 120.25 123.375 118 126.375 115.625 129.5 113.25 131.625 111.75 133.75 110.25 135.875 108.75 138.125 107 140.25 105.25 142.5 103.5 144.125 102.375 145.75 101.25 147 99.75 143.625 102.125 140.25 104.5 136.75 106.875 134.5 108.375 132.25 109.625 130 111.125 126.625 113.375 123.375 115.75 120 118 117.625 119.625 115.125 121 112.625 122.625 110.375 124.25 108.125 126 105.75 127.5 103.75 129 101.625 130.375 99.625 131.75 96.875 133.5 94.125 135.25 91.375 137.125 89 138.625 86.5 140.125 84.125 141.75 81.625 143.375 79.375 145.125 77 146.75 75.125 148 73.25 149.375 71.25 150.625 68.125 152.75 65 154.875 61.75 156.875 60.5 157.625 59.375 158.5 58.125 159.125 57.5 159.5 58.875 158.625 58.375 159 45.25 168.25 47.5 167 54.625 161.5 51.5 163.875 41.375 171.125 38.25 173.625 35.625 175.75 38.375 173.25 35.5 175.625 34.125 173.625 32.625 171.75 31.5 169.625 29.5 166.125 27.75 162.5 26 158.875 25.25 157.375 24.625 155.875 24.125 154.375 23.375 152 22.625 149.625 22 147.375 21.5 145.125 22 144.375 23.875 143.375 26.875 141.875 29.75 140 32.625 138.375 35.25 136.875 37.875 135.375 40.375 133.875 44.375 131.5 48.375 129.125 52.375 126.75 54.75 125.375 57.25 124 59.625 122.625 62.5 120.875 65.5 119.125 68.375 117.375 70.625 116 73 114.75 75.25 113.375 78.625 111.375 81.875 109.5 85.125 107.625 87.875 106 90.75 104.5 93.375 102.875 95.875 101.375 98.375 99.75 100.75 98.375 102.75 97.25 104.75 96.25 106.625 95.125 109.25 93.625 111.75 92 114.375 90.5 116.5 89.25 118.625 88 120.75 86.75 124.25 84.625 127.75 82.625 131.25 80.625 133.875 79.125 136.625 77.625 139.25 76.125 140.125 75.625 140.875 75.125 141.625 74.375 139.625 75.375 137.5 76.375 135.5 77.5 134.25 78.125 133.25 79.125 132 79.75 126.75 82.75 121.375 85.5 116.125 88.5 111.5 91 106.75 93.625 102.125 96.25 97.5 98.875 93 101.625 88.375 104.25 86.875 105.25 85.25 105.875 83.625 106.75 80.375 108.625 77.125 110.5 73.75 112.375 71.25 113.875 68.625 115.125 66 116.625 62.875 118.375 59.75 120.125 56.625 122 53.25 123.875 49.875 125.75 46.5 127.625 43.625 129.25 40.625 130.75 37.75 132.375 35.875 133.375 34 134.375 32 135.625 31.625 132.5 31.125 129.75 30.875 126.875 30.5 123.25 30 119.625 30.125 116 30.375 110.75 31 105.5 31.875 100.25 32.75 95.875 34.125 91.5 35.625 87.25 37.125 83 39 79 41.25 75.25 43.75 70.875 46.75 66.875 49.75 63 52.125 59.875 54.875 57.125 57.625 54.375 60 52.125 62.5 49.875 65.25 48 69.25 45.25 73.375 42.5 77.75 40.25 81.625 38.25 85.75 37.125 89.75 35.5 95 33.25 100.625 32.625 106.25 31.75 111.75 30.75 117.375 31 123 31.25 127.25 31.375 131.5 32.125 135.625 33.125 139.5 34 143.25 35.25 147 36.625 150.25 38 153.375 39.75 156.625 41.25 158.25 42.125 160 42.875 161.625 44 164.25 45.75 166.75 47.625 169.375 49.5 171.125 50.75 172.75 52.125 174.5 53.625 174.875 54 175.125 54.5 175.75 55.375 171.75 57.5 168 59.625 164.125 61.75 165.625 63.375 167.25 65 168.75 66.625 169.5 67.375 170.125 68.125 170.625 69 170.75 69.25 170.5 70 170.25 70.125 166.375 73.125 162.5 75.875 158.75 78.875 156.875 80.25 155.375 82 153.5 83.375 151.625 85 149.5 86.375 147.625 87.875 145.5 89.5 143.375 91 141.375 92.625 139 94.375 136.75 96.25 134.5 98.125 132.625 99.625 130.75 101.125 128.875 102.625 128.25 103.125 127.625 103.375 127 103.75 127.125 104 127.25 104.125 127.25 104.25 131.25 101.5 135.125 98.75 139 96 141.375 94.5 143.75 93.125 146.125 91.5 148.75 89.875 151.25 88 153.875 86.375 158.375 83.25 163 80.125 167.625 77 169.75 75.625 172 74.25 174.25 72.875 177 71 179.625 69.125 182.25 67.25 184.25 65.875 186.375 64.625 188.375 63.25 190.375 61.875 192.25 60.625 194.25 59.25 195.25 58.625 196 58.5 196.75 59.75 197.375 61 198.375 62 199.125 63.25 199.375 63.75 199.25 64.75 198.875 65 197 66.5 195 67.75 193 69 190.375 70.875 187.75 72.625 185.125 74.5 184.875 74.75 184.875 75.75 185.125 76.25 186.875 79.875 189 83.375 190.625 87.125 192.375 91.625 193.75 96.125 194.875 100.75 195.875 104.875 196.375 109 197 113.125 197 113.625 196.375 114.5 195.875 114.75 192.125 116.875 188.375 118.875 184.5 120.875 179.625 123.5 174.625 126 169.875 128.625 164.5 131.5 159.375 134.5 154.125 137.375 150.375 139.5 146.5 141.375 142.75 143.5 139.875 145.125 137 146.75 134.125 148.375 132.125 149.5 130.125 150.375 128.125 151.5 124.125 153.625 120.125 155.875 116 158.125 113.125 159.625 110.25 161.125 107.5 162.625 104.375 164.25 101.375 166 98.25 167.75 96.875 168.5 95.375 169.25 93.875 170 89.75 172.125 85.625 174.375 81.5 176.5 79 177.875 76.375 179.125 73.875 180.5 69.875 182.75 66 185 62 187.25 60.875 187.875 59.625 188.375 58 189.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}m 26.375 141.5 b 83.75 110.625 144.125 78.125 202.25 46.875 203.875 54.125 206.875 60.875 206.875 67.875 206.875 72.375 205.375 72.25 204.125 72.875 189.875 79.25 175.75 83.75 161.375 90 120.75 107.75 80.125 125.5 39.5 143.25 30.75 147.125 32.125 150.5 26.375 141.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H37BA71&\p1}m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx18.75\fscy25\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(20.267,27.447)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&HFFFFFF&\p1}m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0)\fade(1000,1000)\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp-0.853\fs21.333\fn微软雅黑\b0\pos(66.003,22.858)}O{\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&}range
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.64,0:42:27.69,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\frx0\fry0\t(2000,5000,\frx360\fry0\\fade(1000,1000))\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp2.133\fs19.2\b0\pos(66.203,47.524)}字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp-0.853\fs32\fn微软雅黑\b0\pos(207.818,130.641)}{\fs26.667}欢迎关注微信公众号 \N{\c&HDDDDDD&}{\fs21.333}搜索  {\c&H017BAD&}{\fs26.667}o_meiju
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.64\fs14.933\pos(208.938,173.947)}{\fs26.667\c&H0471E1&}或微博{\c&HF0F0F0&} {\fs21.333}@{\c&H0471E1&} {\fs21.333}Orange字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\pos(103.019,137.395)}m 65 187.5 b 69.625 185 73.75 182.875 77.75 180.75 82.875 178 87.75 175 92.875 172.25 95.75 170.625 98.875 169.25 101.75 167.625 105.75 165.375 109.75 163.125 113.75 161 116.5 159.375 119.5 158 122.25 156.5 125.25 154.875 128.125 153.125 131.125 151.5 133.125 150.5 135.125 149.5 137 148.5 140.125 146.875 143.125 145 146.25 143.375 149 141.875 151.75 140.625 154.5 139.125 157.375 137.5 160.25 135.875 163.125 134.25 164.75 133.375 166.375 132.5 167.875 131.625 172.25 129.25 176.625 126.875 181 124.5 184.125 122.875 187.375 121.375 190.5 119.625 194.5 117.5 198.375 115.125 202.375 113 202.75 112.75 203.25 112.375 203.625 112.25 203.625 117.375 203.875 122.75 203.5 127.625 203.125 131.75 202.375 135.875 201.375 140 200.25 144.5 199 149.125 196.75 153.25 195 156.625 193.75 160.375 191.75 163.625 190 166.75 187.75 169.5 185.75 172.375 184.75 173.875 183.75 175.375 182.5 176.625 181 178.25 179.375 179.75 177.875 181.25 176.125 182.875 174.5 184.625 172.75 186.125 171.375 187.25 169.875 188.375 168.375 189.375 165 191.5 161.625 193.75 158.125 195.875 156.375 197 154.25 197.75 152.25 198.5 149.75 199.625 147.125 200.75 144.5 201.75 143.875 202 143 202 142.25 202.25 136.625 204.125 130.875 205 124.875 205.25 121.125 205.375 117.375 206 113.75 205.75 108.5 205.375 103.25 204.625 98 203.625 94.375 202.875 90.75 201.625 87.25 200.25 83.75 198.875 80.25 197 77 195.25 74.125 193.75 71.5 192.125 68.75 190.375 67.5 189.625 66.5 188.625 65 187.5 m 58 189.125 b 53.875 185.125 49.625 180.875 45.25 176.625 48.5 174.25 51.25 172.375 54 170.25 58 167.25 61.875 164.125 65.875 161.125 68 159.5 70.375 158.125 72.5 156.5 75.375 154.25 78.125 152 81 149.75 83.75 147.625 86.625 145.625 89.375 143.5 91.75 141.625 94.25 139.875 96.625 138 98.5 136.625 100.5 135.25 102.375 133.75 106.25 130.875 110 127.875 113.875 125 116 123.375 118.125 121.875 120.25 120.25 123.375 118 126.375 115.625 129.5 113.25 131.625 111.75 133.75 110.25 135.875 108.75 138.125 107 140.25 105.25 142.5 103.5 144.125 102.375 145.75 101.25 147 99.75 143.625 102.125 140.25 104.5 136.75 106.875 134.5 108.375 132.25 109.625 130 111.125 126.625 113.375 123.375 115.75 120 118 117.625 119.625 115.125 121 112.625 122.625 110.375 124.25 108.125 126 105.75 127.5 103.75 129 101.625 130.375 99.625 131.75 96.875 133.5 94.125 135.25 91.375 137.125 89 138.625 86.5 140.125 84.125 141.75 81.625 143.375 79.375 145.125 77 146.75 75.125 148 73.25 149.375 71.25 150.625 68.125 152.75 65 154.875 61.75 156.875 60.5 157.625 59.375 158.5 58.125 159.125 57.5 159.5 58.875 158.625 58.375 159 45.25 168.25 47.5 167 54.625 161.5 51.5 163.875 41.375 171.125 38.25 173.625 35.625 175.75 38.375 173.25 35.5 175.625 34.125 173.625 32.625 171.75 31.5 169.625 29.5 166.125 27.75 162.5 26 158.875 25.25 157.375 24.625 155.875 24.125 154.375 23.375 152 22.625 149.625 22 147.375 21.5 145.125 22 144.375 23.875 143.375 26.875 141.875 29.75 140 32.625 138.375 35.25 136.875 37.875 135.375 40.375 133.875 44.375 131.5 48.375 129.125 52.375 126.75 54.75 125.375 57.25 124 59.625 122.625 62.5 120.875 65.5 119.125 68.375 117.375 70.625 116 73 114.75 75.25 113.375 78.625 111.375 81.875 109.5 85.125 107.625 87.875 106 90.75 104.5 93.375 102.875 95.875 101.375 98.375 99.75 100.75 98.375 102.75 97.25 104.75 96.25 106.625 95.125 109.25 93.625 111.75 92 114.375 90.5 116.5 89.25 118.625 88 120.75 86.75 124.25 84.625 127.75 82.625 131.25 80.625 133.875 79.125 136.625 77.625 139.25 76.125 140.125 75.625 140.875 75.125 141.625 74.375 139.625 75.375 137.5 76.375 135.5 77.5 134.25 78.125 133.25 79.125 132 79.75 126.75 82.75 121.375 85.5 116.125 88.5 111.5 91 106.75 93.625 102.125 96.25 97.5 98.875 93 101.625 88.375 104.25 86.875 105.25 85.25 105.875 83.625 106.75 80.375 108.625 77.125 110.5 73.75 112.375 71.25 113.875 68.625 115.125 66 116.625 62.875 118.375 59.75 120.125 56.625 122 53.25 123.875 49.875 125.75 46.5 127.625 43.625 129.25 40.625 130.75 37.75 132.375 35.875 133.375 34 134.375 32 135.625 31.625 132.5 31.125 129.75 30.875 126.875 30.5 123.25 30 119.625 30.125 116 30.375 110.75 31 105.5 31.875 100.25 32.75 95.875 34.125 91.5 35.625 87.25 37.125 83 39 79 41.25 75.25 43.75 70.875 46.75 66.875 49.75 63 52.125 59.875 54.875 57.125 57.625 54.375 60 52.125 62.5 49.875 65.25 48 69.25 45.25 73.375 42.5 77.75 40.25 81.625 38.25 85.75 37.125 89.75 35.5 95 33.25 100.625 32.625 106.25 31.75 111.75 30.75 117.375 31 123 31.25 127.25 31.375 131.5 32.125 135.625 33.125 139.5 34 143.25 35.25 147 36.625 150.25 38 153.375 39.75 156.625 41.25 158.25 42.125 160 42.875 161.625 44 164.25 45.75 166.75 47.625 169.375 49.5 171.125 50.75 172.75 52.125 174.5 53.625 174.875 54 175.125 54.5 175.75 55.375 171.75 57.5 168 59.625 164.125 61.75 165.625 63.375 167.25 65 168.75 66.625 169.5 67.375 170.125 68.125 170.625 69 170.75 69.25 170.5 70 170.25 70.125 166.375 73.125 162.5 75.875 158.75 78.875 156.875 80.25 155.375 82 153.5 83.375 151.625 85 149.5 86.375 147.625 87.875 145.5 89.5 143.375 91 141.375 92.625 139 94.375 136.75 96.25 134.5 98.125 132.625 99.625 130.75 101.125 128.875 102.625 128.25 103.125 127.625 103.375 127 103.75 127.125 104 127.25 104.125 127.25 104.25 131.25 101.5 135.125 98.75 139 96 141.375 94.5 143.75 93.125 146.125 91.5 148.75 89.875 151.25 88 153.875 86.375 158.375 83.25 163 80.125 167.625 77 169.75 75.625 172 74.25 174.25 72.875 177 71 179.625 69.125 182.25 67.25 184.25 65.875 186.375 64.625 188.375 63.25 190.375 61.875 192.25 60.625 194.25 59.25 195.25 58.625 196 58.5 196.75 59.75 197.375 61 198.375 62 199.125 63.25 199.375 63.75 199.25 64.75 198.875 65 197 66.5 195 67.75 193 69 190.375 70.875 187.75 72.625 185.125 74.5 184.875 74.75 184.875 75.75 185.125 76.25 186.875 79.875 189 83.375 190.625 87.125 192.375 91.625 193.75 96.125 194.875 100.75 195.875 104.875 196.375 109 197 113.125 197 113.625 196.375 114.5 195.875 114.75 192.125 116.875 188.375 118.875 184.5 120.875 179.625 123.5 174.625 126 169.875 128.625 164.5 131.5 159.375 134.5 154.125 137.375 150.375 139.5 146.5 141.375 142.75 143.5 139.875 145.125 137 146.75 134.125 148.375 132.125 149.5 130.125 150.375 128.125 151.5 124.125 153.625 120.125 155.875 116 158.125 113.125 159.625 110.25 161.125 107.5 162.625 104.375 164.25 101.375 166 98.25 167.75 96.875 168.5 95.375 169.25 93.875 170 89.75 172.125 85.625 174.375 81.5 176.5 79 177.875 76.375 179.125 73.875 180.5 69.875 182.75 66 185 62 187.25 60.875 187.875 59.625 188.375 58 189.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(103.019,137.395)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}m 26.375 141.5 b 83.75 110.625 144.125 78.125 202.25 46.875 203.875 54.125 206.875 60.875 206.875 67.875 206.875 72.375 205.375 72.25 204.125 72.875 189.875 79.25 175.75 83.75 161.375 90 120.75 107.75 80.125 125.5 39.5 143.25 30.75 147.125 32.125 150.5 26.375 141.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(103.019,137.395)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H37BA71&\p1}m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.89,0:41:48.89,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,200)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(103.019,137.395)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&HFFFFFF&\p1}m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\1c&H00B4FF&\fsp-0.853\fs32\fn微软雅黑\b0\pos(205.226,211.623)}O{\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&}range 字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\c&HFFFFFF&\fsp-0.64\fs14.933\pos(207.306,237.01)}更多精彩请访问 www.{\c&H0C82F8&}orangesub{\c&HFFFFFF&}.com
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\pos(107.787,205.791)}m 65 187.5 b 69.625 185 73.75 182.875 77.75 180.75 82.875 178 87.75 175 92.875 172.25 95.75 170.625 98.875 169.25 101.75 167.625 105.75 165.375 109.75 163.125 113.75 161 116.5 159.375 119.5 158 122.25 156.5 125.25 154.875 128.125 153.125 131.125 151.5 133.125 150.5 135.125 149.5 137 148.5 140.125 146.875 143.125 145 146.25 143.375 149 141.875 151.75 140.625 154.5 139.125 157.375 137.5 160.25 135.875 163.125 134.25 164.75 133.375 166.375 132.5 167.875 131.625 172.25 129.25 176.625 126.875 181 124.5 184.125 122.875 187.375 121.375 190.5 119.625 194.5 117.5 198.375 115.125 202.375 113 202.75 112.75 203.25 112.375 203.625 112.25 203.625 117.375 203.875 122.75 203.5 127.625 203.125 131.75 202.375 135.875 201.375 140 200.25 144.5 199 149.125 196.75 153.25 195 156.625 193.75 160.375 191.75 163.625 190 166.75 187.75 169.5 185.75 172.375 184.75 173.875 183.75 175.375 182.5 176.625 181 178.25 179.375 179.75 177.875 181.25 176.125 182.875 174.5 184.625 172.75 186.125 171.375 187.25 169.875 188.375 168.375 189.375 165 191.5 161.625 193.75 158.125 195.875 156.375 197 154.25 197.75 152.25 198.5 149.75 199.625 147.125 200.75 144.5 201.75 143.875 202 143 202 142.25 202.25 136.625 204.125 130.875 205 124.875 205.25 121.125 205.375 117.375 206 113.75 205.75 108.5 205.375 103.25 204.625 98 203.625 94.375 202.875 90.75 201.625 87.25 200.25 83.75 198.875 80.25 197 77 195.25 74.125 193.75 71.5 192.125 68.75 190.375 67.5 189.625 66.5 188.625 65 187.5 m 58 189.125 b 53.875 185.125 49.625 180.875 45.25 176.625 48.5 174.25 51.25 172.375 54 170.25 58 167.25 61.875 164.125 65.875 161.125 68 159.5 70.375 158.125 72.5 156.5 75.375 154.25 78.125 152 81 149.75 83.75 147.625 86.625 145.625 89.375 143.5 91.75 141.625 94.25 139.875 96.625 138 98.5 136.625 100.5 135.25 102.375 133.75 106.25 130.875 110 127.875 113.875 125 116 123.375 118.125 121.875 120.25 120.25 123.375 118 126.375 115.625 129.5 113.25 131.625 111.75 133.75 110.25 135.875 108.75 138.125 107 140.25 105.25 142.5 103.5 144.125 102.375 145.75 101.25 147 99.75 143.625 102.125 140.25 104.5 136.75 106.875 134.5 108.375 132.25 109.625 130 111.125 126.625 113.375 123.375 115.75 120 118 117.625 119.625 115.125 121 112.625 122.625 110.375 124.25 108.125 126 105.75 127.5 103.75 129 101.625 130.375 99.625 131.75 96.875 133.5 94.125 135.25 91.375 137.125 89 138.625 86.5 140.125 84.125 141.75 81.625 143.375 79.375 145.125 77 146.75 75.125 148 73.25 149.375 71.25 150.625 68.125 152.75 65 154.875 61.75 156.875 60.5 157.625 59.375 158.5 58.125 159.125 57.5 159.5 58.875 158.625 58.375 159 45.25 168.25 47.5 167 54.625 161.5 51.5 163.875 41.375 171.125 38.25 173.625 35.625 175.75 38.375 173.25 35.5 175.625 34.125 173.625 32.625 171.75 31.5 169.625 29.5 166.125 27.75 162.5 26 158.875 25.25 157.375 24.625 155.875 24.125 154.375 23.375 152 22.625 149.625 22 147.375 21.5 145.125 22 144.375 23.875 143.375 26.875 141.875 29.75 140 32.625 138.375 35.25 136.875 37.875 135.375 40.375 133.875 44.375 131.5 48.375 129.125 52.375 126.75 54.75 125.375 57.25 124 59.625 122.625 62.5 120.875 65.5 119.125 68.375 117.375 70.625 116 73 114.75 75.25 113.375 78.625 111.375 81.875 109.5 85.125 107.625 87.875 106 90.75 104.5 93.375 102.875 95.875 101.375 98.375 99.75 100.75 98.375 102.75 97.25 104.75 96.25 106.625 95.125 109.25 93.625 111.75 92 114.375 90.5 116.5 89.25 118.625 88 120.75 86.75 124.25 84.625 127.75 82.625 131.25 80.625 133.875 79.125 136.625 77.625 139.25 76.125 140.125 75.625 140.875 75.125 141.625 74.375 139.625 75.375 137.5 76.375 135.5 77.5 134.25 78.125 133.25 79.125 132 79.75 126.75 82.75 121.375 85.5 116.125 88.5 111.5 91 106.75 93.625 102.125 96.25 97.5 98.875 93 101.625 88.375 104.25 86.875 105.25 85.25 105.875 83.625 106.75 80.375 108.625 77.125 110.5 73.75 112.375 71.25 113.875 68.625 115.125 66 116.625 62.875 118.375 59.75 120.125 56.625 122 53.25 123.875 49.875 125.75 46.5 127.625 43.625 129.25 40.625 130.75 37.75 132.375 35.875 133.375 34 134.375 32 135.625 31.625 132.5 31.125 129.75 30.875 126.875 30.5 123.25 30 119.625 30.125 116 30.375 110.75 31 105.5 31.875 100.25 32.75 95.875 34.125 91.5 35.625 87.25 37.125 83 39 79 41.25 75.25 43.75 70.875 46.75 66.875 49.75 63 52.125 59.875 54.875 57.125 57.625 54.375 60 52.125 62.5 49.875 65.25 48 69.25 45.25 73.375 42.5 77.75 40.25 81.625 38.25 85.75 37.125 89.75 35.5 95 33.25 100.625 32.625 106.25 31.75 111.75 30.75 117.375 31 123 31.25 127.25 31.375 131.5 32.125 135.625 33.125 139.5 34 143.25 35.25 147 36.625 150.25 38 153.375 39.75 156.625 41.25 158.25 42.125 160 42.875 161.625 44 164.25 45.75 166.75 47.625 169.375 49.5 171.125 50.75 172.75 52.125 174.5 53.625 174.875 54 175.125 54.5 175.75 55.375 171.75 57.5 168 59.625 164.125 61.75 165.625 63.375 167.25 65 168.75 66.625 169.5 67.375 170.125 68.125 170.625 69 170.75 69.25 170.5 70 170.25 70.125 166.375 73.125 162.5 75.875 158.75 78.875 156.875 80.25 155.375 82 153.5 83.375 151.625 85 149.5 86.375 147.625 87.875 145.5 89.5 143.375 91 141.375 92.625 139 94.375 136.75 96.25 134.5 98.125 132.625 99.625 130.75 101.125 128.875 102.625 128.25 103.125 127.625 103.375 127 103.75 127.125 104 127.25 104.125 127.25 104.25 131.25 101.5 135.125 98.75 139 96 141.375 94.5 143.75 93.125 146.125 91.5 148.75 89.875 151.25 88 153.875 86.375 158.375 83.25 163 80.125 167.625 77 169.75 75.625 172 74.25 174.25 72.875 177 71 179.625 69.125 182.25 67.25 184.25 65.875 186.375 64.625 188.375 63.25 190.375 61.875 192.25 60.625 194.25 59.25 195.25 58.625 196 58.5 196.75 59.75 197.375 61 198.375 62 199.125 63.25 199.375 63.75 199.25 64.75 198.875 65 197 66.5 195 67.75 193 69 190.375 70.875 187.75 72.625 185.125 74.5 184.875 74.75 184.875 75.75 185.125 76.25 186.875 79.875 189 83.375 190.625 87.125 192.375 91.625 193.75 96.125 194.875 100.75 195.875 104.875 196.375 109 197 113.125 197 113.625 196.375 114.5 195.875 114.75 192.125 116.875 188.375 118.875 184.5 120.875 179.625 123.5 174.625 126 169.875 128.625 164.5 131.5 159.375 134.5 154.125 137.375 150.375 139.5 146.5 141.375 142.75 143.5 139.875 145.125 137 146.75 134.125 148.375 132.125 149.5 130.125 150.375 128.125 151.5 124.125 153.625 120.125 155.875 116 158.125 113.125 159.625 110.25 161.125 107.5 162.625 104.375 164.25 101.375 166 98.25 167.75 96.875 168.5 95.375 169.25 93.875 170 89.75 172.125 85.625 174.375 81.5 176.5 79 177.875 76.375 179.125 73.875 180.5 69.875 182.75 66 185 62 187.25 60.875 187.875 59.625 188.375 58 189.125{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(107.787,205.791)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H196FEC&\p1}m 26.375 141.5 b 83.75 110.625 144.125 78.125 202.25 46.875 203.875 54.125 206.875 60.875 206.875 67.875 206.875 72.375 205.375 72.25 204.125 72.875 189.875 79.25 175.75 83.75 161.375 90 120.75 107.75 80.125 125.5 39.5 143.25 30.75 147.125 32.125 150.5 26.375 141.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(107.787,205.791)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&H37BA71&\p1}m -48.375 2.5 b -44.375 -5.625 -28.5 -8.5 -20.75 -2.875 -23.625 4.625 -39.375 7.75 -48.375 2.5 m -5.25 -56.5 b 5.75 -41.75 -2 -13.75 -14.625 -6.625 -23.875 -14.375 -21.25 -48.125 -5.25 -56.5{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.89,0:41:54.49,LOGO,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,0)\an5\p1比例调这里—>\fscx26.25\fscy35\1c&H00B4FF&\frz0.6327\pos(107.787,205.791)}{\an7\pos(0,0)\1c&HFFFFFF&\p1}m 44.75 -41.75 b 46.25 -41.875 47.5 -42.125 48.875 -42.25 50.125 -42.375 50.625 -41.75 50.75 -40.5 50.75 -38.5 50.375 -38 48.5 -37.875 48.25 -37.875 48 -37.75 47.75 -37.75 46.625 -37.5 45.75 -37.625 45.625 -39.125 45.5 -39.875 45.125 -40.625 44.75 -41.75 m 32.375 -26.375 b 31.375 -30.75 30.375 -35 29.5 -39.25 32.125 -40.875 34.875 -42.375 38.125 -42.25 39.75 -42.25 40.5 -41.75 41 -40.125 42 -37.125 41.75 -34.125 41.5 -31 41.375 -28.875 40.5 -27.75 38.25 -27.5 36.375 -27.375 34.625 -26.75 32.875 -26.375 32.75 -26.375 32.625 -26.375 32.375 -26.375{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.19,0:00:22.19,人员,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\c&H0073FF&}翻译：{\c&HFFFFFF&}呆呆 艾莉 AlexaJU 歪歪船长 一菲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.19,0:00:28.19,人员,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\c&H0073FF&}校对：{\c&HFFFFFF&}olivia {\c&H0073FF&}监制：{\c&HFFFFFF&}呆呆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.19,0:00:34.19,人员,,0,0,0,,{\fade(1000,1000)\c&H0073FF&}后期：{\c&HFFFFFF&}橘子  {\c&H0073FF&}压制：{\c&HFFFFFF&}小疯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.86,0:09:09.32,片头,,0,0,0,,{\fsp2\fs25\c&H029AD0&\bord0\shad0\pos(196.4,189.253)}第三季第十三集(季终集)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.73,0:09:07.81,片头,,0,0,0,,{\b1\fade(200,10,255,0,500,3114,3114)\t(0,1490,\fs80)\t(1482,1524,\fs45\1a&HFF&\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&\4a&HFF&)\t(1657,1698,\c&H025072&\1a&H14&\3a&H14&\4a&H14&)\t(3030,3031,\c&H00588B&)\move(196.8,276,196.9,202.419,1482,1649)}困兽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.49,0:01:44.79,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,600)\fs45\b1\pos(189.3,193.6)}围墙内
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.60,0:04:13.23,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fad(68,0)\fs12\frz2.964\c&HFFEFCB&\b1\move(189.9,110.4,197.8,110.4,694,1611)}是否执行命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.77,0:04:13.23,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fad(68,0)\b1\fs12\c&HB48C64&\frz3.751\move(192.3,130.4,198.4,128,399,1441)}取消     {\c&HF7D4AC&}执行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.82,0:04:21.24,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fs\c&HF9DFBB&\b1\frz355.2\move(232.2,106.8,182.8,112.8,22,1398)}是否执行命令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.82,0:04:21.24,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\\b1\fs12\c&HB48C64&\frz354.6\move(234.6,147.2,176.2,163.6,22,1732)}取消     {\c&HF7D4AC&}执行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.29,0:05:20.80,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\b1\fs16\c&HFFECCF&\frz359.1\move(128.7,18.8,108.4,72.8,0,988)}侦测到信标激活
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.29,0:05:20.80,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fs12\b1\c&HC8F1D6&\move(183.3,25.2,174.4,74.4,0,863)}美国 圣路易斯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.76,0:23:00.02,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\fad(0,600)\fs45\b1\pos(190.2,200)}圣路易斯
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.84,0:33:17.01,硬字幕,,0,0,0,,{\b1\c&HDBFFA0&\frz1.96\pos(251.1,67.2)}信标失效