Hi, Magic, have you been a good boy today?
Oh! I've missed you.
Thank you!
Just a silly old tearjerker!
What about getting dinner for
this hungry man of you
Really you have a heart of stone
Magic, you've been a brave boy today.
How about your favorite for my little here?
It's a tiny burned but you'll forgive me!
Kathy How long is it going to be - I'm starving!
Hang on, just coming!
If you really want to eat
Don't just sit here like a bean bag!
Here try this, my special pork chop noodle.
It's the best of world.
It's only bones; no meat &
what's the hell do with the noodle?
Add half a pound of salt?
Honey, sugar cubes, salt & a spoon.
Help yourself!
Kathy!
Magic, sit.
Don't be so rude
I'm sorry!
You always said you wanted
me to be honest with you?
Just a little advice on ways to improve
your cooking that's all.
Where's my earring.
Have you seen it?
Don't just stand there!
God, where's it!
Never mind, I'll buy you another pair!
No, you don't understand.
This was a birthday gift from my mum before
she moved to the States.
It's irreplaceable. How can I lose it?
Have you kicked it away when you
were watching the football match?
No.
Thanks my little prince.
That dog really gets on my nerves he does
She's a fool for him.
Kathy, this is the most delicious coffee ever.
Don't overdo it.
I didn't make the coffee. It's instant.
You still boiled the water perfectly
to make good coffee.
Liar.
You're still angry?
Let me give you a kiss!
My Magic wants a hug?
I think you like that dog a lot more
than you like me.
Of course, he's not as phoney as you
I'm wrong if I'm honest and I'm wrong if
I exaggerate a little.
What can a guy do?
And you don't make it any easier for me!
Are we good friends, give me some face, OK'?
I've to kiss her.
Maggie, she's my girlfriend alright,
why can't I kiss her?
You're quite a rival, shithead!
Get lost, alright?
Not that dog again! What are you doing to Mary?
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill your dog!
Why don't you keep that dog tied up?
He's always chasing Mary.
He even brought a bone with him today.
He's not very subtle.
I'll cut his balls off.
Magic.
I'm very sorry. It won't happen again.
I'll take care of it, alright?
Haha, well, that's great.
Alright, we'll forget it!
Yes, indeed.
Magic, how could you?
She's a virgin!
They're g0ifl9-
It's too late, they're for the chop!
That's the end of your love-life!
I said took him for a walk.
I didn't ask you to
I did it for your sake.
Look, he won't be a nuisance any more.
Your neighbor's not gonna complain about!
I have to fly to the States and
I want to see my parents.
I won't be back for a week.
I'd like you to take care of Magic.
Here's a list of his needs.
He has a can of "Good Boy" dog food
in the morning and
He has the dried food at night, exercise at 6 pm.
Don't forget.
Oh yes, Jack, just because I'm not here,
don't think you can drink and smoke
with your friends.
You can trust me! I know
you don't like it so I won't do it.
Now listen, Magic, you be a good dog.
Let him take care of you for a few days.
If he doesn't treat you nicely,
complain to me when I get back.
Don't worry, I'll deal with him,
I'll get revenge for you.
Jungle Jungle
It's so comfort
Big-ass, low down please.
They're arrived.
Go and look at yourself.
That's a girl's style.
My mother has never treat me like this before.
What? Does it mean that
I've to obey to your master?
I won't listen, so what?
Follow me.
Ok guys, it's party time.
Let's all get drunk!
Whatever you want, we've got it!
Each for everyone.
Jack, I want it too.
Kathy's only been gone for half an hour
And we're really having a good time together.
But she's left that dog, and he's watching.
PIZZA...
Hey, Magic go away. Leave us alone.
Get away, wretched dog!
He doesn't like all the fun.
Take care he's going to report rat on us.
Go away...
What's all this? Who dealt this damn hand?
Getting ready to lose?
I think I will.
You...
I think he must be hungry. I forget to feed him.
Forget the dog. We're playing a game!
He can wait!
He won't die if he's not fed.
I'll die if we don't start.
What's it?
Nine.
What nine?
Diamond nine.
There's a fire!
My face is on fire.
I must be drunk.
It's a little photo of you and
Lucy kissing each other.
Give me back.
Come, you bastard! Hand it over!
Come on, give it to me!
Go for it, Jack! Lucy wanted
your ass for a long time.
We'll make ourselves at home.
Go & enjoy it!
Hey, drink up!
What are you doing?
Just giving Magic little bit of fun.
Better give him more than that then!
Hey, good show!
The show is soon coming.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Kathy!
I'm Lucy not Kathy!
He couldn't get it up,
and I think it's all your fault.
Alright Lucy, why not let one of us do it!
The 2 dogs have gone!
I'm a happy ghost.
You've just saved my temple.
If not for you then all this could have
gone in smoke.
Happy ghost never remembers bad things.
But I'll always remember my benefactor.
Now you've saved my temple.
I'm indebted to you.
No matter what it is.
I'm going to give you a reward.
Make a wish!
To be a man?
No I'm sorry.
You want me to change fate.
I mustn't fiddle with destiny.
You've be human 1 day - you've got
a lot of karma to burn off first.
Listen it isn't good avoiding karma your know
It always ends in tears.
Listen, what about something else
Wouldn't you rather have a bag of bones?
You sure about this 7
A human?
You're certain?
Alright, and you're totally intent on being human?
I can do it for 49 days,
after that it's dog again.
Are you in agreement?
Nice dog. Nice dog!
Buddha Buddha ...
You can't be naked,
I'll have to find you something to wear.
No, don't sit there begging.
As a man you'll have to stand up.
So, stand up!
You still stand like a dog.
Look, put your paws down
Ah, let's learn do talk.
Now you can start speaking,
open your mouth and try.
You must talk, not bark. It's quite simple.
You just think & say it.
|...
You're not getting it exactly.
Relax! Alright.
Do some different shapes with your mouth.
I'm in .
Pain
Now, maybe this'll encourage you.
And what's your name then?
Magic I
That's badge, or is it magic?
Come on then Magic.
Be careful!
You must remember, you can only remain
a human for 49 days.
One more thing, don't tell anyone
you're really a dog.
It has to remain our secret.
Or
You'll be a duck in your next life.
You got that?
You can't pee against lampposts anymore.
You have to go in there.
Do you miss your mistress while she's away?
Yes.
She hasn't come home yet, we'll return.
Magic, being human isn't easy.
Perhaps you've heard of this,
that is a man works from sun to sun.
While you were a dog, you were safe.
Life was handled for you.
As a man now, you'll have to work.
You need a job.
Work?
I'm not so sure.
No need to worry, it's easy getting a job.
Here.
In you go!
What is it?
Can I work here?
Don't look at me. To him, I'm invisible.
Come on then!
Mr. Chan, this guy wants a job.
Fine, I'll talk to him.
Good evening sir.
Sit down.
Sit straight.
You're sitting like a dog!
No him. I was talking to you!
Listen you nerd, I don't care who
you're talking to, you'll ...
Listen, shut up!
Stop begging, sit down.
What was I saying?
You were asking my name.
Oh right, well, what is it?
I'm called Magic.
Tell him your name's Jacky Chan.
My name's Jacky Chan.
Why sure it is.
You got an ID card?
You're an illegal then.
I'm a hard worker!
As night watchman and cleaner.
A thousand dollars a month.
Do you think you can handle?
How is it?
Well don't let me down.
Alright, go and get started
Up and running.
Well enjoy your time and good luck
as a human being.
Take care.
Hey ... ..you ...
This is what you wanted, you're a human being!
Hey, I need you over there.
Now, pile up these soft drinks.
Hey, come on.
Over there, come.
He's heading for trouble!
Walks like a dog!
Good day sir!
You could learn from him.
Eats like a mouse, works like a horse.
Never answer back, not like you, bunch of duffers.
You guys eat like horses.
Think hard work'll kill you.
And talk all day like a load of starlings
Yes, I'm impressed with him.
This new guy's a winner.
He works his best off but why?
To prove he's better than us, heard what he said.
Let's put an end to it.
Hurry! Don't linger!
Get a move on! That's it keep going.
Don't waste time!
Tired? You look pooped.
Why don't you take a rest.
The guys'|| finish up for you.
Good.
You look thirsty. How about a milk?
No thanks. Water's fine.
No need to drink water.
We can have anything we like.
After all we work here, that's right,
isn't it boys?
Yeah, here!
How about canned fish?
And this!
Eats dog food?
He's from China, they eats dogs there,
he thinks it's canned dog.
Eat up. And take your time.
We'll go and work!
There he is. Look at him sir!
Making it look he's working hard.
And we have to do everything,
all he does is waste time.
You see I wasn't lying. He does nothing!
You waste time? Comes off your pay!
Got it!
What? You lost Magic?
I haven't any idea where he went to.
I woke up and he wasn't with me.
Last time you looked after him you lost his balls.
This time you've gone and lost the whole dog!
I've looked for him everywhere.
Stop the car!
Kathy, look. I'm really sorry!
Where are you going?
Taxi!
Kathy ...
Pal!
Where are you going?
Cousre you don't talk human,
OK I'll talk dog then.
I'm called Magic. And how about you?
I'm Spotty Dick. I guard the pharmacy.
How is it?
It's OK, they're nice people.
So he's finished up.
Look over there.
Do you think what we did to him, upset him?
Well he isn't seen nothing yet.
I agree guy5_
Who are those 3 guys anyway?
Just idiots.
Some people.
Right, not all though. I like my mistress.
Is she kind?
Yeah, very.
The old guy at the pharmacy taught me to do this.
Can you do it?
No. I'm too heavy for that.
But I can catch a ball. Can you do that?
And I've been in a car too!
Who is it?
What are you doing?
Come on guys, stock up!
Let's have some cognac!
Yeah ...
Where's Fatty Turtle'?
Who knows?
Take more!
What? Stealing?
Ghost!
Help! Ghost!
What's the matter!
I did a little bit of ghostly magic,
those guys need a bit lesson.
Let's hope they learned
what's right & what's wrong.
I didn't know people were like that.
Well they aren't all so, don't you worry.
Change me back,
I don't want to be human any more.
Absolutely no way at all.
I asked all that is for special permission.
You haven't even done 1 month
you can't just give up like this.
Come on.
How would I be able to face All the Gods?
You mean I've to stay like this'?
It isn't as bad as all that really.
In a little time you'll get
the hang of it & it'll be just fine.
Happy Ghost!
Pass me that come on.
What's the matter.
You're the matter!
Do you want dog food?
That's right. I don't know which one I want to.
That one's full of gristle, I never want to.
This, here is my favorite.
Full cut prime beef. It's wonderful!
Really? You eat it?
Yeah! It's the best one.
It's got all the nutrition!
Need for a nice wet nose.
And a wiggly tail too.
Excuse me, how much is this please?
I'm sorry, I don't know.
Kathy!
Kathy?
I'm sorry.
Are you blind?
I'll pick it up.
The windows need cleaning - please go & do it!
I'm very sorry boss.
Thank you.
Mummy! Kathy!
Kathy ...
Looks a bit old to have lost his mummy.
Kathy!
Mind what you're doing.
Theft!
Get up
Are you alright?
Is your head alright sir? You'd go to hospital.
I didn't have the chance to find out your name.
My name is Kathy.
I'm Magic.
What coincidence!
Magic was the name of my dog too.
I didn't mean to say that you're a dog.
No really I ...
Alright, Magic be quiet.
Doctor, how is he?
He's fine, just minor wounds.
I'll give an anti-tetanus shot & he'll be OK.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're alright.
I know I caused you all these troubles
& I don't know how to repay you.
To tell you the truth I ...
Here we are.
Thank you.
Didn't you've something to tell me? What's it?
I ...
You'd not tell others the secret, or ...
You'll become a duck in your next life.
I can't tell you or |'ll turn into a duck.
A duck?
Nice car nice dame!
This's during working hours
we'd learn a thing or two from ou.
See you.
Bye bye!
Don't let us hold you up, come on!
What's all this?
You can't just come & go as
you see fit young man.
I can replace you very easily.
But I was in an accident,
it wasn't what you think.
She didn't look like an accident!
We think she's gorgeous!
She had her bag snatched ...
And along came sir Galahad!
Without his armour or his horse?!
You're fired. I don't need to hear anything more.
This's all you get, get out of here.
Get lost ...
But boss ... ..
Alright get your shirt off!
What am I going to do now'?
She'll keep you busy!
Magic, get in, |'ll find
you a better job than this one.
Come on!
Michelle!
Family!
Old friend?
Family?
Is this the guy you told me about
the one who wants a job?
He's a hard worker.
Old friend!
The job is quite easy actually.
You just have to like animals.
But he does have to sleep here as well.
Don't worry, he knows all about that.
He looks like a man after my own heart.
Michelle, Gigi's not well today.
She won't do pee pee or eat.
She ate yesterday?
Yes, her usual chicken & brawn rice.
Yes, you've to be careful.
Let's get her to a vet, maybe its serious.
A vet? Loosen my collar!
Relax.
It's her collar, it's too tight. Let's loosen it.
It's so nice!
It's better!
How did you know'?
I did what she told me.
You've a very strange sense of humor.
I'm happy I can breathe again.
Kid...
What?
Want to eat something?
Eat or not?
No.
A mini typhoon!
Delicious!
Not this again.
Someone is coming.
Maisie's got the grumps,
I don't know what's the matter with her.
Can you help?
What do you expect with that hair style?
I hate it!
She's to wear it like this'd
all the rage over in Italy.
I'm not in Italy!
I hate this hair style.
Yes, but Maisie hates it,
she feels that she looks stupid.
He understands me!
Dogs don't find this beautiful.
Try & imagine being a dog
you'd not like this, right
Right Winston?
It's ugly -'Maisie's a dog not a toy'.
Stupid!
What can I do about it?
First of all, take all these silly clips out.
And let her hair grow naturally.
That's right!
Get her to take this horrible coat off.
I hate this coat! Horrible!
And let me roll in cows hit sometimes
Well, |'ll do what you said
He understands me.
Thanks a lot.
Come on Maisie, let's return
you back into a real dog.
Hi Magic
Michelle.
Hi Kathy
Look, he's amazing.
Aren't you glad you're not a poodle'?
But I wish I was a bit more handsome.
You are handsome!
Really!
That's great! He's been here
for one week & now a raise.
I don't like his dress sense,
those funny old pajama he wears!
If I give you some money.
Can you make him presentable?
Can you read this'?
And so now?
How about now?
Can you see this one?
Why can't you? You must be blind.
What's this?
O...
O right?
O right? So you're blind then.
But I can see the letters,
I don't know what they are.
20 minutes.
Hi!
What's the matter with him?
Smartie!
He kissed me'.!
He is so smart!
I love you
ROSE * MARY
That's the thing with dogs,
they do exactly what they like.
Sir
This restaurant is famous for its steak,
have you ever been here before?
Never, they wouldn't let me in.
Why not?
I... ...I don't have the money.
This time it's my treat.
Their fillet mignon with butter & garlic
is the house specialty here.
Try!
Jack, this is Magic,
the one who got my purse back.
Magic, meet Jack.
Magic, what's the matter'?
Hi!
Have you eaten yet?
Yes I have, don't forget
your playing tennis with me.
Magic, can you play tennis?
Well that settles it, we're going to teach
you how to play.
Madam, anything else.
That's all, thank you.
Waiter, bill please.
Do you still want it?
Magic, your turn.
Jack, won't you let Magic at least try?
Ru play with him.
You're tired anyway, just take a rest.
Magic you go & play a while.
Jack, It's no fun for him sitting here,
you play with him.
Jack will teach you.
OK!
I'll get ice cream.
Serve you right!
I surrender.
Ice cream.
Did you play?
He learns fast. He's almost as good as me.
I've lost my earring again. Help me lind it.
Honey, it's such a big place here.
Let me buy you another pair?
They have sentimental value,
they were from my mother.
So we spend the rest of the evening here.
I know where to find
a pair that's exactly the same.
Nobody could tell the difference.
I could tell the difference
Look! I've found it!
Here it is! Well, is this it?
Yes.
It's been in the drain, it's got to be washed.
We'll go & fetch the car.
Do we've to have that jerk with us for the night?
Here it's clean.
Did you wash it in the swimming pool then?
Thank you!
Jack, just a minute.
Have you lost your key?
Yes, it must be in my other clothes, the old one.
This excuses this guy, comes up with.
So you don't have anywhere to sleep tonight?
Well, he can't stay over at my place
Alright, he can stay over at my place then.
This way.
Don't be shy, just make yourself at home.
Jackie a good guy.
Jack, Magic can sleep in the study I'll fix it up.
Well, I'll do the room later.
I'll take you home first.
It's alright, I'll take a cab,
I'll call you when I'm home.
Goodnight, Magic.
Look after him, won't you?
Yes honey.
Boy, I've to hand it to you,
you may look like a 4-eyed nerd.
From nowhere but you sure know how
to get in on a good thing.
And as for calling yourself
Magic go to the top of the class.
You really scored a lot of brownie points there,
didn't you?
But get this, she's my girl has been for 3 years,
And don't forget it.
Where are you going?
To sleep in the study.
You'll sleep right where you are, the sofa.
You better be warned because I'm serious.
I hate rivals, I'm going to out your balls off.
Just like I did to her dog.
If you hang around her any more.
No need to sleep on the sofa,
why don't you come in the study?
What are you doing here?
I took your key home by mistake, I'm returning it.
Thank you.
Why don't I take you out & help you find a taxi?
What's that?
Jack, while I was away what did you do?
You...
Kathy come back, I can explain!
Look you know I love you Kathy.
What's the matter?
Don't move!
I've been with you for 3 years now.
Kathy, listen, you know I love you.
Listen, I can explain!
I'm not interested in any other girls.
Get away from me.
Stop following me around like a stupid dog.
I'm the dog!
Why you hanging around?
I'm talking to you, not him!
Mel?
You'll regret this, Kathy I promise!
Alright, can't win all.
Come on.
Your place or mine'?
Not you.
Excuse me.
How did you know where my slippers were?
I just guessed, I guess ...
Thank you.
Sit down.
Let me get you something to eat.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Nothing, I've never seen a bed like this before.
It's really a nice bed, isn't it?
There's another one just like
it in the guest room.
Would you mind waiting out there for me?
OK!
Well, eat it.
Should I make you something to go with it'?
No need, I've got this.
I don't know, but when I see you,
you give me this strange feeling,
The feeling, I used to have with my dog Magic.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to compare you to my dog.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, your dog'll come back.
It was all Jackie fault.
If he'd had looked after Magic instead
of fooling around.
It would never have happened.
I never want to see him again.
See you tomorrow.
Why'd I have to apolegise?
She's got to be kidding,
she's not the only lish in the sea.
With my look & charm, straight up,
eat your heart out.
Sleep!
My God, I've to see her!
That makes me look weak though.
No way, do I need aa woman'?
Sleep!
You're here.
Why not? Kathy's here as well.
You mean you never went home last night?
Well of course I didn't, I stayed with her.
I did.
Where did you sleep?
Also. ..
What's it?
We just stept together.
Stept together?
What is it?
What's the meaning of all these noise?
Come here, I need to talk to you, Out!
Lock out big boy?
Come on in.
Why is your bed such a mess'?
And what's this? 2 pillows, why 2 pillows?
Oh you didn't have company in bed, did you?
One for you one for him!
What are you talking about?
Listen to that!
Your voice is all bucky Kathy.
You obviously didn't get any sleep last night!
You are a real ass.
This time you're insulting me & my friend.
What friend?
You hardly know the guy -
what is it a week at the most now.
I've known you for 3 years.
Shut up, we've had 3 years.
But how long have you'd with that woman'?
So you went to bed with that dog to spite me,
did you Kathy?
Get out right now.
I never want to see you again.
I won't! I'm going to stay here.
Out, get out!
You...
Hi, it's you!
I love a man when he's angry.
Would you like to come over
here for a little drink?
No! I wouldn't, what are you? A bitch'?
Get lost!
You stop it!
I'm pretty good at this!
I'm outtalk here.
I'm lucky!
Get away quickly!
Stop it.
No, Kathy, don't throw the fridge,
it's too heavy to kill him.
I just want a drink.
Magic, let's go to a party tonight.
Good heavens, he looks like the dog's dinner.
Kathy did a good job really,
you do look so different.
She even invited me to a party tonight.
Uh? What about Jack?
Excuse me!
I'd like to buy a collar
Of course, These are the new designs from Italy.
It's beatutiful
It's snazzy!
Just a minute.
Can you wrap it up?
Disgusting!
Who does he think he is?
You're just jealous.
You're so handsome!
I like it, take it off my salary.
This one's for Kathy, see you later.
Why are you wearing a dog collar?
You see dogs in sweaters,
why not men in dog collars'?
Why not? Know what it's great!
This one's for you.
Is it a fashion of this year?
Not bad!
And it matches my dress, Thanks.
Hi!
Why not!
What's happened? Who's Kathy with'?
Hey, so who ditched who, Jack?
Gross.
Disgusting.
I'm sorry.
Lucy, would you care to dance?
Thank you.
Jack is really something
Dance with me.
I don't know how to.
Never mind, I'll teach you.
I'm sorry.
Not up there, here.
Good! That's better.
I'm sorry, I've to go to the washroom.
What's it?
Hi Magic, I'm John, a friend of Jack's.
Shake your hand!
I'm George.
John, George.
Like some snails? Delicious!
Go on, dig it.
Yummy
(Wasabi)
Hey, buddy, someone invites you to sing.
Are you interested? Can you sing'?
Jack!
Water at last!
You really are something!
I'm something at least I'm not a dog.
Not like him!
How do you know I'm a dog?
Don't call yourself a dog.
Anyone who jumps into bed with someone
elsefls girlfriend is a dog!
He is a dog!
What did you say?
Sir...
Are you alright?
Come on, let's go.
Are you hurt?
Howl hate him!
You're becoming drunk, too much cognac!
I hate him.
You tell me, what's she got that I haven't got?
You're a nicer girl.
And a lot cuter.
Then why won't he tell the bitch to go?
I'll get you some water.
Vodka
I want cognac!
Drink this water
You lie to me, I hate people who lie.
I didn't really lie.
I just twisted the truth.
The truth is I'm your dog.
D09
I know, you're an old dog?
I'm your dog!
I like dog, dog is faithful.
Kathy ...
Suppertime, guys!
Come 8» ea“!
I'm so hungry!
Here it is, dinner delicious ...
See this!
It's fun being together, I love being a human.
I'm so hHPPY-
| feel happy fOF Yo"-
Me too.
I jealous you.
I envy you.
What do you think.
I don't think it'll workout.
Human are nothing but trouble.
I don't speak dog, what's going on?
Bring me some chicken tomorrow.
Happy Ghost, can you help me please?
Magic, how many times have I said it.
Impossible to be a dog again before your time.
But I don't want to be a dog.
I want to stay like this.
Well, now that's even more difficult.
Reincarnation-wise,
you're pretty low down the ladder.
Not long out of the plant kingdom,
so don't push your luck here.
Even in your next life.
You won't be human,
you got a lew more dog lives yet.
You're very lucky you'd these 49 days.
Don't upset the Gods,
or you may return as a grasshopper.
But that feeling I've with my mistress.
The warmth & wonderfulness.
It's not like being with
your average bitch at all.
It's reserved for the human kingdom,
only human beings can have feelings like that.
They say I love you.
Love you?
Other than making money,
Love motivates human to do anything,
The trouble is ...
People just treat love & money in the same way.
Think they can own love.
When in fact it's a gift to give.
Many live, spent working that one out.
But why?
Just believe it.
You try & control love.
& you'll live to regret it.
Come back, it's not true.
I want love.
I want love!
I really like it here.
I'm sorry sir, you're not allowed
to bring your dog in here.
I can't go in.
What's the matter with you? You're not a dog.
That's right, I'm not a dog.
Let's go in.
Magic, would you like a hot dog?
A dog? I can't eat a dog!
Not a dog, a hot dog.
It doesn't matter if it's hot or cold.
I just don't eat it.
Two hot dogs please.
Eat up! It's sausage, there's no dog.
I promise you that
Be careful with love.
So what happened'?
Thought I saw something
Well, why don't we go to a movie?
Piss off, go on!
Be careful with love.
What is it?
It's a scarey movie.
Did she scare you with her body?
No love!
Let's go.
No love my friend.
Do you know why I asked you over for dinner?
Today's my birthday.
I'm sorry but I don't have a present.
But wait till next payday.
Happy birthday
Excuse me.
Hello?
Happy birthday
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry Jack, I'm not alone.
Be careful in love.
No love.
You mustn't fall in love with her.
Now what?
Nothing, just spilled my drink,
I'll just go clean up.
Remember, you'll live to regret
it if you love her.
Come here.
You made me human,
how come you won't let me love?
You've only got 7 more days left.
Don't wreck it by falling in love.
I want to stay human not a dog.
But you can't change your destiny as a dog now.
Listen, it's not the same thing,
a man is not a dog.
I don't care about that,
I've got 7 days left to be a lover
And I'm going to use them.
But it isn't worth it.
It won't work really, cause you aren't a man.
You're only man's best friend.
Kathy still loves Jack.
And Jack loves her too.
How you know it?
I've watched their diaries
They're perfect couple.
You'd be responsible for this mess.
Let do a good job before you leave.
Match them as a merit for yourself.
Kathy we need to talk, I want to thank you.
For making me happy, in my new life.
I understand.
It must be very hard in Mainland China.
I'm glad you came to HK.
I want to say ...
Jack loves you, you can't just leave him.
Forgive him.
What are you talking about?
Lucy means nothing at all to him.
I'm sure of that!
How do you know'?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Saw it with your own eyes'?
I'm really your dog Magic.
I see, you've met someone new.
Do you have a wife in China, is that it?
If you don't want to be my friend.
Just say so, you don't have to show up
with such excuses.
I really am your dog Magic.
I can prove it. I know so much about you.
What do you know about?
That earring you're wearing was a present
years ago from your mom.
You mist aid it, I found it for
you there in the rubbish.
And I know about that watch,
it's a present from Jack on Valentines Day.
But...
You stop it.
You read my diary!
Do you have no sense of privacy?
I didn't do it.
Get out!
Open the door!
I didn't read it, I swear to you.
Hi hunky, you've been thrown out again?
No wonder you call yourself a dog.
The 2 of you make a perfect couple.
You've ruined everything.
In the end you'll thank me.
It's better this way.
Never mind, come to my place.
Little cuddle, come on honey.
Hello.
I'm downstairs Kathy.
What do you want?
Please Kathy, I want to apologies.
Please let me come up & explain, alright?
These human games.
He's all sad.
All the need is a good walk, he'll be line.
Are you puzzled by love?
I've that experience.
Be a man!
Women are trouble.
It's a broken heart.
Someone to see you, Mr Chiu.
Thank you.
It's the last day.
Time to go back to the Kennel.
I've to get Kathy a present.
I promised her that I would.
Your only have one hour left.
I know.
Kathy doesn't know what a lucky woman
she is to have a loyal dog like this.
Hurry up Magic.
Big wills only.
Sorry, close for lunch.
I've got 10 cherubs to pay in.
Well shill!
Can't you see there's a line?
Backward ...
A thief's line up too'?
Thank you, that's a great help.
Delighted.
Goodbye then guys
We'll miss you
And your funny ways.
Good luck, think about us sometimes
I'll think about you
Let us out then.
I miss you too.
Handsome, |'ll miss you.
Goodbye guys-
I'll miss you too.
Goodbye!
What's you? Are you leaving?
I don't have any choice
But why not? Wasn't the raise enough for you?
I want to raise you salary next month still
It was more than enough
But I fell my life's going to the dogs here
So you're going?
It's time I got back to my roots, you know.
I get your meaning, you nust miss your family
Ready.
Stay there!
Or I'll have to shoot her.
Nobody more. I'll shoot to kill
Keep still! And shut up.
Keep still!
Thousand dollar bills
Magic, I want to give you this
No thank you, buy something
for my friends here would you?
This is a news flash
There is a robbery under way at
the Philippine Tai Sung Bank
A robbers taken a woman hostage
& is holding her at gun-point
The poilce are fully armed & ready for action
The thief is also armed,
& psychiatrists think his behaviour...
indicetes he is under heavystress
& would kill with very little provocation.
Hostages are very dangerous now.
I've gonna rescue her.
You cant, you might get killed.
Go for it Magic. Go for it
Taxi, Philippine Tai Sung Bank, tast as you can
No way. I'm on lunch break
Hey buddy, pleace take me to the Tai Sung Bank
Over there.
Nancy, you like driving fast?
You call this fast? There's a guy
there going past us on foot.
Don't believe it! We're doing almost a hundred
kilometres an hour
Pull over!
This is crazy!
I just got overtaken by a guy on foot.
Go charge him first!
Cut the crap licence
Let me through... I've got to rescue my friend
I've got to rescue my friend
No. Heill hurt you
Be still, or I'll shoot her
Magic, don't!
Don't come over, I'll shoot!
Magic
I surrender.
Magic... Magic
Out the way!
You'll be alrighy, Magic
Go & get the doctor.
Hang on in there, the doctor's coming
I promised |'ll get you something
gor your birthday
Thank you.
I'm your dog you know.
I'm didn't lie to you Kathy
Doctor
Doctor, he's been shot in the chest
Relax, let's see
Hey, come here
What?
You are in the wrong place, guy
You'd have taken him to the vet
He really is Magic
Magic
Well there's nothing I can do for him
I'm going
Magic
Time to go
Just one last goodboye
Alright!
I told you not to mess around with love
Oh no, I'm crying as well
Come on
Don't cry Kathy, you know he loved you!
Magic
Don't get upset
And the best love stories are riddled with tragedy
Think of Romeo & Juliet
Anyway you've some practice as a man
Kathy
Here's what the stork brought
for Pansy the poodle
Congratulations
I know how much you like dogs, accept it
Thank you
Do you recognize me?
He looks like Magic
The only one in the litter that did!
Is it he son f0 Magic?
I'm scared he's ugly.
Don't make that face, you'll scare the puppy
Alright. I promise |'ll never scare him again
Come to daddy, there's a good little boy
Taste good!
They say puppy peepee good for virility,
old Chinese saying, right?
Pal, go home now
Watch your step!
So we've got a happy ending.