We managed to put Chu Tu behind bars, but the operation was a costly one.
You destroyed the squatter village,
and the government had to relocate the families
and pay damages.
During the operation, you damaged the shopping centre as well.
We paid well over a million for the chandelier alone.
The taxpayers know police work doesn't come cheaply.
But they don't expect to pay the cost of someone's heroics.
Why didn't you use the stairs? Did you have to destroy that chandelier?
Do you always have to be different?
You're right. The force doesn't need superstars.
We need disciplined policemen.
I wasn't expecting a promotion.
Ka Kui, the operation succeeded through team effort,
not just because of you.
You should be grateful we didn't fire you.
The bosses wanted you disciplined
for holding me hostage.
I managed to talk them out of it.
I'm very grateful.
I worry about your individualism.
You're just a police officer. Don't forget that point.
As of today, you're back in uniform.
You'll be assigned wherever needed.
You mean he'll be an errand boy?
I think you'll be very busy.
What else do you do besides giving out tickets?
Calling all units.
There's been a serious road accident at the Industrial Park.
Traffic is at a standstill.
All units in the area, please respond.
May, go home. I'm working now.
Just think of me as a member of the public
who wants to talk to a policeman.
About what?
I think you look very smart in uniform.
Stop it. I'm on duty.
I've brought you a cold drink.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir!
- I can't drink here. - Go on, you need a break.
If I have a drink, pretty soon I'll need the toilet.
Come on.
May, I'll get into trouble.
Hello, superhero! You still haven't been sacked?
You're lucky you're not in jail with Chu.
You think so?
Three Swiss doctors said I had only three months to live.
It's called compassionate release.
Three months can pass quickly. Very quickly.
My boss will be alive long after you're dead.
Don't you know you're threatening him?
Really? In that case, he can sue me.
Just be careful! Drive on.
Ka Kui?
Ka Kui, Chu Tu is out of jail.
I know. So?
You already knew? That's good, then.
If you'd never nabbed a thief, who would you have to be scared of?
Just remember, there are 250,000 Royal Hong Kong Police at your back.
Bill, are there really 250,000 police in Hong Kong?
We're always recruiting new blood. Didn't you see our newspaper ad?
What are you waiting for? Go on patrol!
Hey, I've talked to Raymond.
He said you could carry a gun, even after work.
I'm very happy tonight.
The show and dinner were great.
- You don't seem very happy. - Really? I am happy.
I wish you had enjoyed it as much as I did.
- Are you worried about Chu? - No. But I'm just being careful.
- Maybe next week... - Hey, superhero!
Off duty already?
- What are you doing here? - I can park here.
You can't give me a ticket.
Yeah, you must have a nice view from Flat B of the first floor.
- Am I right? - Go upstairs.
How did you find this address?
It's amazing what information you can get with money.
People will do anything for money, you know?
What do you mean?
There's a narrow stairwell in this building.
If there ever happened to be a fire,
it would spread quickly through the building.
Because of the narrow access,
the fire brigade couldn't get in there.
Your girlfriend's cute. You'd better keep a close eye on her.
If she were to get her pretty ass burnt, it'd ruin her marriage prospects.
Bastard!
Oh, hero, I'm so happy!
Sorry.
It's my fault really.
Policemen like me have lots of enemies. You face threats.
I'm not scared.
If you had no enemies, that would mean you'd never caught a thief.
Think you could stay somewhere else for a while?
Don't worry about me. They're just morons.
No. We'd just stand out while they stayed hidden.
Okay, then. I'll move to my aunt's and hide out for a while.
Don't worry too much about it.
But if you drop a vase on him, I'll definitely be the dead one.
May.
Auntie.
You're on your own? Where's Ka Kui?
He's still on duty.
It's okay, I can manage.
I'm not against you dating a policeman,
but I don't want him to spend too much time on his work.
He's stubborn, too.
But a man should do his duty.
That's why he has lots of enemies and you have to move back home.
Actually, I don't worry at all.
That way, he doesn't need to worry about me.
He ought to worry about you.
- Who are they? - They're the ones from last time.
I guess superhero isn't here.
Wait for me in the restaurant.
Right.
- What do you want? - We have a score to settle.
I just want to know where you're going.
It has nothing to do with her.
You must be her mother. Am I right?
Bastard!
You call me a bastard?
You're wrong! I'm the bastard son of a bastard!
- I'm not afraid of you. - Don't waste time with him. Let's go.
Auntie, why has your daughter fallen for a cop?
That could be dangerous.
Living on the 19th floor is dangerous, too.
What if you took a fall while cleaning the windows?
It would take more than glue to fix you!
Go ahead!
Don't be silly.
- Go away! - Get off!
You bastard!
Don't grab my hair!
You're hurting me!
You bitch!
Easy, she's just a girl.
Count yourself lucky. If you were a man, you'd be dead!
- I won't forget this! - Come on.
You just watch out!
Are you okay?
Auntie!
It's your job that brings the bad guys here.
Look. May was badly beaten because of you!
I've told you to stop seeing him.
Did John Ko attack you?
I started hitting him first.
He just hit me back.
And they knocked me down.
My backside still hurts. Now I can't sit down.
How did they know you'd be here?
They followed her, that's how.
They're watching us from across the street.
I wonder what's next.
Ka Kui, don't!
He should go and scold them.
If it's as easy as all that, then I'll be relieved.
Idiot! Are you crazy?
What else do you do besides bullying women?
It's my favourite hobby.
Get the bastard!
You know the law, don't you?
They may have threatened her, but an arrest requires evidence.
Don't you know you're a policeman?
I got carried away.
That's not a good reason!
He reacted like anyone else would.
He's not anyone else. He's a police officer.
What you've done is disgraceful! It's a disgrace to the force.
I don't think so. If a policeman fails to respond to a personal threat, that's a disgrace.
- And it disgraces the law too. - You're a show-off.
You won't let us forget you arrested Chu. How can I explain this to the chief?
You don't have to. I quit.
You think that will solve the problem?
Why not? This is probably the best solution.
I'll leave now.
Thank you for your support in times past.
Goodbye.
Ka Kui.
If that's your last word...
then try to find a less stressful job.
Bye-bye.
I will.
You think you can do anything you want just because you're cops!
Don't you know the law?
You can't beat me up just like that! Kill me if you can.
Shut up and sign this.
I'm not signing anything. No way!
I'll sue you for every penny you've got.
I've got lots of money. I'll get a lawyer. I'll sue you!
What?
No!
See? You saw this officer try to assault me.
He wants to beat me up like before, when he hit me and broke my glasses.
You'll pay for that. Would you dare to beat me up here?
Come on. What are you waiting for?
Come on. I'm going to sue you. You're going to jail.
These youngsters have no patience.
Bill, why didn't you ask him to stay?
You should have said so!
I thought you meant throw him out of here.
Now that I know what that gesture means, I'll remember it.
Ka Kui, what's the matter?
You don't want me to be a policeman, do you?
Of course I do. I'm proud of you.
What do I have to show for all my time as a cop? Just enemies.
There you go! That means you've done your job well.
If a cop has no enemies, there can only be one reason.
He hasn't caught any crooks.
I'm glad they're out to frighten me.
It proves you're a tough, good cop.
Thanks for that.
But I've had enough.
I resigned today.
- Really? - Are you disappointed?
You're really quitting?
I'm so happy!
Calm down.
What's with her?
May, all these years I haven't treated you as well as I should have.
It's my fault.
I have three month's holiday. Let's go somewhere else to relax!
Ka Kui, you really mean it? Where to, then?
- Bali. - Good idea!
We haven't travelled in years.
Right, so let's go.
It always feels good to fly on a plane.
- That'll be $5,540, please. - Right.
I'll see you outside.
- Credit card? - Sure.
Here's our catalogue, sir.
Thank you. Bye.
What clothes should I take?
You won't need any in Bali.
Don't be silly!
I can't believe we're going.
I just hope they don't rip us off.
They're a big company. They're trustworthy.
Well, it's paid for now. Let's cross our fingers.
- Fay! - Ka Kui.
- Long time no see! Is this your area? - Yes. What's up?
We've received a bomb threat here.
- Really? - Yeah. Can you help us out?
- All right, then. - Thanks.
Ka Kui!
I'll just take a look, all right?
Sun.
Just in time. What's up?
We got a call about a bomb.
Are you sure it's real?
I don't think the guy was kidding. He told us to clear the area.
We have ten minutes.
Really?
The manager said he's nuts.
Start clearing the building now.
There are too many people.
If it's a hoax, who'll be to blame?
I'm used to getting an earful.
If it is real, we'll endanger lives.
That's true. What do we do?
Consider it real.
Clear the building. Call headquarters.
Where's the fire alarm?
Over there.
Ka Kui.
We're gonna set off the fire alarm. Come on!
- Your baton. - But...!
Come on! I'll take responsibility.
Follow me.
Don't panic. Don't worry.
Come back. I've opened the till already.
Have they paid?
What's going on?
It's nothing.
What should we do? They're not taking any notice.
Ka Kui!
Don't stay here. Go on!
Your attention please.
Evacuate the building.
Everybody please leave immediately.
There's a fire in the building.
Please leave now.
Please leave in an orderly manner.
Everybody outside.
Be careful.
What's going on? Why is the alarm on?
What about our business?
- Fay. - What's up?
Get them out of here.
This is for your own safety. Go now!
What about you?
I won't be long. You go first.
Check the building.
I can't understand this. It's crazy!
- Who's in charge? - You talk to them.
Please leave now. The police will take care of it.
Ka Kui. Ka Kui!
I'm all right. You go home first.
Hello, sir.
Who made the call?
We received a bomb threat, but we didn't know if it was a hoax.
Who set off the alarm?
It was me, sir.
You may leave.
Why did you do it?
Sir, when I was in the Police Academy,
I was taught that public safety comes first,
so I set off the alarm.
Do you think you're indispensable?
Superintendent, there's no fire,
but your men cleared the building.
Right. The Bomb Disposal Unit is coming.
You won't be needed now.
Right. I hope this isn't a hoax.
So do I, Uncle Bill.
Raymond, they want to see the head man.
Shall I go?
- Where's the Bomb Disposal Unit? - On their way.
What a mess.
Did I do the right thing?
How do I do know? Don't ask me.
Right now, we have to wait and see.
Tell them to leave.
You can go back in very soon.
My ball!
When can we go back in?
- Now what? - Very soon.
- Here's your ball, kiddo. - Thank you.
Ready?
The Bomb Disposal Unit is here.
If they don't find anything, the boss will blow a fuse.
Uncle Bill, I'm very sorry.
I'm not...
Red alert! All units move in.
Go and fight the fire. Go on.
I suppose the good news is nobody got hurt.
What are the losses?
The insurance will cover it.
I'm more worried about the damage to our image.
I've asked the press to cooperate, and I'm sure they will.
But who did it? And why our company?
It may not be against us.
It could be someone who's mentally disturbed.
There's a man on the line, sir.
- He says he planted the bomb. - Have it put through.
Put him through.
Hello? Hold on.
Listen, we planted the bomb in your shopping centre.
We want $10 million.
Pay up or your other properties will get bombed.
Let me talk to him.
All right.
But it's a huge amount of money.
We'll need to call a board meeting.
You've got 24 hours. And don't coll the police.
- What do we do, then? - Must be some kind of hoax.
Yes. So what do we do?
Call the police.
We pay enough taxes. The police should do something for us.
- Get me through to the chief. - Yes.
Raymond, you were extremely lucky.
It's amazing that no-one was hurt in the explosion.
Thank God for that.
And the Chu case... well done!
- Thank you. But it wasn't just me. - That's right.
You've proven yourself.
You should handle this case. Do you agree?
- Sure. - Of course.
This is a very tough case.
That's why they gave it to us.
Who in our department do you think can solve it?
You're the only one.
I want a better idea.
It's definitely not me.
Maybe we could bring back somebody who's on leave.
Do you mean somebody like Ka Kui?
He has substantial experience.
I don't know.
He's unorthodox, impulsive.
He'll only give us trouble. We have to bear the responsibility.
I agree he's a little bit rash, but underneath he's a good cop.
I won't let him do it.
But if you think he's our man, you go and find him.
Let's see who's the boss.
- Over there. - Here?
Fasten your seat belt, please.
I forgot the sunscreen!
Buy it when we get there.
Did you get your passport when you were younger?
Put out a call for Detective Chan Ka Kui.
Sure.
Your attention, please.
Will Chan Ka Kui...
Let me see. No, don't look!
- It's cute. - It's horrible.
...Ka Kui please contact us.
That's you. Yeah.
- What's up? - I don't know.
I won't be long.
- Are you Mr. Chan? - Yeah.
I'm afraid there seems to be a problem with your passport.
Really?
It'll just be a quick check.
What's going on?
I'll be back right away.
Hurry!
Okay.
Bye.
What do you want?
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
What is it? I have a plane waiting.
We have a problem.
It seems that the bombing case has become a blackmail case,
and it's a very tough one.
-So? - This case is a real challenge.
Raymond was hoping...
I was hoping that you might cancel your holiday.
No! I've already boarded the plane.
Plus, I've quit.
I know how you feel.
You've been under a lot of pressure lately.
- But ducking out like this? - I'm not ducking out.
He said he's not ducking out!
Raymond is a great admirer of your abilities.
I don't have any abilities. I'm too impulsive.
Impulsive? More like... a man of action!
If only I could control my actions.
A true man of action acts on instinct.
I think the police force needs men with discipline.
Instinctive men have to be unconventional,
even at the cost of discipline.
If you did everything by the book, no case would ever get solved.
- Am I right? - Absolutely.
I'd better get back on board.
You're right.
Goodbye.
How much is the ransom?
Ten million. That's all we know.
- Do we have any suspects? - Not a clue.
Do you think these people are insane?
Why are you asking me? I don't know.
Have you traced the dynamite?
- Why? - Yes, Why?
Simple. Dynamite is a controlled substance.
You either smuggle it in or you steal it from a local company.
He's right. We hadn't thought of that.
We must find their bomb factory before the company pays the ransom.
If we do that, we can foil their plans.
How is it you always solve problems so easily?
You're made for this case!
You're in charge.
I've got a plane to catch.
Wait! Ka Kui.
You can go there anytime. This case is once-in-a-lifetime.
Go there next time. Okay?
I'd better talk to May first.
Hurry up, then.
Hurry UP-
- Miss! - Yes, sir?
- My plane... - It just took off.
It's taken off!
You've missed your flight!
Count on them to stay on schedule.
I still have May's passport!
Damn! It sure isn't your lucky day!
Now what?
Uncle Bill, we'd better go.
- You all right? - I ate something bad.
- That way, sir. - Thank you.
Excuse me. We're police officers. We're here to see Mr. Fung.
- 30th floor. - Thank you.
Bugging devices.
A bug? Look out... Nixon lost his job because of these.
If we want to solve the case, we have to know our targets well.
We're counting on you. Put them away.
Miss Wong, there are two police officers here.
- Where's the bathroom? - On your right.
Thanks.
Twenty-five, please.
Twenty-four, please.
Wait!
Uncle Bill, I'm really worried about May.
I'll call Jakarta Airport as soon as I get back to the office.
Uncle Bill.
You should be ashamed of yourself. Haven't you got any manners?
Let's use the others.
Detective Chan to see Miss Wong.
- Please wait. - Thank you.
- Ka Kui. - Uncle Bill.
I figured you were used to taking the blame.
That's no excuse!
Gentlemen.
I'm Detective Chang. This is Detective Chan. We...
- Please come with me. - We're...
I know. Mr. Fung is busy now, but he's signed the papers.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me, where's the toilet? - Down the corridor.
Here, sir.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Where's your friend?
He had a sudden urge.
There's the chairman.
That site is worth three billion. There would be a profit.
Yes, Mr. Chairman?
- Detective Chan is here. - Thank you.
Thanks for all your help.
You're developing the new properties very quickly.
Please sit.
Directors, managers, and department heads, welcome.
I've called this meeting to review the performance
of our property portfolio over the last six months,
and to set the sales target for the next year.
You may all know that since the stock market collapse last year,
the Hang Seng Index has risen 66%.
Let me show you the performance of the major blue chip shares.
However, given the performance of the bank and property sectors,
the outlook of the stock market for the next six months remains uncertain.
In situations like this,
small investors are likely to put their money in property.
So we have to accelerate the pace of our new housing developments.
Hi, gorgeous.
If someone asks the chairman for this, it's $500 to get it back.
Really?
Yeah. Bye-bye.
- What happened? - It's a meeting.
- Did you plant the bugs? - Sure.
- And the desk? - All done.
- Was it easy? - He wasn't against it!
- What did they say? - Something about houses.
Really?
- Where are you going? - I'll take the next one.
May's here.
May, you're back!
May.
You scumbag!
Let me explain.
You... you didn't want me to come back!
You left me there and took my passport!
When I got there, I couldn't do anything.
Before I was sent back here, they detained me for ten hours in a cell!
Why should I keep my voice down?
When you take your dog for a walk, do you not take him home afterwards?
I'm even worse than a dog!
May, they're watching us.
What are you staring at?
This is none of your business!
I want you to tell me in front of everyone what you think I am!
What the hell do you take me for?
You're my girlfriend!
Your girlfriend?
Open up! Open up!
If that's true, why do you treat me this way?
You treat strangers better than me!
Let me tell you...
...it's over between us!
Chan Ka Kui, I hate you!
Uncle Bill, did you make that call?
I had to go to the toilet.
You've ruined my life!
May!
Go away or I'll run you over.
- Go away! - Don't be childish!
Don't grab my bag! Go away!
Don't even touch me. Go away. Leave me alone.
Let me explain.
I don't want to know.
I've nothing else to say to you.
May!
May, are you all right?
Stay away from me. Don't touch my motorbike.
Keep away. I don't want you anywhere near me.
- Let me explain. - Keep away.
Why won't you help me?
Just keep away from me. I never want to see you again.
May.
All right, get back to work. I want to see Ka Kui.
Ka Kui, the boss wants to see you.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all right.
Do you want me to call May to explain?
I don't think it would help.
Don't explain anything to women! This is my way to handle 'em...
if a man's not at home, it's obvious he's working.
Excuse me, I have to go to the toilet.
Don't pay any attention to his chauvinism. Go and get changed.
May...
It's better than wasting my time here. Good night.
Can I walk you home?
No thanks.
Don't be foolish!
I won't.
Get me, it's me you want. Don't be foolish.
- You're in this together. - Don't try anything.
Prepare to die!
I really had you going! I got the both of you!
Ka Kui!
I've found it.
Looks like you're outnumbered.
If I thought it was just a simple game, I wouldn't call my men to come.
I'm flattered.
My boss asked me to teach you a lesson.
I'm getting paid to do it.
But I don't need to dirty my hands. My men can take care of you.
Get on with it.
We'll give you a chance.
If you apologise to Mr. Ko now, we won't break both of your legs.
We'll just break one of them.
Cut the bullshit. Go on, kill me.
Kill a cop? I don't think so.
My boss wants to teach you a lesson.
Ripping a few limbs off should do the trick.
Get him!
Go!
There he is. Beat him up!
Go on, finish him off. Get up.
Move over. Let me drive.
I'll turn you into mashed banana.
It wasn't my fault! I was paid to do it.
Keep away or I'll shoot!
Shoot me!
- I'll shoot. - Shoot here!
It's not my fault.
It's not. It's not my fault.
Next time I'll kick your ass.
It's not my fault!
May.
Did they hurt you?
I'm all right.
You'd better be careful.
Why did you chase him? That's dangerous.
I wanted to make things up to you.
If it had been acid in that pistol and not ink...
I'd be scarred for life.
Maybe they wanted to distract you and then kidnap me.
Then what would happen?
Ka Kui, I want my boyfriend to be gentle, not a savage.
Do you understand?
Come in.
"Police Detective in Park Rumpus." Who was that?
Look!
I'll check out the surveillance team.
ACTIVE-DUTY POLICEMAN INVOLVED IN 10-MAN PARK BRAWL
It was me. Sorry, sir.
I know Chu wants revenge, but don't take the law into your own hands.
Sorry, sir.
Anything I can do?
No, thanks.
I can cope with it. I just want them to leave me alone.
All right. But keep your eyes open.
Now we've got a surveillance team.
They're very good. Go and talk to them.
Did he give you an earful? Did he...?
Let's go over there.
He just wants to help.
How can somebody show off if they don't have an audience?
Sir!
Let me introduce you.
This is Detective Chan Ka Kui. Detective Ng, Detective Mui.
Hello.
You guys introduce yourselves.
This is the Special Tactical Unit.
Please take a seat.
They have great expertise in tracking targets.
But why? Will this be useful for the case?
Because we don't even know who did it.
That's easy.
Follow anyone suspicious, and then you'll know.
Follow the suspects.
Then we can find the their hiding place for making bombs.
We could follow them during the transaction, then arrest them.
- That simple? - Of course.
Good. That's why I always have faith in you.
Hope you have a smooth collaboration.
Detective Ng, could I have a word with you?
There will be room for you soon.
Go.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Detective Chan. - Yes.
What does that mean?
You guys are cool.
Anything yet?
Fung said his shares would go up.
That's hardly relevant.
And his girlfriend is a supermodel!
I'm not interested.
I'll take it. You go and call May.
Go on.
Ka Kui! Listen!
Your conditions have been presented to the board,
and they have agreed to pay.
No shit. Do you have the money?
We don't have it all. $10 million is a lot of money.
Trace it.
It's from Tai Po.
Check it out.
He's on Ting Kok Road.
HQ, calling all foot patrols. Are there any units on Ting Kok Road, over?
This is PC 12674 on Ting Kok Road, over.
PC 12674,
check anybody leaving a phone box in the area.
Are you stalling for time?
No, we didn't call the police.
Now we want 20 million.
Twenty million! Such a huge sum.
Find it.
Wait!
This is PC 12674.
Anything?
I think I've got a suspect.
Be careful. He's very dangerous.
He could be armed.
Keep everything low key.
Excuse me. You're supposed to use the pedestrian crossing.
- Move along. - Give me a chance, Officer.
Can I see your ID card?
Calling HQ...
PC 12674, do you copy?
An officer needs assistance on Ting Kok Road.
I'm sorry, he isn't here.
Don't be sorry.
That's the way things go. It wasn't your fault.
How long have you been in uniform?
About two months.
Then you're excused.
Will I get in trouble for losing my gun?
What about promotions?
Don't worry.
As long as you learn from the experience, it's okay.
- It happens to every cop. - It won't happen again.
Do you think you'd recognise him?
Sure.
Phone.
I could do with someone like you on the team.
I'll see to it.
Thank you. Can you file this for me?
- Hello. - It's Joker.
- Go ahead. - News.
What news?
A guy called Crazy Fai sells dynamite.
Nine o'clock, Hoi Wong Bar.
- Do you know what we'll do next? - No.
Really?
- What do you want? - Are you Fai? I want to talk.
Do I know you?
No, but you will.
All right. Let's go over there.
I'll be right back.
- What's your name? - Lo.
What do you want?
Some explosives.
Explosives?
Do you have some?
- What are they for? - Fishing.
You don't look like a fisherman.
What if I told you it was for business?
I'll give you a good price. What do you say?
All right... but I need to speak to someone.
It's not my stuff. Don't go away.
Thanks.
Sorry, he's out of stock, but he'll call me back.
Stay here, I'll be back when I've finished.
Thank you.
Hey, you. Stand up.
What's the matter?
CID. On your feet.
Hands up!
- I only came here for a drink. - A drink?
We heard you were dealing contraband.
Eyes front.
Hold it!
Throw me your gun. Quick!
Stand over there.
Easy. Don't do anything stupid.
Come on. Move.
Come out!
Get lost.
You screwed me over, you bastard!
Why did you call the cops?
Stop! Stop it!
Please, that's enough.
Please stop.
Why did you double-cross me?
To make sure you weren't a cop.
That's why I called the cops, to prove it.
I can get what you need.
Where is it?
Have you got the money?
It's cash on delivery.
Keep a lookout.
Is it good stuff?
It's from the quarries.
Got any more?
Yeah, plenty.
There's enough to blow up the Empire State Building.
I just met him! I've never seen him before!
Do you think you can get away?
Would you like some coffee?
A cigarette?
Two spoons of sugar?
Yes.
The temperature okay?
Fine.
This is stretching the law. If I were him, I'd clam up.
You seem comfortable. Will you cooperate with us now?
Cooperate?
You want me to die?
If you cooperate, you can walk out of here.
We'll keep everything secret.
If need be, we'll keep you under protection.
If you three could protect me the rest of my life,
then I would consider it.
Don't talk that way.
Even if we were to release you now,
we might, say, "find" drugs on you after you were gone,
or maybe "discover" you've been molesting young girls.
Does this get you good results?
Sure. It never fails.
What's the charge?
I've seen a lot worse than this.
I'll play along before I'll go to jail.
You all seem like nice young ladies!
Have you not seen anything like this before?
No! Stop! I've had enough.
No, please!
Nice young ladies, huh?
Aren't you going to play along?
I'll sue you!
Say that again.
Guns have a way of going off when you least expect it.
We'll just say it was an accident.
Yeah. Escaped prisoner!
Escaped prisoner!
No! I'll talk.
Why didn't you say so? Come on, sit down.
- Cigarette? - No.
There are men in here.
Shaw's over.
I have sold three explosives lately.
One buyer named Xing, he was u fisherman.
I've known him a long time.
He bought it to blast reef fish.
The other guy buys my stuff to refill empty bullet shell cases
so he can sell them.
But he's only bought a few.
The third guy's name was Polar Bear. He's a big-time dealer.
He usually hangs out at the Yaumatei Pool Hull.
Taxi.
Target's in a taxi. It's DP5608.
Got it, Big Mouth?
Taxi number DP5608, heading north to Kok Road.
Copy, Big Mouth. I see target DP5608.
It's headed to TST Metro Station.
All copy. All copy.
Renew info. Get to TST Metro Station.
Target on metro heading to Kung Tong.
Roger.
- Stay there. - Yes.
Target off metro.
Target in taxi CW721, heading to industrial area.
Target out of the car, heading to Yat Sing Street.
Copy. Over. Sun, your team leaves first.
Car to Yat Sing Street.
Start supervision. Wait for orders.
Yes.
I'll take a look.
Hey, buddy, where is Pak Lok Street?
- No idea. - Thanks.
Someone carrying two bags heading your way.
Polar Bear.
You went shopping?
Were you followed?
No. Don't worry.
Come on. Open up.
There are three of them.
Detective Chan, it's him. These must be the guys.
Three voices.
Louder, let me hear it.
Brother, stop waiting!
Everything ready?
Of course.
Then I have to make a call.
Not here. Make sure we're not being bugged.
Find a place at the TST. Make sure everything is fine.
Don't waste time. Get going.
Three people.
- They're coming out. - Roger.
- You don't deserve this. - You don't!
Check the plates and follow the van.
You stay here. I'll go and take a look.
Right. Let's go.
We're starting the car.
Yes.
- Where are you going? - To take a look.
- Be careful. - I will.
I see.
Detective Chan, they've shaken off our unit.
Don't worry, they'll come back. Call them off.
Come back here.
Don't shoot! It's me!
Be quiet.
You scared me.
- I fell over. - Someone's up there.
Hold it!
Turn around.
Police! Who are you?
This guy must be deaf.
Did you see three men come through here a few hours ago?
You ask him.
Do you work here?
Do you sleep here?
Right. I can't communicate with him.
I got an answer, but I have no idea what it means.
You ask him.
Take him down to the station.
It's okay. You're coming with me for questioning.
Come along. It won't cost anything.
No need for cuffs.
Why do you collect such things?
He's deaf.
Are all these toys in here yours?
- Freeze! - He can't hear you!
After him!
Sir! Are you all right?
There's a deaf-mute running around. Find him.
Yes, sir!
I didn't know he could fight.
Neither did I. Go and find my gun.
Okay.
If we can manage to finance the buyout of Indian Ocean Bank,
it would be a welcome addition to our portfolio.
Mr. Fung, telephone.
I said no calls.
I know, but it's that man again.
Jimmy.
Excuse me.
You called the cops.
No, you must be mistaken. We haven't!
You needn't try and deceive us. We knew you'd go to the cops.
To make you abandon that idea,
we will demonstrate our power to you tomorrow at 12:00.
We won't waste time bargaining with you ever again.
After 12:00 tomorrow, if you decide it's prudent to pay the $20 million,
place an ad in the name of your Zhiye Group
in one of the major newspapers the day after tomorrow.
Call Mr. Lam!
After 12:00 tomorrow, if you decide it's prudent to pay the $20 million,
place an ad in the name of your Zhiye Group
in one of the major newspapers the day after tomorrow.
Again.
Where was the call from?
It was a modified mobile phone, so we couldn't trace it.
We knew you'd go to the cops.
To make you abandon that idea,
we will demonstrate our power to you tomorrow at 12:00.
We won't waste time bargaining with you ever again.
Don't worry, they're bluffing.
We've sent extra officers to protect your buildings.
You'll be fine.
Listen up!
We will never tolerate such an outrage! It's time to act!
Yes, sir!
Fay!
Long time no see.
Polar Bear.
This is Ken. He'd like a word with you.
I didn't snitch on you!
Really? Then why did they turn up after you got caught?
And why did they let you go so quickly?
Lack of evidence. They granted me bail.
I didn't snitch, I swear!
It's all the same to us. We don't care.
- Where are we going? - Make any difference?
- Miss Wong. - Yes?
- We've checked the mail. - Thanks.
And these are for you.
Who on earth sent those?
Don't know. Someone special, maybe?
If you don't know, who would?
Thanks.
Plant this bomb and we're even.
Do the job or you're finished.
- Where shall I put it? - I'll tell you later.
Let's go.
Roger. Thanks a lot. Keep an eye out.
Ready.
I'm a cop. What's this?
I'm a cop.
ID card.
- What? - Nothing.
Nothing.
CID. Your case.
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
What's that?
Excuse me. CID. May I see your bag?
The red bag.
Excuse me. CID.
Make it quick.
- It should be fine. - Here's the mail, sir.
Roger.
Do you think it's a bluff?
I hope so, but we can't be sure.
Okay. Keep in touch.
Yes?
Ask her to wait a minute.
Roger.
Ka Kui, May's downstairs. She wants to talk to you urgently.
Thanks.
What's the matter?
I've written a letter for you. Goodbye.
May. You came all this way to give me this?
It's important, so keep it safe. Bye.
Oh, yeah, where's the scooter?
We didn't get along, so I sold it.
I'll follow her.
I have my backup units in position.
Yes. I think they're bluffing.
Then we should depend on the police.
All right.
What is going on?
Get an ambulance.
Get the fire extinguisher.
Call Mr. Lam.
How did this happen?
- Go and investigate. - Stay calm.
Don't panic. Ka Kui, come with me.
Call the fire department. Come on!
Bring a fire extinguisher.
Come on. Put the fire out first.
Come on, get moving.
- Is the ambulance here? - No.
Go call them!
We need more help.
- Phone, sir. - Bill, you take the phone call.
Ka Kui, meet me upstairs.
I thought you were supposed to protect me.
What's going on?
Package bomb. Miss Wong lost an arm.
THE ZHIYE GROUP, TOGETHER WITH EVERY HONG KONG CITIZEN,
STRIVES TO PRESERVE THE BEAUTY OF HONG KONG
- How's Miss Wong? - She's doing well.
The doctor said her arm would recover.
They'll do a skin graft on her face later.
So we'll wait and see.
Wong's decided to pay up.
What am I going to tell Raymond?
Uncle Bill, that's the way it goes.
We always said it was going to be a tough case.
We're dealing with well-organised criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead. I don't like putting lives at risk.
But don't worry.
If they come to collect the money, I'm sure we'll get them.
If I pass on what you said to Raymond, he won't be happy at all.
What we need is real action.
Sir!
I guess you've seen the papers.
Now what do I tell the Chief?
That's the way it goes.
We always said it'd be a tough case.
We're dealing with well-organised criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead.
I don't like putting lives at risk.
But don't worry.
If they come to collect the money, I'm sure we'll get them.
All this is talk. What we need is some real action.
Somethings up. Raymond's in trouble.
That's the way it goes.
We always said it'd be a tough case.
We're dealing with well-organised criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead.
I don't like putting lives at risk.
But don't worry.
If they come to collect, I'm sure we'll get them.
I understand your situation, and I'll note it in the report.
Good luck with the case.
You come, too.
Why the long face?
Did you two have a fight?
Right. But this is the last one.
Yes?
I'll get him!
Hold this.
Ka Kui, telephone.
Put it through.
Right. Put it through.
- Hello? - Ka Kui.
May's been kidnapped!
When?
We'd just left the shop when someone dragged her into a van.
Who did it?
I don't know. But it must have something to do with you.
Could it be those thugs again?
Chu Tu.
Ka Kui! Hello?
- Ka Kui! What's up? - An old score. May's been kidnapped!
Ka Kui!
- What happened? - May's been kidnapped.
What's the matter? Sign this cheque before you're dead. Our brothers...
- Please stop. He's a patient. - Let me finish.
We did what you asked. That's why we deserve something.
You won't need any money when you're dead.
Chu Tu!
- Chu Tu! - Hey, you!
Bring May back!
I know nothing! I did nothing! It's him! Him!
Sir, you can't do that to a patient! Stop it!
Put him down!
Speak up! What have you done with May?
- I didn't take her. - Who did, then?
I was very nasty to you before... but now I'm sick and penniless.
What reason would I have for taking her?
If he did have any money, he'd be pouring it into treatment.
This is none of our doing. Hassling you was business, not personal.
We only did it on account of the money.
Then who could it be?
There's a phone over there.
Don't die before you sign this!
You! I've had about enough of you!
He's got one foot in the grave, so what do I care?
- Hello, this is 1378. - Ka Kui!
May!
You recognise her voice.
We're at the Hung Fung Industrial Building.
Who is this? What do you want?
Come alone or she's dead.
Hello?
I know where that is.
May!
Are you all right?
Be quiet.
I'm okay. Why have you kidnapped her?
"Ka Kui, by the time you read this letter..."
Stop!
"...I've decided we should be apart."
No.
"I don't think I'll see you again."
It's a love letter!
Just like they say... unlucky in love, lucky in money.
There's more.
Bastard!
"When we first met, I thought you liked your job very much,
"and you'd be my Mr. Right.
"Now I realise the only thing that matters in your life is your work.
"I tell myself what made me fall in love with you
"is also what makes me want to leave you."
Yeah, why? Why did you break up?
"You told me you didn't want me involved with your work,
"but I didn't mind.
"What I did mind, though, is that you never spent enough time with me.
"Being with you was the happiest time of my life.
"But when you weren't there, it was the worst time of my life."
That's just not right.
"If I didn't leave you,
"I'd spend my life waiting for you to come home!"
Can't you stop it?
She's crying!
So is he.
Keep reading, go on.
"...because you can never stop being a policeman."
A policeman who never stops.
We're in trouble.
"I think it's the right decision.
"Please forgive me for making such a selfish choice. May."
What do you want?
We want you to help us get rich.
You must have heard the Zhiye Group was blackmailed.
The hardest part of the job is the pick-up.
You'll collect the ransom for us.
No way!
You don't have a choice.
He said no.
I think you'll enjoy this.
Stop!
Don't!
Stop it! Please!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Ka Kui, are you hurt?
Don't worry.
So you want to play the hero?
Now it's your turn.
Please don't!
You rotten swine!
Nice one!
Kill me if you've got the guts.
So tough!
Really? Let's see if his girl is tough, too.
What do you want?
How's that? How's that?
Enough! You've made your point.
Does that mean you'll do it?
Just let her go. I'll do anything.
We won't let her go unless you help us.
What do you want me to do?
Collect the money for us. Then I'll let you go.
You don't have any choice.
I'll do it.
Good man.
I wouldn't advise you to remove it.
Break one wire and the whole thing blows.
The same thing happens if I press this button.
You'd better be careful.
Ka Kui.
Be careful.
I'll come back for you.
Ready?
- He's on the line. - Trace the call!
I'll get Uncle Bill.
Is the money ready? We'll collect it in ten minutes.
It's ready.
- Did you call the cops? - No.
Where's Ka Kui?
I can't find him.
How could he be so irresponsible?
I can't wait. Don't take any risks.
Let's go.
You'll have ten minutes to get back here again.
No tricks.
If we don't get our money, your vest will go bang!
We'll be waiting.
Get going.
Good luck.
Can I help you?
Police.
- Mr. Fung. - Chairman.
You will pay me.
Is that so? Have a seat.
You promised to let us bug the phones.
We could trace the calls.
It's too bad you can't handle the bomb case so effectively.
We have everything ready.
Once they pay the money, we move into action.
I hope you won't do anything to make matters worse.
Because this will encourage the bombers.
So the police couldn't help. We could only depend on ourselves.
Ka Kui, the boss was looking...
Ka Kui!
- Ka Kui! - Out of my way.
Let me go!
Get out of my way!
Ka Kui!
Excuse me!
Ka Kui.
Ka Kui, where have you been?
Never mind. I'm here to collect the money.
What?
- Is he your man? - Yes, he is.
Ka Kui, what's going on?
We don't have much time. The money!
- What are you doing? - Ka Kui!
Move and I'll shoot you.
Don't pull the trigger.
No!
Don't push me.
If you shoot me, everybody here...
...will be blown sky high.
If one wire breaks, the whole thing will explode!
Ka Kui, what's going on?
Can't we work this out?
If I don't leave here in ten minutes, it will go off.
I don't have time!
Let him go.
Attention all units! Do not stop Ka Kui.
Ka Kui! Ka Kui!
Don't follow me.
Get out of my way!
- I think he did it. - Great.
- Looks like he was followed. - Let's go.
Tell him to move up.
Give me the money.
I'm being followed. Let me shake them off first.
Trust me.
Are the cops behind us?
Stay back! Don't come near!
Why did you stop here?
- What are you doing? - What's going on?
A bomb's about to blow. Run!
A bomb! Run!
There's no cops!
I'll blow him to bits.
Wait! What about the money?
And you can't get a radio signal in the tunnel.
What now?
- We've got the girl. Don't worry. - Let's go.
If anything goes wrong, kill her.
Where is May?
Where is she?
Look, he's back.
I told you he wouldn't play tricks.
May!
Quiet.
Freeze! You're under arrest.
Really?
Come on then, arrest us.
Don't move.
Move and I'll shoot you.
You think so? You'd have to shoot fast.
There are three of us.
Think about it.
If I don't shoot you, you'll only spend a few years in jail.
And then you'll be a reformed person. That's better than dying in this condition.
Better to die than to live as a pauper. We are ready.
We want to be rich.
There's no shame in wanting wealth. But your way is wrong.
So what is right and what is wrong?
You can get everything you want in life
by helping other people get what they want in life.
You'd have a whole new outlook. That's what you should do.
But what you have done now has hurt society.
- This benefits no-one. - What does that mean?
Other than you guys, who thinks you're doing the right thing?
Who would think highly of your purpose?
You are right.
Yes.
That doesn't sound too bad... but there's still one question.
We might take your advice if we had certain opportunities.
See, we don't want to go to jail.
We don't want to be punished.
Don't push me!
Run! This is a fireworks factory.
- May! - I'm over here!
May, are you all right?
Ka Kui, be careful!
Good work!
Ka Kui! Come here! There's the rubbish chute.
There's an exit.
May, you go first.
It looks too high.
Just jump!
Ka Kui, are you all right?
I'm fine. Get out of here, May. Go as far as you can.
Be careful.
How do you like it? Want some more? Huh?
How about some more, you little bastard?
Want some more?
Want some more? Here!
More?
Shit!
Stop crying, okay?
Look. The fireworks are beautiful.