I lift up my head
Here I am at the Fengyue Brothel
The girls are lovely here
All very charming
Cuihong, Xiaoxiao
Haixian, Yindi and Jinbao
Big eyes
Slim waists
Gorgeous figures
Perfect! All the right curves
in right places
Girls, upstairs downstairs,
front and back courtyards
Come out to greet the guests
They're here
Haitang, Qingwen
Xiaoyu, Meibao, Meihong
Guohua, Xiaojuan, Yulan
Yingchun, Meifang, Huijuan
What's going on?
They are like Romeo and Juliet
They've got hearts for each other
Really?
Mr. Wang has been here for over a month
He has very much taken to Jinbao
They seem serious
He has spent all his money
He'll go back home in Shanghai
to get more
Crying their eyes out
Exchanging their vows, and love tokens
What kind of love tokens?
Mr. Wang said he'll take out a tooth
He will marry no one but Jinbao
And Jinbao will cut off her hair
She said she'll be his wife for sure
I'm getting her a pair of scissors
Did she mean it?
This is the Fengyue Brothel
That's the Chonger Room
Named after the famous brothel
Over here is the Yinshuo Room
Meaning relaxed so to speak
Things are true and false
at the same time
No, I meant the tooth
Of course
You... have done it?
Yes, a word is a word
Jinbao, I'm serious about you
Xiaowang, my heart aches
And I'm in pain too
She's doing this for real?
Of course not
You can't trust a prostitute
The rich customer has fallen in love
Jinbao, have you cut your hair?
Take this;
you'll know I'm always with you
Jinbao
My precious...
Don't worry, once I arrive in Shanghai
...I'll let my parents know
I'll come back for you
Remember to bring the things I want
Yes I will
Mountains of gold, silver,
anything you want
Baozhu, Cuilian, Xiaofeng
Xiaocui, Qiuhong
They're all here, sirs
Some have customers, some are escorts
I heard there are three new girls
One is the lady boss of a pottery store?
I heard she's quite a woman
You meant Haixian?
Yes, call her here
Because of her affairs her husband died
Really?
Call her
She's very popular
We'll wait
There's a long list; maybe not today
She's so popular?
Yes, let me tell you
She's good in bed, and off the bed too
Right next door
Stop it
Why are you in such a hurry?
I can't wait
Are you for real?
The word is that
you cheated on your husband
Is that the truth?
All men cheat
...on their wives. And then
...you go around accusing wives
to be promiscuous
Tell me what happened
Cheating on husbands
It's so unfair
If a woman is caught cheating
She got beaten to death
Marriage to a useless guy
is so unfortunate
Lady boss...
Hey, you scared me!
What were you thinking about?
She's quite pretty
Can't believe she cheated on her husband
Right, she deserves to be cut into pieces
What do you want to buy?
A chamber pot
My husband broke it
How come she knows your size?
Oh!
What?
What are you talking about?
Ain't the first time
you buying a chamber pot from her
Wang Dachui
Lawyer Diao...
You have a pen?
A pen?
To write down my accounts
I use charcoal
Lady boss...
Lawyer Diao...
Could I borrow a pen?
What?
A pen
Speak clearly
So, working on a new case?
Yes, that case
For the plaintiff?
No
Caught in the act, sent to the judge
Sentenced to be beheaded
For the defendant?
Can you help?
Of course, otherwise I won't get paid
I don't sell chamber pots
Shut up
Eat chamber pots
What's there to eat?
Do you eat a banana with the skin?
You lawyers just like to argue
You can turn right to wrong
Of course
I've got to help others
I love to help
You saw her
That girl looked pretty
And she's married to an aged fella
Aged fellow?
Hello, Boss
What aged fellow?
Wang, the boss is back
I'm chatting with the lady boss
Brew this herbal drink for me
Yes
Collecting money?
I've been to Xuzhou
Got it all?
Give that to me, boss
Of course not
I'm going to freshen up and lie down,
don't forget
I won't
Be careful when you open your mouth
next time
...or I'll slap you
Come on, it's an accident
If something happens to you one day...
What do you mean?
Forget about what I said,
thanks for your pen
Go to hell
What now?
Lawyer Diao...
Sorry
Would have spat on you
if you were someone else
I want to buy a chamber pot
Too big. Another one
Pick yourself
That's for kids
It's all right
Sorry...
I want to learn
What's with you? Are you mad?
I'm mad...
See you
Damn cat
Damn it
Where're you going?
Asshole, stop running
Who's that?
Zhang
Help me,
the boss is getting suspicious again
Or he'll beat me up
I can't take it
What happened?
Don't ask
Take this
Go over to my bed in a while
No matter what the boss does
Keep your mouth shut
Then...
Just go
Asshole
I'll kill you, bitch
Beat you up good
Bitch
Bastard, I'll tell your mom about this
What're you doing? Come to bed
You go ahead
I'm itchy, scratch me
A little higher
Lower
That's it
So comfortable
Come on, Dachui
Open up...
Coming...
What's going on? It's late
He said you're cheating on him
And that he's beaten you up
Cut your hair
What hair?
Whose hair?
Tell me
Whose hair is this?
Unbelievable
What're you looking at?
I think it's the other way round
Whose hair is this?
Whose?
I'm asking you
Stop the act
You said that you beat me up
Where're the bruises?
Yes, you can't unnecessarily accuse her
Sister, mom is worried
She'll hang herself if this was true
You accused me of cheating
And you complained to my mother?
How can I face people now?
Stop it, sister
Don't try to stop me
No, sister
Look at him
I don't know who he's with
Red string on his toe
You're not unlucky...
I'm unlucky
You've a piece of red string on your toe
And wish your wife
to have an affair too!
Well said
You know what's going on
Be careful
You better be careful
Yes, I will get my proof next time
Your husband is full of nonsense
Our family is not going to be
bullied around
What's there to listen, huh?
Send out the goods to Xuzhou
on the day after
And for the goods to Suzhou
Better work on those soon
How long will you be away?
10 to 15 days
Take care of things
Don't worry
Mr. Tao, going away on trip?
Yes
Is he here?
What have you got to say now?
What's going on?
Tie it up
Hurry, think of something
How could he do that to me?
He deserves to die
You're his wife
You must try to save him
He's now tied with that bitch
...inside the sack
Get Lawyer Diao to think of a plan
What do you want? It's late
Yours?
Carry it inside
Go
Think of a good plan
which can save Mr. Wang
And also save my lady boss
A good plan?
Got it
Leave now, I'll take care of it
Great, thanks
Strip
Go on, take off the clothes
We've got to do what we got to do
I'm thinking here
And you must do your part
Why do you want me to strip?
We don't have much time now
Otherwise they won't be saved
Then... I won't be able to help
Fine...
It's not that hard, is it?
Turn your head away
I want to watch
Lie down
Don't get this wrong
We have to leave some proof
Of what?
That we've had intercourse
Now you get it
Your honour
Bring in the prisoners
Bring in Wang Chenglong, Mrs. Tao
The adulterers are here
I've been wronged...
Silence...
Open it
Yes
I've been wronged...
Judge, I've been wronged...
Wang Chenglong
Here
Mrs. Tao
Over here
Judge
Are you Mrs. Tao?
Yes
Then who's she?
Wang Chenglong's wife
Wang Chenglong
Is she your wife?
Yes, my wife. Her maiden name is Zhou
We were asleep at home
I'm not sure what we had done
to offend Mr. Tao
Mr. Tao came in and tied us up
Tao Sanxing, what do you call this?
This... it's all so baffling!
Phew! You're the one who's baffling
Your honour
He accused me of having an affair
a few days ago
He made a scene at my mother's house
Summoned my brothers
Sir, he's a neurotic
He has always been suspicious
Tao Sanxing will get...
forty strokes of cane
Yes
End of case
Please count
It's fine
We're not in it for money
I know
Thanks
I've told you to leave
I...
This can't be?
Why not?
We had a deal
And you don't have to pay us
Your wife will. Isn't that great?
I mean...
Just go...
Which one of you wants to go first?
Come on
You go ahead
You're taller. After you
You're older, after you
Go on, please
The elder first, please
- No...
- You first
- Please
You two figure it out
I'll go first
Then I'm off
Please
"Be a good civil servant"
And then what happened?
My husband was angry when he got home
Then he fell sick and died
What happened to Wang Dachui's wife?
She's working here too
Really? What's her name?
What's on your mind?
Waiter...
Coming...
Where's Yindi?
She'll be right here
Go look for her
Yes...
Big...
How's your luck today?
Hurry
Coming...
Come on, the customer's waiting
Let him wait
He can take care of himself
Come on
I'll be right back
Go...
Coming...
So annoying!
It's you?
Peiqin
Cousin Erhu
How have you been?
Are they treating you well?
How did you get out?
I sneaked out
How?
They'll catch you
No big deal
I'll take my chances in order to see you
So sweet!
What are you doing?
Don't feign ignorance; Go
Go back to where you belong
Let go of me...
Go
Peiqin
Cousin Erhu
Let go of me...
Peiqin
Cousin Erhu
Don't worry, Peiqin
I'll come back for you
Cousin Erhu
Let go of me...
Peiqin
Cousin Erhu
Let's check on her
What's going on? Who's he?
My cousin, Fan Erhu
Your cousin?
I was engaged to him since we were little
Then my father opted for wealth
He married me off to the Gao family
To a husband who's 10 years my junior
Yuzhu
Father
What are you doing?
You're about to get married
and start a family
How could you behave like a child?
What kind of a person will you turn into?
The young master is about to be a groom
I think he's just very happy about it
Father, I asked him to play with me
Shut up
Come with me
You're about to get married...
and start a family
Bouncing around whole day
So childish! This just isn't done
Yuzhu
After one gets married,
one gets along well...
with the in-laws and starts a family
The day after tomorrow is your wedding
The Hans are a respectable family
A family of scholars
Miss Peiqin is a learned lady
She's twenty four
24? She's a year older than
my seventh mom
Nonsense
Master, the virility supplement is ready
What did Mrs. Ke say?
She'll be here soon
Mrs. Ke is a well-informed lady
That's why I invited her here. I mean,
to teach you about the bedroom etiquette
You must pay attention
Mrs. Ke is teaching the young master
about sex?
And see if he's ready to have sex yet
Have sex? Of course I can
I've just tried it with Yuzhen
What?
Jumping on the ground
That's not what it is
Simply ridiculous
You should be more careful
If we don't teach him properly,
then he'll...
make a fool of himself in front of Ms Han
She'll of course forgive him
Master, you said that Mrs. Ke can tell
whether the young master's ready or not
She said she can...
Around the neck once
Put this in half
Measure from the nose to the ear
He's ready if it passes the ear
Otherwise...
He'll have to postpone his wedding
...to a later date
Emperor Guangxu
became sexually active too young
That's why he was impotent
It's recorded in the book?
Absolutely
The Emperor Guangxu...
had four sex education teachers
One of them was my Third auntie
Another my fourth auntie
Unbelievable! Is he really 8 years old?
Like father, like son
Right, you have a good name
Gao Tiande, meaning the blessed one
Congratulations! I think...
you will have a grandson within one year
He's a naughty boy
Let's see how good the teacher is
That's not fair
Teacher can teach,
but the student must learn
An accomplished pupil
must have a good mentor
We don't have to go into this
Man's lust for food and sex is natural
Nothing can be excessive... especially sex
that involves staying healthy
and birth control
There are certain dates
I mean... during the year
There're 101 days
you can't have intercourse
Then during First day of Spring
First day of Autumn
Summer solstice, winter solstice
And on a few particular festivals
During the middle of a month;
all these days
you must refrain from having intercourse
Remember...
or you'll suffer when you're old
You'll be in pain, coughing all the time
Do you agree?
All right
Let's begin
Let's start
Please start, Mrs. Ke
Sorry?
Please start
You want to listen too?
Sorry, this lesson is meant as one-to-one
No third party
I understand
Gao Ming, Gao Ma, leave us
You too
Sorry
No problem
What are you doing? Get up
What were you thinking?
Sex, of course
Pardon?
Hey, are you mad?
With you?
Silly brat
Get up, get dressed
What then?
Theories and the terms first
You aren't ready...
for the real thing yet
Look at this
Done?
This represents your willy
My willy? What willy?
Your peepee
My...
My peepee is called a "willy"
Then what does your peepee go by?
Ridiculous
No
Listen, Miss Han is so learned
Remember to be civilized
You can't say peepee or willy
What then?
There're many ways to call it
Just observe the proper etiquette
Not the prick, too vulgar
The penis
Or the member
Member of what?
Not that kind of member
The member
The private part
The Phallus
Phallus
Genitals
Pecker
Got it?
Got it
Have you memorized?
Yep
Let's repeat
This is called...
A...
What?
Handkerchief
Dayu, Mrs. Ke is teaching
Keep quiet, leave
The male has 5 principles;
& the female- 5 desires
You must practise sex correctly
Only then can both partners benefit
Although there are many styles
Most well known
being the 9 ancient styles
Dragon, Tiger, Ape
Cicada, Turtle, Rabbit
Phoenix, Fish and Crane
At your age, just go with the flow
Male is Yang, female is Yin
Heaven is Yang, earth is Yin
Sun is Yang, moon is yin
After you're married pay your respects...
to the gods
before you engage in intercourse
The heaven is above, earth below
The sun is above, moon below
You're on top, Miss Han under
Otherwise you'll be hurting yourself
Really?
Yes
Oh no!
What?
Dayu has done it wrong
Who's Dayu?
The Seventh aunt's maid
What has she done?
She's on top every time!
Here's the bride
Zhang, get the fire pan
Coming...
Hurry
Over the fire, blessed with children
Over the saddle,
blessed with lots of gold
To bear children soon
Longans
Lychees
Happily together ever after
Congratulations
All the very best
A happy occasion indeed
Congratulations
Eat up
So? Not done?
It's hot
Not done yet
Bride, yes?
How?
Congratulations
You'll have a grandson next year
Let's go
Yes
Come on
I'm going too
Let's go over there
Quiet
Heaven on top, earth below
Sun on top, moon below
I'm on top, you're below
Keep quiet
One sound and I'll kill you. Get down
Don't!
No...
Please
My name is Fan Erhu
I'm her cousin
We were engaged since we were little
Her father opted for wealth
You were just a kid
Tonight is our wedding night
You sit still
If you make a sound
Blood will be on my dagger
You understand?
Hu
Hu? Who's that?
As strong as a tiger
Heaven on top, earth below
Sun on top, moon below
I'm not on top, you're on top;
how absurd!
I'm impressed
You'll have a grandson next year
You're a good teacher
Of what good is that?
Your son outshines you
Harmful to your health!
It's breakfast time,
young master and lady
It's time for breakfast
Young master
Who is it?
It's time for breakfast
Ask them to leave the food outside
They said to leave the food outside
They?
I heard a man's voice
Why's that?
Master, it's almost noon
You should get up
Again
Young master, young lady
Coming...
Morning, young lady
The master's still asleep, let me
Young master
Dayu
Get out
I'll beat him if you don't leave.
Now scram
Just get out
Out
Yes
What did you say?
They tied up the young master?
What should we do now?
Master, we must be careful
They have the young master
as their hostage
Call the police...
Come on
Get them out now
Or I'll kill him
Dad...
Everyone, let's talk over there...
Cousin Erhu
Don't worry
They treat us terribly
We'll do the same
Now that they're worried
We should just enjoy ourselves, come on
Tell them to give up
Or Han Peiqin's parents
will get the cane too
Yes
Go on then
They're the ones getting the cane
If they really love me
They wouldn't have married me here
40 strokes of cane?!
Even 80 won't suffice
Sir, then...
Look
Shut up
Shut up, little ass
A pair of animals
Animals?
Then what happened?
Cousin Erhu got caned 100 strokes
Sentenced to life in prison
Do you know
who's my first customer here?
Who?
Tell us
The judge for my case
Morals and virtues; bloody hypocrites!
They are the ones who are the worst
I heard you've left our line of work
What are you doing back here again?
Back here again?
I've been in and out of this place thrice
Three times?
I was married to a pawn shop owner once
We separated because of a tree
A tree?
A tree
A tree of sin
It was actually a pear tree
Just like any other tree
It grows normally
Deng Hongfa knew that
...the tree was unique
Mr. Deng opened a pawn shop
He's a well known miser, quite well off
His hobbies include Taichi,
keeping birds as pets
In order to feed his birds...
He often looked for grasshoppers
in the garden
The story regarding the tree of sin
happened one day when Deng Hongfa
...looked down from the tree
Everyone under the tree appeared naked
But it's all normal
when not seen from the tree
He put up a notice on the tree
No climbing
Actually it's my trick
Are you hungry?
Hungry?
Comfortable?
Yes
After his first wife passed away
...I took her place
The old man is quite young at heart
But he's lousy in bed
My maid Xiaoyu acted as my go-between
There're plenty of young guys in the shop
Xiaocai
Madam
What?
Xiaocai said a sailor pawned his wife
Pawned his wife?
How?
One who doesn't need to be fed
...and who never gets jealous
That's ridiculous
It's been written in books
They are made for the sailors
Made from rubber, called puppet wife
When you blow it up,
it becomes a life size doll
I want to take a look
Xiaocai
Yes?
I heard a sailor pawned a rubber doll
Yes, anything is possible
I want to take a look
What? I better safe keep it
Otherwise you young lads
...will steal it and ruin it
It's all wrapped up
The boss is mean, no one would dare
Yes, maybe for the others
I mean, you ain'tjust stealing
the rubber doll!
Quick, let me see
Okay, come with me
Hurry
I'll get it
It's horrible!
How could it be compared to you?
Sailors spend most of their time onboard
Well, something is better than nothing
Anyone will do when one is desperate
Almost
Done
Stop it
Xiaocai has been acting strange lately
He can't focus on his work
Do you know why?
Not focused?
I haven't noticed
Of course you haven't
These few days whenever he sees me...
He's been acting very sneaky
I think he's up to no good
Xiaocai has been working for
over 6 years now
One must protect his own interests first
You take over his job starting tomorrow
Me...
Send him to manage the front desk
Then we'll see after a few months
I'll get him
to pass you the keys tomorrow
I've got my own set of keys
You must be responsible
I...
Remember
You must be loyal to me and the company
I'll test you from time to time
If you're loyal, you'll be rewarded
If not...
You trust me
Of course I'll be loyal
That's good to know
Follow me
Practise first
You'll get used to it
...once you gain more experience
Pay attention to details, work seriously
Most important is being loyal
Yes...
You
No wonder you've been
acting strange lately
You're sleeping with someone here?
A customer pawned this,
I'm just trying it out
Trying it out?
You'll ruin it,
can you pay for the damages?
I was... just curious
Curious! What kind of excuse is that?
Why don't you just find a woman?
Clean it up right away
Send it to my room tonight
Right, starting tomorrow
Pass the keys to Guo Zixiang
You work on the front desk
He'll take over, got it?
Yes, boss
Go
Xiaoyu
Where were you?
I've been looking for you everywhere
I was right here
Cook some ginseng soup for me
I'm busy
What?
The madam has asked me
to run some errands
What kind of errands?
Buying dried melon seeds
What kind of attitude was that?
Come along...
Let's play mahjong
We are very lucky
You're in a good mood today
For business
one has got to be in good spirits
You'll make more
when you're in a good mood
24 rounds are too much, 8 are too little
12 rounds is fine
Go ahead, I'll go check on the books
I hope you'll win more, dear
You should treat us today,
you are promoted
Right...
The madam should treat us today
The boss loves her so much
Goes without saying!
When he loves her...
she will be nicer to him too
As for my husband, the most...
he loves his moustache,
his pet birds the second
His teeth the third
He doesn't take me seriously though
...unless he needs a favor
I win
Didn't expect you to win!
Just going with the flow
Good going! You're cool
Where is the White Dragon?
You're trying to be elusive but anyhow...
I still adore you
Be loyal, I'll test you from time to time
Xiaoyu, you take my place
I'll get even today
Xiaoyu, your small nose and small eyes
What a lovely face
You're a good girl, lying down so still
So submissive
I'm going to show you what I've got
Such a pretty face
Take a closer look, I'm your wife
Well? Yes or no?
Must have cost you a fortune
Yes, if you like it...
you may have it
Are you teasing me? This is from you?
Of course not
The madam gave this to you
The madam?
A gift for your promotion
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
You'd feel uneasy
when you've received a gift
...which you know you don't deserve
So you should do your part, agree?
My part? What part?
The boss is going away
...for a short trip
Madam will be bored alone
Why don't you accompany her tonight?
To do what? Play mahjong?
You and her together
Do what? Play chess?
I don't know how
There're plenty of things you could do
Notjust playing chess
When the door is closed...
You can do whatever you want
No one would care
I've got it
At least you're not stupid
The boss sent you to test me, right?
Test you?
For what?
My loyalty
You thought I don't know?
You're unbelievable
What are you talking about?
You should know madam's nature
Am I the type of person to do
such a thing?
That's so wrong of you
I believe you,
I don't want you to get into trouble
If the madam is serious about it
I've a problem for her to solve
What problem?
She must prove that
the boss isn't testing me
First, kill one of the boss' birds
Why?
Then
Pluck out three hairs of his moustache
He hasn't got many
Lastly... take out one of his teeth
Fine if you're not interested
You think you're the last man on earth?
She will give up now
And you won't be caught in the middle
No big deal
When there's a will, there's a way
Tell him to wait and see
Xiaoyu
Yes?
Come here
I'm busy
You're a champ
I love my moustache
Dense & thick. Great, isn't it!
Look at you
One can have anything except sickness
One can do without anything
except money
Yes, you're quite a man
Rich, healthy
What's so unusual about it?
People at my age...
don't have the sturdy teeth I have
I'm not bluffing
I've never been to a dentist
And for my moustache...
It's unique too
You'll need to have the right amount
You know?
Good, champion is champion
So?
Good, it's the champion
I've told you so
It's clear who's the winner, right?
Yes...
So impressive
What do you say?
Of course...
Needs to be cleaned everyday
So spoiled
Or he'll be in a bad temper
So crazy
More demanding than my wife
So spoiled
Right...
Exactly
Look
Look, from Emperor Kangxi
These accessories
I've spent a fortune on them
But they're worth it
I saw a bird cage a few days ago
Twenty six thousand dollars
Twenty six thousand!
One could buy a house with that
He said it belonged to
the Emperor Qianlong
It's the best porcelain
With the seal of the famous artist
What are you doing?
What?
Are you mad?
Yes I am
Since we got married...
I haven't had one good day
I had to take nonsense
from your dead wife before
And now I have to deal with you!
I can't stand it
This is the champion
My champ
The champion?
He is the champ in your eyes
You spend time with him everyday
Wash him and feed him
Why don't you spend some time with me?
Why don't you buy antiques for me?
Why don't you bathe me?
Are you married to your wife or the bird?
I have a tough life
What a bitter life!
I mean, see... she's jealous
I'd say you're blessed, it's love
Love?
Love
My dear, well...
What now? We'll get a divorce
if you keep the birds
You...
She is jealous.
That's what is love, you know
Love?
I've wasted my money
Great moustache, good for longevity
Boss, here are the accounts
from last month
Please take a look
Pass this to the lady
Madam, please take a look
Wait, say that again
A goose in the sky, a goose on the ground
I eat an goose egg, I become the goose
Listen to me
You've got it wrong, so silly
What? It sounds easy
Try it yourself
Listen
Hold on
If you can't memorize it...
What? I get beheaded?
No, but we'll punish you
Do I get rewarded if I get it right?
Of course...
How?
I'll be generous
If you can get it right
Xiaoyu will smother you with a kiss
Really?
Yes, Xiaoyu?
And the punishment?
If you get it wrong
A hair plucked
from your moustache each time
Pluck my moustache? No way
Then I won't kiss you
If you refuse
Fine, it's a deal
Guo Zixiang, you're our witness
Repeat it
A goose in the sky, a goose on the ground
I eat an goose egg, I become the goose
It's simple
Hold on
You must keep your word
Xiaoyu, you too
Go on
One, two, three
A goose in the sky, a goose on the ground
I eat the goose...
I eat the goose? That didn't count
No way
Drop it down
No
You'll do this for real?
Come on, Xiaoyu
Sure
You'll really pull?
Don't try to get away with it
Come on, again
Listen...
A goose in the sky, a goose on the ground
Goose... over
Another one, come on
This side
It has to be even
One more go
Listen well
A goose in the sky, a goose on the ground
I eat an goose egg, I become the goose
I eat... a goose egg?
I give up, not again
No, the last one
Xiaoyu, come on
Pluck from the middle
What did you do that for?
Xiaoyu, be good
Let him kiss you
All right
Come on
It stinks
Excuse me?
The master has bad breath
No way! You smell it
So?
I think I'm used to it
I don't notice it anymore
I've wanted to tell you since long
My father had the same problem
After he went to the dentist
...it was discovered that
he had cavities
My tooth...
It hurts?
Of course...
Better now?
A little
Let's have a look
Pass it
Closer
Better now?
My tooth?
It doesn't look like mine
Of course it's yours
It's your tooth
Am I a dog?
It doesn't look like mine
Of course it's yours
They all look the same
It hurts
Any smell?
Yes
Smells like medicine
Gradually it'll be okay
No, I'm still worried
I'm looking forward to it
I'm just trying to be a good guy
How about another problem?
Another one?
Just trying to back her off
Tell her that
In front of the master
In front of the master?
Do what?
Whatever she wants to do
In front of the master?
I'm impressed
Fine, I'll do it
He must go with the flow though
It's the Guanyin Festival the day after
Look, the pears are huge
Still not ripe yet
I want to eat
It's not time yet
I like it
You're really wayward
Guo Zixiang, help me out
Go get some pears
Boss, you...
How could you do this here?
What about us?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with us?
You...
Today is the Guanyin Festival
and you're like this here...
What? Get down here...
What's going on?
This... it's strange
What?
You're wearing clothes again?
Of course I'm dressed, are you crazy?
I'm dressed
You said I was naked?
This tree...
What about it?
You should go take a look yourself
I...
Let me help you
What are you doing?
What? We aren't doing anything
How could you?
This is a tree of sin...
Excellent trick
Then the old man went berserk
...and died soon after
What about the young man?
Heartless man
He might seem silly...
but actually he's up to no good
What did he do?
He and Xiaoyu
...they ran away together
Terrible!
Miss Jinbao
Mr. Wang is here
Who? Which one?
The one who took out his tooth
Really?
Jinbao...
Who are you?
What's your name?
Don't you recognize me?
Any woman could be my mother here
Any rich man could be my customer,
poor man...
Jinbao...
I know I've left for too long
I came back as soon as possible
I've bought everything you wanted
from Shanghai
and the money, but I...
You got robbed on the way, right?
How did you know?
Well, I have heard the story before
An old tale, huh?
It's the truth, you don't believe?
Yes, I believe you. It's over
Do me a favor
Find another Juliet
I've no time for you
Have you forgotten about me?
What about your hair?
C'mon, give me a break
What? It's fake?
Really?
If that's for real...
then all the girls here would be bald
What about my tooth?
You want it back?
Should have told me sooner
Mr. Wang
Oh, cheer up
Pick it yourself
Our teeth!
Come out and greet the guests
Girls from upstairs, downstairs,
front and backyards
Greet the guests
Coming
Haixian
Yindi
Jinbao