[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 人人二维码,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00016A17,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134
Style: 哒哒字幕组,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,4,1
Style: 滚屏广告,思源宋体 Heavy,14,&H0001EEF1,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.5,8,10,10,1,134
Style: 歌词,【初遇】你好，旧时光,10,&H0004A7FB,&H000000FF,&H001B1B1B,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,9,5,5,5,1
Style: 屏字,微软雅黑,20,&H23E5EAEC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,60,1
Style: 硬字幕,文鼎霹雳体,20,&H00507497,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 备注解释,思源黑体 CN Medium,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.3,8,10,10,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.39,0:00:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主啊  我就这样一直一直走
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.19,0:00:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沿着那条你为我选的路
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.36,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是它究竟是通往哪里呢  这又是为了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.08,0:00:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被困住了  而且永失自由
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.20,0:00:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人死了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.82,0:00:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师托马斯贿赂你的飞行员让他降低飞行高度
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.46,0:00:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是一次自杀式的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.50,0:00:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孙子失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.57,0:00:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是你计划的一部分吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.38,0:00:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你作出了你的决定  你也得让我有选择的余地
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.19,0:00:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个行为叫做堕胎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.47,0:00:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主和我绝不会原谅你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.58,0:00:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在耍我吗  还是你在考验我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.31,0:00:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为我愿意做任何我必须做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.75,0:00:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈要处理一些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.09,0:00:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还得做一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.62,0:00:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切原来都是为了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.78,0:00:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个累赘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.03,0:00:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是目击证人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.06,0:00:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 快报警  - 宝宝快要出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.73,0:00:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伟大的主  请您开导我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.29,0:00:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在继续  加油  请您与我对话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.76,0:00:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了与我对话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.58,0:00:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个孩子丢失了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.88,0:01:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.89,0:01:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是丢失
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.06,0:01:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被带走了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.64,0:01:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,34小时前  我们的宝贝杰西被绑架了\N{\fs12}34 hours ago, our baby boy Jesús was kidnapped
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.57,0:01:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个叫哈门德·辛的男人将其绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.32,0:01:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在在警察和联邦调查局正在努力搜查
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.10,0:01:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这宗犯罪时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.27,0:01:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想向他保证
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.41,0:01:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和家人们对杰西的信念是坚不可摧的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.70,0:01:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  把我们的杰西还回来\N{\fs12}and bring Jesús back to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.24,0:01:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的心碎了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.15,0:01:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友  我们需要一个奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.09,0:01:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您的提示
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.43,0:01:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.02,0:01:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和一个男人走了  然后就
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.06,0:01:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让杰西独自一个人\N{\fs12}I left Jesús alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.82,0:02:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝才是作出判断的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.16,0:02:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他将宽恕一切
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.14,0:02:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.96,0:02:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不生我气
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.52,0:02:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  不会再有人惩罚你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.04,0:02:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你现在正在惩罚你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.65,0:02:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦白说  我们现在没有时间去浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.12,0:02:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝爱众生  你的电话响了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.47,0:02:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拯救杰西  这里是瑞秋\N{\fs12}Save Jesús, this is Rachel.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.87,0:02:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做得太过分了  我逼错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.82,0:02:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我第一次戴上手套的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.98,0:02:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在普莱·马诺利托的健身房
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.68,0:02:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得你是怎么跟我说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.01,0:02:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你会一直站着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.55,0:02:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会一直战斗下去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.27,0:02:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他就在外面  妈妈  - 真希望我也这样认为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.33,0:02:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是让我要坚持战斗的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.83,0:02:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果现在你放弃了  我就真是一无所有了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.59,0:02:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.12,0:02:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要带走我的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.68,0:03:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可怜的人没有意识到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.35,0:03:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的荣光是我的庇护
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.68,0:03:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们永远也无法打破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.30,0:03:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的意志必将实现
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.02,0:03:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及我的信念
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.14,0:03:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及我的信念必将得到回报
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.48,0:03:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您  我的救世主
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.96,0:03:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  这是我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.55,0:03:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拳赛结束后  你需要过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.27,0:03:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一些关于你父亲的大新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.55,0:03:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及都发生了什么事  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.61,0:03:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回见
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.83,0:03:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都没说是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.08,0:03:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事关于尤金的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.56,0:03:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不是  - 尤金的死
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.89,0:03:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克的谋杀  贝琪的袭击  现在是杰西\N{\fs12}Luke's murder, Becky's attack, now Jesús?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.05,0:03:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都与哈门德·辛相关
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.09,0:03:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在卢克家时  他给我看了些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.92,0:04:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在组建一个犯罪布景板
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.40,0:04:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德  1820团体  牧师  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.24,0:04:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  你  玛格利特  我们都在其中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.03,0:04:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他坚信我的父亲是被谋杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.62,0:04:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也曾告诉我这些事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.78,0:04:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果当时我在那里  他就能活着了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.54,0:04:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他不会的  你俩都会死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.67,0:04:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不知道自己的归属了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.35,0:04:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.16,0:04:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我而言再也没有安全的地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.77,0:04:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时此刻有很多人都需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.46,0:04:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你喜不喜欢  自从尤金死后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.73,0:04:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的生活涌入了更多的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.69,0:04:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些人被你所感动  一些人则是感动了你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.17,0:04:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪着他们一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.31,0:04:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会继续追查下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.40,0:04:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看警察在卢克家发现了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.94,0:04:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不禁怀疑  如果那个人当时还在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.41,0:05:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我生了孩子之后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.30,0:05:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被带走的会不会是我的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.02,0:05:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是主庇护了他的平安
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.30,0:05:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得相信这是因为他想让我们解决眼下的难题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.33,0:05:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为我们本应就是的一家人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.48,0:05:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你和我注定不会在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.31,0:05:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.71,0:05:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个孩子失踪了  你应该去帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.52,0:05:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你  贝克
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.52,0:06:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有受伤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.06,0:06:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我很好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.76,0:06:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.19,0:06:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很感谢你保释我出来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.43,0:06:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.46,0:06:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事我得告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.10,0:06:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.88,0:06:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克·康利
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.55,0:06:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.63,0:06:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察告诉了我所有事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.00,0:06:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该让我自生自灭的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.80,0:06:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能那样对我儿子的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.34,0:06:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比任何人都要了解他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.09,0:06:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们流着共同的血液
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.07,0:06:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.40,0:06:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我失去了我的孩子  但幸好我找到了你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.39,0:06:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.74,0:07:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你房间的钥匙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.27,0:07:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却没能保护好你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.81,0:07:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本应是我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.59,0:07:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不适合自怨自艾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.48,0:07:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他见到我的时候并没有很惊讶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.67,0:07:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是去找我的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.09,0:07:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个世界都崩塌了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.76,0:07:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你表现得那么轻描淡写  仿佛都过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.76,0:07:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所有自私的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.84,0:07:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的欲望  我的恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.31,0:07:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们都不会再影响我了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.78,0:07:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是我的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.73,0:07:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想这是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.82,0:07:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可能我没参与其中是好事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.18,0:07:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有名字了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.74,0:07:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没准备好告诉她她的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.96,0:07:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字可是定义一个人的第一要素
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.79,0:07:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在没有他们自身同意的情况下定义了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.47,0:07:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望她尽可能自由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.83,0:07:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.68,0:08:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你教会了我自由是多么美好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.86,0:08:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 同时有多危险  - 我想陪在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.18,0:08:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.19,0:08:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有救世主情结
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.82,0:08:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像其他人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.82,0:08:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们觉得很特别
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.65,0:08:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.49,0:08:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我而言不是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.87,0:08:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那埃里克呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.50,0:08:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想讨论你的兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.46,0:08:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的  我了解那是什么感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.13,0:08:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在没有父亲的陪伴下长大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.52,0:08:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别让她经历这些
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.97,0:08:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说回到埃里克身边
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.53,0:08:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就给他腾点地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.69,0:09:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.46,0:09:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有家  从未有过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.60,0:09:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说只不过是不同的墙和屋顶罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.05,0:09:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你感到难过  金吉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.22,0:09:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.12,0:09:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们认定这是抢劫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.73,0:09:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本月该地区是第五次了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.46,0:09:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的人有移动什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.06,0:09:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这间公寓里的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.07,0:09:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只移动了尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.36,0:09:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他一切都和之前一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.13,0:09:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事再打电话给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.62,0:10:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特  我是为你和你的家人而来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.93,0:10:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候想播出  我都准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.19,0:10:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 请你离开  - 我知道你很难过
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.00,0:10:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  玛格丽特  你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.30,0:10:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.69,0:10:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的宝宝可能就是因为你才去世的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.47,0:10:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西还活着\N{\fs12}Jesús isn't dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.93,0:10:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德绝不会伤害孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.57,0:10:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个狂热信徒  他坚信
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.73,0:10:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是《启示录》的证人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.18,0:10:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是上帝派来让基督重新登上王位的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.35,0:10:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管听起来有多疯狂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.98,0:10:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他坚信杰西是救世主转世\N{\fs12}he believes that Jesús is our savior returned.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.85,0:10:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么对一个疯子想法如此确定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.79,0:10:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我干的  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.02,0:10:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是1820团体
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.63,0:10:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被解雇了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.30,0:10:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你并不能解雇我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.22,0:10:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.39,0:10:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走  我的信徒都会跟我走
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你走的我都放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.93,0:10:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的节目被取消了  牧师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.44,0:11:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.61,0:11:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.15,0:11:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不认识我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.66,0:11:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前在这儿做礼拜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.85,0:11:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是个孩子的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.16,0:11:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也在这儿做礼拜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.75,0:11:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个笑话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.50,0:11:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富人  穷人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.17,0:11:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都像垃圾一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.90,0:11:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又回到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.59,0:11:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝喜欢开这样的玩笑  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.96,0:11:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把我像昨天的垃圾一样扔出去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.26,0:11:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开我的信徒我还是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.91,0:11:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从贫穷一路走到富裕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.04,0:11:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼓舞了数百万的基督徒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.80,0:11:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记住我们从哪儿来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.08,0:11:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的父母  连这个称号都配不上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.19,0:11:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们酗酒  给我们的只有二手衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.95,0:11:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和食不果腹的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.36,0:11:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的信念和你的才能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.70,0:11:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们从绝望中拯救出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.42,0:11:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别怪我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.03,0:12:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别因为他对你做的事怪我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.55,0:12:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.91,0:12:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能再次完全信任你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.73,0:12:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是我的家人  保罗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.09,0:12:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有了尤金·蒙罗  我们该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.19,0:12:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上天自有安排
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.95,0:12:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金找到我们  是上天的安排
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.58,0:12:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特现在开除你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.25,0:12:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是上天的安排
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.31,0:12:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好事会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.82,0:12:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个宝宝就是一个迹象
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.38,0:12:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望能相信
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.51,0:12:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须始终相信自己的信仰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.02,0:12:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的民众会追随你  在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.01,0:12:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会建立一个新的更强大的盟约
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.67,0:13:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德  有人说你是一个真正的信仰者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.99,0:13:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.95,0:13:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道有时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.95,0:13:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会曲解上帝的话语
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.24,0:13:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以满足自己的需要和信仰
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.13,0:13:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.79,0:13:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真相是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.58,0:13:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也因此感到惭愧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.97,0:13:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.99,0:13:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都有缺点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.39,0:13:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们的小男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.67,0:13:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是你的救世主
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.98,0:13:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.93,0:13:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝会告诉你把这个孩子还给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.27,0:13:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  非常感谢您的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.32,0:13:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会传达出去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.89,0:13:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝福你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.34,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看得出来你不太舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.90,0:14:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都在盯着我  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.39,0:14:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们知道我干了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.07,0:14:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.52,0:14:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想要原谅自己
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.80,0:14:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就必须
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.36,0:14:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竭尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.35,0:14:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解决这个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.53,0:14:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拯救杰西行动组  我是萝丝\N{\fs12}Save Jesús, this is Rose.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.27,0:14:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 埃里克  跟我谈谈  求你了  - 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.17,0:14:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 发生这事我真的很抱歉  - 瑞秋  别提了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.84,0:14:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 为我们做的事万分抱歉  - 瑞秋  别提了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.22,0:14:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.34,0:15:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你看着我的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.31,0:15:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我我不是个坏人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.43,0:15:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞秋  你是个天使
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.65,0:15:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我认识的唯一一个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.96,0:15:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  我会传达这个信息
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.54,0:15:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝您生活愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.91,0:15:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守夜怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.76,0:15:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是个守夜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.71,0:15:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太糟了  你怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.29,0:15:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是像其他人一样做分内的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.18,0:15:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是说纽约这事发生之后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.66,0:15:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉很惭愧  难过  焦虑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.44,0:15:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但都是关于杰西的\N{\fs12}but all of that is about Jesús.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.02,0:15:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我今天确实脑子很乱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.14,0:15:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得这都跟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.51,0:15:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纽约没有任何关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.14,0:15:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.81,0:15:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.98,0:15:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以写得清楚点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.80,0:16:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*耶稣  让我待在十字架旁*
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.69,0:16:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*有一个珍贵的喷泉*
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.26,0:16:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您  很感激您的祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.31,0:16:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在坎昆看到杰西了\N{\fs12}You saw Jesús in Cancún?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.36,0:16:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两周前
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.98,0:16:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是他  不过谢谢你打过来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.51,0:16:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.85,0:16:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.22,0:16:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在十字架旁*
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.00,0:16:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在十字架旁*
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.16,0:16:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人要咖啡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.69,0:16:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不用了  谢谢  - 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.58,0:16:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去喝点咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.99,0:16:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*直到我欣喜的灵魂*
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.51,0:16:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在第一声响时接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.37,0:16:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.91,0:17:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚从纽约回来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.54,0:17:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚从监狱出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.88,0:17:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你揍了那个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.17,0:17:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只为了捍卫我的荣誉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.69,0:17:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  他的确是自找的  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.19,0:17:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但请不要再做这种事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.03,0:17:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我反应得很不好  我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.75,0:17:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还有别的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.59,0:17:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在我周围散发光芒*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.86,0:17:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察来的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.40,0:17:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了我的真实身份
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.90,0:17:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在十字架旁*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.08,0:17:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉他们你是马克·康利
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.07,0:17:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言越说越大  我的内心太过煎熬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.20,0:17:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  继续说谎的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.96,0:17:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再继续下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.38,0:17:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*直到我欣喜的灵魂可以找到*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.39,0:17:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在纽约到底发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.68,0:17:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在河边休息*
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.73,0:17:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拯救杰西行动组  我是萝丝\N{\fs12}Save Jesús, this is Rose.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.89,0:18:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在河边休息*
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.32,0:18:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神圣的天父
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.42,0:18:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我谦逊地信仰着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.64,0:18:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在守护我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.92,0:18:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那谁会在反对我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.65,0:18:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是对我信念的测试
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.42,0:18:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我之前的先知
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.49,0:18:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会升华到更伟大的荣誉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.43,0:18:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你已为我安排好的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.05,0:18:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我的妹妹和宝宝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.48,0:18:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我的信徒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.84,0:18:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能感觉到  主
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.90,0:18:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*正如我一样*
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.79,0:18:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*可怜  卑劣的瞎子*
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.02,0:18:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*视线  富裕*
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.13,0:19:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*健康的心灵*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.33,0:19:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我需要去寻找的*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.02,0:19:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*上帝的羔羊啊  我来了*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.73,0:19:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我来了*
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.83,0:19:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我帮助你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.65,0:19:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们见面那天你就这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.19,0:19:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你给了我那本书
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.33,0:19:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教我怎么正确阅读
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.56,0:19:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能找到最深处的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.37,0:19:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那样做了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.34,0:19:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你误解我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.89,0:19:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是你理解错了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.41,0:19:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到这儿祈祷上帝给你安排
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.80,0:19:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是牧师啊  你软弱的思想无法理解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.75,0:19:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝给你的安排是我的出生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.14,0:20:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.02,0:20:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德  我是个简单的人  你也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.95,0:20:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我要把预言变为现实
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.78,0:20:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是目击者  哈门德
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.04,0:20:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是目击者
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.62,0:20:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我最大的罪过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.63,0:20:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的任务完成的很好  保罗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.24,0:20:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.80,0:20:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神圣的天父啊  原谅我  为我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.55,0:20:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有帮忙找我儿子的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.77,0:20:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.65,0:20:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是个从纽约来的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.44,0:20:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们所做的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.75,0:21:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德·辛  我是尤兰达·里维拉·坎达拉里亚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.54,0:21:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西是我孙子\N{\fs12}Jesús is my grandson.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.32,0:21:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个受伤的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.59,0:21:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心和灵魂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.50,0:21:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被你伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.52,0:21:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该恨你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.06,0:21:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但内心深处
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.85,0:21:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该试着理解你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.51,0:21:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉我在科罗拉多发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.77,0:21:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你流产了是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.85,0:21:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.63,0:21:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.65,0:21:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌经历这些却没有你在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.19,0:21:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  我恳求你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.49,0:21:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你还有一丁点道德
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.26,0:21:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请找到它  请你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.26,0:21:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把杰西还给我们  求求你了\N{\fs12}please bring Jesús home to us, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.63,0:22:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他还给我们  求求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.69,0:22:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.86,0:22:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些线索都没什么用
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.27,0:22:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联调局的说已经过去这么久了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.48,0:22:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本没什么希望
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.81,0:22:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们要继续找  永远不能放弃的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.49,0:22:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克 我需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.98,0:22:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要所有人  你也是  金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.83,0:22:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我还是别去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.91,0:22:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞出这么多事情来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.99,0:22:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的有毒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.49,0:22:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远不许再
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.34,0:22:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.76,0:22:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝琪和卢克那件事  本来该我的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.29,0:22:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要找的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.57,0:22:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真是这样  你现在还在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.01,0:22:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说明是上帝想让你在这
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.24,0:22:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 萝丝呢  - 在呢妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.47,0:22:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  我需要所有的孩子们跟我一起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.25,0:22:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直等待一个奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.20,0:22:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在该自己创造奇迹了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.27,0:22:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得有一次我就坐在那个座位上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.85,0:22:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道之后桌子上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.10,0:22:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会有任何食物出现的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.90,0:22:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就一直祈祷一个奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.75,0:23:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够填饱肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.42,0:23:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等可以从教堂出去之后  我们上了车
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.66,0:23:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜我找到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.42,0:23:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满满一车的杂货
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.41,0:23:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像天赐之物一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.61,0:23:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个奇迹是我母亲弄的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.84,0:23:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她放的吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.89,0:23:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母亲可真是个善良的天使啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.23,0:23:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远及时出现帮助所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.65,0:23:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道门口那个车吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.48,0:23:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.46,0:23:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 知道怎么搭上火吗  - 不需要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.40,0:23:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的车
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.52,0:23:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这车开着好像三条腿的狗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.76,0:23:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是还是能送你的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.08,0:23:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再躲藏了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.36,0:23:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来祈祷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.64,0:23:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.61,0:23:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你听听我们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.28,0:23:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此无奈的想要让杰西回家的召唤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.08,0:23:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个带走杰西的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.38,0:23:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁了我们的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.95,0:23:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他能够打开双眼看到自己的罪恶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.46,0:24:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他柔软一点能够意识到自己的错误
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.89,0:24:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.13,0:24:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赐予大家力量吧  主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.23,0:24:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞美主
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.97,0:24:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 哈利路亚  - 赞美主
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.01,0:24:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请听听吧  主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.12,0:24:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不仅仅为了丢失的孩子祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.90,0:24:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为全世界所有丢失的孩子祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.62,0:24:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有被绑架被带走的孩子祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.96,0:24:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为无家可归的孩子祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.95,0:24:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们看到你的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.62,0:24:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带给他们宁静  带领他们回家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.51,0:24:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们回到可以和家人团聚的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.50,0:24:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有尊严被认可被呵护的回来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.59,0:24:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.83,0:24:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.59,0:24:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.65,0:24:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈利路亚
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.66,0:24:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝福那些野兽和孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.61,0:25:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在这个世界上  他们没有话语权
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.89,0:25:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有选择
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.01,0:25:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝福那些野兽和孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.70,0:25:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一张去拉斯维加斯的票
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.85,0:25:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界永远不会成为
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.80,0:25:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们眼中的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.58,0:25:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照亮他们的路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.48,0:25:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱散他们周围的黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.43,0:25:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们爱
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.32,0:25:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照亮他们的路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.71,0:25:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝福那些野兽和孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.55,0:26:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们躲避风雨的家园
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.89,0:26:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你弄醒我之前
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.78,0:26:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在祈祷上帝对你人生的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.39,0:26:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.92,0:26:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.73,0:26:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不会说话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.93,0:26:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德看着点
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.46,0:26:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照亮他们的路
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.43,0:26:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱散他们周围的黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.47,0:26:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.29,0:26:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 给与他们爱  - 需要帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.44,0:26:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可能找到自己的意义了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.03,0:26:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是  我们应该悄悄离开
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.65,0:26:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝福那些野兽和孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.71,0:26:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好了  主
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.42,0:26:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们躲避暴风雨的家园
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.33,0:26:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护他们安全
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.64,0:27:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来庆祝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.49,0:27:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.51,0:27:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞扬主
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.33,0:27:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制造这些奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.46,0:27:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是好累人的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.85,0:27:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都该休息下了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.13,0:27:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  我也得换衣服了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.96,0:27:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真诚感谢各位
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.46,0:27:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝保佑大家
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.16,0:27:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起祈祷  赞扬主
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.02,0:27:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.52,0:27:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.65,0:27:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞扬主
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.73,0:27:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赞美主
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.99,0:27:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赞美主
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.65,0:27:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.24,0:27:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说你真是厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.53,0:27:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我没去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.49,0:27:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切也都不会发生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.17,0:27:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 别这么说  - 你为了我儿子努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.08,0:28:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不顾自己的危险
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.03,0:28:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一点我不会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.54,0:28:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.91,0:28:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要珍惜自己的幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.26,0:28:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特也说了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.02,0:28:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝肯定还是很神奇的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.36,0:28:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  他把我的孩子送回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.02,0:28:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你拥有阳光电视台百分之十六的股份了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.86,0:28:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.59,0:28:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拳赛之后我和唐·卜夏尔做了交易
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.09,0:28:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的股票给我了  现在是你的了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.11,0:28:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才觉得这都是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.92,0:28:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了孩子  无所畏惧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.76,0:28:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒的可是好酒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.75,0:28:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟不是每天抢孩子的神经病
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.84,0:28:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都能被撞死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.73,0:28:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你们多了一千万新用户
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.85,0:28:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才应该度个假吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.81,0:28:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能会去试试有钱人的度假
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.56,0:29:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我去伯利兹一个私人岛屿怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.93,0:29:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 迷茫  - 富有  迷茫  开心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.49,0:29:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的新口头禅
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.10,0:29:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 干杯  - 干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.66,0:29:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚真的很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.91,0:29:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为上帝我们聚集到了一起
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.58,0:29:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本可以走的  金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.25,0:29:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你选择成为这个家庭的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.09,0:29:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里也会永远有你的一席之地
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.08,0:29:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.43,0:29:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周末去露营吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.84,0:29:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花点时间互相了解一下
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.76,0:29:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像一开始就该做的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.79,0:29:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.79,0:29:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们半小时之后出发
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.39,0:29:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.80,0:29:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要单独跟你谈下
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.66,0:29:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.68,0:29:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了一件坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.81,0:29:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不值得被原谅的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.07,0:29:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你做了什么  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.62,0:29:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林都可以搞定的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.24,0:30:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝都会原谅的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.74,0:30:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在保佑我们全家呢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.05,0:30:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便意味着我会失去你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.14,0:30:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要告诉你这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.98,0:30:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.53,0:30:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我兄弟  也是你兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.38,0:30:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他刚醒来的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.82,0:30:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看到了尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.58,0:30:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看到了爸爸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.72,0:30:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实一直没什么信仰的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.33,0:30:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.06,0:30:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他跟我说他看到尤金了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.37,0:30:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我信了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.90,0:30:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后他说  他还想再见他一次
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.43,0:31:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立刻就懂了他的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.69,0:31:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森让我帮他放下这一些
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.59,0:31:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我做了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.29,0:31:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.46,0:31:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮我兄弟自杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.62,0:31:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.00,0:31:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝会怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.78,0:31:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然替上帝做不了主
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.78,0:31:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.18,0:31:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很慷慨
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.59,0:31:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有爱  很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.93,0:31:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很善良
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.94,0:32:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世界好可怕啊  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.37,0:32:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.61,0:32:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.42,0:32:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个记者  卢克
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.09,0:32:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要毁掉我们俩
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.96,0:32:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么努力在弥补的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.35,0:32:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他墙上贴着我们所有人的照片  跟罪犯一样
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.44,0:32:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过跟他解释    你不应该出现在墙上
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.06,0:32:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该因爸爸犯下错误而一起受过
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.86,0:32:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该的   但他不听
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.36,0:32:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想把你照片拿下来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.23,0:32:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克不让我拿
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.78,0:32:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抓着我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.97,0:32:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  你也知道了  我推了他一把
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.51,0:32:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他向后倒去  那儿有个
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.45,0:32:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个裂缝  然后就听到他的呜咽声
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.18,0:32:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再然后就有血冒出来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.35,0:32:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  血太多了 妈  -  我很遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.52,0:32:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我像个胆小鬼一样逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.96,0:32:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把一个人扔在那里等死
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.99,0:32:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把一个人扔在那里孤独等死  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.50,0:33:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我我该怎么办  我不知道该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.69,0:33:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  认真听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.32,0:33:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  你的任务就是陪着贝琪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.27,0:33:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你们新出生的宝贝女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.16,0:33:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  别哭了  站直了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.44,0:33:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的儿子不会是杀人凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.22,0:33:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孙女不会在没有父亲的陪伴下长大
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.75,0:33:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.92,0:33:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会搞定的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.36,0:33:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.92,0:34:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你声音真好听
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.79,0:34:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的歌声  我说不好
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.93,0:34:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我听到了天籁之音
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.95,0:34:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.64,0:34:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想看看我犯了多少罪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.24,0:34:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你背着贝琪出轨瑞秋
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.60,0:34:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你犯了错
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.99,0:34:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.75,0:34:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道圣经里
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.47,0:34:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有罪孽是无法弥补的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.92,0:34:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想大卫王
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.75,0:34:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背着老婆和拔示巴偷情
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.48,0:34:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人滥杀无辜
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.87,0:34:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果呢  他不仅被宽恕
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.54,0:35:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得到了上帝的眷顾
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.10,0:35:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为他所做的善举多于他所犯下的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.26,0:35:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但我不是大卫王
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.63,0:35:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是  但你是个正派人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.01,0:35:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想做正确的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.63,0:35:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说做孩子的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.28,0:35:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝基不想和我扯上关系
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.51,0:35:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怪她
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.27,0:35:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不了解我们的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.96,0:35:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只了解我在电视上看到的他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.78,0:35:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友善  风趣
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.69,0:35:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能闻起来有香草味
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.46,0:35:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但自从我到了新奥尔良
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.29,0:35:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一直有人给我讲
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.55,0:35:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金做的那些可怕的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.00,0:35:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些我印象中的尤金绝对不可能做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.39,0:35:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他做了  他做了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.09,0:36:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.89,0:36:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定很累了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.58,0:36:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克的遗产
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.20,0:36:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪儿拿到这些的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.51,0:36:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从埃里克那里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.04,0:36:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.80,0:36:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他告诉别人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.56,0:36:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.76,0:36:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.14,0:36:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要他别声张  把嘴闭严实
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.51,0:36:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会过去的  但这些不能留在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.68,0:36:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随它去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.27,0:36:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要操心事已经够多的了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.86,0:36:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是你人生中最艰难的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.72,0:36:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来处理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.52,0:36:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道我人生中最难的一天吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.43,0:36:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是去年的十二月二号
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.45,0:36:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金死的那天
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.99,0:36:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他穿着常穿的那件奶油色西装
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.79,0:36:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搭配一块白色口袋方巾
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.63,0:36:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从工作室回家
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.66,0:37:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着佩茜·克莱恩的心碎欲绝
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.76,0:37:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那场景至今都历历在目
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.01,0:37:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说是创伤导致
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.56,0:37:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是上帝给你的考验
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.06,0:37:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你仍旧保持理智  非常难得
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.46,0:37:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  十二月一号
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.73,0:37:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那才是我面临的麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.89,0:37:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天1500万美金转到了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.11,0:37:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金的飞行员账户上
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.99,0:37:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说  富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.77,0:37:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么尤金会在他死的前一天
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.41,0:37:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给一个死人打钱
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.10,0:37:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得在  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.10,0:37:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成人礼舞会那天
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.12,0:37:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来约好
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.26,0:37:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去河边野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.50,0:37:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你没去
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.63,0:38:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林  你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.44,0:38:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被自己的血呛到的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.28,0:38:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你正在和尤金跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.02,0:38:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.67,0:38:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜你的好丈夫和他朋友所赐
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.81,0:38:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我孩子们的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.45,0:38:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是很多孩子的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.66,0:38:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是怎么对待你和其他那些女人们的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.85,0:38:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.35,0:38:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的所有事都是为了你好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.13,0:38:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都在尽力帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.12,0:38:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.30,0:38:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你不任命我为执行总裁
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.71,0:38:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和埃里克并没准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.19,0:38:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比任何人都了解这盘生意
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.97,0:38:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么建立  如何维系
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.16,0:38:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我知道那些尸体埋在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.16,0:38:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么现在我被略过了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.89,0:38:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是直系血亲  富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.01,0:38:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.31,0:38:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信我  我知道我能帮得上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.50,0:38:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是唯一一个爱过你的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.56,0:39:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你想为了尤金把我拉下水
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.56,0:39:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会带走你的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.38,0:39:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  你出去  - 遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.19,0:39:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  嘿  -  嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.64,0:39:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张的一天 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.09,0:39:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.26,0:39:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真的认为是哈门德杀了卢克吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.06,0:39:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是这么想的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.76,0:39:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是没想明白敲门声
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.90,0:39:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈门德·辛是职业杀手
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.92,0:39:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抓住我的时候  迅速且没闹出动静
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.76,0:39:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以为什么  轮到卢克
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.55,0:39:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要一直纠结这些会把自己搞疯掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.59,0:39:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候最简单的答案就是真相
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.50,0:39:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但是这个简单的答案不合理
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.62,0:40:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道玛格丽特在哪儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.18,0:40:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本应该去和她汇合  一起去营地的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.22,0:40:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说不上来
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.90,0:40:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其实还挺期待跟她去那间房子的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.15,0:40:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.06,0:40:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特不会同意的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.06,0:40:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我打算等她
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.32,0:40:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你有的等了  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.75,0:40:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你是庄家  那我就退出牌局
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.63,0:40:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是现在是家人了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.42,0:40:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你是医生  想必我就是一瘸一拐
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.39,0:40:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你享受荣耀
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.69,0:40:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我只能忍受耻辱
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.65,0:40:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在是百万富翁了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.34,0:40:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们还在这破地儿待着干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.07,0:41:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你向往黑暗  就让我们扑灭光明
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.12,0:41:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你送我们回来
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.95,0:41:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气  我能帮的不止这些
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.95,0:41:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字神圣而光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.03,0:41:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血肉之躯却被折辱钉死
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.03,0:41:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万支蜡烛祈求着无法降临的庇佑
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.73,0:41:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你向往黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.23,0:41:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  嘿  - 我的天呐
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.51,0:41:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你今天出来的事情忘得一干二净
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.15,0:41:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  今天发生太多事了  -  没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.27,0:41:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人送我  有个老朋友给我个惊喜
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.44,0:41:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.22,0:41:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么味道
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.78,0:41:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  我在做饭  -  你做饭了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.61,0:41:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个故事中有一个爱人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.75,0:41:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但故事还是一样的结局
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.89,0:41:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人份的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.36,0:41:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦难之中有一首摇篮曲
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.99,0:41:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  金哲
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.45,0:41:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一个可以归咎的悖论
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.92,0:41:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这些都写在圣经文中
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.23,0:41:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是什么无由的论断
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.93,0:41:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你向往黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.57,0:42:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我们扑灭光明
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.06,0:42:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们将囚犯排成一队
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.36,0:42:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守卫们已经举枪瞄准
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.18,0:42:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我抗争过一些恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.53,0:42:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不过平庸怯懦
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.86,0:42:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不知道我被允许
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.52,0:42:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀人伤人
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.76,0:42:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你向往黑暗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.82,0:42:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.16,0:42:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主啊  我做好了准备
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.38,0:42:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不求更多  主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.61,0:42:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经给予我很多了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.05,0:42:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要指点
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.28,0:42:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你告诉我  作为一个母亲我的所作所为是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.29,0:42:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字神圣而光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.79,0:42:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗斯
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.89,0:42:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血肉之躯
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.80,0:42:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却被折辱钉死
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.02,0:43:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  一切都好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.26,0:43:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的  不能更好了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.33,0:43:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.91,0:43:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我们扑灭光明
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.42,0:43:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这里  我做好了准备
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1347\fscy540}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx411\fscy398}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(337.866,150.555)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1326\fscy535}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx409\fscy401}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(336.266,149.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\fscx1420\fscy538\pos(194.48,214.214)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\frx0\fry2\fscx394\fscy391\pos(152.133,211.556)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(219.599,189.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(152.134,244.999)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.97,0:43:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(191.714,65.904)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制\N合作请加QQ:{\c&H0607F9&}2643527418
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.00,0:30:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(194.933,27.178)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.97,0:03:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)\fs25\t(0,0,\fs45)\pos(192,105.067)\c&H1314CE&}富 贵 逼 人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.35,0:03:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：琛Cr 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.61,0:03:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：Allison  廿八 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.37,0:03:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：一江春水向西流 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.66,0:03:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}校对：一江春水向西流 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.34,0:03:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}统筹：折木奉太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.81,0:03:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}总监：一芹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.57,0:03:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(198.08,57.6)\c&H2C1D01&\frz19.91}语音留言
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.10,0:13:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(284.16,64.426)\c&H63500F&}寻人启事\N杰西·里韦拉\N#拯救杰西#
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.38,0:33:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(82.56,192)}“阳光网络”
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.38,0:33:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz37.88\pos(91.84,54.613)\c&H2C1D01&}“交易明细”
