[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 人人二维码,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00016A17,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134
Style: 哒哒字幕组,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,4,1
Style: 滚屏广告,思源宋体 Heavy,20,&H0001EEF1,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.5,8,10,10,1,134
Style: 歌词,【初遇】你好，旧时光,10,&H0004A7FB,&H000000FF,&H001B1B1B,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,9,5,5,5,1
Style: 屏字,微软雅黑,20,&H23E5EAEC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,60,1
Style: 硬字幕,文鼎霹雳体,20,&H00507497,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 备注解释,思源黑体 CN Medium,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.3,8,10,10,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.98,0:00:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的主
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.30,0:00:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你保佑这个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.82,0:00:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大声朗读预言的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.25,0:00:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金在这些照片的最中间
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.40,0:00:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.68,0:00:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你们知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.63,0:00:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在短短的四个月内
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.53,0:00:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们上市了阳光俱乐部
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.95,0:00:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个好兆头
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个脚踏月亮头顶太阳的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.54,0:00:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个头戴12星王冠的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.15,0:00:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怀孕了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.50,0:00:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她生下孩子的时候巨龙正窥探着她
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.07,0:00:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.92,0:00:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他的孩子被上帝眷顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.01,0:00:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好了  我的主
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.68,0:00:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这个女人向荒野逃去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.51,0:00:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在是百万富翁了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.02,0:00:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是至于杀人凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.54,0:00:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没管那个男的  让他独自死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.19,0:00:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 奸诈者  - 我想在这里陪你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.43,0:00:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巫师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.88,0:00:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 原谅我  我必须要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.02,0:00:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶像大师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.19,0:00:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你为了尤金伤害到我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.53,0:00:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你孩子带走
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.69,0:00:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于所有说谎的人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.03,0:00:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哥哥死的时候是我帮过他
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.65,0:00:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们应当葬身于
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.42,0:00:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火海里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.03,0:00:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让那些不义之徒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.41,0:00:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续不义吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.41,0:01:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让神圣继续神圣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.33,0:01:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.45,0:01:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 看好了  - 你好金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.24,0:01:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很快回来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.92,0:01:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,启示录22：12
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.30,0:01:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以你的名字祈祷  阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.52,0:01:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.28,0:01:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这干嘛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.40,0:01:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我有点难过
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.24,0:01:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是厨师的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.36,0:01:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远都没法拥有楼下那些女孩所拥有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.08,0:01:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.99,0:01:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的裙子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.24,0:01:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我第一次亮相的时候穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.17,0:01:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么让富女孩都把乐趣夺走了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.30,0:01:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三  二  一
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.97,0:01:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部上线啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.65,0:02:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.36,0:02:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个特别的时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.06,0:02:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令你的满意的产品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.23,0:02:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在来的路上了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.47,0:02:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有你们的陪伴我们不会有今天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.64,0:02:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们花点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.12,0:02:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来铭记那些已经不在我们身边的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的牧师  保罗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.35,0:02:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是一个正直又令人尊敬的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.87,0:02:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.34,0:02:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们亲爱的尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.97,0:02:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这时他正在天堂望着我们呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.80,0:02:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为上帝的所作所为感到骄傲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.67,0:02:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝做的啥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.76,0:02:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该为她开心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.31,0:02:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部  电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.87,0:02:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贪婪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.10,0:02:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是我过去生活的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.94,0:02:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要小心  不可将善事行在人的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.77,0:02:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故意叫他们看见
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.61,0:02:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是这样  就不能得你们天父的赏赐了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.83,0:03:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥和杰森和她在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.67,0:03:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也应该过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.06,0:03:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是马克了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.38,0:03:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.67,0:03:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几个月前那些
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.55,0:03:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至无法计算蒙罗无限百分比的男孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.17,0:03:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今都有了自己的股份
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.07,0:03:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金钱摧毁了人们  我很高兴自己摆脱了它
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.39,0:03:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  如果是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.24,0:03:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就可以有25年的无偿子女抚养费了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.76,0:03:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们说几句话  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.05,0:03:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别和他计较太多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.81,0:03:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金养活着埃里克和萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.69,0:03:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  安东尼奥和马克拥有他一半的公司了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.07,0:03:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.74,0:03:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你爱他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.37,0:03:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年我一直都不清醒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.15,0:03:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他选择了回归咱们的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.41,0:03:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要留住他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.71,0:03:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少要再留几天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.77,0:03:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是不理解
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.04,0:03:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你要护着玛格丽特和萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.45,0:03:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在乎他们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.88,0:03:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这些在前厅摆成一条线
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要每五英尺放一盆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.05,0:03:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿你们俩  能不能等会再卿卿我我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.30,0:04:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还在适应
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.63,0:04:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们实际上不是亲戚关系这个事儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.28,0:04:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你上楼把你自己打扮的好看点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.27,0:04:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切尽在我的掌握
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.42,0:04:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很感激你对这些事情都这么洒脱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.64,0:04:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  我还在习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.74,0:04:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的女儿嫁给了一个骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.11,0:04:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们承受不起另一个丑闻了  对吗  小可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.15,0:04:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与骗子的相处经验来说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.65,0:04:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远都不会知道最糟糕的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.25,0:04:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除此以外  我的萝丝爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.91,0:04:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱她
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.20,0:04:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好别干啥出格的事儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.93,0:04:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我会立即把你扔到监狱去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.62,0:04:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么可以破坏我女儿完美的婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.59,0:04:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是她的新郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.40,0:04:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这星期打了三轮高尔夫球
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.76,0:04:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天早上要去大岛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看一个房子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.57,0:04:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去沙滩上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.73,0:04:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五英亩的海滩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.46,0:05:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没没见过你脱下过西装和领带
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.22,0:05:01.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个工作狂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.63,0:05:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  以后都不是了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.94,0:05:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上市阳光俱乐部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.06,0:05:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让我四五辈子衣食无忧了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.11,0:05:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我准备坐好数钱了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.99,0:05:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和玛格丽特发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.09,0:05:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直计划提早退休
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.80,0:05:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  她说了什么关于我的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.04,0:05:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主啊  你们上床了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.58,0:05:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特和我确实有些越界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.93,0:05:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了一些我们彼此不应该做的事儿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.96,0:05:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.72,0:05:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国最有权势的基督教妇女
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.72,0:05:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正接到华盛顿每位游说者的电话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.09,0:05:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,华尔街的秃鹰们都在争取她让她走入公众视野
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.03,0:05:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.36,0:05:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女的不需要任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.07,0:05:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为我们的新董事会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.31,0:05:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们将承担重要的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.66,0:05:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.83,0:05:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你去监督每一条点赞的评论
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.46,0:05:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克  你要经营欺诈部门
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.30,0:05:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  这里需要一个懂欺诈的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.34,0:05:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林同意你安排的这个新的董事会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.99,0:06:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林走了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.03,0:06:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.80,0:06:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.06,0:06:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要富兰克林  知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.19,0:06:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为安东尼娅  无论他他妈叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.18,0:06:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都一点也不了解我们的业务
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.99,0:06:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥可以有所作为的  马克很快也可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.99,0:06:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这场结婚安排的可太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.20,0:06:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果萝丝嫁给了马克
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.00,0:06:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的百分之31的股份就仍然在这个家里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.17,0:06:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我从来没想过这些
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.95,0:06:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵  我从来没想过这些
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.65,0:06:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有做过任何事会不向着自己的利益吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.88,0:06:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经对马克进行了尽职调查
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.18,0:06:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保护萝丝就像我保护你一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.99,0:06:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别了吧  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.04,0:06:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我喜欢这样是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.38,0:06:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都不清楚你在想什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.54,0:07:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不包裹住她
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.25,0:07:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要用她那小巧的指甲把自己眼睛给扣出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.33,0:07:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.00,0:07:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡一会儿就会感觉好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.39,0:07:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我闭上眼的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.72,0:07:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会一直看见我哥哥的尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.56,0:07:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是血
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.90,0:07:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.97,0:07:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才会让一个人那样的死去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.07,0:07:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 埃里克  - 嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.28,0:07:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服务怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.06,0:07:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于可以用上你利伯缇大学的学位了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.90,0:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真的疯了才会这样做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.91,0:07:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  别太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.58,0:07:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为你的婚姻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.06,0:07:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失败的一败涂地
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.03,0:07:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我却得到了妈妈的祝福
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.96,0:07:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈这么装模作样只是为了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.46,0:07:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把韦罗妮卡的股份留在家族里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.28,0:07:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她教我们是非对错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.04,0:08:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只是在合适的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.09,0:08:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下  你要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.00,0:08:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别当一个贱人  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.80,0:08:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经给了玛格丽特一些时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.66,0:08:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我认为对我来说是时候重新和我的家人联系了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.93,0:08:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是  除了你和你母亲以外的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.77,0:08:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我理解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.13,0:08:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我得接一下电话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.11,0:08:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.73,0:08:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  你在哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.17,0:08:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这像个心理病房一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.17,0:08:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一个正常的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.81,0:08:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在准备你的结婚礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.19,0:08:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.45,0:08:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿见  我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.33,0:08:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.33,0:08:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.63,0:08:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝今天要和
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.80,0:08:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.41,0:08:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.46,0:08:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前为什么不告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.01,0:08:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你去了  大家就会将今天铭记成
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.68,0:08:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金 · 蒙罗死而复生的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.22,0:08:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而非萝丝 · 蒙罗的结婚日
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.09,0:08:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是我陪她走过红毯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.88,0:08:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才说过不想引人注意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.64,0:08:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能把这个秘密背负在身上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.90,0:09:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负担太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.77,0:09:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母教育我成为正直的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.88,0:09:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是这么教的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.19,0:09:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵循上帝法则  你会得到奖赏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.32,0:09:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,违背上帝法则  你会被惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.85,0:09:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那如果违背上帝法则但仍受到奖赏呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.87,0:09:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你会变得
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.04,0:09:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越来越富有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.75,0:09:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那什么都不重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.66,0:09:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧  什么都不重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.17,0:09:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能生活在上帝是个儿戏的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.47,0:09:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,签了认罪书  他就不是儿戏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.89,0:09:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很快回来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.99,0:10:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.10,0:10:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来要去找你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.33,0:10:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过谢谢你让我们少跑一趟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.89,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  你终于安定下来了  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.68,0:10:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  对  -  感觉如何
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.23,0:10:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我脑子终于正常了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.75,0:10:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强烈推荐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.40,0:10:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次打架之后  肯定有不少女人找你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.28,0:10:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  没我喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.40,0:10:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你个建议  我们现在是有钱人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.15,0:10:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很幸运  我在变富有之前认识的萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.12,0:10:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面可是有大把拜金女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.83,0:10:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  嘿  闪闪动人  -  嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.50,0:10:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.96,0:10:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见你们上电视了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.26,0:10:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在镜头里都非常  非常帅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.26,0:10:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特拖我们上去的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.13,0:10:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  你那时候在哪儿  -  只有股东才能参加
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.95,0:10:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.16,0:11:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,致一直以来支持我们的金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.60,0:11:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后也会继续支持
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.81,0:11:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能想象出来假如我们接受第一笔钱然后就回家会怎样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.18,0:11:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是你  我们不会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.93,0:11:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦白来说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.50,0:11:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是因为你们生命中的女人们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.99,0:11:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维罗妮卡  约皮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.12,0:11:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩还是会破产
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.62,0:11:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,致让这一切变成可能的女人们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.66,0:11:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.66,0:11:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想分她点我的股份
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.46,0:11:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.96,0:11:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也应该进入董事会
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.78,0:11:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你不用因为富有而有负罪感
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.15,0:11:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会有别人进入到你的生活中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.30,0:11:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是他们会心怀不轨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.16,0:11:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰一直以来都替我着想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.51,0:11:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.33,0:11:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事会维持原状
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.70,0:11:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该彩排了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.17,0:11:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的要彩排这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.96,0:11:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这辈子都在这些台阶上走上走下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.69,0:11:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是在紧张且穿高跟鞋的情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.86,0:11:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很有挑战性  信我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.85,0:11:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克  你站这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.02,0:12:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伴娘  你在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.19,0:12:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里本该是埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.83,0:12:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于找不见他人  就由我替他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.51,0:12:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远不会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.18,0:12:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下楼和你们爸爸共舞的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.67,0:12:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那晚是我的成人礼舞会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.06,0:12:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金  他在楼下等待
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.04,0:12:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我伸出手  看向我的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.52,0:12:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我觉得我是他世界里唯一的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.58,0:12:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几个月后  我就成了尤金·蒙罗太太
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.75,0:12:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐停
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.22,0:12:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成人礼仅几个月后
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.72,0:12:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就嫁给了尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.22,0:12:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  那时候他多大  -  我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.70,0:12:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,23或24岁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.08,0:12:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时非彼时
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.71,0:12:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很荣幸被选中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.42,0:12:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们接下来去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.20,0:12:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望是天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.67,0:12:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说接下来你以什么为生  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.09,0:12:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算重新收回
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.08,0:13:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视台吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.91,0:13:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从世俗财产中解脱了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.42,0:13:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也许想让金杰和他们分担这些世俗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.06,0:13:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正试图引领我的孩子走向光明
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.40,0:13:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你满脑子只有钱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.35,0:13:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让她重蹈覆辙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.07,0:13:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,25年了  你不能对此事避而不谈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.40,0:13:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还指望她像你一样思考
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.90,0:13:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.08,0:13:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.86,0:13:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.20,0:13:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰不让你去的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.20,0:13:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得为我的女儿们做点好事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.27,0:13:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来  你都是个警察
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.76,0:13:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我是联邦调查局的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.53,0:13:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你还活着  那就没有证据指控我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.11,0:13:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有手写认罪书  谋杀未遂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.22,0:13:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪现场逃逸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.72,0:13:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是诱捕  你策划好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.56,0:13:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能因为你没有成功实施犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.22,0:13:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说明没有犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.29,0:14:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窃听器
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.61,0:14:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  你疯了  -  直觉告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.24,0:14:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你看到犯罪现场时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.72,0:14:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就把注意力集中在你认识的人身上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.95,0:14:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师  他的朋友  家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.36,0:14:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我姐夫死了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.10,0:14:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的叔叔们都不做这行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.47,0:14:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些是你认识的恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.46,0:14:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你不认识的恶魔  他们危险得多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.96,0:14:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1820团体没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.42,0:14:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年来  它们变得越来越国际化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.78,0:14:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于到你母亲的影响力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.43,0:14:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会对她下手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.31,0:14:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得知道他们要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.35,0:14:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以对我做你想做的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.63,0:14:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不会监视我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.09,0:14:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有24小时考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.65,0:14:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不重新审视家人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.65,0:14:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扪心自问
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.64,0:14:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们值得让你的女儿在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.16,0:14:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有爸爸陪伴的环境下长大吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.45,0:15:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是把钥匙藏在假石头下面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.88,0:15:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  你是鬼吗  -  不是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.13,0:15:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要让你帮我死而复生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.88,0:15:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你帮玛格丽特穿上那条裙子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.49,0:15:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她永生都会铭记这一晚的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.99,0:15:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.98,0:15:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金先生已经过了适婚年龄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.16,0:15:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要找到一个心仪他的姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.15,0:15:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个待他入王子般的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.50,0:15:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有信仰的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.08,0:15:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箴言31 才德的妇人谁能得着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的价值远胜过珍珠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.22,0:15:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都希望孩子们得到最好的  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.34,0:15:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  阿门  -  艾莉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.85,0:15:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫妮克  富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.39,0:15:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.38,0:16:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有谁知道你还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.07,0:16:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.51,0:16:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和缇娜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.81,0:16:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你在期待什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.37,0:16:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不能就这么走回家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.12,0:16:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活在继续  人们在改变
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.02,0:16:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部已超出你我最疯狂的预期
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.62,0:16:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要你帮玛格丽特做好准备
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.73,0:16:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她别太震惊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.62,0:16:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说你想拿重回公司掌权
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.57,0:16:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的灵魂是纯净的  我已经放下世俗琐事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.72,0:16:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有些别的事我得做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.10,0:16:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怕她会不高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.05,0:16:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么来找我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.72,0:16:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是我永远可以信赖的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.86,0:16:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.02,0:16:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁让你这么摆桌子的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.78,0:16:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别妄加评论  我是吃叉子长大的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.36,0:17:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有给安东尼奥拉过小提琴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.99,0:17:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他对自己的好运感到内疚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的好运很大程度上要归功于我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.70,0:17:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给过你公司股份  一份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.93,0:17:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.38,0:17:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩们也没要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.99,0:17:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们却都在董事会占有一席之地
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.62,0:17:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做那些他们没资格做的重大决定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.79,0:17:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们拥有唯一至关重要的资格
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.72,0:17:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  性别  -  耳根子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.05,0:17:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们听我的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.27,0:17:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  你从不听我的  -  我听过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.44,0:17:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周  我随时都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.15,0:17:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁掉阳光俱乐部
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.28,0:17:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我没有  因为我在乎这个家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.57,0:17:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是又一次任性的虚张声势吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.62,0:17:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.11,0:17:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该庆幸你在我们的餐桌上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.74,0:17:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍有一席之地  金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.49,0:17:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你永远都不会坐进董事会中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.12,0:18:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车  老家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.29,0:18:03.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-  卢克  -  嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.04,0:18:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南方女人随时为结婚而准备
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.52,0:18:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像童话故事一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.32,0:18:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情本不应该是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.15,0:18:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没意见
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.05,0:18:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了在种植园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.44,0:18:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚这部分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.49,0:18:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在打破南方传统这方面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.94,0:18:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得都很好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.16,0:18:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个营地
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.32,0:18:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲  是个植物园
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.73,0:18:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一让我伤心的就是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.38,0:18:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸不在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.46,0:18:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森看到他了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.39,0:18:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森  我们真正的兄弟  不是我要嫁的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.18,0:18:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他告诉马克  他失去意识后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.23,0:18:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸去找过他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.64,0:18:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.69,0:18:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从马克跟我说了这事后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.68,0:18:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在祈祷爸爸的灵魂也会来找我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.70,0:18:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祷告是很灵的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.20,0:19:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.95,0:19:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.57,0:19:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲来找过我了  你知道他活着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.92,0:19:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是的  - 问问他来不来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.20,0:19:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然没告诉我  简直太蠢了  这个我们以后再说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.50,0:19:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.89,0:19:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我跟他说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.13,0:19:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  富兰克林  我知道你跟妈妈干过那事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.72,0:19:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上我在家  你俩好大声
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.05,0:19:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没意见的  听着  我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.35,0:19:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱你  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.90,0:19:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.81,0:19:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.36,0:19:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但祝你今天幸福美满  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.06,0:19:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.58,0:19:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在新奥尔良想乖乖当死人可不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.44,0:19:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时你说想作证
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.46,0:19:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我信了  我以为是在法庭上作证
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.96,0:19:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能指认许多有权势的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.62,0:19:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会尽力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.30,0:20:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  这很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.10,0:20:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们愿意给你提供证人保护服务
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.71,0:20:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换个地方  换个身份
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.01,0:20:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新开始  你想要的不就是这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.85,0:20:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师让我坠机的时候  其实是帮了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.82,0:20:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看到了更高的人生目标
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.32,0:20:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要保护  我有上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.99,0:20:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪儿  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.02,0:20:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得赶去参加婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.48,0:20:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的  我们的誓言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.15,0:20:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从  我们从
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.46,0:20:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科林斯人那里学会婚礼誓言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.00,0:20:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,13章  爱是耐心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.00,0:20:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱是仁慈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.17,0:20:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.75,0:20:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它不粗鲁  不易怒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.92,0:20:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记仇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.47,0:20:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾切尔  嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.33,0:20:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能跟你说句话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.65,0:20:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗牧师的事我很难过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.32,0:20:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太太一定伤心欲绝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.43,0:20:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 嘿  - 我都不知道你会来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.32,0:21:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在酒店里愁眉苦脸的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.77,0:21:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把她当对象带来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.20,0:21:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好吗  兄弟  - 嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.44,0:21:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这对帅哥靓妹去给我们点两杯酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.15,0:21:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好  - 当然
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.03,0:21:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你爱她
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.96,0:21:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就放她继续生活
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你要穿去参加我和布雷特婚礼的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.21,0:21:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也许很有钱  但我很节俭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.73,0:21:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这衣服很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.02,0:21:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我不让你穿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.85,0:21:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.55,0:21:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我换一件
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.15,0:21:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.65,0:21:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你和富兰克林之间发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.23,0:21:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以接受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.21,0:21:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  不管怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.07,0:22:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想开始新生活
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.22,0:22:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都会理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.27,0:22:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我能不能穿你设计的衣服去参加婚礼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.01,0:22:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给啥你穿啥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.10,0:22:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给啥我穿啥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.31,0:22:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空气中弥漫着爱情
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.15,0:22:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到安东尼奥和蕾切尔讲话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.28,0:22:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈呀  新娘的母亲怎么选了这么条裙子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.27,0:22:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为父母
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.44,0:22:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会明白牺牲的含义
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.14,0:22:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  为了你妹妹  开心点
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.98,0:22:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝琪要跟我离婚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.10,0:22:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她出轨了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.57,0:22:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.07,0:22:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出轨成性
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.58,0:22:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这有多伤人  我懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.91,0:22:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直培养我们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.73,0:22:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去潇洒地生活
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.08,0:23:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不留遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.63,0:23:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在  我总是情不自禁地
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.09,0:23:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一遍又一遍地重复
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.79,0:23:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早知今日  何必当初
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.29,0:23:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拿冷水洗把脸
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.96,0:23:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给你妹妹丢人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.30,0:23:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.34,0:24:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  瞌睡虫
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.34,0:24:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.32,0:24:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了个好奇怪的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.70,0:24:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我逃离了这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.61,0:24:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我现在家里有客人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.87,0:24:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他马上就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.36,0:24:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以过来跟我住
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.50,0:24:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.63,0:24:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上那么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.21,0:24:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏偏是你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.22,0:24:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.98,0:24:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.36,0:24:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.72,0:24:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情没那么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.53,0:24:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没那么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.61,0:24:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有其父必有其女
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.04,0:25:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.90,0:25:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你可是首席伴娘
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.22,0:25:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧去现场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.41,0:25:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.67,0:25:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.44,0:25:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的好女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.27,0:25:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.26,0:25:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太美了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.78,0:25:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.52,0:25:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望我不会让你伤心
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.06,0:25:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.39,0:25:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为了公事调查过马克
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.74,0:25:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来我不想给你看的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.90,0:25:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不管这里面有什么  我都要嫁给马克
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.33,0:25:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.66,0:25:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想你以后变成我  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.37,0:25:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你有多爱他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.26,0:25:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我希望你在进入这段婚姻时
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.43,0:25:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是客观清醒的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.73,0:26:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.45,0:26:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老婆在和我妹妹上床
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.18,0:26:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我弟弟在勾搭我女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.65,0:26:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人比我惨了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.62,0:27:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  请回吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.72,0:27:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 小萝  - 就当你从没认识过我
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.46,0:27:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小萝
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.42,0:27:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了他两次  马克
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.55,0:28:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嗑药磕嗨了  撞了车
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.30,0:28:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会陷入昏迷本来就是你害得
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.91,0:28:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没撒谎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.84,0:28:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老老实实地告诉了你一切
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.56,0:28:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是没用同样的词
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.60,0:28:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是安乐死
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.06,0:28:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是安乐死  我
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.85,0:28:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  这是过失杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.35,0:28:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在安乐死之前
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.93,0:28:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真相是很简单的  马克
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.48,0:28:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要简单的真相吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.95,0:28:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你哥  我们是在街头卖大麻的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.41,0:28:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们过着放肆的生活  有时候会出事
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.11,0:28:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次车祸就属于出事了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.61,0:28:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想听
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.92,0:28:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不想再听了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.92,0:28:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  我也不想
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.64,0:28:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和我的世界太不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.17,0:28:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.60,0:28:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才回了家
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.46,0:28:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又让你把我拽回来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.96,0:28:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把自己的生命都交给了你
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.32,0:28:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且为此高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.32,0:29:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我爱你  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.03,0:29:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真爱
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.45,0:29:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.86,0:29:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基督徒不是能赎罪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.79,0:29:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们离开这儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.46,0:29:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去市政厅结婚  地方由你挑
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.87,0:29:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我们一定会幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.63,0:29:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要考虑一下我的生活  马克
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.97,0:29:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能等
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.31,0:29:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别等
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.35,0:29:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全没想到
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.16,0:29:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为他们很相爱
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.85,0:29:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱没什么用
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.07,0:29:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问问蕾切尔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.19,0:29:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.23,0:29:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跟我妈回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.75,0:30:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会上她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.16,0:30:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.68,0:30:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你俩能不能别跟两个小娘们似的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.54,0:30:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.26,0:30:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彩虹骚货
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.58,0:30:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.90,0:30:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你妈是妓女吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.34,0:30:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想打架吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.47,0:30:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是想打架吗  - 打吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.57,0:30:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 住嘴  - 那天晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.94,0:30:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然还能坐在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.39,0:30:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个劲地安慰我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.35,0:30:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我别对出轨的事太难过
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.95,0:30:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该对你老婆更好点
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.53,0:30:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.73,0:30:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们俩伤害了你  那也是无心之失
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.53,0:30:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无心之失  无心之失
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.87,0:30:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你们才是无心之失
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.90,0:30:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你  你们才是无心之失
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.77,0:30:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们才是  你们才是无心之失
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.77,0:30:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  冷静点  否则你明天会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.37,0:30:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会后悔  我会后悔
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.55,0:30:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥说我会后悔
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.37,0:30:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 没错  - 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.63,0:30:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我会有后悔的事  - 好了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.26,0:30:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会后悔什么呢  我会后悔这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.77,0:30:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.97,0:30:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛  后悔吗  你想来毁我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.75,0:30:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁我啊  来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.64,0:31:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们  别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.94,0:31:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.29,0:31:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打了  有毛病吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.07,0:31:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别别
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.62,0:31:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.97,0:31:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 住手啊  - 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.91,0:31:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.08,0:31:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.03,0:31:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.98,0:31:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 住手啊  - 怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.14,0:31:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 杀了我吧  - 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.09,0:31:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.46,0:31:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 弄死我啊  - 不
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.87,0:31:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 弄死我  - 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.62,0:31:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.30,0:31:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.91,0:31:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是家人  不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.27,0:31:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.44,0:31:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛来了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.61,0:31:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顾好你兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.12,0:31:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.90,0:31:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.43,0:32:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能我没说清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.42,0:32:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.76,0:32:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来找你的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.98,0:32:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得做一件你不喜欢的事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.49,0:32:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说你根本不会理解的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.81,0:32:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是为了保护家族产业
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.53,0:32:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不用你保护
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.56,0:32:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要任何人保护
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.99,0:32:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要大乱了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.45,0:32:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.83,0:32:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金还
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.29,0:32:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.44,0:32:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.30,0:32:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.13,0:32:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.14,0:32:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金和他三个朋友打了我儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.50,0:33:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子浑身是血
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.34,0:33:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.15,0:33:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金会的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.98,0:33:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要正义
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.10,0:33:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹啊  莫妮克
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.07,0:33:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金不会坐牢的  你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.70,0:33:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这件事不说出去
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.83,0:33:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会确保
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.00,0:33:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林再也不用在这工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.36,0:33:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.43,0:33:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得回去招呼客人了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.72,0:33:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的机会啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.19,0:33:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有比这再好的了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.23,0:33:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要让我扔掉我儿子的尊严吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.03,0:33:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是机会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.22,0:33:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  希望他们之后会感激我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.80,0:34:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跑哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.39,0:34:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝让我踏上精神追求之旅了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.90,0:34:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路崎岖回到了家
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.61,0:34:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这崎岖的一路上没有电话可以打吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.73,0:34:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是被你母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.69,0:34:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母亲  和富兰克林的母亲引领这回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.76,0:34:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在科罗拉多复活了我儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.39,0:34:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很短暂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.56,0:34:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定累坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.25,0:34:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了都比我经历的一切要容易
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.62,0:34:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你经历的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.96,0:34:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有脸说
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.64,0:34:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让你家人以为你都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.26,0:34:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们捧在手心的一切原来都是一个谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.43,0:34:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真不要脸
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.59,0:34:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该像一条两条腿的狗一样
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.09,0:35:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摇摇晃晃的爬向我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.01,0:35:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富贵还真是让你逼人了  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.29,0:35:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经比你有钱的多得多
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.11,0:35:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在多亏了我  你更有钱了  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.09,0:35:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经放弃了物质生活
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.90,0:35:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你还是穿着笔挺的燕尾服
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.95,0:35:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了参加婚礼  尊重新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.07,0:35:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么要这么对我们
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.29,0:35:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他病了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.65,0:35:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都太变态了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.98,0:35:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他干嘛就这么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.32,0:35:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然出现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.37,0:35:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家人都是疯子  我都不知道该咋说
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.82,0:35:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求他再等一天的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.89,0:35:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一天
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.42,0:35:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你和马克成为焦点的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.46,0:35:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫你求他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.93,0:35:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们的父亲还活着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.48,0:35:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.86,0:35:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很久  我就是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.71,0:35:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我是他女儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.44,0:36:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有权利知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.55,0:36:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是他女儿的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.33,0:36:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都拥有他几十年了  我就想要一点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.61,0:36:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都想的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.86,0:36:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 闭嘴  - 他是我父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.62,0:36:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说   他只是贡献了精子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.29,0:36:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.35,0:36:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱过我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.85,0:36:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.97,0:36:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的掌上明珠
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.02,0:36:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们的感情基础是财富和血泪
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.86,0:36:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不想掺和  你还来干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.20,0:36:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来跟我的孩子们赎罪
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.53,0:36:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打开了埃里克的双眼
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.48,0:36:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他不至于这辈子就这么堕落下去
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.79,0:36:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从疯子手里救下来安东尼奥的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.66,0:36:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让杰森有了生命
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.05,0:36:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我辜负了女儿们
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.72,0:37:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想牵着萝丝走过红毯
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.79,0:37:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我来的太迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.56,0:37:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要给金杰一个新的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.47,0:37:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个她以为她想要的生活  但是虽然你俩都不愿承认
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.96,0:37:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她其实跟你很像
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.22,0:37:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我意识到  只有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.16,0:37:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以满足她
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.06,0:37:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在蒙罗无限公司的股权
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.45,0:37:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没要他这样的  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.09,0:37:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.47,0:37:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是你想要的  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.26,0:37:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比什么都想要
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.60,0:37:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在你需要
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.79,0:37:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己找寻救赎了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.93,0:37:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该你接受上帝的考验了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.05,0:37:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.94,0:37:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我很清醒
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.65,0:38:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝救了我  让我为我的六个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.32,0:38:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做出正确的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.45,0:38:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.78,0:38:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.48,0:38:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.17,0:38:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来找我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.17,0:38:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那时只是孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.72,0:39:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子引领我回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.35,0:39:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.19,0:39:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.73,0:39:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是个谦卑的罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.73,0:39:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个重生的谦卑的罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.36,0:39:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不许再踏进这个家一步
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.35,0:39:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生意可以给你  房子是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.43,0:39:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个珍贵的基石
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.39,0:39:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我孩子新生活
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.23,0:39:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚实的基础
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.56,0:39:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.23,0:40:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都给我滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.91,0:41:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.40,0:41:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会变成孩子的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.33,0:41:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.18,0:41:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要不惜任何代价  保护我母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.56,0:42:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.06,0:42:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我装备上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.99,0:42:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.28,0:42:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要怎么解释这一切呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.91,0:42:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旧的不去
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.57,0:42:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的不来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1347\fscy540}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx411\fscy398}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(337.866,150.555)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1326\fscy535}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx409\fscy401}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(336.266,149.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\fscx1420\fscy538\pos(194.48,214.214)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\frx0\fry2\fscx394\fscy391\pos(152.133,211.556)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(219.599,189.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(152.134,244.999)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.50,0:43:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(191.714,65.904)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制\N合作请加QQ:{\c&H0607F9&}2643527418
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.00,0:30:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(194.933,27.178)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.12,0:04:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)\fs25\t(0,0,\fs45)\pos(192,105.067)\c&H1314CE&}富 贵 逼 人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.50,0:04:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：Evelyn 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.76,0:04:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：廿八 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.52,0:04:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：二师姐 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.81,0:04:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}校对：一江春水向西流 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.49,0:04:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}统筹：折木奉太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.96,0:05:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}总监：一芹
