[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 人人二维码,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00016A17,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134
Style: 哒哒字幕组,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,4,1
Style: 滚屏广告,思源宋体 Heavy,20,&H0001EEF1,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.5,8,10,10,1,134
Style: 歌词,【初遇】你好，旧时光,10,&H0004A7FB,&H000000FF,&H001B1B1B,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,9,5,5,5,1
Style: 屏字,微软雅黑,20,&H23E5EAEC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,60,1
Style: 硬字幕,文鼎霹雳体,20,&H00507497,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 备注解释,思源黑体 CN Medium,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.3,8,10,10,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.51,0:00:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的上帝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.49,0:00:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光网络电台怎么变成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.99,0:00:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前还是一个充满信仰的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.49,0:00:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视频道
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.02,0:00:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在已经成为24小时无休止的垃圾了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰不只是很婊  还能吸引所有人的注意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.44,0:00:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧  小妞们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.26,0:00:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而玛格丽特呢  不得不用一整集的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.84,0:00:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来扑灭金杰展露了自己的“信仰”
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.30,0:00:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所带来的各种影响
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.26,0:00:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特的观众可不是闹着玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.45,0:00:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了安慰他们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.12,0:00:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她决定让尤金所有的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.60,0:00:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都戴上天使翅膀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.29,0:00:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我和埃里克  我俩在烈日炎炎下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.85,0:00:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在石棉纤维和蚊子大军中做苦力
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.46,0:00:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰大闹一场  因为有个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.87,0:00:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去汽车旅馆威胁了她妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.61,0:00:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计只是个想尝到甜头的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.80,0:00:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她非要以半冷冻糖浆的办法来把事情搞大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.80,0:00:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便这出闹剧之后的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.45,0:00:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观看量已经要爆棚了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.18,0:00:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但阳光电视台的投资人们开始不开心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.59,0:00:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们看到了钱  但是没从玛格丽特身上分到钱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.12,0:00:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的钱祈祷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.87,0:00:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当金杰知道  玛格丽特的投资人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.55,0:00:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会光顾她的淫荡农场时  她有了主意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.52,0:00:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们全部录下来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.48,0:00:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有权有势的人到处都有朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.49,0:00:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特想带他们去露营
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.40,0:00:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把事情平息
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.56,0:01:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝  感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.55,0:01:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金看不到玛格丽特搞得这一大堆事情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.33,0:01:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 尤金  - 她把电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.14,0:01:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和尤金的名声搞得一塌糊涂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.74,0:01:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是做慈善啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.11,0:01:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上帝之名祈祷  阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.57,0:01:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方就我们几个人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.08,0:01:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.89,0:01:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像去水疗馆过周末
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行李随便放
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.58,0:01:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森你能不能帮忙拿上去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.59,0:01:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来拿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.92,0:01:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.59,0:01:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都吃早餐了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.71,0:01:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要咖啡还是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.80,0:01:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有安保系统吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.39,0:01:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比那更好  我们有狗还有枪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.62,0:01:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人想偷偷溜进来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.93,0:01:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  萝丝不会带你来危险的地方的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.77,0:01:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不不
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.10,0:01:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前也来过疯狂粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.69,0:01:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过都没啥事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.61,0:01:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许她这次多虑是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.65,0:01:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.23,0:01:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅馆外面那人留下的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.60,0:02:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道他怎么弄来的  也不知道是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.64,0:02:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这里是安全的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.90,0:02:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有粉丝  没有威胁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.15,0:02:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都可以玩的开心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.02,0:02:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互相了解
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.62,0:02:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省的我妈天天烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.26,0:02:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把她弄下来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.17,0:02:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.40,0:02:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰  我们得走了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.61,0:02:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.23,0:02:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈的客人永远不嫌多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.99,0:02:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是她  是他们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那些男人们  - 我都认识他们一辈子了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.48,0:02:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出生之前我就认识他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.83,0:02:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果被他们知道我在  会杀了我的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.62,0:02:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去打开尤金的枪柜了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.56,0:02:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以当他在家一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.12,0:02:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好去猎鸭子了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.63,0:03:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天都好想那个老小子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.84,0:03:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周末可别让我难过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.68,0:03:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我们也有自己的柜子呢  对吧女士们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.41,0:03:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都等了一年了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.91,0:03:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可别出洋相了啊  维罗妮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.47,0:03:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不出我就不会出
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.47,0:03:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭之后呢  我要跟大家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.60,0:03:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探讨一点生意的事情呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.24,0:03:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们要吃超多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.53,0:03:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周末要长胖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.48,0:03:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊   牧师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.73,0:03:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊贝基
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.58,0:03:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.08,0:03:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特  是萝丝邀请我来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.83,0:03:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 萝丝来了吗  - 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.70,0:03:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来只差金杰了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.79,0:03:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.22,0:03:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客人来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.80,0:03:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血腥玛丽和台球桌在左边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.67,0:03:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这早餐绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.62,0:03:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝基  把这个放厨房去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.05,0:03:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把东西放下  先去书房找我们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.44,0:03:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个小惊喜要给你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.43,0:04:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这神奇周末搞得
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.49,0:04:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像传达出来的信息不太对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.78,0:04:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟有权有势的人是不能硬钢的  富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.80,0:04:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是路易斯安纳来的黑人  我不懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.75,0:04:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人是我的电台的大股东啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.11,0:04:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能跟他们疏远了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.08,0:04:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.75,0:04:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部一分都不会给他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.25,0:04:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很担心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.76,0:04:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有天会用别的方法搞你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.57,0:04:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.76,0:04:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每逢教堂必进
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.75,0:04:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每逢女人也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.55,0:04:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安息吧  你个老鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.60,0:04:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不想背后说他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.68,0:04:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是尤金留下一个烂摊子  还没发解决
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.48,0:04:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在弄河口项目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.72,0:04:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有许多未解决的违规问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.65,0:04:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那地方都要塌了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.15,0:04:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸管不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.14,0:04:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我下周叫人去解决
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.14,0:04:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  唐斯叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.95,0:04:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,18:20是家人啊  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.16,0:04:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸之前老说18:20
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.33,0:04:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么  共济会吗还是圣地兄弟会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.46,0:05:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.91,0:05:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡有两三个人奉我的名聚集的地方  就有我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.32,0:05:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马太福音  18:20
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.05,0:05:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是生意人  吃面包  读圣经
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.95,0:05:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像早期的基督徒在秘密的小团体里一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.59,0:05:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你母亲一样的人去抛头露面
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.35,0:05:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的权力是隐形的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.31,0:05:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金忘了这一点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.39,0:05:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不会的  对吧儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.70,0:05:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定你在问我什么  维吉尔叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.72,0:05:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想这么说  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.66,0:05:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你父亲的意外
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.82,0:05:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是上帝给你最好的安排
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.52,0:05:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们希望你加入
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.08,0:05:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,18:20把尤金的位置给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.06,0:05:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的上帝  我是自由的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.76,0:05:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我被困在我的思绪中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.81,0:06:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过  在救赎时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.72,0:06:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮助你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.36,0:06:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.03,0:06:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必派你归还这地
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.53,0:06:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对囚犯说  出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.78,0:06:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又对黑暗里的人说  现身吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.89,0:06:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金·蒙罗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.91,0:06:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么给我戴手铐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.09,0:06:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.75,0:06:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我借了点钱为了回家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.23,0:06:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会还的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.83,0:06:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这好像也没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.22,0:06:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是搞错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.41,0:06:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里面的东西都是过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.25,0:06:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寻求了原谅  我和上帝和解了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.90,0:06:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只需要这样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.59,0:06:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.26,0:06:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你的罪像猩红
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.49,0:06:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们必像雪一样白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽如深红色  必如羊毛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.69,0:06:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊毛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.70,0:06:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊毛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.53,0:07:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到的是聚酯纤维
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.08,0:07:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我自由吧  上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.92,0:07:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我自由
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.28,0:07:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以上帝之名祈祷  阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 关门  - 好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.80,0:07:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名媛家的衣橱都这么大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.84,0:07:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的工作室
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.49,0:07:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只让我爸进来过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.51,0:07:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都藏着呢啊  好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.72,0:07:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不安全  我们等于被包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.98,0:07:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心我叔叔们啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.30,0:07:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是一帮吵吵闹闹的老男孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.86,0:07:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很容易就看透他们了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.53,0:07:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你年轻貌美的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.99,0:07:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为自己很有能力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.49,0:07:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到有一天  你发现在真正有权有势的人面前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.53,0:07:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连垃圾都不如
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.07,0:07:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给她拿点什么冷静一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.54,0:07:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.19,0:07:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿酒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.12,0:07:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟那个混蛋你留的照片有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.38,0:08:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为那个混蛋是谁派来的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.39,0:08:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不知道我们要对付谁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.35,0:08:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们那种人统治世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.71,0:08:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.21,0:08:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以打电话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.02,0:08:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要审判我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.36,0:08:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是无辜的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.86,0:08:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.55,0:08:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这出了个误会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.20,0:08:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家境殷实  如果你能
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.98,0:08:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要叫警察
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.54,0:08:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜尤金  我就是警察
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.28,0:08:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没见过这么多食物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.10,0:08:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一向主张做食物要多多益善
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.27,0:08:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么比刚刚好更磕碜的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.50,0:08:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是吃米饭豆子还有玉米麦片长大的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.79,0:08:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你饿着的  宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.35,0:08:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物寄托着爱意  我这两样都很充沛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.92,0:08:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  才上午11点就喝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.78,0:09:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  四舍五入基本上就是周末了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.51,0:09:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  谢谢你邀请我来参加派对
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.85,0:09:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能提前通知一下就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.47,0:09:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又不是分时别墅  萝丝  不管怎么样  是为了公事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.64,0:09:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么公事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.02,0:09:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要把朋友家人都
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.56,0:09:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,排挤出去好让她一个人独吞家业
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.27,0:09:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说出来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.82,0:09:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀孕心直口快
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.71,0:09:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.03,0:09:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这是为了公事  你为什么在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.90,0:09:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我作为你兄弟的配偶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.19,0:09:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有他孕育中孩子的母亲的身份到场
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.85,0:09:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的配偶就在这
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.86,0:09:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去自己喝闷酒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.67,0:09:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.67,0:09:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和我哥还有其他的人在尤金的书房里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.96,0:09:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没别人了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.80,0:09:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去去就回
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.41,0:09:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起名叫耶稣这个决定很大胆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.31,0:09:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是杰西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.69,0:09:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半斤八两  随便你怎么渎神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.68,0:10:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有考虑过从政  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.09,0:10:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没考虑过
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.49,0:10:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得跟随上帝的指引
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.19,0:10:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的副州长被起诉了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.75,0:10:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备找人接替他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.37,0:10:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的组织在全国范围内
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.66,0:10:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮助像你这样有才干的年轻人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.29,0:10:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们帮助你的父亲创立他的电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.79,0:10:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们希望能协助你经办阳光俱乐部
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该  你应该去和我母亲谈这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.78,0:10:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她管事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.55,0:10:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别误会  你母亲的母亲很能干
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.77,0:10:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是阳光电视台成为
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.30,0:10:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市值22亿的企业科不是靠卖食谱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.56,0:10:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了  先生们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.26,0:10:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是说吃饭之前不谈公事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.32,0:10:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  亲爱的  我忘记拿叉子和盘子了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.79,0:10:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.87,0:10:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事这么重要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.66,0:11:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都忘了叫上你最喜欢的首席执行官
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.80,0:11:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克在给我们汇报宣道的进展
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.97,0:11:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我交给他的任务  他做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.99,0:11:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个蛋糕看起来很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.76,0:11:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人的手艺能比得上你  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.68,0:11:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不只会烘焙  唐斯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.64,0:11:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想夸你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.77,0:11:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维罗妮卡只知道一个食谱  那就是外卖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.28,0:11:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好好玩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.65,0:11:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗  能和你说句话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.19,0:11:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前进基督徒士兵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.25,0:11:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想要尤金许诺给他们的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.54,0:11:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是得到和他们在电视台里的股份等值的阳光俱乐部股份
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.09,0:11:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部会继续由蒙罗家族控股
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.35,0:11:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对家族的定义不同
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.65,0:12:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不退让
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.65,0:12:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好做好应对恶意收购的准备
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.03,0:12:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要证明什么  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.70,0:12:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有一档热门电视节目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.20,0:12:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有几百万热情的粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.90,0:12:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数在你这个年龄的女人都卸下负担
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.99,0:12:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退居二线了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.61,0:12:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子女共享天伦之乐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.11,0:12:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克没有经验  我们都心知肚明  保罗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.56,0:12:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们更愿意和没经验的年轻人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.50,0:12:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是中年女性打交道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.36,0:12:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续做你的节目  享受家人的陪伴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.67,0:12:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要自傲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.85,0:12:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些真的很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.52,0:12:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭借着你的商业头脑  萝丝能够日进斗金
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.69,0:12:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.71,0:12:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是我反应过激
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.52,0:12:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们这么老远赶来一定没那么糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.52,0:12:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们要躲避善良正直的市民
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.07,0:12:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就意味着我们是坏人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.24,0:12:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜玛格丽特在对全国播送的节目里叫我们荡妇是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.82,0:12:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.37,0:13:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就坦白免得让我觉得自己这么肮脏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.57,0:13:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我受够了躲躲藏藏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.27,0:13:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要下楼去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.44,0:13:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时那是一大笔钱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.84,0:13:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你要明白  - 钱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.08,0:13:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我还年少在赌场跳舞的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.47,0:13:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们来到维加斯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.06,0:13:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加基督徒行业领袖大会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.11,0:13:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是个玩笑  因为他们喝的酩酊大醉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.46,0:13:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不打破十诫誓不罢休
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.22,0:13:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是尤金不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.78,0:13:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很清醒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.29,0:13:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看到了我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.60,0:13:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.23,0:13:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那晚结束的时候  在所有的人离开的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.37,0:13:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒保递给我一个
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.63,0:13:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面装着10000美元现金还有房号的信封
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.15,0:13:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金付给你10000美金和他上床
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.68,0:14:01.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒希望这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.44,0:14:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我能够接受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.09,0:14:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们在他的房间里装了摄像头
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.18,0:14:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那笔钱是他朋友给的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.23,0:14:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们付钱给我勾引他好让他们录下经过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.31,0:14:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.49,0:14:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.14,0:14:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们想要拿到他的把柄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.67,0:14:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想过我们会坠入爱河
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.52,0:14:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就生下了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.49,0:14:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怀孕之后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.45,0:14:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们派了个人见我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.26,0:14:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个你认为是玛格丽特狂热粉丝的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.35,0:14:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说如果我把那天晚上发生的事情告诉任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.51,0:14:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就会让我们人间消失
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.03,0:14:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我隐姓埋名就是为了保住你的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.18,0:14:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.48,0:15:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感到好羞愧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.85,0:15:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金在遇到我之前都是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.95,0:15:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝基
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.08,0:15:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真应该吃一块蛋糕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.92,0:15:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要吃点东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.75,0:15:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道她在里面放了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.48,0:15:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比吸毒还带劲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.59,0:15:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不了解  我不吸毒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.37,0:15:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样  我的意思是  现在不吸了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.38,0:15:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想在我孩子的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.09,0:15:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨论毒品
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.84,0:15:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕在娘胎里他们也很容易受到影响
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.22,0:15:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你看到弗兰克林了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.63,0:15:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有段时间没见了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.72,0:15:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  他能上哪去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.19,0:15:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到处都找过了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.72,0:15:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝基  肚子越来越大了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.97,0:15:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不  你不能来这
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.86,0:15:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来参加会面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.45,0:15:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后瑞秋告诉我你在农场
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.95,0:16:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 她准备把你喂肥了再宰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.62,0:16:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说杰西需要新鲜空气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.07,0:16:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不新鲜的空气锻炼肺
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.53,0:16:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们才住在高架桥底下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.34,0:16:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约比·康德拉里亚  好久不见
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.30,0:16:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见  唐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.08,0:16:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我英俊的儿子安东尼奥吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.22,0:16:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得  一表人才
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.69,0:16:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是只猛虎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.45,0:16:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该让他上阵厮杀  他会给你赚一大笔钱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.81,0:16:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  就像他给你赚的一样多吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.20,0:16:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道么  你总是不自量力  约比
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.96,0:16:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走  你让我丢人现眼了  妈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.60,0:16:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真会说笑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.37,0:16:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把你当成吉娃娃一样遛来遛去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.67,0:16:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还指望那个男人尊重你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.27,0:16:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是她的宠物  我是她的亲人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.49,0:16:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.85,0:16:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢上她了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.77,0:16:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本来只应该做戏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.94,0:16:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真喜欢上她了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.24,0:16:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不会侮辱我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.95,0:16:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对人和善
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.27,0:16:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富人有资本和善
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.82,0:16:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们衣来伸手饭来张口
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.71,0:16:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车吧  车还在打表呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.79,0:16:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等她把矛头转向荷酥的时候你就会知道这是什么感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.22,0:16:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好看好你的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.46,0:17:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.26,0:17:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这台令人激动了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.85,0:17:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听起来不激动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.23,0:17:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我替你激动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.64,0:17:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜  如果你进入政坛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.48,0:17:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就意味我们不能再联系了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.24,0:17:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.54,0:17:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.62,0:17:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们交流想法谈论喜欢的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.83,0:17:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是耶稣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.20,0:17:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.96,0:17:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的经验之谈  干我这行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.05,0:17:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情感上的亲密关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.50,0:17:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候会发展成为肉体上的亲密关系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.34,0:17:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞秋   我结婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.60,0:17:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也没拦住其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.84,0:17:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没拦住你爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.05,0:17:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你有时间吗   我需要和你谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.35,0:18:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心的是牧师
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.96,0:18:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把你当成给他跑腿的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.63,0:18:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  牧师想让我做州长的副手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.48,0:18:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我去拿碟子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.77,0:18:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁把我当跑腿的使
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.11,0:18:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.71,0:18:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是在躲着我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.51,0:18:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 女士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.06,0:18:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫我女士  听着显老
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.17,0:18:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  女士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.38,0:18:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能告诉你一件事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.22,0:18:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.35,0:18:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很有钱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.54,0:18:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.85,0:18:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.02,0:18:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意我带走她一段时间吗  维罗妮卡姑妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.05,0:18:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你答应把他还回来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.74,0:18:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去给我们拿点喝的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.45,0:18:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很友善
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.92,0:19:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是个荡妇  她一直都是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.25,0:19:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她不是你的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.25,0:19:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有喜欢的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.37,0:19:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家人除外
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.75,0:19:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一个人在这干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.09,0:19:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有见不得人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.37,0:19:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦泄露会让人家破人亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.87,0:19:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了假装是我昏迷的兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.92,0:19:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有件事没告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.73,0:19:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.02,0:19:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我叔叔的儿子订过婚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.07,0:19:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以是你的堂兄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.95,0:19:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们不是我的亲叔叔  杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.49,0:19:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实证明他撒谎劈腿
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.96,0:19:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现之后及时取消了婚约
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在我意识到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.09,0:19:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是随了他父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.04,0:19:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我和他待在一起会怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.59,0:20:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会像蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.25,0:20:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈或者维罗妮卡姑妈一样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.64,0:20:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是秘密吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.58,0:20:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我当作家人的男人都是禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.89,0:20:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依我看来  你也是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.93,0:20:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能让我清净一会儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.95,0:20:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴赶上了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.78,0:20:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维吉尔  我希望你今天用尤金的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.75,0:20:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来打猎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.01,0:20:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他会希望你来用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.16,0:20:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的荣幸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.47,0:20:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道尤金许诺给你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.47,0:20:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部的股份
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.31,0:20:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他告诉我阳光俱乐部是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.83,0:20:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  公平起见  我提出一个妥协方案
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.98,0:20:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我继续持有完全所有权
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.48,0:20:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是把你作为无投票权承保商的身份拉你入伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.97,0:21:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个提议很有趣  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.86,0:21:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你之后跟弗兰克林去谈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.87,0:21:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗兰克林不在这里  我在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.11,0:21:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你买断怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.07,0:21:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真大方  唐斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.28,0:21:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心维罗妮卡的信托负担不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.84,0:21:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那通过慈善机构转移的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.03,0:21:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部两成的营收呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.90,0:21:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金许诺我们借教会免税地位帮我们避税
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.92,0:21:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.57,0:21:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将教会的事务交由埃里克打点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.54,0:21:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由他全权负责
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.50,0:21:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我认识的唯一可敬的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.69,0:21:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.19,0:21:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受狩猎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.86,0:21:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要来吗  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克要射猪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.49,0:21:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就到这了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.75,0:21:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要杀一只吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.25,0:21:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你来杀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.66,0:21:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎加入家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.75,0:22:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能用枪  综合格斗的规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.83,0:22:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.89,0:22:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那个小胖墩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.72,0:22:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过瞄准镜瞄准  就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.78,0:22:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扣动扳机
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.06,0:22:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准双眼之间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.77,0:22:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是它吃饲料放松又没招惹谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.05,0:22:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  你吃培根  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.90,0:22:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为培根是从哪来的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.26,0:22:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.45,0:22:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这新鲜的猪肉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.62,0:22:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金的基因真不错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.91,0:22:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的酒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.62,0:22:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不拿我就替你喝了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.25,0:22:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  维罗妮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.94,0:22:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们俩去屋子里喝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.57,0:22:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.13,0:22:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是有夫之妇而且都能给你当妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.04,0:22:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你给我好好讲讲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.77,0:22:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准你能跟我说说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.79,0:22:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对萝丝的未婚夫都了解什么\N{\fs12}What do you know about Rose's fiancé?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.60,0:22:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.22,0:23:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们很般配
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.94,0:23:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被相中作为最高法院的候选人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.67,0:23:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.61,0:23:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在哪  这是什么地方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.45,0:23:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勒夫农场
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.01,0:23:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是维吉尔·勒夫的监狱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.24,0:23:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.94,0:23:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.44,0:23:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家离这就几公里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.11,0:23:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一通电话我就能把这件事 解释清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.25,0:23:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到我家人身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.36,0:23:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没准他们不想要你回家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.01,0:23:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你进监狱之后家人就会忘掉你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.39,0:23:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得到教训了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.35,0:23:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真够快的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.69,0:23:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷了那笔钱  我没打算还
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.32,0:23:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦白交代  没想到
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.55,0:23:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对我妻子撒了谎  我伤害了我的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.65,0:23:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续说
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.87,0:23:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贪婪  怠惰  觊觎邻居的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.61,0:24:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为所有的这些感到懊悔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.15,0:24:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家顺着这条路走几公里就到
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.88,0:24:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我妻子打个电话她就会来接我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你跑掉试试看
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.22,0:24:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你想套我  - 你自己选
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.01,0:24:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以待在这服刑
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.71,0:24:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者可以试着逃脱法律的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.54,0:24:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全看你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.90,0:24:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.52,0:24:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.07,0:24:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花200美元打车来回  为了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.25,0:24:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被像垃圾一样扔出来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.40,0:24:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.72,0:24:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那帮有钱的混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.91,0:24:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在乡间度周末
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.22,0:24:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我以前周末的时候带安东尼奥去哪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.56,0:24:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带他去中央公园
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.78,0:24:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和瘾君子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.08,0:24:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有疯子那样的正常人在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.95,0:25:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他们没那么糟糕  - 得了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.30,0:25:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉我你也信了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.68,0:25:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的鬼话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.12,0:25:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打住
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.92,0:25:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真希望能让那帮蒙罗家的人跪地求饶
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.64,0:25:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个客户好这一口
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.76,0:25:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要拿他过过瘾吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.28,0:25:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.77,0:25:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我得脱衣服吗  - 不用
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.39,0:25:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要是说狂欢节你就得停下
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.45,0:25:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他的安全词
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.46,0:25:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听他们打得多热闹
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.92,0:25:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像过去一样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.44,0:25:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴望着你父亲带着打来的鸭子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.61,0:25:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从树林里走出来
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.62,0:25:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间过得真快
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.15,0:25:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  我得把爸爸和蒂娜的事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.12,0:25:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.60,0:25:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.60,0:25:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真英俊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.72,0:25:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在外面有点太激动了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.61,0:25:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我憋不住
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.23,0:25:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等了25年才见到我的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.37,0:25:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上去是个好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.04,0:26:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你给他找了个好人家
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.84,0:26:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人问起你是怎么知道他的下落的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.40,0:26:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  玛格丽特认为我雇了私家侦探
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.05,0:26:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.03,0:26:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都后悔当初把他送走
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.10,0:26:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金现在不在了  把他领回来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.54,0:26:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐斯会立马跟我离婚的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.90,0:26:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者更糟  他会派哈格蒙德·辛来让我消失
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.67,0:26:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  弗兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.89,0:26:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要把这个秘密带进坟墓
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.59,0:26:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就该公开了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.96,0:26:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该勇敢一点
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.92,0:26:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该告诉尤金真相
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.22,0:26:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该一起对付他的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.31,0:26:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却撒谎骗他说我不爱他
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.91,0:26:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让他回到玛格丽特身边
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.03,0:27:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂娜  我很抱歉  那些人都是禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.29,0:27:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金和他的朋友对你做的事情很糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.61,0:27:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会为他们的灵魂祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.71,0:27:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到这来还说什么祷告
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.92,0:27:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看来恶人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.62,0:27:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃香喝辣逍遥自在
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.09,0:27:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们却得躲在柜子里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.91,0:27:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽好我们自己的本分让上帝履行祂的职责
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.75,0:27:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这些男人不给我们谈判的席位
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.88,0:27:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就自立门户
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.35,0:27:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士专桌
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.01,0:27:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄出个女士专桌做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.30,0:27:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝茶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.19,0:27:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该会需要
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.99,0:27:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比茶带点劲的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.95,0:27:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我们看看这三个男人有多聪明吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.16,0:27:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人很厉害的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.00,0:27:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倘若姐妹齐心  我们也势不可挡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.65,0:27:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以找出他们的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.13,0:27:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们永远从我们的生活里滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.96,0:27:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.79,0:27:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全看不出拉个钩能起到什么作用
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.63,0:27:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该听妈把话说完
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.47,0:27:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我们可以互相帮助  - 我不需要帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.97,0:28:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你母亲需要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.83,0:28:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.52,0:28:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得康复中心现在对你而言是最安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.27,0:28:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管精神上  还是身体上
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.65,0:28:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正好知道这么一个地方  很清静
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.16,0:28:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只不过是想甩掉你
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.20,0:28:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.83,0:28:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候对抗内心的魔鬼了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.86,0:28:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能想到接下来  你一定不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.75,0:28:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个非常勇敢的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.89,0:28:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此话当真
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.46,0:28:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当真
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.56,0:28:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  如果我要加入你的战线
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.86,0:28:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要点回报
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.81,0:28:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.90,0:28:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喜欢我卖的东西  可以
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.98,0:29:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想能做自己
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.58,0:29:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管我的生意
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.12,0:29:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能做到  我们就能并肩战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.33,0:29:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士专桌万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.05,0:29:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又安全保管了一年
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.93,0:29:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受不会因穿这些大衣
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.22,0:29:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被评头论足的周末吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.73,0:29:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们  来选吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.23,0:29:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  快来找妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.05,0:29:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可比高中时候的汽车后座
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.74,0:29:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要热呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.74,0:29:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定不会买这些
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.41,0:29:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我奶奶遗嘱中给我了一件
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.94,0:29:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 看法都憋肚子里哈  - 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.75,0:29:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是尤金妈妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.03,0:29:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真喜欢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.69,0:30:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了  找你半天
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.99,0:30:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打猎去  弄了一头猪回来烤着吃
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.12,0:30:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森和安东尼奥比看上去的要好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.45,0:30:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 都是的  - 不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.85,0:30:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们鬼话连篇  残忍  邪恶
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.14,0:30:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天收到了好消息
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.43,0:30:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维吉尔·洛夫想让我担任州长的副手
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.38,0:30:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政治很世俗的  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.83,0:31:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不就是听从上天的安排吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.18,0:31:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.88,0:31:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我妻子亲热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.57,0:31:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性只是为了传宗接代  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.59,0:31:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经有孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.33,0:31:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲密一下能增进夫妻感情
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.35,0:31:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话  魔鬼就会让一些
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.81,0:31:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯狂的想法和憧憬  溜进你脑袋里
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.06,0:31:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这也太臭了  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.65,0:31:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.48,0:31:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.61,0:31:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的累了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.85,0:31:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时看着杰西
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.19,0:31:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着他们望着他
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.85,0:31:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就对那孩子一点都不上心
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.42,0:31:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.29,0:31:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.18,0:31:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歇会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.56,0:32:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.52,0:32:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  我都快饿抽了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.51,0:32:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  再等几个小时就好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.98,0:32:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等大家都睡着  我送你出去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.98,0:32:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女士专桌的事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.61,0:32:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真相信你妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.72,0:32:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.93,0:32:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩也要有人信
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.82,0:32:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.62,0:32:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞秋发了段视频过来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.23,0:32:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你去拿狂欢节的珠子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.21,0:32:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 狂欢节  - 赶紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.07,0:32:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.72,0:32:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屋子里都有这种声音了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.38,0:32:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维吉尔叔叔太恶心了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.58,0:32:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这代表什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.84,0:32:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表明我有玛格丽特没有的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.32,0:32:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来道别了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.07,0:33:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你要去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.52,0:33:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回科罗拉多州
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.45,0:33:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  我想了一下男人都是怎么对待你的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.27,0:33:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸  还有你那个最高法院的男友
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.47,0:33:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那没可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.70,0:33:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.53,0:33:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不应该跟一个让你成天生活在谎言中的骗子在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.37,0:33:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我配不上你  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.58,0:33:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.21,0:33:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想变成你生命里的另一个怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.33,0:33:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他们说
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.51,0:33:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色情相关  看到就会秒懂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.72,0:33:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.11,0:33:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庄重和体面也是看得出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.45,0:33:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我生命你只有你是真实的  杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.48,0:33:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是马克
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.40,0:33:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  马克
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.70,0:34:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以上法学院的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.49,0:34:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢律师啦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.09,0:34:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这一天都死哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.02,0:34:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我各处找遍了你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.81,0:34:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留我一个人去谈判是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.15,0:34:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有其他事要处理呢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.51,0:34:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错过了我跟他们18:20小团体的精彩对话
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.44,0:34:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们试图给我施压
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.18,0:34:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们把阳光俱乐部分他们一杯羹
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.64,0:34:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.19,0:34:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么不等一下  先跟我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.66,0:34:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.95,0:34:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.56,0:34:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金承诺给他们股权
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.21,0:34:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就谈判  最后任命他们为承包商
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.82,0:34:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢到家了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.34,0:34:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这不是恰好中了他们的奸计
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.54,0:34:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  一旦他们插一脚进来  就踹不出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.54,0:34:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金他可能会变着法的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.41,0:34:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你不忠  但他之于你对阳光俱乐部的愿景
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.06,0:34:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是丝毫不掺假的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.76,0:35:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为了把这个留给你一人  可以去死
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.23,0:35:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新奥尔良见了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.08,0:35:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猪  小猪  让我进去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.21,0:35:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没门儿的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.38,0:35:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就吹一大口气
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.42,0:35:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你房子都吹倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.41,0:35:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.29,0:35:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间刚刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.92,0:36:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们一起吧  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.28,0:36:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 唱一首  - 行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.38,0:36:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唱一段陌生旅人怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.45,0:36:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.45,0:36:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.71,0:36:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12走
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.48,0:36:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只不过是一个可怜的陌生人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.16,0:36:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裹身前行于
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.16,0:36:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苦难的生活之中
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.07,0:36:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.12,0:36:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有辛劳  也无危险
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.49,0:36:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那片我即将去往的乐土
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.56,0:36:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  有个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.33,0:37:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈蒙德·希恩
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.57,0:37:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去那里觐见神父
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.89,0:37:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及所有我真爱
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.23,0:37:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却离去之人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.58,0:37:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.38,0:37:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家  儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.46,0:37:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约旦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.18,0:37:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.80,0:37:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.42,0:38:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.05,0:38:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你不会把应付不来的事交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.94,0:38:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这一次
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.10,0:38:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该是高估我的能力了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.75,0:38:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我们原谅那些让我们委屈不止7次
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.59,0:38:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多要490次的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.07,0:38:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要原谅尤金多少次啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.15,0:38:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去那里去看妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.56,0:38:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她当初曾说  我回家就会等我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.80,0:39:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到约旦
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.93,0:39:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.47,0:39:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与乌云相识  乌云在我周围密布
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.17,0:39:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道自己的这条路
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.84,0:39:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崎岖难行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.65,0:40:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但美丽的田野也浮现在我眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.86,0:40:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝在那里救赎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.16,0:40:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们于漫漫黑夜之中的祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.51,0:40:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去那里见我的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.24,0:40:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及所有我真爱
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.06,0:40:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却离去之人
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.92,0:40:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到约旦
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.86,0:40:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.12,0:40:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回家去见我父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.62,0:41:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去便不再游荡
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.12,0:41:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到约旦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.07,0:41:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.26,0:41:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因着神的恩典  我才有今天
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.24,0:41:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.86,0:41:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1347\fscy540}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx411\fscy398}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(337.866,150.555)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1326\fscy535}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx409\fscy401}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(336.266,149.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\fscx1420\fscy538\pos(194.48,214.214)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\frx0\fry2\fscx394\fscy391\pos(152.133,211.556)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(219.599,189.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(152.134,244.999)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.26,0:41:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(191.714,65.904)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制\N合作请加QQ:{\c&H0607F9&}2643527418
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.00,0:30:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(194.933,27.178)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.93,0:05:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)\fs25\t(0,5000,\fs45)\pos(192,105.067)\c&H1314CE&}富 贵 逼 人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.13,0:05:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2)\fn方正卡通简体\fs20\pos(194.8,7.733)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.97,0:10:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：一江春水向西流 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.23,0:10:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：Efroimson  
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.99,0:10:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：behemoth
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.28,0:06:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}校对：一江春水向西流
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.96,0:06:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}统筹：折木奉太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.43,0:06:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}总监：一芹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.86,0:17:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz7.15\c&H0C1111&\pos(166,87.467)}圣徒马车
