[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 人人二维码,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00016A17,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134
Style: 哒哒字幕组,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,4,1
Style: 滚屏广告,思源宋体 Heavy,20,&H0001EEF1,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.5,8,10,10,1,134
Style: 歌词,【初遇】你好，旧时光,10,&H0004A7FB,&H000000FF,&H001B1B1B,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,9,5,5,5,1
Style: 屏字,微软雅黑,20,&H23E5EAEC,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,1.5,2,10,10,60,1
Style: 硬字幕,文鼎霹雳体,20,&H00507497,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,5,1
Style: 备注解释,思源黑体 CN Medium,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.3,8,10,10,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.88,0:00:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬爱的上帝  我们再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.70,0:00:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要您神圣的介入
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.92,0:00:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特的媒体发布会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.38,0:00:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟破车一样适得其反了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.04,0:00:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部的供应商都威胁说要退出
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.21,0:00:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特召开家庭会议  要留住所有的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.92,0:00:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然也包括私生子了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.76,0:00:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实也就是等于贿赂大家都能发挥各自的作用
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.43,0:00:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她等于让你成了员工
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥当然是接受了提议
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.97,0:00:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西服不错
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.10,0:00:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定很需要钱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.31,0:00:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝去不知道什么毒品贼窝里面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.39,0:00:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把藏着的杰森找出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.56,0:00:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他最好小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.85,0:00:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然会昏迷的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.48,0:00:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.82,0:00:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫不醒他的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.11,0:00:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有金杰  真是个贪心婊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.90,0:00:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝了玛格丽特出的价
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.36,0:00:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就是这么婊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.11,0:00:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且把她的网络小姐们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.78,0:00:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都搬到了一个小破旅馆里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.78,0:00:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以玛格丽特就去找了唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能解决这一切的人  我的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.29,0:00:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他提出要给金杰做洗礼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.33,0:00:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此来交换让埃里克掌权阳光项目
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.04,0:00:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是容易的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.96,0:00:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他才一直对着电脑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.59,0:00:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是金杰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.71,0:00:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把本来神圣的圣礼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.17,0:00:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了她自己黄片网站的湿淋淋的广告
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.55,0:00:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都看到她的乳晕了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把画面切掉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.26,0:01:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不敢想  如果尤金看到这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.68,0:01:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.72,0:01:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是呢  这些争议
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.43,0:01:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们得到了所需的订阅数
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.85,0:01:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特很嫉妒我哥哥的收视率
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.90,0:01:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定让金杰上她的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.77,0:01:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样对大家都好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.07,0:01:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是会很滑稽了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.98,0:01:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.70,0:01:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉丝  莎乐美  耶洗别
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.87,0:01:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣经告诉我们所有这些堕落的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.20,0:01:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在罪孽的暗影中与毒蛇共舞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.83,0:01:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但上帝之手永远伸向她们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.08,0:01:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高呼着  来吧  我的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.04,0:01:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忏悔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.17,0:01:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周我们见到了另一位堕落的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.30,0:01:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰·斯威特小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.92,0:01:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像上帝曾经的救赎一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.43,0:01:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也通过我这名使者  向斯威特小姐伸出了双手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.09,0:01:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起帮忙救赎她
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.97,0:01:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她竟然嘲笑圣礼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.93,0:01:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五分钟  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让金杰上节目
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.73,0:01:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对咱们的品牌不好的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.15,0:01:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都情绪很亢奋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.02,0:01:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白鸽之翼的重点不是争议
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.15,0:01:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以对抗争议  或者可以接受它
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.82,0:02:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣一直教导我们要选择接受
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.03,0:02:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.16,0:02:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以跟提高阳光俱乐部的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.41,0:02:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会员人数没关系咯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.16,0:02:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰的小把戏确实很有帮助的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.00,0:02:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你的个人形象是好客和优雅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.17,0:02:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想你把节目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.30,0:02:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得无法控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.84,0:02:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师就做到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.30,0:02:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师多俗气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.88,0:02:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你最近压力很大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.59,0:02:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果压力之后不能保持优雅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.30,0:02:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还有什么好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.76,0:02:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能控制的了金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.06,0:02:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟我有我的军队
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.56,0:02:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.32,0:02:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个不要脸的婊子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.11,0:02:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这嘴这么脏你还亲你妈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.86,0:02:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来吧  我是贝蒂  你今天的助理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.24,0:02:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要以为所有人都跟他一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.70,0:02:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特的粉丝就像一个大的保守的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.41,0:02:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个家庭都有自己家的麻烦事  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.79,0:02:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.87,0:02:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  进去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.33,0:02:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有另一种方式可以触动到斯威特小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.09,0:02:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过一个依照圣经生活的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.92,0:02:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以黎贝卡  内奥米和圣母玛利亚为榜样的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.97,0:03:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个会为正确的事情而战的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.80,0:03:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个母亲一般的玛格丽特·蒙罗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.93,0:03:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回家  杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.30,0:03:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你关掉你的大麻工厂了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.27,0:03:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是的女士 -  很好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.18,0:03:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟萝丝一起弄邮件袋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.10,0:03:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 什么是邮件袋  - 妈妈会选出
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.10,0:03:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些读者来信在节目上朗读
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.06,0:03:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我七岁就开始帮忙弄了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.73,0:03:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你想让所有的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.90,0:03:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天都上你的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.11,0:03:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是好像不太适合我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.82,0:03:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会不想上镜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.57,0:03:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我不想
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.32,0:03:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森  今天我们要向世界介绍我们一家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.04,0:03:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他们我们是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.66,0:03:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.92,0:03:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢你展示的做饭那部分
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.67,0:03:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.79,0:03:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把我们的文化相融合
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.88,0:03:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会展现他的美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.92,0:03:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我则会增添我的优雅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.05,0:03:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要让金杰和粉丝们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.18,0:03:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将不同之处融合起来  是很美味的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.93,0:03:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩好好学着点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.02,0:03:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是团队合作
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.06,0:03:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么埃里克不用来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.02,0:04:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克今天代替你父亲去弄阳光项目了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让埃里克去弄爸爸的项目啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.82,0:04:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那对他肯定意义重大
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.37,0:04:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  想着你父亲  去弄邮件袋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.62,0:04:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.21,0:04:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣让我们更强壮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.29,0:04:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你别把杰森扯上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.96,0:04:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.92,0:04:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.13,0:04:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们帮助玛格丽特赢得这场胜利吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.47,0:04:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个和时间一样古老的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.43,0:04:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个堕落的女人面临着两个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.89,0:04:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到救赎或者下地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.19,0:04:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急迫的想要让她做出正确的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.40,0:04:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 玛格丽特  - 金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.90,0:04:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白鸽之翼接下来的精彩节目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.03,0:04:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上直播  三  二
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.36,0:04:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们位于新奥尔良的阳光直播间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.87,0:04:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是白鸽之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.71,0:04:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我力量吧上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.12,0:05:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了  你们的主持人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.29,0:05:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的朋友  玛格丽特·蒙罗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.09,0:05:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的上帝  我的本意是好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.51,0:05:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.10,0:05:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直独自走在这条道路上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.98,0:05:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心我会被驱逐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.98,0:05:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是对于我毅力的考验
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.03,0:05:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近一直在反思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.15,0:05:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回归的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.78,0:05:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那种离开了很久
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.62,0:05:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后回来  然后更加珍惜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.66,0:05:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所拥有的一切的感觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.66,0:05:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到露珠买电视DB
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.08,0:05:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.09,0:05:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,税后八小时的最低工资
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.42,0:05:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让你买半张公交车票呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.89,0:05:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.05,0:05:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝最近扩充了我们的家族
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.68,0:05:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来介绍一下他们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.11,0:06:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自抚养孩子的单身爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.11,0:06:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他自己都从没有父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.45,0:06:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是可爱的杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.95,0:06:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是杰森  这是科罗拉多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.83,0:06:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有杰森的照片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.66,0:06:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不开心我不上去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.87,0:06:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对待自己的节目很认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.84,0:06:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像是她的教堂一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.17,0:06:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森本来要跟萝丝一起读观众来信的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.05,0:06:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他有点怯场了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.76,0:06:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很正常啊  但我是不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.43,0:06:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我上电视了  老家的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.72,0:06:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会看到  就都知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.48,0:06:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.40,0:06:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.91,0:06:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.66,0:07:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.75,0:07:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个你们已经看了太多的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.51,0:07:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观众在喝倒彩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.63,0:07:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.63,0:07:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无需多言
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.30,0:07:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰是需要被拯救的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.10,0:07:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在白鸽之翼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.22,0:07:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的重点是好客  金杰是我们的客人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.10,0:07:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.44,0:07:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么建议给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.27,0:07:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.86,0:07:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈喜欢把事情都搞成对她有利
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.53,0:07:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且观众都是站她的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.16,0:07:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有观众  而且多亏了阳光电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.91,0:07:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数越来越多了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.62,0:07:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次她和牧师说到我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.62,0:07:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的利润就翻十倍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.50,0:07:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里看是很容易的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.83,0:07:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是到了台上就不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.34,0:07:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次上节目
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.30,0:07:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是五岁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.13,0:07:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还没叫我  我过早的去拿了饼干
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.55,0:07:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就狠狠打了我的手  痛了一周
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.43,0:08:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 玛格丽特太欺负人了  - 节目刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.27,0:08:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是该有人扇回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.27,0:08:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.73,0:08:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.07,0:08:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有不到四个月
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.03,0:08:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就要发行阳光俱乐部的线上购物部门了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.41,0:08:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你今天订阅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.20,0:08:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会免费得到一瓶我的经典香水
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.21,0:08:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,箴言31号
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.00,0:08:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们  看看椅子下面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.05,0:08:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路易斯安那本地制造
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.17,0:08:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都有香水拿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.30,0:08:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种香味只属于最完美的女基督徒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.97,0:08:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这帮黑手党是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.93,0:08:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑手党  哦  是我叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.77,0:08:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是叔叔  其实是我爸的老朋友啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.40,0:08:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  不是家人  胜似家人  那种
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.86,0:08:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是布沙尔先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.07,0:08:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈肯定不会相信的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.99,0:08:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  州长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.41,0:09:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富兰克林
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.91,0:09:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么风把您们吹来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.74,0:09:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是觉得股东应该会喜欢这种精彩的演出吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.37,0:09:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还亲自过来  真是太客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.62,0:09:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视上看也是一样的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.67,0:09:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说这几位朋友对金杰上了我的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.17,0:09:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而引发的会员增长
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.55,0:09:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感到非常满意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.71,0:09:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们仍因掌权者的变更而担忧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.30,0:09:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是来提供帮助的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么个帮法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.14,0:09:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们准备接手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳光俱乐部的一部分股权
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.27,0:09:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  是匿名的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.14,0:09:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不缺资金
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.23,0:09:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但当然感谢您们的好意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.11,0:09:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布沙尔先生  我是安东尼奥·里维拉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.73,0:09:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是您改变了综合格斗的格局
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.99,0:09:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有您就没有现在的我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.15,0:09:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有机会  我很想为您展示一下身手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.20,0:09:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤佩·坎德拉里亚的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.20,0:09:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你认识我妈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.04,0:09:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都认识尤佩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.33,0:09:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧师  你带这几位先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.08,0:09:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去就座吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.71,0:09:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.13,0:10:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙就是综合格斗之王
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.26,0:10:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人走到哪里都是王
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.93,0:10:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机灵点  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.10,0:10:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离他们远点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.48,0:10:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒计时三  二
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.77,0:10:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝的伟大创造
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.73,0:10:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友们  一分钟后  我们将切给
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.82,0:10:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河口置业的埃里克  进行直播
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.37,0:10:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但首先  让我们欢迎皇家少年合唱团
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.21,0:10:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.63,0:10:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和妈妈一起住在城市
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.30,0:10:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投资人怎么来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自我委任为首席执行官  好像惊动了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.35,0:10:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,匿名合伙人决定不再匿名了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.52,0:10:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜  牧师请他们过来  是为了证明
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.93,0:10:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法胜任
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.73,0:10:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是有人更胜任
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.81,0:10:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他  他们会照顾好他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.24,0:11:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.32,0:11:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 这些人都是你治愈的  - 不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.53,0:11:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是上帝  你怎么能进到后台
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.66,0:11:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识富兰克林·李
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.45,0:11:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来尤金·门罗的私人飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.41,0:11:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞行员也名列其中啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.29,0:11:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十年前  我们将手掌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.67,0:11:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按在他身体上  主带走了他的癌症
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.84,0:11:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到你带着洛夫州长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.84,0:11:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和几个胖子来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.13,0:11:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和他们什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.30,0:11:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是他们的精神顾问
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.97,0:11:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大权在握之人还会寻求开导
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.84,0:11:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.18,0:11:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬得越高
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.43,0:11:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就越想谦卑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.10,0:11:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  是关起门来谦卑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.52,0:11:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金·门罗有很多秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.85,0:11:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这些秘密在阳光俱乐部启动之前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.77,0:11:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴露出来  投资人会很紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.36,0:11:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的秘密还是暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.61,0:11:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,测试  测试  一二三
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.03,0:11:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二三  一二  没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.66,0:11:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候  我爸带我来过这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.20,0:11:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会儿这里一无所有  只有希望
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.70,0:11:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸把上帝带到了河口区
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.00,0:11:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好神奇啊  他造了这么多房子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.42,0:11:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  埃里克  他是个伟人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.96,0:11:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们不能在摄影棚里录这段吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.84,0:11:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里有空调
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.80,0:12:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗  好像很累
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.38,0:12:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特把黄金时段
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.59,0:12:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了那个亵渎上帝的荡妇金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.72,0:12:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 行啦  - 她要录一段
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于家庭的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.93,0:12:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我是唯一等待新生命的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.35,0:12:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了二位  准备切回你们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.14,0:12:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.77,0:12:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  来看看你们的捐款都花哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.77,0:12:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给你了  埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.19,0:12:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好  妈妈  - 你好  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.86,0:12:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 贝琪和我在这个  - 今天的新奥尔良
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.70,0:12:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常温暖  阳光强烈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.82,0:12:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  今天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.37,0:12:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真的很热  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.87,0:12:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们愿意忍受酷热
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.04,0:12:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此为一所崭新的社区中心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.66,0:12:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破土奠基
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.00,0:12:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心中充满敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.25,0:12:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  是20年前吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.42,0:12:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在塞尔玛飓风过后  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.92,0:12:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了重生的愿景
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.97,0:12:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伪君子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.10,0:12:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开挖吧  埃里克  开挖
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.68,0:12:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 好吧  - 帮我拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.64,0:12:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢  - 切回给你  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特居然让埃里克
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.57,0:13:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负责慈善项目
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.48,0:13:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么会这么天真
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.65,0:13:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不如说你怎么会让她变得这么天真
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.32,0:13:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对人撒谎可并不慈善
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.30,0:13:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特又派了个怪咖探子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.01,0:13:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 在停车场猫着呢  - 不会吧  哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.93,0:13:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  自己看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.27,0:13:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就坐那儿盯着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.02,0:13:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.27,0:13:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.07,0:13:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是来找我的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.20,0:13:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都进去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上进屋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.33,0:13:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎大家回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.04,0:13:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢手写的信啊  你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.83,0:14:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写起来费点劲  但心意可大不相同了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.75,0:14:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢我们母女一起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.42,0:14:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读信的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.80,0:14:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是观众们手写的信哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.93,0:14:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  拿一封出来念念嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.80,0:14:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的玛格丽特  你能对金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.56,0:14:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出手相救  不啻于英雄所为
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.89,0:14:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱你  圣路易斯奥比斯波的维琪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的被感动到了  维琪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.86,0:14:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是慈母般的言语啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.15,0:14:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的玛格丽特  萝丝是我的最爱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.70,0:14:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢好喜欢她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.20,0:14:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科罗拉多的马克敬上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.54,0:14:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.20,0:14:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是容光焕发
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.58,0:14:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 她恋爱了  - 你怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.58,0:14:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 当妈的就是知道  - 如果他真像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.05,0:14:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写得这么痴情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.63,0:14:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你算是吊到金龟婿了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.97,0:14:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有时间再念一封
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.01,0:14:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝丝  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.93,0:14:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这封我不念  你来念
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.85,0:15:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的玛格丽特  金杰·斯威特会在地狱中燃烧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.73,0:15:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪恶的代价就是  死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.69,0:15:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有点过分了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.57,0:15:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰·斯威特是个肮脏的骚货
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.99,0:15:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.53,0:15:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家保持冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.12,0:15:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰·斯威特的确让有些人激愤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.50,0:15:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们  我们可以一起度过难关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.33,0:15:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.58,0:15:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们休息一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.59,0:15:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.46,0:15:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢  萝丝  - 喂  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.59,0:15:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才那样做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.80,0:15:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很没礼貌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.30,0:15:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来干好事的  你却对我出言不逊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.47,0:15:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父母呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.76,0:15:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去挣钱了  好让我们搬走
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.24,0:15:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河水又涨了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.67,0:16:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你们圣诞节寄来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.84,0:16:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它后来减肥了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.80,0:16:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年把肚子里的东西寄来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.64,0:16:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位嘉宾让我看到了融合家庭的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.73,0:16:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疗愈力量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.56,0:16:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大家热烈欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.77,0:16:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的继子安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.49,0:16:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的衣服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.61,0:16:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安东尼奥
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.53,0:16:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可不能穿成这样来做饭呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.58,0:16:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想来分享另一样东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.29,0:16:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我比美食更爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.54,0:16:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天打得还不够多吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.21,0:16:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  武术的精髓并不是打斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.30,0:16:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是在危机爆发前解决危机
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.97,0:16:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这句话是放之四海而皆准的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.26,0:17:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你教我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.43,0:17:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 没问题  - 走着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.77,0:17:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我站哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.56,0:17:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的高手永远控场
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.94,0:17:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  千万别动啊  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.02,0:17:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.57,0:17:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.53,0:17:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备好再进一步了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.07,0:17:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.79,0:17:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.08,0:17:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是要演好人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.34,0:17:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会把她的鼻子打断的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.34,0:17:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我连动都没动
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.76,0:17:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能相信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.89,0:17:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我的儿子安东尼奥鼓掌
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.35,0:17:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是明星  是我的明星
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.73,0:17:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.90,0:17:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把咱俩都耍了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.03,0:17:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最愚蠢的是  我曾经好想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.24,0:18:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上这个节目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.53,0:18:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你还有埃里克一起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.62,0:18:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个慈祥干净的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.58,0:18:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在终于有机会了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.21,0:18:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们却都讨厌我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.67,0:18:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.17,0:18:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们讨厌的不是你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.88,0:18:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们讨厌的是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.43,0:18:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈和牧师创造的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.26,0:18:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  只管出去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.48,0:18:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的故事说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.90,0:18:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要比我们剩下的人勇敢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.70,0:18:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特的另一个跟踪者
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.95,0:18:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你妈妈吓坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.45,0:18:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你报警了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.70,0:18:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  你妈妈不让我报
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.33,0:18:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没出什么事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.45,0:18:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是下一个  - 我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.66,0:18:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能离开  嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.67,0:18:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.79,0:18:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身为人母  不是一件容易的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.25,0:19:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些时候  你会觉得想要抓狂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.59,0:19:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我的下一位嘉宾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.09,0:19:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打住  玛格丽特  打住
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.80,0:19:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰不见了  金杰不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.39,0:19:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转到合唱团  转到合唱团
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.85,0:19:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我开心得想要抓狂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.64,0:19:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有请皇家男孩合唱团
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.56,0:19:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我们返场演出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.24,0:19:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的世界似乎偏离了正规
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.12,0:19:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和平与爱化为仇恨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.66,0:19:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,众人可鉴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.88,0:19:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么在外面  我们的节目正在直播
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.34,0:19:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的一个变态粉丝在旅馆门口
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.34,0:19:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的姑娘们都不敢出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.51,0:19:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来处理  这就过去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.30,0:19:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.14,0:19:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你满意了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.93,0:19:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一整个节目都在挑唆他们和我对着干
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.27,0:19:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰  你搞出来湿衬衫那一出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.44,0:19:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能怪我们的观众不满
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.90,0:19:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怪你把他们煽动地群情激愤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.11,0:20:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怪他们听信你的煽动  而且你还不阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.65,0:20:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来弥补
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.70,0:20:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你让我感到愧疚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.74,0:20:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起平息这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.46,0:20:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  马上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.54,0:20:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  对  好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.25,0:20:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终止战争
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.30,0:20:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你用得上我  我愿意效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.14,0:20:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经常自问
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.14,0:20:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果天下太平
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.77,0:20:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人和谐相处会是什么样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.65,0:20:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这可能没办法在今天实现
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.94,0:20:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们进行下一个环节之前
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.28,0:20:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.87,0:20:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这一刻
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.07,0:20:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰·斯威特的母亲收到了威胁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.29,0:20:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  有些好人  有些忘乎所以
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.79,0:20:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在阳光电视台
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.75,0:21:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是一家人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.92,0:21:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴力  从来不是解决问题的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.47,0:21:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们受到轻慢  我们懂得忍让
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.93,0:21:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不该让她上电视
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.72,0:21:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不安全
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.22,0:21:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰和我  会讨论我们之间的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.39,0:21:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分歧  就像母女一样谈心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.40,0:21:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰  你愿意配合我一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.23,0:21:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我   我愿意效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.11,0:21:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出改变  除旧立新
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.99,0:21:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我   我愿意效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.83,0:21:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我愿意  - 指引方向
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.92,0:21:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我   我愿意效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.29,0:21:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 拯救世界  - 拯救世界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.80,0:21:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.80,0:21:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.26,0:21:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我让我帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.60,0:21:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.27,0:21:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.77,0:22:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.98,0:22:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息片刻有请金杰·斯威特  不容错过
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.70,0:22:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你收到了我的信
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.99,0:22:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太鲁莽了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.62,0:22:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用了你的真名
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.95,0:22:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我很喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.08,0:22:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能告诉任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.25,0:22:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要谨慎处理
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.54,0:22:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经失去了我的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.09,0:22:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望再失去你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.80,0:22:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人已经走了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.68,0:22:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都没事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.30,0:22:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中精力  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.64,0:22:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.60,0:22:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好  各位
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.77,0:22:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.19,0:22:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.57,0:22:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只管做自己  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.70,0:22:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克  埃里克  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.24,0:22:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母亲在拿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.62,0:22:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危楼筹款
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.74,0:22:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要把这件事处理好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.41,0:22:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是你得处理好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.58,0:22:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才拿到这份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.79,0:23:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就要跑回去找妈妈了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.46,0:23:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.00,0:23:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实跑步来着  但是我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.21,0:23:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要咨询
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.80,0:23:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去和我兄弟坐坐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.22,0:23:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把你妈扯进来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.80,0:23:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果爸爸在这  我会寻求他的建议  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.68,0:23:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你爸在这  这份工作就轮不到你来做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.93,0:23:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人一点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.81,0:23:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,节目回来我们请上了金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.57,0:23:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.19,0:23:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰  我知道在你洗礼之后
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.03,0:23:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的几天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.20,0:23:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多人对你颇有微词
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.53,0:23:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和牧师还煽风点火
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.08,0:23:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是消防员  我只是个忧虑的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.62,0:23:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望这一刻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.96,0:23:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给所有人一个教训
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.59,0:23:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我相信这件事情的两方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.05,0:23:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有好人在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.30,0:23:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在笑什么  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.10,0:23:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 请继续  - 好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.56,0:24:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.43,0:24:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不认为你是个恶人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.44,0:24:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谢谢你  - 但是你所做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.61,0:24:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤害了我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.27,0:24:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那伤害了很多人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.07,0:24:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你借我们的圣礼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.99,0:24:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打低俗广告
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.32,0:24:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.12,0:24:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为2.5亿信奉基督的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.95,0:24:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都很愚蠢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.08,0:24:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不  我不这么想  - 哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.83,0:24:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我信奉基督  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.21,0:24:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个话题里难道容不下尖锐的反对观点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.84,0:24:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.51,0:24:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目的是进行深度对话交流
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.35,0:24:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是你邀请我来的原因  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.81,0:24:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了教化观众
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.27,0:24:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望帮助你理解你的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.02,0:24:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是存在后果的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.15,0:24:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以跟踪者  仇恨邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.07,0:24:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有被吐口水  都是我自找的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.07,0:24:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还真是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.07,0:25:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为女权主义争光呢  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.20,0:25:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在互联网上出卖身体就是女权主义吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.75,0:25:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我的身体属于我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.29,0:25:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么处置我说了算
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.25,0:25:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以每个妓女都是女权主义者
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.30,0:25:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没这么说  而且不要暗示
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.01,0:25:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是妓女
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.59,0:25:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不是说这个行当有什么过错
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.64,0:25:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从时间伊始
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.47,0:25:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就存在着神化的妓女形象  伊西塔  阿佛洛狄忒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.31,0:25:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们理解不应以身体为耻
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.94,0:25:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诗篇25：3
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.40,0:25:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡等候你的必不羞愧  惟有那无故行奸诈的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.03,0:25:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必要羞愧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.45,0:25:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段经文中的你指的是上帝  不是金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.24,0:25:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们能给
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.58,0:25:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们带来喜乐有什么区别
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.00,0:25:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在玩火
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.50,0:25:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才刚开始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.30,0:25:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人们向我们寻求慰藉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.30,0:26:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们尊重他们的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.43,0:26:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给他们提供他们在家中得不到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.43,0:26:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满足男人的需求
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.73,0:26:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是脱掉衣服这么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.15,0:26:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不对  女士们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.57,0:26:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你满足了尤金的需求
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.69,0:26:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就不会在维加斯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.40,0:26:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我母亲出轨
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.57,0:26:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  妈妈  如果你在看的话
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.12,0:26:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在自欺欺人了  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.91,0:26:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不只是性
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.62,0:26:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金爱她
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.04,0:26:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他向她寻求救赎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.54,0:26:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她满足了你提供不了的需求
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.34,0:26:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有什么话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.89,0:26:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有什么话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.06,0:26:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多年以来  尤金背着我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.03,0:26:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻花问柳
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.95,0:27:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我闭口不言
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.53,0:27:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道真相  但是为了维护家庭我保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.62,0:27:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你怎敢将通奸和救赎相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.42,0:27:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的女人  自私自利
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.38,0:27:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来不在乎自己会对外界造成什么影响
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.17,0:27:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和尤金一起经营了一段人生
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.43,0:27:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个事业  一个家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.93,0:27:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后某个俗艳的风尘女子看到我所建立的事业
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.22,0:27:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就想要乘虚而入
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.60,0:27:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大可以随意粉饰你的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.14,0:27:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是当一时的新鲜感过去之后
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.61,0:27:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像尤金这样的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.02,0:27:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会夹着尾巴回家来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.24,0:27:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.11,0:27:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为和你不同
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.53,0:27:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会助长他们本性中邪恶的那一面
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.16,0:27:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们让他们良心无愧  而你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.12,0:27:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们深陷罪恶和羞耻的泥潭
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.71,0:27:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次婚外情之后  尤金都会回到我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.30,0:28:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仍然接纳他
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.05,0:28:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我向上帝宣誓
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.43,0:28:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至死不渝
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.56,0:28:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这意味被公开羞辱
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.52,0:28:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让搞淫秽色情的大嘴巴上电视
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.73,0:28:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也认了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.81,0:28:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝用你们这样的女人考验我们
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.40,0:28:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕我想要用指甲
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.86,0:28:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,划破你们放荡的面颊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.95,0:28:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.12,0:28:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为尤金  他可能夺走了我的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.08,0:28:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他夺不走我的尊严
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.00,0:28:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个低贱  败坏
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.38,0:28:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假仁假义的小贱人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.64,0:28:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有什么话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.97,0:28:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.48,0:28:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我们马上回来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.81,0:29:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别走开
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.32,0:29:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金杰·斯威特恭候大驾
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.36,0:29:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得漂亮  说得好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.53,0:29:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好  马上回来
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.83,0:29:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个阳光项目你看过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.16,0:29:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.54,0:29:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尤金在负责
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.67,0:29:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阳关传教项目简直太卑鄙了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.46,0:29:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俱乐部没上线呢  这可是个坏消息
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.13,0:29:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论何时都是坏消息
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.97,0:29:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.22,0:29:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.64,0:29:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边这些朋友是承包商
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.01,0:29:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,节目结束后再找他们谈
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.68,0:29:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  维吉尔叔叔  汤斯  唐
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.60,0:29:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗说你是最合适人选
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.73,0:29:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.94,0:29:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别像你父亲那样让我们失望
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.53,0:29:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在该你一展身手了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.87,0:29:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.66,0:29:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你进后台
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.20,0:29:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可没说能来这
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.87,0:29:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想着如果金杰要大干一场
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.67,0:30:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些消息肯定会泄露
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.71,0:30:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你滥用了我们的友谊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.80,0:30:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.30,0:30:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克娶了牧师保罗·托马斯的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.76,0:30:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于尤金的私生子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.43,0:30:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她似乎比他要说的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.10,0:30:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道得更多
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.60,0:30:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在你拉走我的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.14,0:30:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃里克和你的牧师正在跟
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.77,0:30:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路易斯安那州某些最有权势人窃窃私语
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.06,0:30:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还漏了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.74,0:30:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有两或三个以我名义聚集的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.41,0:30:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与他们同在
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.87,0:30:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马太福音第18章20节
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.08,0:30:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我传经
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.16,0:30:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在问你问题
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.67,0:30:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应的已经给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.93,0:30:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走好不送
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.40,0:31:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要什么  喝水吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.78,0:31:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不用  - 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.53,0:31:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你是谁  - 她是你助理
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.53,0:31:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没见过她
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.70,0:31:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我爱你  玛格丽特  - 节目马上开始
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.95,0:31:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒计时3  2
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.58,0:31:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧  你这个罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.01,0:31:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.81,0:31:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺拉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.93,0:31:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能进广告吗  诺拉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.06,0:31:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.40,0:31:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要大家都看看
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.90,0:31:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你需要清理干净  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.78,0:31:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天看着你的节目长大
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.03,0:31:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你那学会了做饭  学会读圣经
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.29,0:32:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想着某天能见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.58,0:32:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦想着站上这个舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.42,0:32:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想这样
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.17,0:32:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.34,0:32:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点就信了你  玛格丽特
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.22,0:32:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的欢迎会
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.59,0:32:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 现在进广告  - 进广告
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.97,0:32:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.43,0:32:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马太福音第26章15节问道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.89,0:32:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意给我什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.56,0:32:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特  还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.03,0:32:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没见过这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.78,0:32:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不知道怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.08,0:32:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的凳子拿来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.17,0:32:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此之前她只拿过两次凳子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.25,0:32:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次是911事件后
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.47,0:32:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一次是最高法院
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.01,0:32:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认可同性恋婚姻
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.80,0:32:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才一幕让人不安
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.14,0:33:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于金杰承受的公众羞辱
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.81,0:33:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我深表遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.52,0:33:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个母亲  我立志每天
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.23,0:33:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引导并保护我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.07,0:33:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而今天这两个目标我都没完成
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.99,0:33:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于金杰说的关于我和基督教的话
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.29,0:33:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们都很生气
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.50,0:33:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.96,0:33:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道金杰生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.79,0:33:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和她母亲都得到了净化
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.80,0:33:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问上帝  我们该何去何从
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.72,0:33:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们继续威胁彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.34,0:33:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃彼此吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.39,0:33:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.52,0:33:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基督徒  一如优秀的木匠
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.02,0:33:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们建造宽恕的桥梁
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.31,0:33:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不嘲笑  不引诱
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.28,0:33:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们投资
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.90,0:34:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在阳光广播电台
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.20,0:34:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们投资自己
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.08,0:34:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及这个世界的每个金杰·斯威特
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.50,0:34:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如其他人投资我们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.83,0:34:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些好人就像维吉尔·洛夫州长
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.92,0:34:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐·布沙尔  还有汤斯·道克提
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.26,0:34:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺拉  给个镜头
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.80,0:34:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给前排这些优秀的人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.01,0:34:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5号机位  转向前排
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.43,0:34:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 用5号机位  - 当尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.68,0:34:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果听过就告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.72,0:34:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当尤金和我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.89,0:34:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们在
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.23,0:34:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纳契托什市公共广播
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.06,0:34:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的三位绅士
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.77,0:34:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们看到了特别之处
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.73,0:34:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给了我们机会
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.32,0:34:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识那个胖子  他喜欢穿高跟鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.16,0:34:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得赶紧离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.24,0:34:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于金杰  也许今天没能拯救你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.33,0:34:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们会继续努力
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.50,0:34:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们相信救赎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.63,0:34:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要证明
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.34,0:34:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要看看你哥哥杰森就好
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.13,0:35:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森  你在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.43,0:35:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请站起来  亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.43,0:35:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2号机  找到杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.47,0:35:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2号机走起
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.18,0:35:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几周前  大家听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.19,0:35:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森曾是个毒贩
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.02,0:35:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在科罗拉多州的拖车里
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.57,0:35:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看他现在
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.11,0:35:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们家庭的怀抱中安然无恙
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.24,0:35:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.49,0:35:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到你了  杰森
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.74,0:35:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全世界都看到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.75,0:35:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  那是马克
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.83,0:35:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 马克  - 真的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.55,0:35:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.72,0:35:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天投资阳光俱乐部
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.26,0:35:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家齐心协力  让金杰·斯威特回到基督的怀抱
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.07,0:36:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明天还会来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.32,0:36:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后天  大后天
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.36,0:36:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.95,0:36:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将相互投资  相互努力
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.58,0:36:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿我们都在上帝的荣耀中复活
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.67,0:36:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.75,0:36:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行行好  就当做慈善
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.84,0:36:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是偷窃行为
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.76,0:36:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.55,0:36:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.76,0:36:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  尤金  继续走
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.93,0:36:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都回去吧  明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.68,0:36:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到你跟他做我们的事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.77,0:36:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我很伤心
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.86,0:36:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在场  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.91,0:36:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐·布沙尔本人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.74,0:36:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须表现好点
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.43,0:37:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯威特女士
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.18,0:37:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的事我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.48,0:37:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的车来了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.32,0:37:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个神父真帅
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.20,0:37:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 他是个牧师  - 有什么区别
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.87,0:37:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停车场那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.00,0:37:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留了这个给你
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.67,0:37:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你妈妈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.97,0:37:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 她怎么样了  - 她挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.48,0:37:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜怎么着
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.23,0:38:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格丽特观众席里那些人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.52,0:38:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姑娘们认识他们
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.07,0:38:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是客户
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.28,0:38:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次他们再来  录下来
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.49,0:38:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都录下来
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.91,0:38:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能这样做  客户信任我们
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.08,0:38:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁不想上电视
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.26,0:38:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰森就拜托你这么一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.17,0:38:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都没做到
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.88,0:38:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应过的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.93,0:38:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是尽力做到最好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.97,0:38:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对谁最好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.10,0:38:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.27,0:38:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在台上说金杰的那些话
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.89,0:38:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许可以让阳光俱乐部大卖
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.19,0:38:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.11,0:38:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人之间的整个激烈争辩
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.48,0:38:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  太让人心累了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.70,0:38:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很累  萝丝
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.32,0:38:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我厌倦了我这么努力工作
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.29,0:38:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我的女儿们却有权
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.50,0:39:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断告诉我有多让她们失望
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.17,0:39:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少这点我们是一致的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.83,0:39:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实很失望
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.26,0:39:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  房屋正在倒塌
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.84,0:39:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水不能喝
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.93,0:39:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们需要帮助  我们就会出现
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.72,0:39:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬慈善
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.35,0:39:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敬慈善
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.78,0:39:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我留了言
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.53,0:39:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  我知道你们都担心
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.87,0:39:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只要女士们不停争吵
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.74,0:39:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手就不知道左手在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.74,0:39:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原话出自圣经马太福音第6章第3节
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.58,0:39:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.17,0:39:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天开始新工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.50,0:39:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.96,0:39:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让很多人的生活更好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.96,0:39:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如从我开始
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.55,0:39:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.27,0:40:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.44,0:40:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.70,0:40:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.96,0:40:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的人不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.96,0:40:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在阳光俱乐部分一杯羹
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.57,0:40:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是今天节目结束后
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.37,0:40:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,订阅量飙升
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.25,0:40:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会带他们去营地
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.46,0:40:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会用点庞沙图拉的蜂蜜
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.05,0:40:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们的投资慢慢下降
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.18,0:40:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饼干和蜂蜜也许不能满足他们
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.89,0:40:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有其它办法
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1347\fscy540}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx411\fscy398}■
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(337.866,150.555)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\pos(311.68,176.347)\fscx1326\fscy535}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\pos(269.333,173.689)\frx0\fry2\fscx409\fscy401}■
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(336.266,149.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(269.334,207.132)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\3c&H000000&\c&H000000&\alpha&B0\fscx1420\fscy538\pos(194.48,214.214)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\bord0\fad(0,500)\shad0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\\t(0,500,)\frx0\fry2\fscx394\fscy391\pos(152.133,211.556)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,\h\h人人视频APP \N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs26}美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧\N{\b0\u0}{\bord0\blur0\fs23}离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏\N{\fs29}各大应用商店皆可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs12\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(219.599,189.844)}在线看美剧的追剧神器
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\fn时尚中黑简体\bord0\shad0\fs8\b1\c&H51DAFF&\2a&HFF&\pos(152.134,244.999)}扫描即可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.44,0:40:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(191.714,65.904)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制\N合作请加QQ:{\c&H0607F9&}2643527418
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.00,0:30:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\fad(1000,500)\move(311.2,1,15.6,1,16,15000)}免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2\fn方正卡通简体\pos(194.933,27.178)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.19,0:05:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(800,0)\fs25\t(0,5000,\fs45)\pos(192,105.067)\c&H1314CE&}富 贵 逼 人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.39,0:05:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord2)\fn方正卡通简体\fs20\pos(194.8,7.733)}本视频由{\c&H0102FB&\3c&HFAD673&}哒哒{\c&H0DF6F9&\3c&H042B79&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&}原创译制
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.23,0:09:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：Efroimson
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.49,0:09:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：一江春水向西流
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.25,0:09:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}翻译：莲子米 & 二师姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.54,0:05:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}校对：一江春水向西流
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.22,0:05:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}统筹：折木奉太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.69,0:05:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\pos(10.8,7.467)}总监：一芹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.08,0:08:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\u1\c&H8ADCF0&\pos(58.4,193.067)\b1}距离阳光俱乐部上线                                                                  	 订阅人数{\u0}\N106天 9小时  49分钟  	                                                              	 820，0406
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.64,0:10:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\u1\c&H8ADCF0&\pos(58.4,193.067)\b1}距离阳光俱乐部上线                                                                  	 订阅人数{\u0}\N106天 9小时  41分钟  	                                                              	 820，0415
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.42,0:14:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\u1\c&H8ADCF0&\pos(58.4,193.067)\b1}距离阳光俱乐部上线                                                                  	 订阅人数{\u0}\N106天 9小时  32分钟 	                                                               	820，0458
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.62,0:33:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\a5\u1\c&H8ADCF0&\pos(58.4,193.067)\b1}距离阳光俱乐部上线                                                                  	 订阅人数{\u0}\N106天9小时3分钟  		                                                                    820，1153
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.33,0:21:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz6.152\frx12\fry344\pos(191.6,126.933)\c&H212121&}斯威特女士收
