Composer: Zhu Shirui
Record: Lan Hua
Playwrights: ZhouXiaowen Luwei
Director: Zhou Xiaowen
Leading actors: WuYujuan Lijing
Sister,what is wrong
Lanlan,dont be afraid.You have grown up
Every girl will experience
this when they grow up
Now Lanlan
you have grown up to be a colleen
OBSESSION
Right,hold on and exert yourself
Good,try harder!
Ok,let down slowly
Hold on
Let down
Come on,once again
Ok it will be fine in no timeCarry on
Exert yourself
Ok
You are so close to the fan again
Be careful of your health
I have tried so hard just
to enjoy this moment
You come and play,too
Qingqing,I didnt find out
that your neck is as nice
as the beauty in the pictorial
Hey,check whether
I have prickly heat or not
Ijustsaid thatyouwere fat
you really then breathed
heavily like a lard-bucket
No.48 has been seven days late
If she does not take caesarean birth
she is likely to suffer massive hemorrhage
But her husband didnt allow
He said that it would
be ugly if a scar is left
What a baddy
His wifes life has been in danger
Have him responsible for
the birth and bear the pain
It is said that making man pregnant instead
is under research in foreign countries
If it succeeds
then women can be free from this suffer
Right,men are pregnant for ten months,too
Then use the scalpel to cut their paunches
and finally sew the incision
Have them go through al
the pain that women have to suffer
And women and men will be equal
Ha,thank you for your great effort
Thank you very much
Come on,have a drink
Sorry
After B ultrasonography examination
it was a baby girl,but it turns out
to be a boy with your effort
There is always a way out
Excuse me
Can you tell me who the midwife is
It is the woman with a nice neck
Come,this is for you
Take it.This is the second one
It really matches her
She looks like a beautiful goodness
Look,she is so pretty
Shoe,give me,give me
Dont grab
Traveling shoes
Fine,I have not taken any exercise yet
Five seconds
Ten seconds
Fifteen seconds
Is it the time
Not yet
Ok,we can have breakfast now
What do we have
Bread,orange juice and milk
Here you are
I have not brushed my teeth yet
You forgot again
Have breakfast first,then brush teeth
When you pass the book house
return the book to Li Changwei
Why not give it back by yourself
Do me a favor,please
Twill take you to
have fun in summer holiday
Really
Twill keep my promise
Ok
61.What a score
My brother has told me to
choose the subject Jam good at
Anay
I am going to study medicine in the future
As long as I can do well
in mathematic physics,chemistry
and foreign language,it will be fine
What is the point of learning history
It is fine to just pass the exam
You would not exist without history
It is my parents who gave birth to me
not history
My brother said that history
is the least credible
Only science is the most reliable
I always feel that it
is my sister who gave birth to me
It is not scientific.You are totally a laic
even having no idea of
some common knowledge on medicine
Doctor will be the most
promising occupation in the future
It is boring
Just like my sister
She is always together
with pregnant women
and has to comfort them
WeliThat is the job of nurse
You need to take a degree of doctor
if you want to study medicine
San Mao had traveled all around
the world in her life
Have you read her books
I never do light reading
She fell in love when she was eight years old
Later she married a man
with big moustache
He was able to dive
Eight years old? You are kidding
There was little gonad-tropic hormone
when she was eight years old
What a boloney
Goodbye
Hey
I have already make room for you
Why do you still crowd in upon me
Sorry.I didnt mean to
I just pulled on my new clothes
Let me wrap it for you
Stop,stop
You have made it dirtier
How can I come home like this
It doesnt matter
no one will notice it since it is so late
What if I muddy you
What about letting me send you home
For heavens sake
Twill not charge you fare
Twill not askyou to pay for my clothes
Go ahead
Chewing gum
Go along and turn left
Let me get off
Let me get off Stop
Let me
Where can you escape
Wang Qingqing,has her period come
What is the matter
What is his ascent
What are his facial features
Did you bite his hands badly
What is going on
Brother,did you lose or win
What hell are you playing with
Thing that is
not suitable for good guys
You should read some good books
There are no good books
There are a lot of good books
Like Legend of Hero Shooting Vultures
Invincible Yuanyang Legs
both of which are better than this one
All are about men and women
What a mess
What is wrong with your hands
Nothing
What did you do last night
You,come here
Sit down
Dont try to lie,tell me the truth
I just thieved a car for a drive
Whose car
The one in front of the door
I dont know whom it belongs to
Where is the car
I have deserted it
You want more troubles,right
If not for our mothers sake
Twill cut your legs down
The young one or the old one
Is it the old one,The young one
How young that boy is
Maybe it is the old one
How poor the boy is
How piteous
Was it what its like when its found
Yes,it was
At five in this morning
People in Eastern Restaurant reported that
their cars were stolen
A man who fished by the water found it
The type and brand of this car are
coincident with those of the stolen one
Any other clues
The man said
The whole shape of this car
There is a magazine under the car
Look,Qingqing Book House
Bxcept the strange smell of the rope
Did you have other responses
like feeling dry in your mouth
or tearing
Eat this
Dont be afraid.This is just almond
Is this smell
This
Sister,I dont want to smell any more
Should we do this
Try to think whether it is this smell
I dont know.
My mouth was hurt by the tight rope
Furthermore,I couldnt see anything
How can I know
Stop here
Twill go back by myself
Stop,dont drive ahead any more
Ah,ah
Stop,stop
When women are attacked
they should yell hysterically
exert the utmost strength to
cry out,understand
Ok,once more
Action
Ah,ah
Ok,stop.What are you doing
Making trouble
Jam wanted.I go out for a moment
What is up
The heroine asked me to dub for her
Policemen have
already called on my brother
My brother said that this kind of
magazine was stocked a month ago
The two hundred copies have been sold out
He could not remember the buyers at all
What is more,this magazine
always goes the rounds
Therefore,it is not certain that the
criminal ever bought this magazine
My brother felt rather afflictive
He was reluctant to respond to me
Hey,Qingqing
My brother is really nice to you
Which one? This one
A Satyr from the North
This one,Bugbear
Do you want
If not,give it back
All right,you gave the correct amount
All of my books enjoy
a sound market all over the world
How much does this book cost
1.2 Yuan 1.2 Yuan
What do you think
Do you think it expensive
How thick this book is
Both of its sides are colored
Want to buy or not
Qingqing
You change the sign
Change it or not
What has it to do with the sign
Qingqing
If you have anything to say,please tell me
Qingqing,please dont get angry
Twill tell you.I will tell you slowly
Everyone,I am sorry
Whats the matter?
She tears my book into pieces. Sorry. Sorry
I have pay for it I only lmow that
something has happened to their family
I have the hump
Although unhappy
you still cant tear my book
How about this
I change another book for you
How about this one
Sorry,very sorry
Sorry
Goodbye and Twill drop in another day
Do drop in again
What are you tearing?
Burning them will be easier
Twill pay for you
There are several hundreds
of bookstalls in the whole city
How can you tear all these books up
Although the criminals can escape
to the ends of the earth
After 40 years
they will still be caught and sent to gallows
Anyway,that guy cant escape that far
It would be good if
I had gone to take Lanlan back
What did the policemen say
What could they tell me
Actually I also know what they have known
First,he may have visited the Book House
Second,he has local accent
He is a driver
and he left his footprints
Furthermore,Lanlan once bit his hand
It is possible that a scar
is left on his left hand
Oh,also
He likes chewing gum
The only problem lies
on how Lanlan can recognize him
Moreover,it was dark at that time
Thus she might not recognize exactly
Lanlan needs to go to school
Qingqing,do your parents know this thing
This is the representative of the works
of the Japanese writer Du Bian Chun Yi
The hungry love desire
Extreme in secret
Flaming passions
Who wants? Who wants
How about buying one
Ok
Who would like to buy the book?
Who would like to buy the book
This is the representative one
of Japanese writer Du Bian Chun Yi
The hungry love desire...
It seems that you had an appointment
I picked him up and then it was your turn
He was four hours earlier than you
Yes
We should return,shouldnt we
Can you not come back after
what happened
You are right
If have something to say,tell me here
No matter what,you should
let me see Lanlan first,right
Be quiteBe quiet
Mr.Li is iliThus
Twill take over the classes for him
The course is long-distance
running outside the school
Notice your rhythm of breathing
when running
Run back as soon as you reach
the turning of SI Ping Road
Take care
Why did you take off the shoes
I can run faster if I am barefoot
Just like Zola Bard
Teacher,she is called Zo?
Ally,a family member of the Zola Bards
Be serious
Stand out that girl in the back row
who does not take off the clothes
What are you laughing at
Why did you not take off the clothes
Didnt your parents buy
short sports wear for you
When runing out of the school gate
you represent our school spirit
Teacher
Except this girl
all the students turn right
and run
Ok,close up
Close up
Spread apart
You practice shooting
a basket by yourself first
How much can be earned in a month
You can earn the cost
in less than three years
You can drive such a nice car
puff foreign cigarettes,and drink coke
Lao Zhao,watch it for a moment
Ok
You should put on this kind of dress like his
The older youre
the more loudly you get dressed
You are the only one who
becomes rich first among us
Why dont you have retired early
Like you,turn out for work every day
Only 0.8 yuan per km in the city
and 1.2 yuan in outskirt
Oont you think
that you have worked long enough
Uncle,can I have a cigarette
Lao Zhao,you should
have followed my suit long before
You also can do some contributions
to the four modernizations,right
Uncle,will I be kept in custody
For what
Just because I played mah-jongg
Oh,gambling
Everyone gambles
my parents,my grandparents
my brother and sister all play it
Why did you only capture me
Dont you think it is unfair
As you came in
you confessed all your family members
I don t think it is unfair
Why dont you confess your cahoots
It is they who won
and took all the money away
The police didnt arrest the winners
but only captured me,such a loser,instead
I have been unlucky enough
We catch you and you confess them out
The police then can arrest
them and have the money back
Really
Dont mock me
You bought this gasoline
at high price,didnt you
Bought the gasoline?
I dont have so much money
I will try to borrow a car to you
Four to five hundreds a month
Really Yes
Then I can buy a piano to my grandson after
I have worked for one or two years
Quite right
Now this is popular
Captain,I am suffering a diarrhea
I couldnt hold out much longer
Can you see it? It is at least the
second time that he has been imprisoned
I really couldnt hold out any more
Go,go,go
Please wait for a minute
Ok
Lao Bait you cant buy parts back
we cant do the work
no use complaining to me
The bank said that we have overdrawn
I dont see any hopes left for our stall
Here you are, Catch
Cover the gasoline basin
Ok
There is something wrong
with our boss today
Both of them must know inside out
There is really nothing to that
Our boss was subpoenaed by the police
I want to return to my hometown
Maybe the police will make arrest again
It is possible about
the thing happened in the chapel
What is it?
What? A teen-age girl was attacked
It is said that she
was bubbled by the chauffeur
Her eyes were covered
The criminal like this will be
shot directly when is caught
One is charger,one is theft
A daughter must be taken good care of
Mine is ahoy
You have quarreled
with your wife for three months
It is probable the trouble your son has made
Puck you
Ah,dont tweak
If I was hurt badly
you would fail to have a little brother
In the past,it was considered that having
a boy or a girl is depended upon by women
This is obviously a kind of blind faith
Actually,it is not the mans will that
decide whether to have a boy or a girl
All right,boys and girls
do you have any other questions
Teacher
Stand up
Mr.Yang
Your statement has been outdated
This is what the teaching materials say
Then it is the teaching
materials that are outdated
Huang Xiaolin
What is the new idea you have invented
I did not invent itIt is what the book says
What is about? Can you read it?
I am sorry
It doesnt matter
It is fine to let
students know the new viewpoint
According to the research of Banger
Harrison,a Swiss medical doctor
The prospect that human can decide the
gender of our offspring is in sight
As everyone knows
It is the chromosome XY
and XX that decide the gender
The traveling speed
and the life-span of these two
spermatozoa are quite different
Besides,the PH of the womans secretion
also has influence,to some degrees
on the vigor and life-span of
these two kinds of spermatozoa
For example,when the ovum is
in the waiting condition
if the spermatozoon with
chromosome XY reaches first
then the woman is likely to have a boy
On the contrary,if the spermatozoa
are in the state of waiting
owning to the comparatively long life-span
of the spermatozoon with chromosome XX
then it is quite possible to have a girl
Huang Xiaolin,then you are XY.Right
Yes
So are you
Therefore,the time of ovulation
is very important
It also can be said that the time
of insemination is more critical
I do not fear
Twill get divorced as soon as I leave hospital
She really bit
She really likes her father
Since she conceived
the family members have been keeping
on feeding her like spooning a duck
They wished that she
can become as fat as a pig
As a result,she was too fat
to give birth to the baby
either suffering from dystocia
or massive hemorrhage
Hum,they are making
trouble for themselves
Qingqing,do you feel sick
How dangerous it was just now
In our business
two lives are concerned
when we are in delivery room
We shouldnt be slipshod
Since tomorrow you change all
my shifts to night ones
Don t brood on that thing
In fact,as long as there is nothing
wrong with Lanlans neural system
and mentality
There wont be bad influences on her
marriage and having child in the future
Besides,the young will
not care much for such a thing
I remember that a magazine
has mentioned this problem
Let me see,at whose home I read that?
Hey,Qingqing
Lanlan,why didnt you go home?
Twill go later
Lanlan,what are you going to do
Going home
Did your sister come to receive you
I dont want to wait for her
It is too dangerous to go home by yourself
Let me send you home
It is you who will take risks
if go home by yourself
Why are you following me
Who lets you send me home
What? What a response to my kindness
Lanlan,return the book to Li Changwei,ok
But this book is quite expensive
Also,it is the very book I want to buy
But it is he who gave you the book
My elder brother tells me
not to take others things
Lanlan,sorry,I am late
By the way,this is not the former one
This is the new one that
my elder brother bought recently
That will do very nicely
Wait for me at Li Changweis
Twill go home and have
a talk with him about something
Lanlan
Didnt the business of the bookstalls
outside the door come on very well
Why did they stop doing business
I am about to be a standing committee
of National Peoples Congress
I should do something good in front
of the electorates
They should not have
sold those kinds of books
They are doing harm to the youths minds
Dont worryTrue gold fears no fire
The young men are not mature enough
Thus,their feelings are likely
to get the upper hand
How can I not worry
You may have read at least over
one hundred such kind of books here
But you are still honest and just
So,this kind of books will have
no harm so far as the soul is healthy
If you go on talking nonsense
Twill close down your shop
This
This paper is broken
I know
Do you want it
Let me see
The fashion in 1988
Prevailing over the world through
the thought that being stout
is the most beautiful
This book is quite good,healthy
You at least can change
four hundreds hair-styles
Take it home and read it at leisure
Mind how you go
Take your time
Lanlan
Didnt the medical doctor join us at play
What is the matter with you
Lao Wuzhi made an apology to everyone
and also gave the stock of soup
In addition,he picked up
over one hundred pictures
and asked Lao Zhao to take
Tao Lanlan to recognize the criminal
Good
But thing like picture is mostly unreliable
Some were taken several years ago
It is also uncertain about the
appearance of the criminal at that time
It is easyTake Tao Lanlan
with us to every work unit
and identify the criminal one by one
That maybe reliable
You are kiddingIs it disgraceful
Lao Zhao,you should make
decisive decision when necessary
When you have a child in
the future,you will know
If I were his father
I would be reluctant to let you take
the child around either
Right Yes,yes,yes
If she were not to go around with us
she could not bring back the suspects
What is to be done if her
parents want to take the child back
I know
How can we just follow their requirement
The headquarters are
urging us to solve the case
If she went
it would be hard to crack the case
I can manage you but not her parents
All will turn out easy to deal
with after the great effort is made
No matter it is easy or not
we have to solve the case
Xiao Liu,you are possessed by
the idea of driving
It seems a bit off base
Why
I have not suspected Lao Zhao
Go away,you
Hey, Lao Zhao,what is your view
On that day,I noticed the marks
left by the tires on the spot
The criminal was only able to escape
after backed the car in three directions
And he discarded the car among the reefs
Besides,he neither pulled the
brake handle nor closed the car door
It seems that he dose not know his goods
Hey,the criminal was committing a crime
Rather than going on business
Since he would leave
the magazine in the car
he also would forget to pull the handbrake
Of course,I can not be sure about my guess
I just have a kind of feeling
that something is wrong
To crack a case is not to feel
but to look for the scope
Not all the people are suspects
At last you have found the scope
of the case you are in charge of
But I have not any clues at all
I am just talking through my hat
You are welcome
Whether you go or not
if he forces you to
Twill go with you
I cant go
I have to turn to that guy
Sister
Lanlan
Why do you stand humming and hawing?
Speak out
I saw that man again
Who?
The man who attacked me in that evening
Where? When
He was there as I came back just now
Where did he go
He left from here
Are you sure
Maybe
Why didnt you tell Li Changwei
I heard that you thought scorn of him
Then why didnt you cry out
I was afraid.
What a fool.Serve you right
Sister
You,come her and sit down
Brother,you lost money again
In that evening when you stole the car
Something happened in Xiao Huang Tang
The police called me
Fortunately,three men testified
that I was playing cards
If not
Brother,one should
answer for what he does
I did it
It is really you who did it
I really doubt whether
you was born by our mother
Why did you take out you anger of losing
money in playing cards on me
Why must you attack that girl
Why must you do such conscienceless thing
What a hell of your mind
You are born to be a fool
You still go out with these clothes
You are really considerate of the policemen
Take them off
Pour gasoline on and burn them out
But brother,this is new
Hold your jaw!
Put these onTake off the shoes
and burn them out together
I have painstakingly brought up
such a son of a bitch
Brother,didnt you say that it
was not good to gamble but whore
Itold a lie
Twill get anger if you go on hitting me
The man is still around here
Then it is more dangerous
You should go to Shanghai
with your mom in a few days
to keep clear of that fellow
Until the criminal is arrested
you can come back
Right
You can write to me if someone teases you
Or you also can write your uncle
Say nothing of her who is just a child
We will be also afraid
of seeing the criminal
I once saw in broad daylight
a man thrusting the busman with a knife
People around didnt dare to speak
Dont fight with other students at school
Just pay all your attention on study
If trouble comes,there is no way
Everyday when come home after school
First study
I think none but when
she grows up in the future
and marries,she will get to understand
Man,if he cant forget something
he will be unable to keep alive
Suppose that I could forget
what happened on Lanlan
I would not be a human
Fine
It is the polices job to capture the criminal
It is none of your business
Dont forget to add clothes
Did the police give birth to Lanlan
Was she brought up by the police
All right,all right
Dont let Lanlan hear
Lanlan,say goodbye to me
Qingqing
Dont get on,the car starts
Qingqing,the car is about to start
Lanlan,Qingqing
Qingqing,Qingqing
Hurry up, Lao Tao
Qingqing has whipped Lanlan off
Why didnt you stop her
She got up and then whipped her off
Be quick,be quick
Train attendant
Would you please look after the luggage
of the upper and lower berth of No.7
Thank you,thank you
The luggages are two things,under this
Two pieces,please
You have been willful from a baby
Be quiet. Lanlan is sleeping
Your mother and I
Qingqing,in that year you drove us away
wanting to stayed and lived by
yourself with your little sister
You made a tremendous fuss about it
We finally had to yield
Besides,we felt rather guilty
Thus we granted your request
Actually,if you had not made such
a fuss by following your temper
it would have not
Why are you mentioning that
I had thyroid
hyperparathyroidism in that year
Lanlan and you went to
hospital and sent me dishes
and accompanied me
Your father was busy
Fine,please dont mention any more
I cannot bear any other pain any longer
Your present state is also not very good
It would be better to let Lanlan go with us
And Twill manage to
move you to Shanghai
I can find a good school for Lanlan
Please let Lanlan go with us
She then can study in Beijing
Why dont you ask for Lanlans opinion
She is too young to know
Is she is reluctant to
It is not up to her
What if your wife bullies her
Your words are more and more nonsense
What if your man teases her
How can Lanlan hold
her head high in the future
Can she lose her face
Reputation can kill man
You still know reputation
I ask Lanlan to live with me just in
hope of offering her a good environment
What a hell of good environment
Lanlan and I have suffered
a lot since we lived with you
Whenever you quarreled you threw things
You hit each other villainously
I was too frightened to cry
and shivered in the sheet
I really wished to die
Do you know
I felt that I was
a bane as soon as your face fell
I was too nervous to breathe
You just left away
as you finished your quarrel
Lanlan and I had nothing to eat but biscuit
and drank the cool water from the tap
You had made tremendous fuss
about divorcing for five years
Lanlan and I also
had suffered a lot for five years
You never thought
Who led to this
Whom to blame
Whom do you think to blame
You go to askyour mother
She knows better than any one else
It is I who I want to ask
Dont you feel sorry for the child
If every member got along
with each other well
the child would not become like this
It is I who caused the terrible
state that the child is in
It is you who asked for a divorce
Ok,ok
Today you should make everything
clear in front of Qingqing
Tell her the reason why I asked for a divorce
Do you dare to say
Get out of hereGo put to quarrel
You are more unreasonable
than your mother
Both of you should leave,Go
Ah
Coming,coming
Books are coming
Put up the bookstall first
I am about to become the committee
of the Political Association
For being able to buy those books
I am not kidding It is true
What about your parents
They has achieved their goal
They can go wherever they like
Lanlan has been on summer holiday
From today,I want her to
come here every day.Ok
Wait for the criminal
Catch,catch.Lower a little
Ok Is it all right
Calcimine here a little more
Towards here a little
Put this here
I can manage by myself
All right
Here you are
Brother,come here foe a moment
Brother, do you find out that
Qingqings sight fishy
For she is busy wither at work or off duty
I know you like Qingqing.
She is also my old classmate
Now I begin to worry about her as well
She was born with such a temper
Her temper is quite fun
Bah
Suppose that you and she
fall in love with each other
you are damned to suffer
if she gets obstinate
Xiao Wei,lend me the hammer for a while
Here you are
If I were to be imprisoned,
she then would wait for me in
all her life as she is obstinate
You care nothing
Why are you obsessed with her
You have on idea that I am also obstinate
The analytical
points of No.9 are quite similar
This
So are those of No.12
The upshot of No.3 is that that figure
prints on the spot can not show
It is difficult to identify
Xiao Liu,please sign your name here
I am asking our group leader to sign
Party members self-assessment
This
is the application for housing
It is useless to have my signature on
You sign your name first
then it will turn to the section chief
Then it will go to
the chief of the department
After the chief of the department signs
his name,I should hand it out to the
administrative department for research
Finally I have to ask for
deputy director generals signature
There is hell little use of my signature
It will be the same though
you sign ten thousand your names
Bring other suspects data
And this,my retirement report
Is it the case of Tao Lanlan
It is the case of robbing guns
Here you are
Thank you
Hey, Lao Zhao
You set me a tricky problem in front
of the chief of the department that day
What is your theory
I have no theory
I just thought about it
I seemed to have a kind of feeling
Our job is involving human life
We cant just follow our feelings
Do you know
Han Fuju in Shandong province
Everyone knows him.He was a warlord
He solved cases
through following his feeling
He brought the suspects in front of him
Those who had good facial features
can be released
While those had bad ones would be killed
You mean I become the warlord
If I were Han Fuju
all of your facial features
would be considered bad
Hey, Lao Zhao
You can go to the universities for old age
Really Universities for old age
It is quite good
In the celebration,we will send
flowers to you and fire firecracker
Wear flowers and fire firecracker?
Are you going to sweep me out
You neednt care about the aperture
and focus of this camera
Just keep about one-meter distance
And dont shake the hands
when press the shutterThat would be fine
Have a try
You are too close
The face will be distorting in
the picture if you are too close
Is that fine
What is it used for
Do not press that
The rear cover will open once you press it
Why are you absent-minded
What did I tell you to do
Is the distance proper
Do as you see fit
What time is it now,master
A quarter past seven
Thank you
What is up
You
Get on
Master Sorry
Ninety-seven,ninety-eight
ninety-nine,one hundred
Ok,sleep
Wait for a moment
Who is it
It is me.Qingqing
Howls everything going
See by yourself
Lanlan is about to go out
Why is me
Take it
What is wrong
You didnt be taken
Look,only the one I tookwhen I tried
They said that you are beautiful
They are prepared to paste it
on shop window for advertising
What damn are you laughing at
Din you say that everything was done
Just press the bottom
It had no power,didnt it
I put it a new battery
What about the camera
Did you open this
I have seen all the people on the film
You can be the top news in 1988
Girl will become not nice when frown
Finally it is still the girls who are
at a disadvantage situation
The words like those
written in the old novels
I work in gynecology and obstetrics
It is foolish to persuade people
I am a fool now
People in three kinds of jobs have
the deepest understanding of human being
They are gynecology and obstetrics
court and funeral home
You should understand
what human being is
Human is always born out
Grows up
Get old and die
What are leading up to
Qingqing,you go too far on something
If your sister were
What you were me,what would you do
At least I would not add burden to her
I do know you fear to bear burdens
Lend me the camera one more
I have known how to use it
Hey,nothing
Have a sleep
You can sleep for an hour
Especially after committee emotional crime
criminal will hide his criminality
by managing to destroy evidences
He will be afraid of the
witness or the polices track
or the revenge from the victims
and their relatives
Chief of the department
please sign your name on
They may behave unusually
Even the new motive
for crime may come into being
Due to either the fear of being found
or the interest of the outcome
of the crime he committed
he will become sensitive to things around
Criminal might also be attached
to the scene of the crime
or be very concerned
about the circumstance of the victim
Twill spare the time for
a visit to the deputy director general
about your houseThere is no problem
Thank you
In order to fulfill the need of
assaulting instinct or emotion
Also on the contrary
Some criminals always feel that
some evidences might be left on the scene
of the crime.Lao Zhao,set off
Thus they keep alarm all the time
You are even senior
than the chief of the department
It is necessary promote you
before you retire
I am not senior but old
I heard that when you were young
you were famous for your detectivism
Why did you later give up the job
I did not want to give it up
But I was unable to do the job
How could it be possible
A policeman should be just and impartial
even the criminal is his father
At that time people arrested are
all intellectuals like your father
If all of them had been caught
you would have not been born
If you continue to working
even the chief of the department
may become too young
We who have not that ability
can just work with vehicles
There is light on the tower
That is the scene of the Tao Lanlans case
I have also seen that
Will there be any connection
Lao Zhao
The angle of incidence is
as big as the one of reflection
Dont laugh
Did you check the garage in that tower
Df course
Did you check carefully
Sun Dasheng is the boss of that garage
He was once in prison for fighting
He had an alibi
He went gambling again at that night
Do you think this
boy will change to be good
He has made a mistake
Even a good man would make mistakes
Let go
Leave the film
Wait for me
Jam ajournalist with reporting right
Why were you afraid of taking picture
If you were ajournalist
then I could be a policeman
I just praised you at the meeting
of individual businessmen
Why did you set up the bookstall again
I have quit the position of being
a standing committee of NPC
and committee of the Political Association
I cant manage
I need to support my family
You such a fox show your tail again
People are remonstrating against you
They said that students were led
off by you such kind of people
They dare not bully anyone except us
What about the Red Guards in the past
Who taught them?
You are just good at refuting
Books you sell on your
bookstall are not good ones
Of low level
I have good ones full in my house
Shakespeare complete works
Would you like
to buy Guo Moruos anthology
Pig is omnivorous,Sheep eats grass
Everyone has their own kinds of stuff
Like Zola and Suva.
Howls the Steel smelted
Why dont you buy
Please tell me
the publishing company of this
Hey,how much does one cost
People have been corrupted by
the money-oriented spirit
1.5yuan
This book is dirty and broken
You should give me a discount
Ok,ok
There are a few good books by chance
You can take your time and pick
Lanlan,let us make an agreement Ok
Dont read such kind of book
Focus your attention on study
Ok
If you want to read
read the ones in this room
Dont read those outside
You dont apposeThat means you agree
Deal
If you are tired,go into room for a rest
Dont be afraid.I will not tell Qingqing
Li Xhangwei
Hey,I am coming
Look quite beautiful
It is useless.I felt sleepy
What is the bed number
No.73
They are twins
Her little sister died as she was born
She was strangulated by the umbilical cord
I am afraid that the elder
sister has slim chance to survive
How poor the woman on No.73
She is not merciful
She didnt want the babies
as she knew that they were girls
She said that give them
to others if they were alive
Hells bells
Qingqng,I heard that
the charge nurse asked director
to move you to ward
Why
She said you were usually late recently
And always forgot things
She worried that accident would happen
She told the dean that I would not go either
Be quiet.Dont tell others
that it is I who told you
Get on.I drive you home
Thankyou.Dont bother about it
Uncle Zhao,dont bother about it
Use it It is new
Thank you.That is too much trouble for you
That is all right
This is the last time
I have been retired
Every one will be off duty after an hour
I have to give back the car before ring out
Look,staff in my work unit gave me this toy
It is for my grandson
You then will be vacancy from then on
Yes,you are right
Bother you last time
Please drive us to Qingqing Book House
If you and your family need to see doctors
Please turn to me
I can let you see
the doctors through backdoor
At least you neednt stand in a line
There is no one care me at all
Havent I bought you something
to eat and drink
Dont you hate me to care you
I saw that woman again
She took a camera
and took pictures of the drivers
She must have something with that girl
If not
Come here,bugger you
Since you came here
Have you driven the cars at the garage
No
Do workers here know that you can drive
They dont know
Nothing
The action of that woman shows
that the police are still aimless
Dont leave here from now on
Dont talk excessively and unwisely
Dont go to garage either
Such kind of case will draw
no attention as the time passes
Let the dust settle before I send you away
Dont practice that damn thing
If you are bored,beat my waist for me
What about this,How about this
Dose he look like
How about this
Look at this one
Is he looks like Li Zhangwei?
Yes
And this
Qingqing,the great effort you made
to practice taking pictures has worked
It is true; you have made a great progress
Take it easyThere will be nothing wrong
Let me in
I want to send something to eat
I am afraid that she is hungry
Charge nurse,please let me go in and have
a look. No,You had better go back first
It is no problem
I am afraid that they may make mistakes
You ask her to take it easy
when giving birth to the baby
What is the bed number
Go to sterilize first
You have a sister and I have a son
Ah,the pain is killing me
Here,towel
It is paining me to explode
It is killing me.No,no,no
What a damn pain
My heat is about to explode
My head is about to explode
Drink some water
It is icy.You will be better after drink it
No
Let me out for a breath
What is up? What is going on?
Let me out
Cannot go out
Da Cheng.Please dont cry,dont cry
Let me have a walk
Let me have a walk. Let me have a walk
Let me have a walk. Let me...
Please promise not to go out
Brother,if there were no genre
of human beings.That would be nice
It is too good to be true
It would be wonderful if human could fly
Man then can damn go
doggoned anywhere as he likes
No one can find him
All right
It usually lasts one to two weeks that
the umbilical cord tangle the neck
It seldom lasts three weeks
If Qingqing hadnt slept
and been examined earlier
it would not have happened
Qingqing,dont take too much
that medicine. It is not good for you
The interval of Qingqings examination
conforms to the regulation
Arrange this medical record
And verify again
Who was the nurse on duty
It was me
Here you are
Hit her to death
What are you doing
Give my grandson back
I have waited torso a long time
The condition of my grandson was fine
It was always fine
Why turned out wrong when he was born
Twill not let you get off so easily
What were you doing...
Twill not let you get away with it
Twill never
You go out first
Someone was killed
Someone was killed by staff in hospital
You led me to losing grandson
Someone was killed
Mum You go put first
Calm down,You go put first
Twill do my damnedest to fight with her
Lanlan
Lanlan,Lanlan
Be quiet,be quite
Is Lanlan still sleeping
She came here in the evening by herself
She said that she wanted sleep here
She didnt listen to me despite
my effort to persuade her
She refused to be send back either
Why did she
said that she was afraid of you
Why did she fear me
I didnt ask
Qingqing
I beg a favor to you
Please take Lanlan out and have some fun
Where
Wherever will be fine
As long as let her leave home
As far as possible
It would be better if you were Lanlan
Then you would be afraid of her
And thus you could come and live here
You are fishing in troubled waters
Puck you
Qingqing,lets go out
Three of us go together
Set out today
No
You still need
to take charge of the book house
Qingqing Book House
We have to go tonight
What about the book house
It doesnt matter to just shut up
the shop for several days
Brother,you are really determined
to carry on a love affair
You dont look like her boyfriend
But her father
Now then,none of your nonsense
You first have to see about my business
After that,you can enlighten me as you like
I have to wake them out later
And tidy out things,And
And dissipate your efforts
Dont forget to buy a telescope for Lanlan
She said she liked that
You mustnt come back in at least five years
Brother,what if the policemen catch me
So far as you dont commit crime any longer
nobody can find you
It is not a homicide case
The police force will not order the arrest
of you in the whole country
Come and hold my leg
Brother,what is it for
This is my last sum of money
I saved it for the fear
that you might make mistakes
Brother,if you die
Twill burn money
of the nether world for you
You have waked out
I have asked Xiao Qin
to buy train tickets of tonight
Qingqing,no
Qingqing
Qingqing,Lanlan is still inside
Xiao Liu,take other members to have
the brothers be in control at once
Yes
Xiao Zhang.Yes
Look up the information about Sun
Dacheng through computer right now
Yes
You drive a car to collect Lanlan
Prepare to recognize the
criminal through his side face
But I dont know where she is
how can I collect her
Stay here.I am going to withdraw money
And then send you to
the railway station directly
Sister
Screw you
Brother
Brother, Run away quickly
Brother,Brother
Find a piece of cloth quickly
Wrap the wound and
send him to hospital swiftly
Qingqing,you such a bothersome bitch
You are asses,You are also an ass
Brother
there is a car pursuing after us
They are pursuing us
Be quick.The car is coming
Brother,move back,move back
Quickly,catch up
Quick
Dont move
or Twill kill her
Right,kill her
Hurry,go up
Brother,we have no way out now
Youre capable of damned thing
We have to fling caution to winds now
Brother,I go to block up the rear door
You go upstairs first
Are there any other bypasses
in this building
There is a backdoor over there
Da Cheng,run quickly
Brother
If anyone dares come up,I will kill her
He seems not to be a professional brigand
We can delude him in many aspects
Dont rush to action
We must ensure
the security of the hostages
I know
Why don t you shut up
Everything should have been all right
People upstairs dont resist
Only by surrendering right now
can you have chances to be alive
It is impossible
They are cheating me
People upstairs set
the hostages free at once
Hand out the weapons
and set the hostages free right now
People upstairs set
the hostages free at once
Hand out the weapons
and set the hostages free right now
You set free first
People upstairs set
the hostages free at once
Only by surrendering right now
can you have chances to be alive
Go upstairs
Go
Lao Zhao,you are absurd
Come down
You are against the disciplines of police
I have been retired
Go,open it
Go
He is your brotherRight
She is my daughter
You have one bulletin your gun
I have five
Dont male a false move
Dont go ahead any more
Brother,let him stop
Persuade him not to make a false move
You listen to him
People upstairs set
the hostages free at once
Set the hostages free at once
Only by surrendering right
now can you have chances to be alive
You fear that Twill kill her,dont you
Then please dont kill me
People upstairs set
the hostages free at once
Set the hostages free right now
Only to surrender right now
can you have chances to be alive
It has been fineIt serves
her right for her endless investigation
Puck loudspeaker,stop shouting
It gets on my nerves
Go,be quick
No it wasnt herIt wasnt her who kicked
Lao Zhao No it wasnt her
Qingqing,protest that you didnt kick at all
protest,Qingqing,protest
Keep away,keep away
Lanlan