Presented by
ROVER TANG
Executive Producer
ALAN TANG
Starring
ANDY LAU, MAGGIE CHEUNG
JACKY CHEUNG
Special Appearance by
ALEX MAN
Post-Production
STANLEY SIU
Film Coordinator
LAI ON YI
Cinematography by
ANDREW LAU
Action Directors - STEPHEN TUNG
BENZ KONG, POON KIN KWAN
Art Director
WILLIAM CHANG
Written and Directed by
WONG KAR WAI
Hello.
Hello, is this Ha-tau? This is Auntie.
You still asleep? I'll call you later.
Okay.
It's Auntie again.
You're still not up?
All right. I'll call you later.
No, it's okay. Go ahead.
Your young cousin isn't feeling well
and has to see a doctor.
Instead of having her
travel back and forth,
I'm sending her to stay with you
for a few days, okay?
I have a younger cousin?
She's your second uncle's daughter,
Ah-Ngor.
Who could that be?
I thought you were out. I'm Ah-Ngor.
You're my cousin, right?
Come in. Make yourself at home.
There's the kitchen and bathroom.
Listen, if anyone calls,
tell them to call back later.
Hello. Can I speak to Brother Wah?
He's sleeping. Who's calling?
Ha! You don't even know me,
so you must be new.
I'm Fly. Who are you?
I'm his cousin.
Cousin? Never mind.
Tell him I'm waiting
to do business with Fat Carl.
- Have him call me when he gets up.
- Okay.
Hello, cousin. isn't Brother Wah up yet?
Not yet. Is it urgent?
Want me to wake him up?
No. When he gets up,
tell him I'm still waiting for Fat Carl.
Have him call me.
Okay.
Go sleep in the bedroom if you're tired.
I'll sleep in the living room tonight.
Why do you wear that mask?
So I don't infect other people.
What kind of disease is it?
The doctor said
my lungs are malfunctioning
and told me to see a specialist.
Don't worry. You're not gonna die.
Just eat more oranges and you'll be fine.
Tastes strange.
A guy named Fly
called a couple times for you.
Really? What did he say?
Hello, little cousin. Is he up yet?
Hello.
I'm at Fat Carl's place,
collecting what he owes.
You're kidding! What's taking you so long?
He's jerking you around.
Stay there. I'll be right over.
I can't have dinner with you tonight.
You'll have to go out on your own.
Here, get yourself something to eat.
The key's under the mat.
And take that thing off. It's ugly.
Have a cup of tea first.
Fat Carl, I'm telling you,
I'm doing you a favor
talking with you this long.
If I'm not well-known,
it's not 'cause I'm a weakling.
My big brother tells me
to keep a low profile.
You know Airplane?
He ran up $1,600 in debt
and was just two days late in paying.
Now he can't fly,
and he has to use a wheelchair.
I did that with my own two hands.
You trying to scare me?
Airplane's a nobody!
You can't compare him to me!
Let me tell you something!
Fat Carl doesn't pay debts!
You know that guy called Tubby?
He was a lot tougher than you.
Now they call him Skinny.
You know why?
He tried to collect too,
and I beat him half to death.
He's only got one eye left now.
You been at this just two years
and you have the nerve to come to me?
I got more knife scars
than you have hairs on your legs!
Scars? My big brother's only got one,
so I'll cut myself if you have any!
Then start cutting!
Aren't you guys finished yet?
We're just getting started.
Just getting started after this long?
Nobody move!
You gonna pay what you owe?
Yeah!
I never said I wouldn't!
I can't believe it was that easy.
I could tell he was a sheep
in wolf's clothing.
If they had any guts,
they would have jumped you.
You're right.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Hey, Brother Wah.
Here to see Mabel?
- She's not here yet.
- I'll wait for her downstairs.
Mabel!
Come here.
I haven't eaten yet. Will you join me?
It's okay if you don't want to.
- Why were you so late for work?
- I just got out of the hospital.
The hospital? Why?
Did they pump your stomach again?
I had an abortion!
Is this a joke?
Take it that way if you want.
Why didn't you tell me you were pregnant?
Did you ever give me a chance?
Three days I waited, but you never called!
You could have called me.
Call you? To say what?
That you should marry me?
That I'm getting an abortion?
We were together six years,
and what did I get in the end?
You're still not mine,
and I'm not even better off for it.
I'm so poor I had to borrow
from my mother for the abortion.
- And what for?
- Are you done?
You knew what kind of guy I was
from the day we met!
Don't stay with me
if it's marriage and money you're after!
Don't think I'll feel sorry forever
'cause you got an abortion.
I won't.
You say that now, but I know you will!
So you don't give a damn about me? Fine!
I destroyed your baby!
And I'm gonna tell everyone
that I had your baby aborted
so you'll feel guilty
for the rest of your life!
Congratulations.
You win!
Cousin.
Are you all right?
What's the matter, cousin?
Did you break up with someone?
What did you say?
I'm warning you...
never say those words again...
or I'll throw you out.
Did you see the doctor?
I just came back from the hospital.
What did he say?
I get the results tomorrow.
Have you eaten yet?
Let's go get something.
I cooked.
Fly called for you again this morning.
What did that rat say?
Nothing special. Just small talk.
Didn't he ask anything about me?
Like what?
Like what happened last night.
He just asked one question.
One question? What was it?
I'm afraid to tell you.
Just tell me what he said.
You sure?
He asked if you broke up.
You've been in all day.
Why don't you go out?
No place to go.
I've got no friends in Kowloon.
Finish up and I'll take you out.
Are you in school, or do you work?
I'm working already.
What kind of job?
In a friend's restaurant.
Is he your boyfriend?
Not really.
Everybody calls him Uncle Tang.
Hey, let's go see a movie later.
If you're free.
Don't feel you have to keep me company.
Are you the backup?
Ah-Site, how much did you lose?
Five hundred.
I won't play for that little.
Let's settle this with one game...
for a grand.
You in?
A grand?
What do you say, Snooker King?
I should show you my stuff for a grand?
I'll play you one-handed for two grand.
One-handed?
You're on!
Ah-Site.
Piece of cake.
Another ball in the pocket.
How about that?
Snooker King is really great!
Ah-Site, how many points am I behind?
No need to count. He's 30 points ahead.
He'll still be five ahead
even if you knock all the rest in.
What do you say?
This calls for a special cue.
Ah-Site, my special cue.
Come on.
"This little piggie went to market"...
Step aside.
"This little piggie stayed home"...
Give us some room.
"This little piggie had roast beef"...
We need to set up this shot.
Too easy. Let's make it harder for him.
Watch out. You just lost seven points.
Take your shot.
Shoot!
You take me for a fool?
Watch out!
- You okay?
- Run!
Come on, you idiot!
Stop!
Out of the way, damn it!
What the hell!
Die!
To hell with you!
Big Brother!
Ready?
Yeah.
Shut up!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Why don't you go to sleep? It's late.
Cousin, the report said my health is fine.
I wanted to stay and celebrate with you,
but Auntie said the weather's nice,
so the restaurant's busy.
Uncle Tang wanted me to get back earlier.
I called your name twice,
but you didn't answer.
You must have been very tired.
Summer's coming,
and lots of people
will vacation on Lantau Island.
Do you get vacations in your line of work?
I made a meal for you in the kitchen.
I also bought a few more glasses.
I knew they'd all get broken
sooner or later,
so I hid one of them.
One day, when you need that glass,
give me a call,
and I'll tell you where it's hidden.
Bye-bye. Ah-Ngor.
Hey, everybody!
Turn that down!
Honored relatives and guests,
today is my brother Ah-Site's wedding day.
We've prepared
some modest food to serve you.
So drink up.
To my brother!
See, I told you $200 was too much!
Who knew he was so cheap
he'd have it on the roof?
Please help yourselves.
After you.
Stop acting like that. After you.
Look this way.
One more!
That's enough!
Go get your in-laws for a picture.
Hurry up. Go!
- Father, will you join us for a picture?
- No.
- Come on, Father.
Don't be like that.
Come have your picture taken.
No. What's the point?
This is a disgrace!
Hurry up and finish
before I pass out from the heat.
Don't be like that.
You don't hold a reception
if you don't have the money.
Unheard of, having it on the roof!
I just can't get through to you.
Can't you ever do anything right?
This is your brother's big day.
Why did you make it so shabby?
Think I didn't want to do it up big?
But I've got no money. What could I do?
He complains too much.
Shithead.
What did you say?
What did I say?
I said you're a shithead!
I served you shark's fin
and abalone, didn't I?
So what if there's no air conditioning?
Why complain so much?
If you ask me,
this good food is wasted on you!
I only served abalone
'cause your son-in-law said you loved it.
Had I known you were such a jerk,
I'd have served you shit instead!
You want to die?
Don't you dare throw things at me!
Let me go! I'll kill him!
- You wanna fight?
- Big Brother, don't!
Wanna fight, do you?
What are you doing? Get out of here!
And you keep quiet!
Get lost!
Sit down! Sit!
Was I right or what?
A real shithead, isn't he?
- You arguing with your big brother?
- Isn't he a bastard?
Go on talking, I dare you!
After all, he is Ah-Site's father-in-law.
You're making things hard
for your little brother.
All right, it's my fault.
I'm in the wrong.
Younger brother...
I've done you wrong.
Someday when I strike it rich...
I'll throw you another banquet.
I knew it was our turn,
but it all happened so quickly.
The cops arrested our guys last night.
If it had just been the small-fries,
then no big deal,
but Big-Mouth Kay handles the money.
They say the cops
are making a deal with him.
They'll help him out if he squeals on us.
It could be really serious.
So Godfather sent me to tell you
not to make any unnecessary
trouble these days.
Hey, the police are outside.
Any of you bastards got drugs and weapons,
go take care of them, quick.
Ah-Wah, you've got a visitor outside.
Thanks.
- What brings you here?
- I gotta talk to you.
Your brother Fly owes us.
He's missed a couple payments
and doesn't return our calls.
My big brother sent me to tell you
if he doesn't pay by tomorrow,
he gets no more chances.
Tell Tony I can take care of my own guys.
I'll talk to Fly about the money.
If this is true,
I'll bring him to see Tony tomorrow.
Did you wanna see me?
You been hard up for money recently?
I'm always hard up for money.
But I'm used to it.
I've got big prospects.
A fortune-teller told me
I'd strike it rich by 30.
Everything's gonna be great.
I'll be sitting pretty.
Won't need to hang around here.
Did this fortune-teller also mention
you won't make it to 30?
No.
I heard you borrowed money from Tony.
What are you saying?
That's English.
You know I don't understand English,
so why speak it?
I'll ask you again.
Did you borrow money from Tony?
No.
Then why are they looking for you?
They're eating around the corner.
- Want me to have 'em come over?
- Fine.
Who are you winking at?
How much did you borrow?
How much?
Not much. Take it easy.
"Not much" is still money.
How much?
Couple hundred bucks. No big deal.
Don't listen to them.
They wouldn't come to me
for a couple hundred bucks.
You gonna tell me?
A wedding banquet
and a gift for the bride.
You figure it out.
There's 8,000.
Eight thousand?
You counting every dollar of that as two?
That's what he said he owed.
Eight thousand was the principal.
What about the rest?
He's missed four payments.
He owed us 13,500 and change.
I'm doing you a favor.
Why don't you go rob a bank?
Who do you think you are,
talking to me like that?
You're awful fond of talking.
Ah-Kwong, take him in there
and have a nice long chat with him.
- We'll talk about your mother!
- Shut up!
Get out of here!
Get out!
Your brother's lucky
he's working under you.
Anyone else and he'd be dead by now.
Let's cut the small talk.
Enough beating around the bush.
Well?
First, I've paid off the principal,
but he really doesn't have the interest.
We'll have to postpone two more payments.
Two more? Why not just wait till I'm dead
and burn it as an offering?
If you don't trust him, trust me.
I'm good for it.
But I don't have the money now.
I'll give it to you in a couple days.
How can you be a big brother
if you don't even have that much?
Better go be a farmer or something.
I thought you had money,
so I agreed to talk to you.
You're a sorry excuse for a big brother.
You really want it now?
- What? You're crazy.
- What?
Sure, I'll take it if you have it now.
Okay. Let me make a call first.
Why are you just sitting there?
Your boss told you
to talk with me, so talk!
What's your father's name?
What's your mother called?
Stop joking around, Fly.
Why don't you talk to me?
Don't you have any parents?
Are you the boss?
Stay back!
I have a little problem.
Could you lend me some money?
Yes, I could.
Fly.
I'm borrowing the money from your boss.
You can take it or leave it,
but there's no debt between us
from now on.
If I get rich someday, I'll pay you back.
You were wrong to help this guy
rip us off at high interest! Right?
Right!
What are you waiting for?
Give Tony the money.
We're even now.
And here's a little extra, my gift to you.
Think you're tough, huh?
Shafting me in my own place!
You're something yourself,
taking us for fools.
Come here a minute.
Let's go.
Tony, I pay you to guard this place,
not to bring in hoodlums to rob me!
What's the meaning of this?
Boss, he just lost his temper.
Things are heating up on the street,
and you two are still at each other!
Don't you have any respect for me?
He started it.
First he refuses to pay his debt,
then he causes trouble in my place
and robs my boss.
He's been wrong all the way
down the line, Godfather.
You knew he was crazy.
You shouldn't have bugged him!
And you've gone too far,
taking advantage of him.
You knew that was his turf.
Godfather, I was just trying
to pay him back.
He wanted the money back, so I gave it.
It was a fair exchange.
- Fair?
- What are you doing?
I'm still the one
who makes the decisions around here!
Damn it! Just make your payment
every month, and that settles that!
Now shake on it!
Well? I told you to shake on it.
Do it!
Shake!
That traitor Ah-Kay is a snitch.
We can't let him live.
You gotta kill him
before he goes to court.
What do you say?
It's a tough job. Who should we send?
I don't want an outsider handling this.
Here's what we'll do.
You two find some smart boys
to draw lots day after tomorrow.
This guy's perfect.
He acts all tough and brave.
Send your younger brother,
if he wants to do it.
I'll cancel his debt,
and we'll look after his family
if he dies.
You got the guts?
What? You trying to scare me?
Shut up.
Don't pick on the little guys.
You and me are the best here.
It's either you or me.
I'll do it if you won't.
Just say the word and I'll take it.
You'll have to do it
if you don't speak up.
Say you don't want to
and admit you're a coward.
Then I'll take it on!
Stop dreaming!
You two ganging up on me?
Fine! I'll kill you two first!
Not again! Stop arguing!
I have my own idea how to handle this.
Now get out of here, all of you.
Good-bye, Godfather.
Ah-Wah, come back here.
What is it?
I know you and your brother
are good friends.
But he's too crazy.
Straighten him out. He's like a time bomb.
One of these days he'll get you killed.
I know.
I've thought about that.
I want to find him a normal job.
Good idea.
Fish balls!
That's it for today. Time to go home!
Brother Wah is here.
Help me out here.
Fish balls! Get your fish balls!
- Hey, Big Brother.
- Give me one. How's it going?
How do you think?
Think I can't handle a food cart?
You know who you're talking to.
Take it slow.
You'll move up into the big time.
Right. Fish balls here today,
bombs in the Middle East tomorrow.
- You jerk!
- Police!
Stop!
The police are coming!
Who gives a shit?
Hey, fish ball man! Is this your cart?
- What did you call me?
- Fish ball man.
What?
If you don't sell fish balls,
what's with those scissors?
Scissors mean I sell fish balls?
Are you crazy?
I'm just trimming my nose hairs.
- So it's not your cart. Take it away!
- Fine! Take it!
Hey, what are you doing?
That cart cost money!
Saving face is what matters, not money.
I may not be famous,
but people here know me.
I don't want to sell fish balls!
I have to live around here!
Out of my way! You don't own the sidewalk!
It's just a job! No need to be ashamed!
I don't like selling fish balls!
Then what do you want to sell?
You can't just hang around doing nothing.
You're not cut out for the gang!
Yeah, I know! I'm Mr. Fish Balls!
Fine! I'll do it 'cause you say so,
but when I can't stand it anymore,
I'm gonna poison the fish balls!
It's for your own good!
What a coincidence.
Yeah.
How are you?
Fine.
I got married.
Good for you.
Does your husband treat you well?
Very well.
It's really pouring.
No telling when it'll stop.
I'm waiting for my husband.
Want a cigarette?
I don't smoke anymore.
It's not yours.
Well, gotta go.
Hello, may I help you?
Is Ah-Ngor there?
No, she's not. Who's calling?
That's all right. Thanks.
Longing for you like
The never ending ocean waves
A passion in my heart
That can no longer be contained
Though I'm still alone
I hesitate to give my heart away
Your seductive gaze, like flame
Ignites the embers of love
Take my breath away
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Is Ah-Ngor here?
She went to Kowloon and isn't back yet.
- Kowloon?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Awaiting you in darkness
To come together once again
The warmth of your kiss
Sends me reeling out of bounds
My love
Take my breath away
I'm suspended in anticipation
Each time that you come near
Yet my heart remains determined
Whether we have a future or not
When did you get here?
Just now.
You've put on a little weight.
A little.
So have you.
It's all because of him. He's my doctor.
You staying out here tonight?
No.
I'm heading back now.
Ah-Ngor.
I just wanted to say...
I found that glass.
Take my breath away
It was you who lit
The unquenchable flame within
Lovers will sacrifice all for their love
Awaiting you in darkness
To come together once again
The warmth of your kiss
Sends me reeling out of bounds
Miss Cheung called for you just now.
She's going to the wharf
You should wait for her there.
I'm suspended in anticipation
Each time that you come near
Yet my heart remains determined
Whether we have a future or not
I'll go against all odds
To try my luck
Take my breath away
It was you who lit
The unquenchable flame within
Even though I know
It's just like a moth to the flame
Awaiting you in darkness
Just to give myself to you
The warmth of your kiss
Sends me reeling out of bounds
My love
Take my breath away
Go get some sleep.
I'll check you in tomorrow.
Okay.
When do you start work in the morning?
Very early. I'll make breakfast for you.
Okay.
How long are you staying?
I'm not sure.
I should go.
I'll walk you home.
That's okay. It's not far.
Could you maybe not go home tonight?
Why didn't you visit me until now?
I know myself and my work.
I can't promise you anything.
When you're not on my mind...
you won't see me.
If you had waited any longer,
I'd probably have married that doctor.
Mr. Fish Balls, give me
a dollar's worth with extra sauce.
Well?
Why don't you take it?
You said you wanted extra sauce!
Take it or I'm gonna get pissed!
"Mr. Fish Balls"!
Bastard!
That can't be Fly, can it?
What's happened?
You haven't sunk
to selling fish balls, have you?
Poor guy.
What a loser.
Your big brother
must have put you up to this.
You should leave him.
Look at my guys.
All dressed up and suave,
with their own cell phones.
They don't have to do this.
Poor bastard.
Your big brother's got you
selling fish balls in the street.
Working for me is better.
Police!
What are you running for?
You're a gangster!
Your brothers are here.
No need to be afraid.
Take him!
Don't worry, you'll be okay in jail.
Fight back if they beat you.
Don't let us lose face!
Bastard!
Take it easy. It's okay.
You weren't selling drugs,
just fish balls!
- Let's watch the show!
- Asshole!
Stop, you bastard!
Hold it there!
Bring him here!
I'm gonna kill you!
Hey, leave some for me.
How many chicken wings in two boxes?
About 300.
About 300?
- And you used to carry this?
- Yeah.
You let your boss know
he better watch out.
He shouldn't have you lifting heavy stuff,
or he'll get a knuckle sandwich
for every wing in the box!
- You're crazy.
- I'm crazy?
- Don't you want my help?
- It's okay. I'm quitting anyway.
Quitting?
Why?
I want to find a job in Kowloon.
That's fine with me. You can move in.
Better not say that again.
Once you've said it twice,
you can't take it back.
I'm not kidding.
If I leave, I'm never coming back.
Hey, what do you want to eat?
Tell him I'll be there on time.
If he hurts Fly, he'll pay for it.
That's all.
What's the matter?
Nothing special.
Fly's in trouble and I've gotta go.
Is it dangerous?
No, it's all right.
I'll be back tonight. Don't worry.
Why are all these people here, Uncle Kwan?
Fly's in the wrong this time.
But let's not make a big deal of it.
We're all friends here.
Apologize to Tony and it'll all be over.
Go on now.
Tony, whatever Fly did,
I'll punish him my way.
So please give me back my little brother.
Your little brother? Which one?
That one?
You like to protect your "little brother"?
Then protect it!
You think I'm a fool?
I'd understand if he were worth it!
But he's a piece of shit!
How can you be a big brother?
Tony, he tried to set things right.
Let it go.
Save it, Uncle Kwan.
I'm helping him grow up.
If his guy can treat me like this,
then where do you stand in the future?
Sure, I'll let him go.
But humor me. I don't ask much.
Just say one thing to make me happy
and I'll let him go.
Satisfied now?
Wanna keep your "little brother"?
Big Brother.
Bastard!
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Tell your guys to help him up. Do it!
Help him up.
No!
I can get up myself.
I can walk on my own.
Stay back!
I'm telling you two
there's no settling this now!
Fly.
This isn't over yet.
Take this and go back home
until it all blows over.
No, I won't.
I swore I'd never return to see my mother
until I made it big.
Okay, I'll take you to Lantau Island then.
- Why are you driving me off?
- Why?
I don't want you killed tomorrow
when you step outside.
You know he's a mad dog.
Why didn't you listen to me
and stop pushing him?
He's the one who pushed me.
I didn't do a thing to him!
You don't think I can handle him?
You think you can?
Your head wouldn't be the size
of a watermelon if you could!
Fine! I got beaten to a pulp!
If you think I'm dragging you down,
then just drop me!
Those are your words, not mine.
Don't use them lightly.
If I leave you now
and you last one day out there,
I'll call you big brother!
None of us knows
what's gonna happen tomorrow.
Right?
Let's go eat.
Come on.
Get him!
We're gonna kill you!
Did you think I'd never get you?
Leave him alone! It's not his fault!
Beat me up instead!
Haven't you had enough?
When I'm done with him,
you'll look like twins!
Watch me cripple
your big brother, shithead!
Let's see you fight back now!
I'm a fair man.
What you do to me,
I do to you!
Better keep still.
Trigger's real sensitive.
No telling what'll get hit if you move!
What do you know?
You got lucky that time.
Will you be so lucky next time?
Gettin' excited, huh?
Wanna join our little party?
Come join the fun!
Better keep real still.
You might shoot your little brother
or your "little brother."
Fly!
Be strong.
If I don't make it out of here today,
go back home
and never come back to these streets!
You understand?
Tough guy, eh?
We'll see who's tougher,
you or this bat here.
It's real tough too.
Real hard, isn't it?
Look at you now, asshole!
Another one hits the dirt!
Damn, you pissed your pants!
Put a diaper on this guy
before you take him out!
What kind of big brother are you?
That's right.
Look at your reflection in your own piss!
See what a pathetic failure you are!
Then go back home and be a farmer
with your great big brother.
These city streets aren't for you.
Got it?
It's all right.
Where are you going?
I don't deserve to be your little brother.
Just act like you never met me.
From now on, have nothing to do with me.
I'll live or die on my own.
Fly!
Cousin!
Open the door!
Open up!
- Hurry and open up.
- What's the matter?
My cousin fell and hurt himself.
He's all right. Just let him rest.
Where were you last night?
I stayed with my cousin.
Lock the door when you leave.
Call me if anything happens.
You don't get the death penalty
for shooting someone in a police station.
A few years in the can
and you'll have earned your stripes.
Today people call you a boy,
but tomorrow they'll call you sir.
It's your chance to make a name
for yourself, understand?
Godfather, I'm afraid.
Afraid? You drew lots
and now you say you're afraid?
The other guys will kill you
even if I let you off.
Enough talk now! Do it!
Godfather, I'm really afraid.
Chickenshit!
Godfather.
I gotta talk to you.
- That's $23.50.
- Here's $30. Keep the change.
Ah-Site.
Brother!
You're a different person
now that you're a father.
I have no choice with a wife and baby.
I'll do whatever it takes
to earn a living.
Right.
Take this money. Go on.
Why?
I promised you.
Sorry about last time.
Find yourself
a fancy restaurant this time.
And use the rest
to celebrate your son's birth.
Remember: Don't let
your wife's family look down on you.
Stick up for yourself. Understand?
- Where'd you get it?
- That's not your concern!
I'm not always gonna be around.
Call Brother Wah if you get in trouble.
Brother?
All these years
and we still never amounted to anything.
I've been a pathetic big brother to you.
- Don't say that...
- Let me finish!
I know...
you might have despised me in the past.
Fine!
I deserved it.
But in a couple days...
when you read the papers and watch TV...
you'll realize I'm not
a gutless coward after all.
That I can be your big brother!
Remember to tell everyone
you've got a great big brother.
Don't forget.
Will these clothes do?
You didn't sleep all night. Take a rest.
I can't sleep.
Don't worry.
They're minor injuries. It's all right.
You were lucky this time,
but what about next time?
I've never thought about the next time.
There's just one thing.
When I go back to Hong Kong...
I want you to go with me.
Now that I've said it twice,
I can't take it back.
What do you say?
Come on.
Come here.
Stop it!
I'll hit you!
Brother Wah, Fly gave me
a lot of money last night...
and told me to hold another banquet.
He said I'd soon see he wasn't a coward.
Could you come right away?
If you don't look out for him,
no one will.
I'm on my way.
Leaving again?
It's nothing.
Just a friend who needs to talk.
Oh, and I'll pick up some medicine too.
Anything you want me to get?
I'll be back soon.
Double eight.
Miss Cheung called.
She said forget about the medicine.
Just be careful
and come back as soon as you can.
I win again.
Give me the money.
Another game.
Why didn't you tell me
you changed location, Tony?
Get up.
You sure you know the stakes here?
Aren't I welcome here?
Don't go losing
all your blood money to me.
The guilt would drive me crazy.
You?
You're already crazy!
Why feel guilty now, you sorry bastard?
- What are you saying?
- What?
Huh?
Let him be a big man for a few days.
He's risking his life for the chance.
It's just a couple days.
Right, Brother Fly?
Come on.
Mix up the tiles.
Don't you know the rules?
Do it again.
Eight.
Sorry about that.
It just happened.
Come on, let's play.
- Stop messing around!
- Leave him alone!
Let him be a two-day hero.
A man of patience, eh?
Well, fuck you!
Think I won't dare
beat the crap out of you?
Go ahead!
Beat the crap out of me!
Put me out of commission,
and you'll have to take care
of Big-Mouth Kay!
Come on!
Let me have it!
Goddamn you!
You little shit!
Come on!
One move and I'll blast him!
Shoot me if you dare!
You daring me?
Pull the trigger! Do it!
No, don't shoot!
No!
Scared?
Scared to death?
Asshole!
- I'll blow your head off!
- No!
Don't shoot, Big Brother!
I'd like to shoot you,
but you're not even worth the bullet.
Here's the money I owe you.
Pick it up.
Pick it up. This is your last chance.
Pick it up or I'll shoot!
"Thank you, Big Brother."
Thank you, Big Brother.
You've got your fancy suits
and cell phones, but so what?
Look at your big brother now.
You can go to hell!
We're in this for the money, right?
Why not take what he owes me?
Take it and go dancing.
Is this how you treat your big brother?
Mom, I'm at the store.
Will you come meet me?
What is it?
Nothing. I know you don't like the heat,
so I bought you an air conditioner.
We've already got AC here. You keep it.
I can't come meet you. Your father's here.
He's your husband, not my father.
When will you calm down and stop running?
Why did you come out of hiding to see me?
Why don't you leave me alone?
Who's gonna look out for you if I don't?
Don't think this little stunt's
gonna make you a hotshot!
Sure...
everyone will say you've got guts
when you've done it.
But no one will remember you next week!
What'll become of you then?
No one will even recognize you!
I did a lot of things
for our godfather too.
By the age of 14...
I was already getting paid to kill.
I've got more guts than most guys, right?
But look at me now.
I'm just an ordinary guy!
At least you were a hotshot for a while!
But what about me?
What about me?
Everyone looks down on me.
Does that make you happy?
People think I'm nothing,
like some stray dog
just following you around!
Did you know that?
I'd rather be a hero for one day
than go on being a fly all my life!
Let me pull this off on my own, would you?
Just this once!
Okay.
If you've already made up your mind...
I'm going with you.
If they shoot you down,
I'll finish the job.
Stop being so good to me!
I can't pay you back.
Let's not talk about that now.
If you're going, I'm going!
But if you don't, I'll take you
back to Lantau Island with me.
I'll take care of whatever comes up.
Okay, okay.
I'll go back with you.
Hey, why you looking so ragged?
Say hi to my big brother.
Don't be so stingy. Give the dog some.