影片封装:哥本傻根
想要更多高清请加QQ:188295557
Behave yourself! Get away!
Come have some watermelon
You are too polite.
You should come and eat with us!
You're wat too kind. We've already eaten.
Where's Kuei-mei?
Didn't you ask her to come?
Get your auntie here.
Tell her Momma Chai is here.
Mom asked you to go.
Go on.
- Mom asked you to go.
Hurry!
Auntie, mom says Mrs. Chai is here
She wants you to go.
She wants to introduce a guy to you.
Don't run, you'll hurt yourself.
Mr. Hou, what is your Chinese Zodiac?
Dragon.
What about Kuei-mei?
Kuei-mei is...
Here's Kuie-mei.
Kuie-mei, come.
Mr. Hou, where is your hometown?
Same as my husband, Nanking.
Nanking!
During the retreat...
We stayed there for a while.
It freezes you in winter.
In summer, it's hotter than Taiwan.
Yes... Yes...
Have some tea.
- Thank you.
We've lived here for more than 7 years.
Well... in a glance...
Who knows?
We thought we were only staying
for a while...
That's right...
Do you smoke?
No...he doesn't smoke or drink.
Good.
They work in a restaurant.
The manager is a foriegner
He doesn't allow them to smoke.
They can't even eat garlic.
Why not?
The smell might chase customers away.
What about mahjongg?
Sometimes.
They bet little
It's fine to play a little.
Don't play every day, like her.
Without Kuei-mei,
there wouldn't be anybody to cook.
Who plays everyday?
Nonesense!
Can Kui-mei play?
No, she doesn't
That's right! Our Kuie-mei...
Doesn't have any bad habits.
Unlike me.
In his eyes
I am good for nothing
OK, OK.
Don't make a fuss.
Kui-mei is really nice.
She's busy all daylong.
Of course.
The island is like a boat,
swinging in the moon light.
My lady
you also swing in my mind.
Let my voice
pass with the wind.
Open your curtain.
Let my love
float with the river
to you.
Are you ok?
Nothing.
Let me see.
There...that's better.
D you know about my family?
A little bit.
I have three kids
Three wild kids
How old are they?
10, and 8. The yongest is 3.
It's windy here. Are you cold?
Don't you know the time?
You come home late
everytime you play cards.
Leave me alone.
You gripe every time I play.
Do you think you can control me
because you support my living?
Lower your voice
Who should I be afraid of?
You are the boss,
ofcourse you are afraid of no one
I don't want to
When did you ever want to?
Kuei-mei had a date today,
what did she say?
I don't want her to marry a widower
You don't want her to marry or you
want to keen her as a concubine?
Your salary will keep her for a lifetime!
You! Why do you talk like that?
How to say that
When I don't know your mind
Last time you got 2 bottles of
Ponds from the PX.
You gave her one behind my back.
You think I don't know.
You...l don't want to talk with you
Excuse me, where's
Hou Yung-Nien's home?
There.
Thanks.
Kid, where's Hou Yungnien's home?
There.
Thanks.
Anyone home?
Dad, someone is looking for you.
Who is it?
Good kid.
Get out...
Have a seat.
What is your name?
I'm here to make things clear.
Go ahead...
I was engaged when I was in hometown.
I know, Mrs. Chai told me.
If you want to marry me
I don't want to hide anything
I was engaged at 19 in the country side.
The Feis lived opposite to us,
he was very good to me.
Then we ran from the war.
My cousin and I came
took a boat to Taiwan first
Who knows...
I don't want to hide it from you.
I was with him...it isn't my first time.
If you don't want me,
we can stop seeing each other
Here come the brides
The couple come for a toast.
Buttons up.
Congratulations...
Thank you, cheers.
Come meet your mother, hurry...
Today is the happiest day in your life.
You must drink a least 3 glasses.
Say mommy.
Louden
Mommy.
Cheng-hsing, let's go.
It's time for lunch, where are you giong?
To Momma Chai's home.
Don't go at this time.
Stay home...Cheng-hsing!
Why should we listen to you?
You are not my mother!
Cheng-chuan!
Are you Mrs. Hou?
I saw you at the wedding.
He's inside.
Thank you.
He's in the last room.
It's ok...it's my wife.
It's 0k...
Why are you here?
I brought you an umbrella, it's raining.
Hou, have your wife take this home.
It's clean.
They hardly touched it.
Thanks!
Abalone, great for a midnight snack.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
You are back.
This is for you.
What is it?
Open and see it.
Honeyed jujubes.
I never saw any in Taiwan!
You can't find jujubes in Taiwan.
Chads brother-in-law is a sailor.
He imported the jujubes from Hong Kong
It must be very expensive.
I won a little money.
I don't think is right to gamble at work.
Nobody is watching! Try it!
Let's eat it together tomorrow.
I want to eat the dish you took back.
Here.
Where's the dish?
I threw it.
You threw it? Why?
You think it's dirty?
You should not married a waiter.
Waiters are always at diposal
and are used to eat leftover.
Fuck your diginity.
Are you asleep?
Yes.
I don't mean it.
How could I look down on you?
I married you, and I will be with you forever.
I just think we should eat our own food.
We don't need leftovers from others.
You work in a restaurant as a waiter now.
But I believe if we have the will.
We can have our own restaurant some day.
A small restaurant will be good, too.
Listen to me...listen to me.
Tell me...tell me...
You gamble too much,
and you owed too much money.
Promise me you won't gamble again.
I won't, I won't gamble again.
lam adog ifldo.
Turn off the light.
Daddy.
Why are you back so early?
We should made some cured meat
for Chinese New Year.
New Year? Who cares about New Year?
I quit.
I have had enough
from the damned foreigner.
I quit!
I told Hou he is heading to trouble.
He didn't listen
They hid away and played cards again
and were caught at the scene.
They were fired right away.
Could somebody help?
How? Foreigners are strict.
Goodbye.
Kuei-mei.
Keep it for Chinese New Year.
No. Thanks.
This is the last think I took from home.
I planed to keep it for our baby.
Sell it to pay your debts.
We'll find other way out
when the baby is borned.
Please, don't gamble anymore.
Or you will destroy our family.
Don't...
I want to win.
I want to buy something good for you.
You don't know how happy I will be,
just 0t see you smile.
But I can't. Every time...
You think I don't care about our family,
don't you?
I know.
Let me see.
So big. How did baby get in?
You tell me!
I need to take 3% of interests first.
I know, if it weren't for the baby...
Honestly, I really can't bear it.
I got it. You can't take it from me.
Time to eat.
What's that?
Give it to me, give it to me.
NOW!
Do you want to be a gambler in future?
Shame on you...
Where's daddy?
He went to the Chen's.
Cheng-chuan.
Did you see the money in my purse?
No.
Who is it?
Open the door.
It's me. Open the door!
Who is it?
Give me my money.
Why are you here?
What money?
Money for my baby.
The money I put in my purse.
What are you talking about?
I See you. Raise 20. Show cards.
Give my money back to me!
Hou, you'd better go home.
Come on.
Now I've got a flush!
Give me my money.
- You are crazy!
Or I Will kill you!
Give my money back to me!
Shit.
Her water breaks.
She's having a baby! Hury!
Hold on...careful...
Don't worry...
The Queen of Enlgand is having a baby.
The Queen is having a baby.
It'll be OK after the pain.
Hurry.
A boy and a girl, how nice!
They should eat
We have to prepare everything in double
Where's your husband?
Outside.
He's got a lot of problems.
He said he better stay outside
I'll keep him company.
Does he still gamble?
If he does, our family will be done.
Did he find a job?
He said the economy is bad,
and it is hard to find one.
Sometimes I hate it.
I wish I could leave him.
It's our fate.
We have to stay with whoever we marry.
It would be better not to get married!
Our neighbor MissWu, the old pinster
ls working as a servent
She gets food to eat,
room to stay and money to earn.
She's happy-
She doesn't have to take care
of a man like we do
Dad
Daddy.
Cheng-fang.
You are my smartest child
Daddy hasn't done well this year
This afternoon, Uncle Chao said...
He could introduce you
to work in a dental clinic.
You can eat and live there, and get paid...
Are you crazy?
She should study in school.
And you want her to be a maid?
$0?
You think I like the idea?
I tried hard to find a job
You think I plan to be jobless?
A job won't help if you keep gambling.
There you start again.
Did you see me gamble recently?
Din't you? You played cards yesterday.
Ok. It's my fault.
Just put the blame on me.
You want her to stay in school?
Then you Pay-
Anybody home?
Is your faterh home?
No. He is not home.
He's not? I've been here 8 times.
He's never at home.
What a coincident!
Your father always stays out.
Damn! It's only a
few hundred dollars rice bill.
Don't disgrace yourself in the neighborhood.
We are doing a small business.
I don't mind not making money.
But I can't lose my capital.
He is never at home
Then which bastard eat the rice?
Fuck you.
Leave me alone. It's better to be a maid.
He never pay for my cramm school.
I don't want to go to school.
It must be this one.
The family is hiring servants recently
The husband is heading to Japan.
The wife wants a couple to help.
People with family are more reliable.
Giong to Japan?
Yes. It depends on Kuei-mei's decision.
Think about it.
Japan is far away.
You can't travel back and forth easily.
We are talking about Japan.
What do you think?
I don't know
Besides, you can take two children, too.
But I have 5 kids.
They don't care about your whole family.
Right. Allowing you to bring
2 children is generous enough.
Usually maids can't bring kids to work.
This is a special deal for you.
It's great! You will earn US dollars!
When you arrive Japan,
your husband will have no place to gamble.
Japan?
My uncle was killed by Japanese
when he was in Nanjing City.
We coudn't even find his body.
You want me to move to Japan? No way.
I don't want to go, too.
But I want our family to have a better life.
And we'll be working for
Chinese not Japanese.
If you don't want to go, it's fine.
But tell me.
When will you find a job?
When will you put Cheng-fang
back to school?
When will you pay off your gambling debts?
Our family is breaking apart.
Some people get all the money.
We were born to be poor.
Let's go.
Madam.
This is Kuei-mei and Hou.
Good.
Did you explain the rules to them?
Yes.
Fine.
I am leaving
- Yes, mam.
Keep them for dinner.
OK. That's it.
She wants you to stay for dinner.
There's leftover from party last night.
You tell them.
I...I can't.
We don't want to leave any of you.
But we cannot all move to Japan.
Your dad and I have thought it over.
We decided...
Cheng-chuan didn't pass the test.
He can study in Japan.
Cheng-min are sickly and need care.
Cheng-fang, you are the eldest kid here
Take good care of your two brothers.
Listen to Auntie
7 dots.
Kuei-mei,
did my husband call this afternoon?
No.
7 bamboos.
Yun-zi, although you married for year,
you are like newly wed.
You checked if he call three
times this afternoon.
Just wonder if he will come back for dinner.
You've got to keep an eye on men.
Mrs. Wei's is good at this.
She keeps a tight rein on Mr. Wei.
Not at all.
I heard the Japanese keep Mr. Wei busy.
Were it not for business.
Who'd like to move here?
For the long term, US is better.
With that woman in your office...
People QOSSiP-
You should...
Who told you to come in?
Get out!
Yes.
They're fighting again
I never saw any couple like them
Pretending happy in front of people
but fighting in the back.
So a proper match is important.
The husband depends own the wife's family
How can it be easy for him?
I heard his fater in-law is a high official.
His father in-law likes him because
he is well educated
Have you heard? The man wants to divorce.
He can't take it anymore
but the wife doesn't agree.
Marriage is meangless to them.
They should divorce.
The woman won't agree because
she doesn't want to lose face.
What is it? Letter from Taipei?
What does it say?
It says everything is fine.
Fine?
The twin who live with us is fat and healthy.
The other in Taipei is thin and weak.
You cousin is not taking good care of them.
Speaking of the girl
Does the husband really has a mistress?
You tell me...
I'm his driver.
But I don't always stick with him
He's quite old
Having a mistress at this age
Must be a lot of fun
Mommy, Brother fights.
Good girl, go in first.
Brother fights, brother is bad.
Why are you back so early?
You fight again?
Japanese says I am Chinese slave.
What?
They say I am a Chinese slave.
Din't you told me if they said that again,
I can beat them?
But you can't leave school.
I don't want to go to school.
I don't want to study any more. It's boring.
Didn't the Chef introduce me
to learn cooking?
I should better be a cook.
I don't want to go to school.
Go clean up.
I'll fix your wounds.
Please.
Goodbye.
To repeat a year in school is fine.
You should listen to your parents.
You can learn something else,
but always work hard.
Well then, bye.
Bye. I'm fine. Good bye.
Damn.
What else did the teacher say?
I don't understand Japanese too well.
What she meant was, the kid flunked.
I told you he doesn't like to study.
He should learn cooking in Yokohama.
Just like me, it's not that bad.
It's better than to stay here and go astray.
You want to be a cook.
Waterever you choose,
You have to work had.
You can't quit. Do you understand?
If you quit easily,
you'll be a loser in your whole life.
You must “stand to the Master Chef.
Take care of yourself.
Please take care of him.
Of course I will.
Bye.
Be good.
Go.
Smells great!
It's delicious.
You cook better and better.
Don't you know who taught her?
If Kuei-mei opens a restaurant in Taipei,
she will succeed.
Why do you want to go back?
America stops supporting Taiwan.
It's not a good time.
The US military will retreat soon.
It's better to stay here for some more years.
Stay here for some more years?
You take leave everv two or three davs
Sooner or later will be the boss quit
Without a visa, you have to go back to Taipei
Nonsense.
If I stay away from the japanese cops,
I can stay anywhere in Tokyo.
No problem.
They are fighting again.
Do want something to eat?
No, thanks.
Kuei-mei!
Save it.
Wei Chen-tung.
Divorce? Not in your life!
Call a car.
Yes.
You see us fighting all the time
What do you think?
We fight all the time, too.
After I left yesterday,
what did my husband say?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Are you sure?
I heard that you talked for a long time.
I know you have no place to go.
Or I'd have dismissed you long time ago.
I don't want to work here anymore.
What happened?
The woman gave you a hard time again?
The driver can introduce us to
work in a restaurant.
The work is harder but the pay is better.
We can save more money and go home.
We can open a restarant by ourselves.
Leaving...to an unfamiliar place...
They are Chinese, too.
The Japanese call mahjongg "sparrow".
It's a business here.
Why are you starring at me?
Have you ever seen me gamble here?
Hello, we are Mr. Wang's friends.
I know. Have a seat.
Thank you.
We don't have working-visa.
I know. Just hide when the cops come.
Sit.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Damn! I'm working like a dog.
The work 'rs 10 “mes
harder than at the Wars.
What are you diong?
I cut myself with a bowl.
Let me see.
It serves you right.
You wanted to come to Japan.
You wanted to leave the Wei's.
Cops! Hou! Hide!
Welcome.
Let me check your documents.
Sure.
Mommy, let's watch TV.
Damn.
Damn it.
Let me see.
Fuck! I carried dishes all my life,
and done all disreputable jobs,
but I never hid from cops! Fuck.
How long have you came here?
3 years.
Do you plan to go home?
I want to bring my family here.
And you?
We send our son to learn
to cook in Yokohama.
He's still an apprentice.
We'll go back before him.
What for? It's good here.
It's easy to find jobs and make money .
Nomatter how good it is, it isn't our home.
We want to open a restaurant in Taiwan.
It isn't easy, lots of people failed.
We are back!
How do you like the place?
Great.
Cheng-fang...you grow up.
Mommy.
Cheng-hsing.
Cheng-fang.
Come...
So thin.
They're all different now.
Welcome.
Here's your beef with rice.
Here's your soup.
Your soup.
I'd like some beef with rice.
Curry.
Curry. OK, thanks.
A beef with rice and a curry.
Here.
Where are you going?
Library.
She should help, we are busy.
Let her go, she has a test.
Don't let her wear the miniskirt.
She shouldn't show her legs like that.
It's inappropriate.
That's fashion.
I'm giong out.
It's late, where are you going?
To visit some old friends with Old Chang.
I can't say no.
He said I can't abandon friends
I will come back soon.
Who was it?
A classmates' brother.
Invite him home next time.
Not bad.
Rest time?
Lunch time has passed,
there's some time to dinner
Have a seat.
Here's your money, 22,000.
You put on weight.
And so busy, too. What can I do?
I don't drink lemon tea with sugar.
Who drink tea with sugar?
It comes with the meal.
Customers like western style.
It attracts customer.
I don't like it.
Taipei is more westernize now.
Like you are serving western food
and coffee...
Where is Hou?
He went out.
Playing cards again?
Old friends said he had to go.
There's nothing wrong to play cards.
As long as he doesn't play women.
He won't.
Men becomes wolfish
when they have money.
It's hard to tell.
Cheng-fang's got a boyfriend.
You know that?
No! I never saw one before.
She is too young to have a boyfriend.
There's nothing wrong to have a boyfriend.
As long as he is a proper fellow.
You are open-minded.
Living abroad makes you a different person.
Cheng-hsnig. Open the door.
Close the door.
Where is your dad?
A woman called.
She asked him to play cards.
What woman?
She called several times,
I answered the phones many times.
Sister is back.
I don't want to listen to you!
Cheng-fang.
Why do you touch me? Don't pull me.
No! Tell your mom.
You don't dare to, do you?
Cheng-fang.
You fight?
It's ok to have a boyfriend
But whatever happens,
you should let us know. So we won't worry.
Worry?
You left us and went to Japan for years.
Why should you worry now?
I'll see what you can worry about.
Don't be obstinate with me.
You are still young.
Of course I worry about you.
When you get into college,
I won't worry about you anymore, ok?
Cheng-hsing...
Cheng-hsing!
Cheng-fang.
Cheng-fang!
Do you hear me?
Bring your younger brother.
The water is coming in.
Cheng-fang!
Min-min, come.
Don't be afraid, let me hug you.
Mom.
Don't be afraid, here, mom is here.
Go to my room.
Why are you still sitting there, Cheng-fang?
Little brother.
Don't move.
Mom, where's dad?
If the water keeps rising,
We go to the roof.
What a mess!
I planed to come back last night,
but the wind was too strong.
There wasn't a single taxi...
Come, let me help...
What are you doing?
Didn't you ask me to check the house price?
When we come to Taiwan,
the price was $200 for 3.3 square meter.
I didn't want it.
Now it's more expensive.
Chang says,
you can't take a house with you.
You better buy gold.
I'm sorry. We are closed.
Excuse me, does Hou live here?
How can I help you?
Come in.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Is there anything that you can't tell me?
I'm here to ask him.
He said he will be good to us.
But I have not seen him for a long time.
Is that it?
I'm not that kind of...
loose woman.
Cheng-hsing...Cheng-hsing...
Where are you?
Cheng...
The woman...
Her husband is in jail.
I played mahjongg at her house.
In the typhoon night...
I planned to come back.
But I couldn't leave.
So we...
It won't happen again.
I'll make it clear to her. Never again.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving you. I want a divorce.
Divorce? What do you mean by divorce?
You learned from Mrs. Wei in Japan?
Why do you learn that?
I don't need to learn from others.
I can suffer a hard life with you.
But I will not forgive you to have an affair.
There are plenty of jobs, I can survive.
When I settle down,
I'll take all the kids.
I'll come back to pick them up.
Mom.
Come here.
Cheng-fang left.
We checked with her classmate
They said she has a boyfriend.
They met in a library.
I don't where he lives.
Since you left, everything is a mess.
Cheng-hsing burned himself on a pot.
Is your brother hurt badly?
He's okay now.
Daddy, pretend I'm not your daughter.
I'm leaving.
Maybe what I do will make you lose face.
But I will never regret.
You never understand me.
And you never will.
So please don't find me.
Stay away from the kitchen. It's dangerous.
Dad told me to go and help out.
Hello?
This is she.
I see... I'll be right there.
She came and wanted to
marry our son Ah-sheng.
At first I thought she was joking.
But she stood there.
And wouldn't leave.
We were scared.
Right...lf she's really pregnant,
we would take the responsibility.
But Mrs. Hou...
Look at her.
It's impossible that they get married now.
They are kids. They need to study.
Besides,
Ah-sheng wouldn't dare to marry her.
Right, it's Ah-sheng's fault.
The baby...
We don't want to give up the baby.
But we can't help.
Can't help?
Sit, chill out.
I think we should calm down.
Let's find a way to solve the problem.
We can pay for it.
Mrs. Lin,Cheng-fang is young.
She doesn't know anything.
She might not be pregnant.
She's too ignorant
and she believes people easily
If she knows what you said
she should give up and stops being silly.
We will talk to her.
Today...
We'll peretend nothing happened.
I'll beat you to death.
What are youd doing?
Hou Yung-nien!
Come on! Beat me to death!
I don't care! Let me die!
Hou Yung-nien!
Hou Yung-nien! Stop!
You want to kill her, don't you?
What is it?
Feeling unwell?
Dr. Lin, I've been here before.
I had my babies here
Mrs. Hou, twins.
They must be big now.
Yes.
Going to primary school.
So...
I'm here today
to ask for your help.
It's my daughter.
She's only 15.
And she...she's probably pregnant.
Letting it happen,
We are also responsble
We can't destroy her life...
No one can suffer on behalf of Cheng-fang.
No one.
She had to grow up.
When Cheng-fang went to college,
we got a loan from the bank.
Bought a house and run the restaurant.
The business was good.
A husband having an affair
is worse than gambling.
But you have two choices,
to leave or to forgive.
Nether are easy.
But you have to choose one.
This is Cheng-chuan,
he married a Japanese lady.
Cheng-hsing studied International Business.
This is hisoffice and his wife.
When the twins graduated from college,
we took this photo.
But Cheng-chuan's family were not there.
Everybody grows old.
When we were young,
we never think about it.
We not only grow old, but being ill.
Women...
He never cheated on me since then.
But still, he gambles sometimes.
Yet since he knew I have uterus cancer,
he quit gambling.
Kids have grown up.
They have their own business.
After I was in the hospital,
The restaurant
is handled by Cheng-fang.
Everyone says that
she becomes more and more like me.
You should pick them up
from the airport
No fathers will pick up their sons.
Stubborn man.
Grandma!
Grandpa! Grandma!
Everyone is here.
Grandma!
Come here, Bow-bow.
Bow-bow, Bei-bei.
Say hello to your grandparents.
Dad.
Mom.
Granpa, grandma.
Dad.
- Grandma is sick.
Mom
Mom you look better.
Don't pull me.
Let auntie see.
Bei-bei, do you miss me?
Yes?
Mariko, say hello to grandma.
Hurry
Grandma.
She speaks Japanese
with her mom in Japan.
There is no way.
Let grandpa see you
Dad.
A Japanese baby, huh?
Call "grandpa".
Can you say it?
Take it.
Behave yourself.
What do you want to eat, Bei-bie?
Cheng-chuan, you gained weight.
85 kg now.
Bow-bow...
Did you take the pills?
Yes.
Come, let's find grandma.
Give them some apples.
Grandma.
You're naughty.
Let them go.
About your divorce...
Dad is upset about it for a while.
What can I do?
You don't want to stay in Taipei?
It's not easy to make money outside.
Even if you speak Japanese well,
they still see you as a foreigner.
But I'm used to living in Japan.
Taipei is strange place to me.
I wish you could stay and
take over the restaurant.
It's impossible.
How's the business?
Lots of competition.
It's hard to make money.
But the house worth a lot.
I think, the problem is the way
of running the restaurant.
The menu is old fashion.
The decoration is old.
Mom and dad take care of the restaurant.
I seldom come here.
After she became sick,
I quit my job at school and came.
I planned to study abroad
for one or two years.
Study abroad? At your age?
You should get married.
I'm not joking.
I haven't told anyone else.
How about Cheng-hsing?
He think it's too hard.
Chang-shun wants to move to the States.
Two quick meals with orange juice.
The toilet is leaking.
Why don't you have somebody fix it?
I'm sorry. I don't know that.
I don't use lady's room.
Who change the music? Turn it off.
Didn't Mrs. Hou set the rules?
Music with singing is not permitted.
What...What's wrong with you?
Here...Come over here. Look.
What kind of place is this?
As soon as Mrs. Hou leaves,
you mess up the place.
Don't you have self-respect?
Go in. Cheng-chuan's there.
Don't scold here.
It's hard to find one these days.
So what? We can do the work ourselves!
Fine, fine.
What a mess...
Where's Cheng-hsing?
He's busy in and out.
But he earn little.
Sis, there's something
I want to discuss with you.
What is it?
I found a place at Zhongxiao Eset Rd.
I want to open a consignment store.
If we close the Chavannes,
we can work together...
Who said we will close the restaurant?
Who will take care of the place then?
Isn't Cheng-chuan returning to Japan?
Business is not well recently.
Cheng-hsing says it should be closed.
Only dad can make such decision.
It's not our business.
I know nothing about consignment.
Why don't you ask Cheng-min?
Cheng-min? I don't want to bother her.
It isn't the same, you know.
What the differences?
Of course it's different.
Mom treats you and the twins diffrerently.
I don't think there are any differences.
Go on and eat.
Stop playing-
Didn't you say you wanted oranges?
In summer, there are only frozen organes.
Is it expensive?
Less expensive than peaches .
You're stingy.
I'm not as generous as you are.
Spending 8000NTD for a dress.
It's imported from Japan.
It's expensive of course.
I don't know why it is good.
Mom. He's here. I'm leaving.
Save six seats for me tonight.
Where's dad?
I'm treating my friends. See you.
Said he was giong to buy some tonic.
Whatever.
Leaveit
Did Cheng-chuan tell you he was leaving?
Cheng-hsing and Cheng-chun
have their own plans.
Cheng-fang, if you don't want the restaurant,
I'll try to persuade your father...
To sell the place...
I know he won't agree.
I'll tell him nicely.
I'll do it.
I'd like to go out for a walk.
When the doctor says you can go,
I'll borrow Cheng-hsing's car for us.
Your mom left some jewelry.
She said Cheng-chuan is about to leave.
So she wanted me to give it to you.
She said it's just souvernirs.
She doensn't know if it's fair or not.
She wanted to be fair to you all her life.
She had a hard time.
It's too late to be good to her now.
OK. That's it!
Cheng-min will soon get married.
Cheng-fang is handling the restaurant.
OK.
Come back to visit when you have time.
OK. That's all.
Dad, Cheng-fang will get
married sooner or later.
Dad can't handle the
restaurant all by himself.
You should sell the restaurant.
Sell it? Why?
Dad, you can relax if it's sold.
I'm fine. I don't want to relax.
Your mom and I worked hard for the place.
I won't sell it, never!
As long as I am alive,
don't you ever mention this again.
Were Cheng-chun
and Cheng-min born here?
Yes.
I've been thinking these years.
Maybe we shouldn't have gone to Japan.
And left you alone.
You must felt awful.
I feel okay now.
But did you really forgive dad that time?
About the affair?
We're couple. One of us has to be tolerant.
Why are always women being tolerant?
Is that why you don't want to get married?
I think you shouldn't have forgiven dad.
Maybe you're right.
But you wouldn't want us to divorce now.
It that the rich cousin
who open the restaurant?
I thought she has a cancer,
how can she come?
Lower your voice
Let's go. After dinner.
Come and continue the game. Don't forget.
OK.
Hsiao-feng, make some tea
for your auntie and cousin.
Auntie.
Cheng-fang.
Have a seat.
Here.
Thank you.
Cheng-fang,
do you remember Momma Chai?
Momma Chai.
You always went to Chai's house,
and drank milk at church.
I wouldn't recognize her now.
Mrs. Chai moved to next door last month.
Isn't it a coincidence?
Kuei-mei, you've put on a lot of weight.
Your cousin is getting thinner and thinner.
Her health is not good
but she still plays mahjongg.
Or what else should I do?
I'm cooped in this damn house.
Like a bird in the cage.
Unlike you, you have a business to do.
After my husband passed away...
I don't even have anybody to fight with.
It sounds like you love to fight.
Then you can argue with
my husband everyday.
Let's see if you can handle it.
Know what?
Chai's Chinese wife came from Hong Kong.
After so many hard years,
of couse she is not happy.
I'm not unhappy, I'm furious.
He told me he wasn't married.
But now there's another wife.
He sent her money every month.
He also sent her TV, radio, and other stuff.
What could you do about it?
What could I do?
I suffered. The kids have grown up.
When I feel good, I forgive him.
When I feel bad, I fight with him.
You've married for 30 years, right?
You're old now. What can you do?
Kuei-mei,
there's something I forget to tell you.
I asked Chai to have his Hong Kong wife
check the situation of our hometown.
You'll never guess who sent us a package.
Look.
Fei Chen-pang. Your former fiance!
Is it him?
There's no letter.
It's inconvenient to tell everything.
He said he's happy to
know you are well here.
He has 2 daughters and
hope to send them out.
I want to discuss with you.
I'd like to renovate the Chavannes.
And change the manage way.
That's good. I can count on you.
I'll leave the matter of the Fei's to you.
Take care of your dad.
Ask him to play cards
when he has nothing to do.
He's old and has no other habbit.
Playing cards can make him feel better.
You're tired. Go get some sleep.