Would you hurry up? The banquet is about to begin
everybody's gonna be there at six
Change!
Mommy, do I have to go?
Of course!
But I went every time
that's why this can't be an exception
Jody, go change!
If you don't go change at this very minute,
you don't have to go to this banquet tonight.
Thank you, dad!
And you don't go to school starting from tomorrow
thank you, dad!
And don't call me dad anymore
And since I'm no longer your dad,
I don't have to buy you those models
I'll go change now, dad!
Honey, is my suit ready yet?
It's hanging in the bedroom. Take it easy, will you?
How can 1?
Even a Buddha needs his gold robe
in Hong Kong, people respect you for what you wear
you can tell the wealth of a guy from his clothes
for instance...
Toe local emporiums here in Hong Kong
are always behind the Japanese department stores
why? Packaging!
Hong Kong is a mean city, I tell you
give me back my comb
no way. The comb is mine
give it back!
What is this? A war!
This building is built by the housing department
it's extremely fragile!
She took my comb
Jody, come out!
She gave me the comb as a present
but she never used it, so I took it back
then you're wrong
since you gave her the comb
it's up to her whether she wants to use it
if you want to use it, ask her if you can borrow it
mommy!
Go ask her!
Can I borrow your comb?
No!
Sis, would you please lend me your comb?
Take it!
So what did you learn from this?
I learned not to give present to anyone
why are you so dressed up?
Those elderly aunts and uncles won't appreciate it
I don't intent go to the banquet
my boyfriend is going to pick me up later
can I go too?
Honey, why is this tie so wrinkled?
Could you iron it for me?
Alright!
Are your clothes wrinkled?
No, they're ok!
Uncle bill! Auntie Lydia!
All dressed up, so pretty! Going out?
Idiot!
Yeah, we're going to a banquet!
If I were going to throw a feast,
I'd invite your whole family,
everybody who lives in this housing estate
knows that uncle bill's family is always the sharpest!
Just look, their three daughters
are just like princesses!
I say, it's better to have daughters than sons!
Uncle bill only has daughters
he's a news anchorman in a TV station,
so he's at an advantage, really
how's that, auntie nam?
He'll nominate his daughters for beauty pageants
the eldest daughter will be miss Hong Kong
the second daughter miss Asia
how boring!
And auntie Lydia can be miss aerobic
you know... her figure...
What's so funny?
We were saying uncle bill's daughters can be miss...
Miss hooker?
Jody can be miss television
but Jody is still a child
pageants won't be popular when she grows up
why not?
How about miss special area?
Well, actually it's not that far away
isn't that right, uncle bill?
You got a big mouth. Go swallow some k-y!
Darling, you'd better go get her
Jody, hurry up!
Remember, don't drink too many coke in the restaurant
or people will think we can't afford it
lolita, come walk over here
somebody might throw something down, you know
it won't happen!
It's safer here
Smiley Joe!
Mia!
My mom!
Ma ma Mia!
My daddy!
Daddy!
Shut up! Who's he?
My friend, smiley Joe
we are going to a concert
I'm not going to the banquet, bye!
But I paid 500 bucks for the gift certificate!
Bring me some oranges then
look at her attitude
I told you not to give birth to any daughters
I didn't conceive them. Don't put them into my access
what about tier?
Daddy, which way are you going?
Causeway bay!
Not in the same direction. Too bad!
Taxi!
Have you struck a gold mine?
Take the subway
subway?
Subway is fast and safe, and air-conditioned as well
come!
Passengers boarding the island line to central,
please go to platform no. 2!
So crowded!
It's the rush hour!
Passenger who couldn't get on, please take next train
Lolita, there's a seat here
hurry, or somebody will take it
you sit, mom!
Okay!
How boring
you look!
Next stop, tsimshatsui
Oops!
Help!
You creep. Trying to molest my daughter?
What school do you go to?
"Kow kung"
what a weirdo!
Two parents sitting in the middle
smile
Lolita, sit down!
Leave her alone!
Ninth auntie, big auntie come take a picture...
Okay! Please sit!
Driver Chang, gardener bing, you two as well,
and nanny...
Let's go, we can never make it
let's find some place to sit
lolita!
Who else hasn't taken pictures?
Yeah... we missed someone...!
We missed lucky and Dolly!
These two dogs are cute!
Everybody please!
That's enough!
Okay!
I am going to move into my new house
I'll throw a housewarming party and invite you all
how much did you spend on decorating the house?
How much?
Only 2 million plus
yes... only 2 million or so!
It's a nice house, but it's far
I bet you place is more convenient
are you still living in a housing estate?
Right!
We'll pay you a visit some other time
no need to bother!
We are just renovating
right!
Lolita, what grade are you in?
What grade?
Form six
she's going to college soon
why not send her abroad?
- I didn't even let my daughter - 1 go to the bathroom
sit through those exam
- and send her to school in la - Leave me~
and she's going to ucla next year
it will soon be 1997
are you planning to immigrate?
We have no such thoughts
we are Hong kongese
we have Chinese blood, you know
and should stay with our own kind
immigrating is irresponsible
we should live up to the invincible Hong Kong image
and stay here... witness the change of times
we should work towards the modernization of our country
so I urge you all to
stay in Hong Kong
don't be a third class citizen elsewhere
Who wants this bowl?
Give it to my cousin, he doesn't always eat
I want to see the manager
you can't go in!
No, it's sour!
Manager, I've come to tell you
I bought the Mark six for you
I'll see you later, manager!
I've checked the numbers
and your car key...
Uncle bill, sit down!
You didn't see anything just then, did you?
No, I saw nothing
compared to what I saw the screening room last time
this is only chicken shit!
And that time at the car park...
Uncle bill, you've be anchor for more than 10 years
you should know what to say
and what should not to say
please
no, thanks
just any what's in the manuscript
not a word more!
That's good!
There's a superstar concert next week wanna go?
Not very interested!
You should see what you ought to see,
and not see what you ought not to see
is that right?
Yes, thank you, manager!
News department, I'm uncle bill!
The producer wants to see you
that witch?
Producer
what does she want from me?
Uncle bill, you've been with us for 18 years
you'd put in sweat and tears
according to company policy I must notify you...
Of ray promotion?
Your three month trial period starts today
what? But I've been here for 18 years!
Why do I need a trial period?
You were still in school when I started my job
let's not talk about these things
just talk about last month
how many mistakes did you make in reading the news
once, twice...!
Stop counting!
We've edited your bloopers together!
Now watch!
In order to promote industrial safety
we need to pump more education into construction work
don't go near places with danger signs...
That's an accident
this now shouldn't be an accident!
I am covering the typhoon situation in sha-tau kok
there's flooding in several places, and landslides...
It's really windy!
Do you still want to watch?
No, I already know what happened!
Please return this car key to the manager for me
because you are close to him
The mushroom department!
What mushroom department?
This place specializes in mushrooms
I'm uncle bill
the two concert tickets I just mentioned
will be sent down to you
don't bother! Manager,
you can keep them for yourself!
What happened?
You just ask my producer!
Now I see everything!
Now I know why poor son always get mean
I am furious, I'll say anything
I damn wish!
I don't believe it!
You tell me, uncle bill
I got my master in communication in the states
and have been working here for 18 months
and I still need to go through a trial period
what's so strange about it?
Someone who has been with the news department
for 18 years, still has to go through a trial period
who can be that stupid?
I would kill myself if I were him!
Really I would rather die!
Die! Die! Die!
Go kill yourself!
Uncle bill, toe manager just called
he told you to return that letter to me
no, I don't think I want to continue
I want to retire
I'll give you one more change
lots of young men here are waiting for their chance
don't waste two chances on me at the same tune!
I've to stick to your principles if you want to fire me
principles are flexible, you know
not if they are really principles
not if it's uncle bill who's getting fired
life in the housing estate:
Four witches are playing mah-jong
there are witches east, south and west
and gone is the wicked witch of the north...
This is chicken feed!
Don't say it out loud!
Okay, I'll look at mom's
that's good!
- Oh! - Don't shoot!
I'll be damned!
Mom, watch out for my video recorder
you are wasting away watching that stuff
why don't you ever study?
I am the hope of Hong Kong's new wave cinema
I am Stephen spielbug!
See fut Bo?
There ain't no treasure in your asshole! Asshole!
Give him a break, lie's not a small kid
I didn't know why I gave birth to this piece of trash
TV kid, would you please get me a hot tea?
It's degrading to wait on women
you are trash!
Trash can be made good use of
so how did it go?
It's only ten, twenty bucks. Small time for me
are you really quitting?
I haven't got time
my husband and I am going to see a new house
you know, all my daughters are grown
my place is just not big enough
uncle bill is such a smart guy!
Just ain't my day. Lost more than 50 bucks
I can buy more than 20 Mark sixes with that money
don't go honey, don't go!
Leave me alone
I promise you: I'll go look for a job tomorrow
I'll be a responsible man
you lose, penalty!
How come? Penalty for that!
Shit, forgot to bring my keys
honey... please don't go!
I didn't bring me key. How can I get in!
Go to the social welfare department
they are good at breaking in
really?
Tell them you are kwok ah-lui's father
right!
Jody, what are you doing?
Dinner is ready soon. Let me do it
slice it here!
Give it back!
Can I borrow a pair of silk stockings?
You've got your own
but I've worn all mine. Everybody has seen them
turn them inside out and wear them
- come on, lend me yours! - What is it?
I'm going to a dance contest tonight
and she won't even lend me her stockings
what is it?
It's very minor, I'll get some band-aids
stop it!
Lend me your purse!
Why do you always eye my stuff?
You never use them anyway
because you always borrow them
stop it!
Your dandruff is all over my comb
that's your own dandruff
I never had dandruff!
Stop it girls. This is a small flat
you don't have to shout!
I am warning you!
Whoever shouts in this house
will be punished
honey!
Honey, I'm back!
What is it with you?
So you're back. You don't have to shout!
Honey, get with it!
The tempo of the city the fashion of the young...
What on earth are you talking about?
I say, I want to catch up with the times
right!
Darling, there's a registered letter for you!
From whom?
Your brother John from Manila
I never read his letters
but you got to read them at least once!
I really dislike this brother of mine
he never respected me!
So nobody should mention him
are you going to the dance contest?
You're not coming back for dinner then
have some fresh milk!
Have some more!
You don't have to shout!
Yeah, this flat is so small
great. Finally finished!
Sis, what do you think?
Are you going to the science project contest with this?
Yeah, the solar system. The nine planets
so what do you think?
- Not bad! - Of course!
How come the Jupiter is so small?
And there's no moon beside the earth
don't pick on it
I don't know
it is finished already?
These balls are so round and so colorful
and they can rotate!
You are a genius, a whiz kid
you definitely have my blood!
Pick a Mark six number
well, gonna win. So number "1"
number one!
You each pick a number!
Yourself are a gambler
but why make your daughters gamblers?
Just asking them to pick a number!
You're always dreaming of a fortune from the sky
sly stallons is a billionaire
because he is hard-working
go serve dinner!
Mommy!
What do you want? Do you want to come in?
Mommy, you're really smart!
Call me aunt!
Call me smiley Joe!
Smiley Joe!
Wait for me one second, I'm going to change
don't rush, there's 2 hours before the dance contest
you're going to dance?
I'm your sister's partner tonight
we going to get first place for sure
dance, let's see!
You think your blenched hair looks pretty good?
Aunt, you're wrong!
This isn't blenched, the rest is
are you missing an earring?
Aunt, you're really out of fashion
you're supposed to only wear one earring these day!
You pierced your ear?
It's for the young, like me
under 25, everyone has pierced ears
after 26 years old, will you fill in the hole?
Aunt, you're a great kidder
uncle, are you off?
I'm still working
I smell something canny
honey, canned food again?
Daddy!
Call me uncle! It sounds better!
Uncle, canned food is better than nothing
I don't even have rotten vegetables to eat sometime
my mom loves to gamble, playing mahjong and Mark six
she doesn't like to cook
it's disgusting!
You're absolutely right
what do you think, aunt?
You have hands, why didn't you cook?
Cook, myself? And have people laugh at me?
Today's woman won't be your servant
because today is woman hasn't meet tomorrow's man
listen to my warning
my daughter is not suitable for you
suitable. May and myself are perfect together
we are two of a kind
I'm shy grass, she's a flower girl
who said?
Uncle!
Then what are we?
I'm rice, and you're the rice cooker
There's something wrong!
Voodoo!
Mia!
Smiley Joe!
Look at him swing his butt
what an ugly sight!
Bye!
Sis, you forgot your purse
stupid!
Have a good time!
But be careful!
What number?
26, continue...!
How's the dance contest?
I lost!
Those men are real low!
What happened? Quarreled with that punk?
More than that. We are now strangers!
Did he step on you while dancing?
I'm mad!
After we danced I wanted to go eat
and he was just staring at the waitress thighs
the menu was on her thighs?
Why didn't you leave on the spot?
I wasn't that stupid!
I ordered caviar
250 bucks!
And then rock oysters from New Zealand. 280 bucks
the maim course was baked lobster, 480 bucks
and there was dessert
he must be broke!
It's such a big meal,
you should have called and invited us
I ate away more than a thousand bucks
and told him to get lost after he paid the bill
good girl. You've got character!
You're just like mom in the old days
he went after me, after we left toe restaurant
and I gave him a slap on the face
that's wonderful... you're just like me!
That's what I did to your dad back then!
Fatty, don't distort my image
I'll tell you more some other time
what's your number?
Does it really work?
I'm sure it does!
Pack your stuff and go to sleep
Honey, our new room is really great
how's it upstairs?
It's really comfortable here
I had to fart a lot before
to get this sort of effect
come down quickly. The party's beginning
ah Sam, ah say! Get the food ready?
It's almost ready, master!
Either it's ready or not!
What do you mean almost?
Go to the kitchen and get things ready
yes! Master!
Are tonight fireworks ready?
Yes!
Test it once!
Wow! What a luxury!
Tonight guests will be really amazed
daddy, mommy, come take a look!
I don't understand
why did you pay twice the amount for crazy bank?
Just for fun!
Not expensive, very cheap!
Be careful, don't dirty my carpet
be careful don't break my antique flower vases!
Why are you here yet? Hurry up!
It really is going to be festive tonight
honorable guests, besides being a housewarming
we are celebrating my sister's first prize
now, she will demonstrate how her model works
and winning model is...
Tai long wan nuclear power plant
nuclear power plant?
Councilmen, there's no need to research nuclear plant
all you have to do is look at this model,
your reports taken from it would be even better
mon, dad!
What happened?
I got a divorce
where's smiley Joe?
As soon as we left port he hooked on to a blonde
it really pissed me off!
The radiation...
It's alright. There won't be any radiation within 10 metres.
Let's go quick...
Let's go, girls. Hurry up!
Open the door...
Please let the passengers get off first
Don't go near the tram doors
The next station is "chung wan" oh, "central"
It's very stuffy. I can't breathe
Uncle bill!
He went to the washroom
he's out!
You're too much. Always sneaking away
but the woman just...
Look at your translation
"the 1964 Kennedy murder case". What is this?
There's nothing wrong!
It should be "the Kennedy-was-murdered case"
don't you know grammar?
This is called a "passive verb"
repeat it!
"Passive verb"...
Take it back and revise it
It hurts!
How are you? Are you alright?
My stomach!
You okay?
She's got a stomach ache
quick send her to the hospital
the news will be on air in one minute
vtr control, would you play a couple of songs
can't do. The producer has to do something!
Uncle bill, you're going to do the financial report
him?
Hasn't tie made enough mistakes?
He's screwed up so many times
you just cannot trust this kind of people
I'll do it
10 seconds to news live
10, 9, 8...
54,3,2,1
hello, viewers! You are just tuning into the afternoon news.
3,4,5,6,7,8...
1... and now here's my husband reporting the news.
Dodo the panda has been proven that she is not pregnant.
Since the miscarriage from last time, dodo has been showing signs of pregnancy.
The zoo has reason to believe that
dodo the panda is currently in a state of finding another mate.
That is why she has been very tempermental lately.
Miss lui mor is going to report the financial news
close-up on the witch!
And now on the Hong Kong stock market.
Since the rise of the stock market in August 1984,
it has continually made new records.
The hang seng index has hit a record of 1997 last week.
It had even reached the 2000 point in between.
Other investers for the heng seng including cheung Kong realty,
hutchison, and etc
have increased 30%
since the end of last year.
There has even been a 3-5 times increase
in contrast to the crisis from two years ago.
In other news...
Last two minutes on the news broadcast.
The trade has also been decreased to 3000...
In September...
How come it's a two-shot?
One of the buttons got jammed!
I'll find someone to fix it
everybody's gone
the 2-shot is on air
What is he doing?
I don't know
uncle bill is crazy. Find someone to stop him
Damn! This machine doesn't work!
That's the end of the news and financial report
thank you for watching!
You are dead!
Uncle bill, what's the big news today?
The news today is that I don't have to read the news
I want to see the manager
he's out to town!
But I just saw him this morning
he just left. Won't be back until a week later
Your box is pretty
what's inside is much prettier
it was finished three days ago
you've got get first place!
Let your money ready to take me out for a milkshake
miss, where should I put this?
Put it on the last table
guess whether this volcano is active or inactive?
I hope that it's inactive
look!
This entire clock is made of wood
it works!
Why do you always say "wow"?
Sorry!
Don't say "wow" all the time, okay?
I can't help it
let me take a look at your project I want to see it
let me see yours first
where did you make this?
I made it myself
it's a toy not a science project
his science project is a motor
it runs of soiar power
a flash light works also
did your brothers help you?
No, I did it all by myself
look!
What did you make?
A model of our solar system
model of the solar system? I made that in primary 4
I my model, the sun was illuminated by a light bulb
with the nine planets revising on their own
and all of their moons in tow
but compared to this project that one was nothing
take it away!
This robot operates off a specific sound
ha! It doesn't work!
Move!
Look at it!
Great...!
Stop clapping, it going to short out
you destroyed my project
Miss, can I hand you my project two days later?
The contest is today you've to hand in your project
I still have lots of ideas!
It's good to add more detail
I have to be fair to the rest of your classmates
miss!
We're going to start judging back to your seats
factory girl!
Two stripes, I win!
Television addict!
Honey
buy a chicken and two wings to stew
aren't you embarrassed?
You've been fired
don't you know we're almost out of food?
I'm feeling depressed these days
so I want something good to eat
how can I look for work looking so pale?
You've to eat better if you are poor a in ill-health
right! Right! What about the money?
Money? We've got none!
It would be shameful to buy bean sprouts everyday
don't worry, everyone knows that I'm on diet
the whole family is going on a diet
cut a piece of barbecue pork
hurry up, get the money
Mr. fung, don't ask us to borrow any money
we're so poor, we'll even take poker chips!
You want to borrow money, the best is to ask uncle bill
uncle bill is the most charitable
uncle bill
it's me, Mr. fung!
Oh how nice, you're at home!
On vacation!
These days I'm running short too
my wife left
you guys are so well off that I envy you. I want...
Want to borrow money?
No problem
here's five hundred, take it!
We've neighbors, we ought to help each other
that's what neighbors are for
lending money is like sharing coals during winter
uncle bill, you're right
if everyone were like you
then I'd be rich
remember to pay me back when you have toe money!
Auntie Lydia, I appreciate it
what?
During me times of difficulty
uncle bill lent me five hundred so that we could eat
thank you so much!
I'm going out for a steak, see you later
auntie Lydia, you and uncle bill are truly kind
right, generous and willing to help others
that's the way it should be!
Bill!
Worse comes to worse, we don't eat
did you lend five hundred dollars to Mr. fung?
Move your feet, I'm mopping the floor!
Mommy, you're in my way!
Who's in who's way?
We won the Mark six
I lent someone money you give me bruises all over
but you yourself go out and buy Mark six tickets
when you lend someone money, what do you get out of it?
At least when I buy Mark six, there's a chance of win
chance? When we lose I punched out
what if we win? I get hit over the head with a brick
you're scolding me in front of our daughters
you're afraid of the bricks, forget about the Mark six
why forget about it?
We use money to buy it, we got to take a risk!
That's mine!
You bought so many
no wonder we have been sprouts for every meal
look!
The first number is "22"
we've got one ticket with "22"!
Hail Mary, full of grace
a thousand thanks, a million thanks. I hope I win
I'm not greedy, I just hope to win once
the second number is "6"
number "6", I win again, I got to two numbers
we've going to be rich richer than chow yun fat
the third number is "40"
I've got three number
we've going to be rich beyond our wildest dreams
calm down!
Three more numbers & someone will win the $15m grand prize
stay, let's pay attention to what the fourth number
the fourth number is...
Now I will repeat the last three numbers
number 30, number 35,number 39
everyone, don't get discouraged
discouraged!
Don't get discouraged, we'll start again
honey, you first
I got number 5!
10!
While were at it, 15
number 20!
I want number 25!
Honey, pick another number
if we hit here more numbers, three, zero please
30!
Honey, if I win, then I don't need to work
don't day dream, look for a job tomorrow
Miss, give me another cup of coffee
mister, it's your sixth cup of coffee
are you going to get the shakes, drinking so much coffee?
Darling, go and check out
You're sticking around me so much
wait a moment, I ran into someone I knew
don't look over here
manager
how did you know that I was here?
I've been looking for you for a couple of days
how did you find me here?
I have been looking for you, and you are out
but by coincidence I ran into you here
I saw her again
why are you looking for me?
She fired me!
From now on I can't follow you
that's why I feel more relieved
and if I am worried, then I get confused when I talk
unclear, and bullshitting all the time
don't mention it, tonight go back to work
this is no good, seems like I'm forcing you
I'm not that type of person
you're not blackmailing me
I'm blackmailing you so that you can blackmail me
are you blackmailing me?
I'm black mailing myself to blackmailing you to blackmail me
anyway, you got to work tonight
no matter who blackmails who,
anyway, thanks!
Honey, where have the children gone?
Not back from school yet
I have good news for you
the manager asked me to go back to work
starting from tonight, I go back to reporting the news
a couple of days ago I went to wong tai sin
I knew we were going to be lucky
now the time is on our side
honey, come here!
I know you're going to like this shark's fin soup
and also this xo, come!
Honey, you're too much!
I'm still not back at work, not yet getting a salary
you're spending my money already
why are you laughing at me like that?
You idiot, what's wrong with my laugh?
What so happy, where did you get the money to buy the food?
It's my own allowance
you're willing to use your money to buy expensive food
honey, I knew I was wrong in the past
that's why today, you will be fed like a king
who knows where you got the money, I'm not going to eat
you tell me, where did the dirty money come from?
Dirty money?
No wonder these days your laugh is so sexy
I understand, you don't like it because I'm poor
you met another guy!
You idiot, I don't know what you are talking about?
This stuff cost $1000
with $1000,you would have premed your hair
play mahjong, buy Mark six, and daydream
your eyes widen when you see money
you're too practical I won't getting thing from it
what a hell. For money you would sell yourself
you have no values
shut up!
You're trying to force me to lay down all the cards
I know I can't hide anything from you
finally you admit it
if I tell you, you better be able to handle it
there's really a third person
I'll tell you the truth, I...
Won the Mark six!
You win?
I can't hear!
Yes!
How much, tell me fast!
$190,000!
$190,000?
I've never seen that much money in my whole life
honey, wait until we got the money
we'll count the money
until you're satisfied!
What do you mean we'll spend it together?
I bought this Mark six myself. Doesn't belong to you
honey, we are a couple, we share everything
yours is mine!
My money is from other guys, it's dirty
it doesn't matter if it's dirty
we wash it together and it will be fine
it stinks!
It's smells good!
You really know how to turn words around
women usually don't have money
we can't win the Mark six
honey, I was just kidding
a woman like you, you wouldn't have affairs
you mean I'm not attractive
no, you are!
Honey, I need you
I am really love you, honey!
$190,000 is a lot of money?
Uncle bill, this is your last chance
if you don't take it, then disappear
I'll give forgive him
it's impossible for her to make $190,000 in one year, right?
I'd like to learn how?
Dodo the panda is finally pregnant
people at the zoo are extremely happy
before the economic review it's the Mark six news
the winning numbers for this week are
5,10, 15, 20, 25, 30!
I'm going to rich!
Only one person won
the price is $199,700
it's wrong!
It's not $190,000. It is 19 million!
No, it's 19000,000!
19 million?
Honey, is that for real?
Yes honey, yes!
19 million!
Why are you laughing?
Can't I laugh!
Ladies and gentlemen!
He's coming again!
I don't want to work here at the station anymore
the people in charge here are a group of scoundrels
they pick on those who earn less than themselves
I've wanted 18 years of youth
what, woman?
Just like yourself, useless
affairs with our station manager, as if it we're nothing
once you get here, she talks nonsense
Why are you laughing, idiot?
Honey, tomorrow we look for another house
I want to live in a big house
I will never live in such a small place again
if we buy a new house everyone will know we're rich
people will come and borrow money from us
we can more secretly, right?
Let me think, go to sleep!
Honey!
Anyway, we have to move
needn't to pay this month's rent to the housing authority
if we don't have to pay, we won't
they increased the rental too much
okay, let's sleep!
Honey!
Starting from tomorrow
you'll have shark's fin soup to go with your rice
and lobster for your breakfast, okay?
Too much cholesterol
it's easy to get a heart attack
what's the matter, you love shark's fin
go to sleep!
Remember, starting from now don't play with them
if you get excited, you'll spill the beans
I won't say anything
you will!
Okay, tomorrow I will take things to the pawn shop
to let people to know that we are poor
this is a good idea
let's sleep!
What are you thinking about?
What am I thinking about?
You think that I don't know,
now that we're rich, you want me deal?
You're so big, how are you going to die?
I won't let you think about other girls
I won't, sleep!
I won't sleep!
Honey!
Dead beat!
Hands up!
Honey, I know I'm wrong
just because we're rich. I don't want you to die
Mia...
I found Mia
she's by herself
sis, we got a new swimming pool, let's go in?
Do I have a share in the new house?
Because you like me you'll have a room for sure
this is for you
this is for Jody
be careful!
Sorry!
Sis, where are you going for a tan?
If you still have your tan here, my house won't be finished
unless all the guys are legless
you ruined my castle
I'm ss 0 rry!
Mia...
I was wrong in the restaurant last time
you go away. Heartless!
Go for an ice-cream, hurry!
Sis, don't be too soft!
Tire of the girls at the restaurant
and now come to the beach to look
you misunderstood me
I just looked at the mole on the waitress's leg
I thought that was a fly
she didn't feel itchy at all
and closely, I realized that it was a mole
here are a lot of girls who have moles on their legs
why don't you go check whether it is a fly or not?
Look at it, it's no moles, those are flies
get lose!
Buddy, it's not going to work
my car doesn't work too
because of you, my car's dead too
we've going to get fired for sure
as buddies, we have to stick together
no matter what you guys have to help me this time
go!
How can I help?
Why are you here alone?
Let me be your companion
you have a very nice tan
what does it matter to you?
We are just pulling your leg
you're unhappy, you've no boyfriend it's dangerous
I'm here to help you!
Don't be afraid, we won't hurt you
it's hard to say what will happen later
I'm here to save you!
What the hell do you guys want?
We want you!
But it is not time yet
help you!
Help!
Help me!
Smiley Joe, that's embarrassing!
Run!
Smiley Joe
Mia...
I finally rescued you!
Smiley Joe
Mia...
Sis!
Your family won the Mark six
yes, it's more romantic when one has money
I'll ask my dad to buy us a yacht
we can go sailing!
It will be us two only
mama Mia!
Dad, you got a postcard
our uncle six sent it from Manila
see what lie wrote!
It's probably nothing!
He said he will visit Hong Kong
and will have a dinner with you
good, help me to write a letter to him
go tell him to screw himself
dad, you guys are brothers
why not have a dinner with him?
You always have dinner with people you don't like
but that's different, your mother is my wife
I don't understand why you hate uncle so much!
Of course you don't understand
you've never had chili sauce poured into your pants
or while sleeping, having circles drawn on your face
dad, you not the unforgiving!
The worst time was
during my birthday and in front of the relatives
he tossed a cake into my face
And he stood there and laughing
he loves to watch me suffer
dad, I want to buy a yacht
okay!
Dad, you're great, thanks!
Don't thank me!
You have to pay for it yourself
I'm talking about the 20 million
we won't spend our money like that
daddy
dad, I got something to talk over
you got something to talk about, bye!
I'm going with my friends to Japan
no! No!
I haven't finished
you're finished!
I've already invited my two friends to a picnic
go to central park
you're afraid that I spent all the money
it's not safe for girls to go to Japan alone
no!
We're going to a safe place!
Can you speak Japanese?
I'll speak in english
Japanese speak english only Japanese can understand
in Japan, boys and girls bath together
and Japanese men piss all over the place
you can't go there
we're going to the university 1048?
To imitate matsuda seiko and kikuchi momoko
if I become popular, then I'm rich!
You'll imitate okata yuhiko and commit suicide
I just going to check out Japanese culture & history
history? You're talking about history?
The Japanese changed their history
remember when toe Japanese attacked
dad, quit mumbling!
Also, they've seized the island near east China
we don't have anywhere to fish
stop thinking about going to Japan
we're going to China in Christmas
to China?
Why not? If you go to China, people'll admire your clothes!
What a bumpkin
go and see if that is Mr. fung
if he comes here for money, tell him I'm not in
Honey, am I pretty?
That's your hairstyle!
I got it cut and permed, also high-line
only $2000
you're useless
this is "Paris", smells good?
Also my bikini!
That's mine, this year I'm going to wear that
so that I'm in fashion
so whichever beach you're going to, let me know first
so that we can ask them to put up a red flag?
Idiot!
Look at yourself, like a lion
I married you back in the day because you looked casual.
Now you've become a slave to clothing and a prisoner of cosmetics.
Sis, let me help you put it on
honey, watch out!
This diamond costs $3000
honey, people wear clothes to keep warm
you can't judge people from what they are wearing
you have to look at the person's character
the China emporiums won't go bankrupt
because their goods are good and durable
we won 20 million dollars
we can't take to the coffin with us
don't be such a spendthrift
no one in our household has an income
$20m is enough for food during our lifetime
so we can't waste the money
always looking for pleasure you'll be disappointed
it doesn't matter, I always get lost
today you'll need a yacht tomorrow an oceanliner
today it's like this, tomorrow it's something else
daddy
today, you're a lion
tomorrow, you'll be something else
oh, by the way, I just found an apartment
an apartment? What's wrong with living here?
Only $500 where can you find a place like this?
Just now, I picked a Mercedes also
it's easy to buy a car but difficult to keep it up
listen, I'm planning to emigrate
China is modernizing!
What do you know, we got so much money
what happens if other find out
a smart guy never sits under crumbing wall
if we don't leave now, when are we leaving?
You are wrong
like before, each of us will pick a number
everyone of us has the right to spend the money
you so absent-minded, I picked two numbers
I'm the big shareholder, I make the decisions
to decide or not to decide
not fair!
We want democracy!
Chinese don't like democracy!
We want freedom
our bank a/c has no money, what do you mean freedom?
Dad, I'll owe you the money
I've already counted
since you were born to this moment, you owe me $368000
you owe me even more! And you too!
You owe me $138000!
I'll take it from your shares
starting from tomorrow you each get $36
whether you work,
or you don't, you get the same
You crazy!
"Wishing hole"
Honey, you're the best!
Of course I'm the best, go to sleep!
When we get there, there will be lots of sodas
don't drink what we have at home
your suit is great!
Mr. fung, we're not really that well off
clothes are just superficial
we have a banquet to go later
that's why we have to do our best
we're actually poor, I hope you don't mind
let's go!
Since you know, I guess it's ok, if our neighbors know
are you asking me to return your money?
I'm watching a swimming exhibition
My two daughters have taken lessons for 3 months
their instructor told them to represent Hong Kong
this styles is called "lobster"
see if it looks like it
yes!
Idiot, they invite us to come,
and not even serving us a drink
don't be so upset
we now have $20m
and they only got a couple of million
don't worry about it, it's not worth it
Hong Kong living standards are really amazing
you estate is so expensive
cousin, you're really generous
we lived here for over half of my lifetime
comfortably, so why worry about anything
brother!
Uncle!
John, go and talk with your big brother!
Honey!
Baby brother!
Uncle, aunt, you're here!
I didn't know you were sitting here!
You've always looking upward how can you see us?
Brother, sister-in-law!
Uncle!
It isn't easy to get so many relatives together
it helps if you have money
otherwise, we'd never see each other
luckily, we're no longer poor.
Aunt, your gown is really beautiful
I think I saw the last two times we got together
the workmanship is so good, that is why you wear it everytime
this is the last tune I wear it
when it gets cool I'm gong to wear my mink coat
really!
If not, then how can I spend the 20 million dollar
20 million?
Yes, a couple of days, ago, I...
She had a stroke, she doesn't know what she's talking about
you're cr az y!
We have to meet our guests
see you later
mommy, this pool is huge
nothing to be envious about it
later, ours will be even bigger
she said it, not me
call sixth uncle!
Sixth uncle!
Are you the youngest daughter?
We haven't seen each other for a long time
we've got to celebrate
honey, how are you?
I'll take your whole family for dinner tomorrow
it's not necessary
come to my house tomorrow night
okay, but it's going to be a bother
it's not bother, just come
come earlier!
Tamachi kogi
not good enough!
Lower your voice!
You're so beautiful on TV
I'm going to take a taxi back home to watch it
I'm going too!
Junk!
About Japan remind your dad!
If you don't, we won't wait!
Bye, boy!
Quiet down, bitch!
If you don't turn it down, I'm going to blow up your room
You've changed, inviting your brother for dinner?
Yes, I've prepare a great meal
leave!
What's the matter?
I thought you said that we going to see a movie
he's the worst
he's staring at the ticket seller!
You're so dirty-minded!
No, I was looking at her mole
recently, I've been looking into reading fortunes
the book said, depending upon where the mole is located
that person has a certain and distinct fate
why were looking at her chest?
Because her chest had two moles
each person has two "miles" on their chest
but hers were especially big
it means that she is especially confident
you're a pervert!
I'm not a pervert!
You're gay!
It was a man?
How come I didn't know?
Smiley Joe, let me ask you something
do you like men, or women?
Women of course!
Where's your proof?
I like Mia!
I really like her!
Molester!
You're a pervert
you punk, don't come here looking my daughter
daughter, a man doesn't need money
he only needs to love you and treat you well
as for other types of men, forget them!
Men are really shit heads!
This TV should have been thrown away
sound!
Crazy!
Picture!
This is a chimpanzee from Africa
it's only a couple of months old, look how cute it is
it's on, you're in for it now!
Why is Jody on TV?
How come?
This singer looks so familiar
uncle bill's daughter is on TV
Jesus!
We've finished watching the chimp
the next zoological feature will be on Swedish foxes
that's really stupid!
How come it's like this?
I don't know!
Valentino's here!
My hearts wants to say!
Hell!
It sounds awful!
My heart loves you even if you say goodbye
pick a card!
I won!
You punk, go to hell!
You can't, I can still use him
touch what!
Do you like my daughter a lot?
Of course, yes
go some where else to shoot!
You have to answer me one thing
what?
I don't like you!
You like my daughter you have to pass my approval
yes, uncle, tell me!
Do you have time tomorrow?
It's difficult to tell!
Busy in afternoon, then I'm free in the morning!
I'm busy in the morning then I'm free in afternoon!
I'm still free at night time
then do you have anything to do tomorrow?
Tomorrow's Sunday, I'm free the whole day
get a pencil and paper, write it down
I'm going to borrow a uniform tomorrow morning
after which I will deliver cake
did I need to wear a tie?
It doesn't matter!
Why? The better you dress the more tips you get
you're not going to get any tips
you have to go buy the cream cake
does it have to say "happy birthday"?
No, it just has to have cream!
No tie, no tips, more cream
send the cake to my house tomorrow
send it to my house
my house!
You mean my house!
Just write your home address!
Remember this person
when you see him throw the cake into his face
it's going to be great!
No wonder there's not going to have any tips
I've been waiting for this opportunity for ten years
brother!
You thought that it is the same as before?
Come here, say hello to uncle!
This is ray second daughter
this is my eldest daughter
uncle!
What was happened?
She was arguing with her boyfriend
always crying, what a shame!
Good girl, here's a present for you
thank you, uncle!
Be careful, there might be a mouse inside
you still remember that time?
Of course I remember!
Growing up with you, I had to endure a lot
don't do that
brother, I want to apologize for the things before
you never apologize!
I got to say it today
because I'm getting old
and don't have much time
what's he up to now?
I'm serious this time!
I have leg cancer
the doctor said I have a few of months left to live
you're my closest relative
so tonight, I must talk to both of you
okay, fine!
I'm really happy!
It's tragic, so young and still unmarried
I always thought of him as an enemy
this time could be the last time we saw each other
control yourself, don't cry
I can't control myself
Are you going to eat?
No, I'm not going to eat!
Good thing. I didn't prepare anything for you
go and see whether the soup is ready
- uncle! Eat please - Brother, sister-in-law!
Have you ever thought of buying a house and a car?
Yes, yes, why?
I've been working with hang fung bank for 10 years
I still have jots of "quartz" I can give it to you
that way you can get a better interest rate
I hope that you accept my offer
drink the chicken's feet soup, it's good for your leg!
Come and sit down!
Eat...
It's good to eat like this!
Let me tell you guys a joke!
Please!
Once upon a time, there was this guy
is this a joke?
This patient went to hospital for operation
he cut off his left leg
after the operation, he woke up
he saw the doctor and he had a worried look
the doctor said, "I've good news and bad news"
"which one do you want to hear first?"
The patient said, "tell me the bad news first"
the bad news is, "I cut off the wrong leg"
what's the good news?
"There was nothing wrong with your left leg"
Come here and pour the soy sauce for me
hand me the soy sauce plate
you don't need four people to pour soy sauce?
Listen, be careful of what you say
tonight we must treat him well
not only tonight, but from now on
let me open it
who are you looking for?
You!
Don't...!
Is him!
It's funny!
You can lift your head a little higher, driving a car like this.
You don't have to drive yourself hire a chauffeur
that means we have to spend money?
Use my "quartz" to hire him
the car costs less than original price
we hire a chauffeur, we going to be even more proud
mommy, this swimming pool is big, I like it
of course it's big
after buying a house and car, there's only $10m left
it's best to save in my bank
put it in a foreign accounts 18% interest for you
only interest to earn us about a million a year
it'll never be able to use it all!
I could help you keep an eye on it
interest goes up on other accounts, I'll help you swift
we're going to be rich, money from money
it's too bad I won't be around that long
don't shake your leg, you can't have money
you'll be poor if you shake it a lot
you're so stubborn
when I knew I had leg cancer
and had a few months to live
I wanted to do a film
to tell all my relatives
never to shake your leg
no matter what
if I didn't shake my leg in the past
I wouldn't be sitting here now
and telling you about my leg cancer
don't worry!
Uncle, this is fate
life and money is the same
if you have it, you have it. That's fate
you guys come here to see the new house
thought you lied to me
this is a very pretty house, can I stay here?
Where's your sister?
Inside the house
you can't go in!
Do you have to ask to enter this house?
What's your status?
I'm just going to wash room, ok?
Yes, there is wash room in that room
Where can I go take a piss?
- Inside! - Thanks!
I don't think this guy has much of a future
is smiley Joe come here?
Yes, he's is the bathroom
you boy-friend is an embarrassment
This bathroom is big!
You didn't zip up your sipper!
How can you piss like that?
There's only one way to piss
you streaker!
If I don't streak, how can I piss?
How can I piss with my pants in the way?
Get lost, you jerk!
Just because I piss, I'm not jerk
you jerk...!
Pervert!
You are not only a streaker, you a pervert too
you misunderstand
you date my daughter because you want my inheritance
you thought that I didn't know?
Daughter, love can't be like bread
it's important that his status is the same
some treat you good just so they can depend on you
yes! Hop in the car.
Mia...
So what if you win $19 million
who won the Mark six?
I'm not telling you
one more
bro~
coming~
cheers!
Beer~~
don't look down at other people
one day if I have the money
you'll see if I can be a good match for your daughter
drink up...
Did your girlfriend win the Mark six?
It was her mother!
Mama Mia, won it!
Mama Mia, my goodness
let's do something!
Let's do something to her mom
do something to her mom
Right, it's her!
Let's go back. Postpone the plan!
What happened?
This little kid remember me
yes!
Drive by and steal the pantyhose
put it on!
You're smart!
No, this size doesn't fit me
this is size two and I need size four
put it on your head
yes!
This is a European size, size two will fit me
this doesn't fit me
she wants to leave
go!
Lock the door
help!
Help...
Have you finished packing for your Japan trip?
There's nothing to pack empty suitcases will do
and also bring a couple of credit cards
this time I can buy whatever I want
I don't have to be stingy or tightfisted
this television has stereo
hang fung bank is bankrupt after nineteen years
which one?
It's looks like our bank, hang fung
it is $300 billion in the red
it is bankrupt because, since 1985
a couple of banks had financial difficulties
this's the ninth bank to go bankrupt!
I got good news and bad news
which do you want to hear first?
Tell us the good news first
the good new is that I don't have leg cancer
the doctor said that
what about the bad news?
The bad news is that you lost $19 million
- whats! - Sister-in-law!
Don't be depressed
whether you lose or win, it's fate
money and life are the same
if you have it, you got it, it's fate
stop bullshitting you caused us all this trouble
I'm a loser too, I lost my job
give me back $19 million
daddy
give me back $19 million. Give it back!
Kidnapped?
Don't fight!
Our sister was kidnapped!
No more jokes. We're not playing games
who said we're playing games? Listen
dad, help me!
I know you don't like me
I will support you for your whole life
don't let me die
did you hear? We want $19 million ransom
you must be joking we're living in the estates!
You said you won't the Mark six?
We don't have it. Didn't you hear the news?
Hang fung went bankrupt,
whats?
Turn on the TV
uncle bill, don't pretend that you are poor!
No, I'm really poor!
No more games, get toe money ready
if you tell the police, I'm going to kill her
brother, call the police!
We can't call the police. They will kill hostage
anyway it's none of your business. Get lost
What are we going to do now?
A mouse bit me, I'm scared!
It's getting worse and worse
what do you mean worse, it's super bad
brother Joe, you're the one responsible
a one man show
in reality, I just wanted to scare the fat woman
who would've thought that a one-time impulse would get us in a huge mess?
Yeah! It was also out of impulse when America built the atomic bomb.
Now, the world praises them for doing the right thing and having it well done.
Why don't we let her go?
Let her go?
- You're crazy! - Ate too much pig
if we let her go now, it's still a kidnapping
we receive $19 million, it's still a kidnapping
the money first before we let tier go, stupid
I'm out of it!
We're all a part of it!
Whether you're in or out, it's still a bad situation
since they still haven't blown your cover
go to their house and spy
if they call the police, let us know
I'm going to wash my hair
go, go wash your hair!
Smiley Joe, did you know someone kidnapping her?
Do your know who is involved?
How do I know?
Good!
You never were any good!
Why do you have a foreign account?
$20 million, gone just that!
We can pretend that if wasn't real
we can pretend that we never won
why should we pretend? I won!
Yes, you had $20 million!
Look around you, no one else had it
it not the time to talk about money
we should think about how to rescue our daughter
without money, how are we going to rescue her?
I cancelled my plane ticket
even my personal saving are here!
Is this enough money to get sis back?
Crazy girl, you're wonderful
you're really wonderful!
Don't use the phone
I'm n 0 t! I 1 m n ot!
They really don't have money
the bank's bankrupts, they don't have money
that means we're wasted our time?
Why don't we just let her go!
What? That's quite a risk
who knows how much money they have left?
About $10000!
About $10000. Forget it! We won't let her go!
Unless she let's us insult her as much as we want
it's like taking rice from a beggar's bowl!
If we get the rice then you have a part in it too
forget about feelings
her sister is your girlfriend, I know
but we are your brothers!
Really?
Are you or not?
Of course!
Ask them for $500000!
I'm uncle bill, you're... Aware of the bankrupt
what? $500000
I don't even have $50000
don't kill my daughter, I'll...
How's my daughter?
She is safe, she's watching TV
eating candy too
sweet and plenty of it
I want to see her first before I give you money
mommy, there's lot of mice here
you heard her? Go borrow $500000!
Tomorrow afternoon put the money in a briefcase
take with you a portable telephone
go to kowloon tong and take the 3:45 tram
you'll see your daughter then
I'll video tape them secretly
are we going to exchange the money in the train?
I looked all over I still can't see the kidnapper
where are you now?
Our tram just passed the Chinese school
there's a hiway ahead your daughter will be there
when you see her throw the money out of the tram
the windows can't be opened, how do we throw it out?
Go to the bathroom, use that window
it's this window!
It's two inches thick, perfect
this train stops at tai poi
even if we call the police they have plenty of time
I can't even rescue my daughter
they're cunning!
I'm going to shoot it for evidence
dad!
Jody!
Big brother, throw the money out
throw the money?
Dad!
Throw the money!
Jody, come quickly!
Dad!
Big brother!
I have no more money
I'm happy if you got the money!
Uncle bill, I'm sorry!
I'll return your daughter
who are you?
Oh! Shit!
You get off at tai poi
go to the quarry, your daughter will be there
the quarry...?
Money...
The rear wheel's gone, help push the car
Listen kid, I'm going to push you later
you say piss & I'll give you a chance to leave
I understand, smiley Joe
how can you know it's me?
I knew it a long time ago, I just didn't say anything 1639?
I was afraid you would kill me
I need to go to the bathroom
shut up!
I can't hold it
you can't go! You have to hold it!
otherwise, she'll go inside the car
she doesn't even close the door!
Run!
Run, as far as you can!
Why did you let tier go? Are you crazy?
No, it's not necessary!
We don't need to kill her she only a little girl
we don't need to kill her she only a little girl
Still running!
Can't bel
I'll call my wife and let her know
brother, call the police
police?
I'm going to kill you!
Jody!
Help me!
Daddy, help me!
Jody!
Uncle!
Brother!
Daddy!
- Jody! - Daddy,
- don't leave me! - Jody!
One behind the rocks, another at the entrance
the rest, follow me
daughter, I love you!
Sis!
Jody!
Mum!
Good girl, you worried me to deal are you okay?
You bastard, you took my little girl
you drag, I'm going to beat you to death!
There's another one here
no, he's here to rescue me
he's good, the other two are the kidnappers
smiley Joe, I love youl!
Smiley Joe
he's part of it, don't let him go!
Smiley Joe, you are good, I don't blame you
you're a hero in my eyes
you're really good, really good!
He's involved, arrest him too!
Happy birthday to you~
yeah!
Smiley Joe, washing the rice?
Cooking!
You're the only one who know, don't tell anyone
I'll never do anything bad again
Jody
smiley Joe, sis is looking for you
may, I'm coming!
Smiley Joe!
We don't owe each other anything
go wash your face!
I don't want to be rich, risk being kidnapped
it's better to be poor!
I have three daughters, that's precious
not only three
whats? You...
Brother, congratulations!
This time, it's got to be a boy
and if it's a another girl...
Give it back to the hospital!
Yes~yes~
now, there is special news
one hour ago, finance secretary officially announce
hang fung bank was bailed out by foreign currency
even though many councilman are arguing against it
hang fung has got the government s permission
to reopen tomorrow
whoever has an account may get their money back
We're rich again!
Calm down! Calm down!
Not so loud
don't let anyone know, they'll want to borrow money
Mr. fung, I don't have any money to lend you
I'm here to return all the money I borrowed from you
my wife came back with another man
they came back and we're living together!
Your wife is with another man and you're so happy
of course I'm happy, he's rich!
Mr. fung
what?
You bastard, you're not a man!